<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Stuck in Surface Tension Garage</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/stuck-in-surface-tension-garage/63159</link>
    <description>I&#39;m playing the latest version of BM on Steam - the completed one (March 2020). It&#39;s uncommon for me ever to get stuck but I am. I&#39;m in &quot;Surface Tension&quot; probably close to the end. I have crawled through a red-lit ventilation duct where there were a lot of annoying little bugs that munch away your health but finished them off with the Hive Glove. A bit farther on you hear voices and suddenly the floor of the duct falls out and you find yourself in a garage with some vehicles on hoists and a bunch of very hostile marines. I finish off the hostiles and help myself to the health booster on the far wall, then discover after much examination there is no way out.  I seem to recall in the incomplete release (maybe a year ago) when you wax the last marine there is an explosion which blows out a big window other side of the row of hoists. You then worked the hoists and jumped on the vehicles to hop up on some boxes on a shelf and then out the window. This time, the windows is unbtoken and can&#39;t be broken even with the RPG.

Quite a few things were changed for this final release so maybe there&#39;s a different escape route. If anyone has found it, I&#39;d appreciate knowing.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 10 Apr 2020 19:14:27 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Help!</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/stuck-in-surface-tension-garage/63159.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Stuck in Surface Tension Garage</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[JHzlwd]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>No sooner did I post my first note than I discovered what to do  and I’m out. Apologies if I wasted anyone’s time.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/stuck-in-surface-tension-garage/63159/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/stuck-in-surface-tension-garage/63159/2</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Apr 2020 19:14:27 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-63159-2</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/stuck-in-surface-tension-garage/63159.rss">Stuck in Surface Tension Garage</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Stuck in Surface Tension Garage</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[JHzlwd]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I’m playing the latest version of BM on Steam - the completed one (March 2020). It’s uncommon for me ever to get stuck but I am. I’m in “Surface Tension” probably close to the end. I have crawled through a red-lit ventilation duct where there were a lot of annoying little bugs that munch away your health but finished them off with the Hive Glove. A bit farther on you hear voices and suddenly the floor of the duct falls out and you find yourself in a garage with some vehicles on hoists and a bunch of very hostile marines. I finish off the hostiles and help myself to the health booster on the far wall, then discover after much examination there is no way out.  I seem to recall in the incomplete release (maybe a year ago) when you wax the last marine there is an explosion which blows out a big window other side of the row of hoists. You then worked the hoists and jumped on the vehicles to hop up on some boxes on a shelf and then out the window. This time, the windows is unbtoken and can’t be broken even with the RPG.</p>
<p>Quite a few things were changed for this final release so maybe there’s a different escape route. If anyone has found it, I’d appreciate knowing.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/stuck-in-surface-tension-garage/63159/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/stuck-in-surface-tension-garage/63159/1</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Apr 2020 18:56:05 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-63159-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/stuck-in-surface-tension-garage/63159.rss">Stuck in Surface Tension Garage</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
