<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>My New Computer</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/my-new-computer/8786</link>
    <description>I&#39;m pretty much ready to buy my computer parts after months of research, pricing, etc.  But I&#39;d like to run my specs by everyone so I can get some feedback first.  I&#39;ve included all the links so if you would like to, you can read more about each component:

[url=&#39;https://www.google.com/url?q=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FIntel-i7-2600-Processor-3-4GHz-LGA1155%2Fdp%2FB004EBUXSU%2Fref%3Dsr_1_1%3Fie%3DUTF8%26qid%3D1337804044%26sr%3D8-1&amp;sa=D&amp;sntz=1&amp;usg=AFQjCNGbMK2D-X-VwUNP0eohuSYmYYQUMA&#39;]CPU: Intel Core i7-2600 Processor 3.4GHz 8 MB Cache Socket LGA1155 ($294.99)[/url]

[url=&#39;https://www.google.com/url?q=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FEVGA-Superclocked-Lifetime-Warranty-012-P3-1573-AR%2Fdp%2FB004SMUT70%2Fref%3Dsr_1_1%3Fs%3Delectronics%26ie%3DUTF8%26qid%3D1337804264%26sr%3D1-1&amp;sa=D&amp;sntz=1&amp;usg=AFQjCNHSsVtpKVDF3NpxTqGGqmqCa85wOQ&#39;]Video Card: EVGA GeForce GTX 570 HD Superclocked 1280 MB GDDR5 PCI Express 2.0 Dual DVI/HDMI/Display Port SLI Ready Limited Lifetime Warranty Graphics Card, 012-P3-1573-AR ($289.99)[/url]

[url=&#39;https://www.google.com/url?q=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.newegg.com%2FProduct%2FProduct.aspx%3FItem%3DN82E16813131724&amp;sa=D&amp;sntz=1&amp;usg=AFQjCNFxCCqgCBa-ZStM6-IkZs8dAJ9Zsw&#39;]Motherboard: ASUS P8H61-M LE/CSM (REV 3.0) LGA 1155 Intel H61 Micro ATX Intel Motherboard ($70.99)[/url]


[url=&#39;https://www.google.com/url?q=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.newegg.com%2FProduct%2FProduct.aspx%3FItem%3DN82E16811146068&amp;sa=D&amp;sntz=1&amp;usg=AFQjCNG87Z8EelpRpYfNnt1p0TXZuVfGgQ&#39;]Case: NZXT Phantom PHAN-001BK Black Steel / Plastic Enthusiast ATX Full Tower Computer Case ($129.99)[/url]


[url=&#39;https://www.google.com/url?q=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.newegg.com%2FProduct%2FProduct.aspx%3FItem%3DN82E16820145345&amp;sa=D&amp;sntz=1&amp;usg=AFQjCNHehrG_YMY320QlanFfrt56BKdhXg&#39;]RAM: CORSAIR Vengeance 8GB (2 x 4GB) 240-Pin DDR3 SDRAM DDR3 1600 (PC3 12800) Desktop Memory Model CMZ8GX3M2A1600C9B ($49.99)[/url] [b]NOTE: Would 8 gb be enough to run today&#39;s games/programs efficiently?  Just curious.[/b]



[url=&#39;https://www.google.com/url?q=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.newegg.com%2FProduct%2FProduct.aspx%3FItem%3DN82E16822148537&amp;sa=D&amp;sntz=1&amp;usg=AFQjCNHgKimtF-9XiLCkjxyBnFB74a9Ygg&#39;]HDD: Seagate Pipeline HD ST31000322CS 1TB 5900 RPM 8MB Cache SATA 3.0Gb/s 3.5&quot; Internal Hard Drive -Bare Drive ($109.99)[/url] [b]NOTE: While viewing this HDD, I didn&#39;t see any cables in the photos.  So can anyone tell me if it comes with the cables or not?[/b]



[url=&#39;https://www.google.com/url?q=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.newegg.com%2FProduct%2FProduct.aspx%3FItem%3DN82E16833124342&amp;sa=D&amp;sntz=1&amp;usg=AFQjCNFbUJx81COFI15Ew0D-SQQVSxybDA&#39;]Wireless Card: Linksys WMP600N Wireless Adapter with Dual-Band IEEE 802.11a/b/g, IEEE 802.11n Draft 2.0 PCI WEP, WPA &amp; WPA2 Personal, WPA &amp; WPA2 Enterprise ($48.99)[/url] [b]NOTE: I know wireless ins&#39;t the best option but unfortunately, my computer isn&#39;t the &quot;household&quot; computer and can&#39;t be connected via Ethernet or USB[/b]



[url=&#39;https://www.google.com/url?q=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FViewSonic-VX2250WM-LED-21-5-Inch-Widescreen-Integrated%2Fdp%2FB003HFCDLY%2Fref%3Dsr_1_1%3Fie%3DUTF8%26qid%3D1337804666%26sr%3D8-1&amp;sa=D&amp;sntz=1&amp;usg=AFQjCNG_-lX0XxAoarVSNxqqvgs020WGWg&#39;]Monitor: ViewSonic VX2250WM-LED 22-Inch (21.5-Inch Vis) Widescreen Full HD 1080p LED Monitor with Integrated Stereo Speakers (149.99)[/url] [b]I know built in speakers suck.  But I have a VERY nice pair of Sony headphones I&#39;ve been using for almost two years now.  And I&#39;m really only going to be the only one using this computer so it&#39;s not a huge deal.[/b]



[url=&#39;https://www.google.com/url?q=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.logitech.com%2Fen-us%2Ffor-business%2Fproducts%2Fkeyboard-mice-combos%2Fdevices%2F9456&amp;sa=D&amp;sntz=1&amp;usg=AFQjCNHbO5OiUZ85UivQnk5qkHce39Fn0w&#39;]Keyboard/Mouse: Logitech Desktop MK120 (19.99)[/url]



[url=&#39;https://www.google.com/url?q=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FMicrosoft-Windows-7-Home-Premium%2Fdp%2FB002DHGMK0%2Fref%3Dsr_1_2%3Fie%3DUTF8%26qid%3D1337804895%26sr%3D8-2&amp;sa=D&amp;sntz=1&amp;usg=AFQjCNFGthM-TQUVDpDrEIgBZzpUHhhTWw&#39;]OS: Microsoft Windows 7 Home Premium (169.99)[/url] [b]NOTE: OK, this is more of a personal preference but what version of Windows do you use?  Just curious to see what the majority of people use.[/b]

[url=&#39;https://www.google.com/url?q=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.newegg.com%2FProduct%2FProduct.aspx%3FItem%3DN82E16827136247&amp;sa=D&amp;sntz=1&amp;usg=AFQjCNG6YTnHswC0n_gLomIkanMQq_3WSw&#39;]Optical Drive: LG DVD Burner 24X DVD+R 8X DVD+RW 8X DVD+R DL 24X DVD-R 6X DVD-RW 16X DVD-ROM 48X CD-R 32X CD-RW 48X CD-ROM Black SATA Model GH24NS90 - OEM ($17.99)[/url]

[url=&#39;https://www.google.com/url?q=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.newegg.com%2FProduct%2FProduct.aspx%3FItem%3DN82E16817171054&amp;sa=D&amp;sntz=1&amp;usg=AFQjCNEA65oWPQ-GTlKidJjBgW6narcgQA&#39;]PSU: COOLER MASTER eXtreme Power Plus RS700-PCAAE3-US 700W ATX 12V v2.3 Active PFC Power Supply ($79.99)[/url]

Thanks for taking a look.  I apologize for all the information (just copied and pasted my parts list).  Again, please tell me anything and everything you can so I can make my build successful.  I personally think it&#39;s a good start.  Expensive, yes.  But it&#39;s totally worth it.


Thanks!</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 30 May 2012 11:47:44 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Technology and Gaming</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/my-new-computer/8786.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>My New Computer</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[baz_uk]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Regarding the Sli debate here, I have to agree with King_Kaddo - soz</p>
<p>Not saying Sli is rubbish or anything, it certainly does have its advantages and considering how is ‘used’ to be, its come along way.</p>
<p>A single graphics card will always be the better option (in most cases).</p>
<p>However, at the end of the day a personal computer is just that, you can do what ever you like. If users enjoy having sli and think its a better option for them, thats cool. At least we have more options open to us then Apple.</p>
<p>(Sorry had to have a little dig at Apple then as I work on them all day and lately they have really been doing my head in <em>smacks head against desk</em>)</p>
<p>Hope the OP is pleased with their setup once completed. It certainly sounds like he is on the right track!</p>
<p>I think there is some really good advice here  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=9" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/my-new-computer/8786/48">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/my-new-computer/8786/48</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 30 May 2012 11:47:44 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8786-48</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/my-new-computer/8786.rss">My New Computer</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My New Computer</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[King_Kaddo]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>You have no argument in point 1 and can’t deny that it doesn’t happen. You base your facts on your own empirically gathered experience which has no weight at all.</p>
<p>You contradict yourself in point 2 and 4. You are generalizing your own experience again. Graphics card do not work at 50% when they work together. Using basic math two cards would run at the same perfomance of one card if they would only use 50%. You are confusing this with the cpu performance stat of the task manager which always shows.</p>
<p>Point 5, goddamnit do some basic math.</p>
<p>Point 6, you accept my point again and get angry about it and post irrational shit.</p>
<p>Point 7, you don’t even understand what I wrote. 2 gpus in idle use up more power than one in idle, just an addition to point 3</p>
<p>Point 8, Performance here Performance there. This is just another way to ensure your ego that you are the best among the graphics penis size race. If you already have lots of performance and can run lots of games with over 60fps then SLI only makes sense if you want to use heavy graphical improvements as SSAA or Downsampling or graphic mods. We are not talking of mid end cards here. Both 570 and 670 are high end cards that offer lots of performance that is enough for everything in normal conditions. Buying two midrange cards like the GTS450 would be extremely stupid. You would get what? The performance of a single Gtx580 with all the disadvantages of SLI.</p>
<p>Point 9, I am not saying you should wait. I am just saying that upgrading to SLI when the newer generation gets released is not very efficient and even worse than buying a new gpu. You just spend a lot of money to get what exactly?</p>
<p>You are the one who doesn’t know what he’s talking about. I follow the shitrace between every graphicscard out there on technically based tests and know my stuff.<br>
I also gained the experience that SLI users are actively encouraging themselfs and therefor blocking the facts out that SLI/CF is such a big improvement although they won’t feel any difference while playing games. I know the disappointment when you buy a new gpu and test it out but it feels just the same. lame.</p>
<p>You just put some shit on my chest.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/my-new-computer/8786/47">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/my-new-computer/8786/47</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 29 May 2012 21:40:51 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8786-47</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/my-new-computer/8786.rss">My New Computer</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My New Computer</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Mental_Ninja]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="King_Kaddo">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/k/bcef8e/40.png" class="avatar"> King_Kaddo:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>SLI:<br>
microstuttering, higher temperatures, high power consumption, lower lifetime, extremely expensive, more noise, graphics card idle over 90% of the time.</p>
<p>It’s only useful if you have multiple monitors and a resolution way higher than normal FullHD.</p>
<p>700 series? Are you stupid? The time when 700 series comes out buying a second 670 is the dumbest thing you can do. There will be graphis card way more efficient than two 670. SLI is the worst way to spend your money and it’s not worth it. 60-70 percent is a fucking joke.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Why do people who have no idea what the fuck they are talking about, insist on giving advice? Sorry bro, your far from correct. Heres a breakdown of everything he listed for those interested in actually learning something about SLI:</p>
<p>“microstuttering” - Never had this issue at all with my setup, but due to the nature of why this happens, it’s not completely avoidable. However this depends vastly on which cards you have as well as which manufacturer you go with. This is negligible, and happens so infrequently, that it’s almost laughable that you included this as an argument.</p>
<p>“higher temperatures” - Higher temperatures do occur because the two cards are physically next to each other, but overall is very minimal in my SLI rig. With one card you’d see about a 5-10 Celsius decrease in temperature compared to two. Of course this depends on the card combination, airflow, etc… But that is mainly just at idle, once your in game and benefiting from the load balancing that SLI or Crossfire has, you should see lower temps than you did with just one card. At least, this is true in my setup.</p>
<p>“high power consumption” - Yup, you got this one.</p>
<p>“lower lifetime” - At this one i had to say something. Depending on which manufacturer you decide to go with, will depend on how the SLI or Crossfire will perform. However, the cards work by effectively transferring 50% of the load at any given time to the other card in the setup, which increases performance, and decreases wear as one card isn’t getting maxed out. So no, your wrong, this actually improves the life span of your cards, if you run them in an SLI or Crossfire setup, AS WELL as lowers temperatures because the load is equally distributed between the cards.</p>
<p>“extremely  expensive” - Nope. In fact, because it’s cheaper than buying a single high end card, and i can get better performance, as well as longer life is why i did it in the first place.</p>
<p>“more noise” - Yes you will hear a whole one more fan as apposed to just one (depending on the card). Not that big of a deal, and not in any way more noticeable or annoying, except for your post.</p>
<p>“graphics card idle over 90% of the time” - What? I don’t even know what to say here.</p>
<p>“It’s only useful if you have multiple monitors and a resolution way higher than normal FullHD” - It’s useful to everyone thats not a motherfucking idiot, and could use the performance increase the setup offers, as well as the obvious monetary benefit for anyone that would rather get two mid-end cards that can get better performance than a single high-end card for much less money.</p>
<p>“700 series? Are you stupid? The time when 700 series comes out buying a  second 670 is the dumbest thing you can do. There will be graphis card  way more efficient than two 670. SLI is the worst way to spend your  money and it’s not worth it. 60-70 percent is a fucking joke” - I think we all want to ask here: Are you fucking stupid? When the 700 series comes out, sure you will git a tiny bit more performance compared to the 670, you might even get better power management. But you have to be kidding me. You are saying that the 700 series is a more viable alterative than SLI or Crossfire when it comes out because it’s newer, and therefore should be better right? That’s usually not the case, and most of NVidia’s cards from series to series are the exact same board, with the exact same chipset only revised and slightly improved upon to market as a new card. However this is only true usually for the first couple releases of a new series (600 or 700…). Point is, how the fuck is it a better idea to wait for the 700 series and potentially spend upwards of a thousand dollars for a single card, when i can get that same performance from an SLI setup and for 2/3 the cost. If we in the computer industry lived life by your theory of: “everything will always be inefficient to the newer version that has a higher number and will be potentially better than the previous one” then we would all be in debt. You have no argument.</p>
<p>I just took a metaphorical dump on your chest.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/my-new-computer/8786/46">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/my-new-computer/8786/46</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 29 May 2012 20:54:57 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8786-46</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/my-new-computer/8786.rss">My New Computer</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My New Computer</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[DrGonzo]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>That’s only true if you are at the high end. If you bought a mid range or low end card sticking another one in can really help and be a cheap as chips upgrade.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/my-new-computer/8786/45">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/my-new-computer/8786/45</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 29 May 2012 15:46:28 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8786-45</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/my-new-computer/8786.rss">My New Computer</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My New Computer</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[DrGonzo]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>The mobo is not as important as the cpu and gpu. The features may be important to you in certain situations. I just forked out a little extra for Ivy Bridge support, USB 3 and PCIe 3. But a more expensive motherboard won’t suddenly make the pc much faster. It generally doesn’t matter if you aren’t bothered about features.</p>
<p>But a micro ATX board is a pain in the arse to fiddle about with.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/my-new-computer/8786/44">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/my-new-computer/8786/44</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 29 May 2012 15:45:07 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8786-44</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/my-new-computer/8786.rss">My New Computer</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My New Computer</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[King_Kaddo]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>SLI:<br>
microstuttering, higher temperatures, high power consumption, lower lifetime, extremely expensive, more noise, graphics card idle over 90% of the time.</p>
<p>It’s only useful if you have multiple monitors and a resolution way higher than normal FullHD.</p>
<p>700 series? Are you stupid? The time when 700 series comes out buying a second 670 is the dumbest thing you can do. There will be graphis card way more efficient than two 670. SLI is the worst way to spend your money and it’s not worth it. 60-70 percent is a fucking joke.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/my-new-computer/8786/43">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/my-new-computer/8786/43</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 29 May 2012 10:59:54 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8786-43</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/my-new-computer/8786.rss">My New Computer</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My New Computer</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[FunktasticLucky]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="King_Kaddo">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/k/bcef8e/40.png" class="avatar"> King_Kaddo:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>HAHA. The performance difference between Ivy Bridge and Sandy Bridge is extremely small and it makes no sense to upgrade to the next generation if you already have a Sandy Bridge. He said he doesn’t want to overclock so a 2500K is already useless for him. SLI is really worth nothing and has no gain to the user other than to say “HEY LOOK Guys I have 2 grafisk carsdds”.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>you obviously have NO idea what you’re talking about at ALL.  SLI has shown that in some games they come very close to almost double the performance (90 percent) and most games are around 60-70 percent performance increase.  I can easily tell the difference in Skyrim and Diablo 3 when my SLI gets disabled.  When they discontinued the GTX470 I picked up the last EVGA with lifetime warranty newegg had.  No problem playing games of today.  When the prices come down I’ll purchase a GTX670 or 680.  But SLI works. FACT! It’s a cheap way to limp your way to the next generations of cards since they do a new processor every other generation.  So buy a 670 now.  Buy a 2nd one when the 700 series hit the market since it will be a minor update to the Kepler and that will hold you over till the 800 series come out which will be a whole new chip.</p>
<p>I will agree that Ivy Bridge is not that big of a performance increase right now.  The only reason is because windows and games are not programed to take advantage of that many cores.  Windows 8 will take advantage of more than 4 cores but windows 7 will not.  And I don’t expect games to use more than 4 cores for a while.  AMD has had 6 core processors for a few years now and they are about worthless.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/my-new-computer/8786/42">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/my-new-computer/8786/42</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 29 May 2012 10:35:23 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8786-42</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/my-new-computer/8786.rss">My New Computer</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My New Computer</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[King_Kaddo]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="FunktasticLucky">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/f/3ec8ea/40.png" class="avatar"> FunktasticLucky:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>you’re spending more money than you need to.<br>
Then you can upgrade to a Ivy Bridge down the road and add a 2nd GTX670 and you’ll be GOLDEN.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>HAHA. The performance difference between Ivy Bridge and Sandy Bridge is extremely small and it makes no sense to upgrade to the next generation if you already have a Sandy Bridge. He said he doesn’t want to overclock so a 2500K is already useless for him. SLI is really worth nothing and has no gain to the user other than to say “HEY LOOK Guys I have 2 grafisk carsdds”.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/my-new-computer/8786/41">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/my-new-computer/8786/41</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 29 May 2012 08:44:57 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8786-41</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/my-new-computer/8786.rss">My New Computer</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My New Computer</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[FunktasticLucky]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>if I may be so bold to give you some more advice on this one… you’re spending more money than you need to.  Why are you going to spend a little now and then upgrade more in the future if you can afford to do it now??  That’s just spending way more money than you need to.</p>
<p>I have read great things about the Asus Sabertooth.  It’s a very unique looking motherboard.  I own a P8Z68V-Pro and it was rocky at first but does very well now.  If I were building a PC now I would definitely go for a Z77.  If you want to stay a tad cheaper then the Z68 is still a great chipset and supports the 3rd gen Core series CPU’s.  You just lose some things like native USB3.0 and PCI Express 3.0.</p>
<p>Again.  I am telling you save your money and get a Core I5 2500K.  There is NO point in the 2600k.  Games aren’t even optimized for 4 cores so the hyperthreading is just about useless.  It’s not worth the 100 dollars I promise you that.  Put that money elsewhere.</p>
<p>My brother has the Hyper212+.  It’s a nice heatsink.  I’m using the Venomous X with a Different fan.  it’s right up there with the Noctua NH-D14.</p>
<p>my Recommendation is ditch the 2600k.  Like I mentioned above, I disabled my hyperthreading to cut down on heat and allow for slightly higher overclocks. Use the saved money for a 670.  I understand the performance is the same but the heat and power consumption are NOT.  The 670 is running on the new Kepler GPU.  It’s a smaller process which makes it run with less power and heat.  The Fermi GPU was used in teh 400 series cards.  The 500 series are just a slightly updated matured Fermi Processor.  So it’s the same chip just running faster.  I remember reading somewhere that in BF3 the 670 outperformed the 570 by 50 percent.  the 570 isn’t 50 percent cheaper than the 670 so the GTX670 is the better price/performance in that regards.  Go with the Core I5 2500k and put the 100 to a GTX670.  You’re computer will be a better performer in the video game AND video transcoding department.  Then you can upgrade to a Ivy Bridge down the road and add a 2nd GTX670 and you’ll be GOLDEN.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/my-new-computer/8786/40">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/my-new-computer/8786/40</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 29 May 2012 06:25:57 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8786-40</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/my-new-computer/8786.rss">My New Computer</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My New Computer</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[baz_uk]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Not sure if it was mentioned, but make sure you install the 64Bit version of windows 7 or you may find your 8GB RAM being recorded as a little slim, especially if all that VRAM is on top of it too  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=9" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
<p>This may sound silly, but a know many people with 6GB - 8GB and even 16GB ram and they are running 32bit, because they like XP and did not want to change yet.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/my-new-computer/8786/39">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/my-new-computer/8786/39</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 28 May 2012 13:02:12 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8786-39</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/my-new-computer/8786.rss">My New Computer</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My New Computer</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[King_Kaddo]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>A good cpu cooler is really important no matter if you overclock or not. It lowers the power consumption a little bit and increases the cpu lifetime and reduces noise. Take the first mainboard you suggested in the upper post. If you really don’t want to overclock get a normal 2500 or even 2400. They are actually the same, just with a little less frequency. You won’t feel any difference.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/my-new-computer/8786/38">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/my-new-computer/8786/38</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 27 May 2012 15:15:52 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8786-38</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/my-new-computer/8786.rss">My New Computer</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My New Computer</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Mental_Ninja]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="lunertexcosmo">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/l/2acd7d/40.png" class="avatar"> lunertexcosmo:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I found this breakdown of the 570 VS. the 670: <a href="https://www.pcper.com/news/Graphics-Cards/GeForce-GTX-670-vs-GTX-570-Performance-Update" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://www.pcper.com/news/Graphics-Cards/GeForce-GTX-670-vs-GTX-570-Performance-Update</a></p>
<p>In a nutshell, it compares the performance using some benchmarks and some games on max settings.  The significance isn’t too great, but the 670 is clearly the better card.  I’m still planning on buying the 570 since its performance is still really good in comparison with its price.  But if  a game got like 25 fps the 570 as an average and a game on the 670 got like 80-100 frames, then I would definitely be buying that card.  I’ll most likely be buying the 670/680 in the future for when I’m running a really powerful game.</p>
<p>As for the aftermarket coolers, I really don’t plan on overclocking so I really don’t need one.  I’d still benefit from one, but not as much as I would with overclocking.</p>
<p>And as for the motherboards, should I just go with the one I already have, or should I buy number 1 on my suggested list?  The Saber Tooth seems like it’s almost too much for what I need (based on everyone’s opinions).</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Under any other circumstance in the world i would agree, but as an intel 15 2500k owner, and your soon to be purchase of the i7 (which uses the same heat sink), i would spend the extra $25 and get a hyper 212+ at least. With good reason though. The heat sinks that come with those cpus are about as good as blowing on your cpu with your mouth. I measured almost 20 celcius more heat before i switched, and without overclocking. Just an opinion, but i wouldn’t use that piece of crap, and i’m sure most owners of our cpu would agree.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/my-new-computer/8786/37">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/my-new-computer/8786/37</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 27 May 2012 06:18:45 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8786-37</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/my-new-computer/8786.rss">My New Computer</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My New Computer</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[lunertexcosmo]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I found this breakdown of the 570 VS. the 670: <a href="https://www.pcper.com/news/Graphics-Cards/GeForce-GTX-670-vs-GTX-570-Performance-Update" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://www.pcper.com/news/Graphics-Cards/GeForce-GTX-670-vs-GTX-570-Performance-Update</a></p>
<p>In a nutshell, it compares the performance using some benchmarks and some games on max settings.  The significance isn’t too great, but the 670 is clearly the better card.  I’m still planning on buying the 570 since its performance is still really good in comparison with its price.  But if  a game got like 25 fps the 570 as an average and a game on the 670 got like 80-100 frames, then I would definitely be buying that card.  I’ll most likely be buying the 670/680 in the future for when I’m running a really powerful game.</p>
<p>As for the aftermarket coolers, I really don’t plan on overclocking so I really don’t need one.  I’d still benefit from one, but not as much as I would with overclocking.</p>
<p>And as for the motherboards, should I just go with the one I already have, or should I buy number 1 on my suggested list?  The Saber Tooth seems like it’s almost too much for what I need (based on everyone’s opinions).</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/my-new-computer/8786/36">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/my-new-computer/8786/36</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 27 May 2012 04:41:40 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8786-36</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/my-new-computer/8786.rss">My New Computer</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My New Computer</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[papernick]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>tanks</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/my-new-computer/8786/35">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/my-new-computer/8786/35</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 27 May 2012 03:33:44 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8786-35</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/my-new-computer/8786.rss">My New Computer</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My New Computer</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Siggs]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>it just about fits in my mid tower. But mine is cheap, and has bulky side fans with filters on them.</p>
<p><span alt="" class="broken-image" title="This image is broken"><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-unlink svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#unlink"></use></svg></span></p>
<p>I’m sure it’ll be fine.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/my-new-computer/8786/34">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/my-new-computer/8786/34</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 27 May 2012 01:35:06 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8786-34</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/my-new-computer/8786.rss">My New Computer</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My New Computer</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[King_Kaddo]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>The CM 690II is giant. Sure it will fit.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/my-new-computer/8786/33">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/my-new-computer/8786/33</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 27 May 2012 00:31:17 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8786-33</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/my-new-computer/8786.rss">My New Computer</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My New Computer</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[papernick]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Siggs">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/s/f04885/40.png" class="avatar"> Siggs:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Choice of cooler is the arctic cooling ‘Freezer 7 pro’. Yes it is the cheapest one around, but man does it perform.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I’m thinking about getting one of those. I’m not sure if it will fit in my case though. Do you think there’s enough space in a mid tower? (Cooler Master 690 ii and a GTX 560 ti)</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/my-new-computer/8786/32">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/my-new-computer/8786/32</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 26 May 2012 22:18:37 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8786-32</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/my-new-computer/8786.rss">My New Computer</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My New Computer</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[lunertexcosmo]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="King_Kaddo">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/k/bcef8e/40.png" class="avatar"> King_Kaddo:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Mainboards do not really inflict on performance. They are all standardized at some level and only make out a performance differences in the range of 1-2% since they all use the same chipset with minor differences in Audio-,Lan- and controllerchips. If you’re not going to overclock it is meaningless to buy a K model Cpu nor a high class mainboard like the sabertooth. Don’t go for the shiny. Stick to good brands like Asus or Gigabyte. Don’t buy Asrock/Biostar/elitegroup/jetway.<br>
The first mainboard is very good.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>By first, do you mean the one I put on my parts list or the one I suggested above?<br>
<span class="bbcode-b"><br>
And just a FYI to all: I really don’t plan on overclocking.  At least at this time.  I just really don’t want to mess with that stuff until I have to  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=9" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"> </span></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/my-new-computer/8786/31">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/my-new-computer/8786/31</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 26 May 2012 21:34:30 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8786-31</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/my-new-computer/8786.rss">My New Computer</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My New Computer</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Siggs]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>my personal mobo choice is ASUS. great quality and performance, even when overclocking. Especially when overclocking.</p>
<p>Choice of cooler is the arctic cooling ‘Freezer 7 pro’. Yes it is the cheapest one around, but man does it perform.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/my-new-computer/8786/30">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/my-new-computer/8786/30</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 26 May 2012 21:02:36 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8786-30</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/my-new-computer/8786.rss">My New Computer</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My New Computer</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Mental_Ninja]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="King_Kaddo">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/k/bcef8e/40.png" class="avatar"> King_Kaddo:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I am not sure with Asrock. They were terrible in the past. That may have changed.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I can second Asrock, I have the P67 Extreme 4 and love it. The utilities are a plus too, if you want to use them.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/my-new-computer/8786/29">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/my-new-computer/8786/29</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 26 May 2012 19:17:52 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8786-29</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/my-new-computer/8786.rss">My New Computer</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My New Computer</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[King_Kaddo]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I am not sure with Asrock. They were terrible in the past. That may have changed.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/my-new-computer/8786/28">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/my-new-computer/8786/28</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 26 May 2012 13:22:22 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8786-28</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/my-new-computer/8786.rss">My New Computer</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My New Computer</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[FireTime]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Why the hate for Asrock. Very pleased with my X79 Extreme6/GB. Came with some nice windows utilities like Instant boot (from off to desktop in a matter of seconds) and XFast USB (increased USB file transfer speeds). As well as a very easy to use use graphical BIOS.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/my-new-computer/8786/27">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/my-new-computer/8786/27</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 26 May 2012 13:11:48 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8786-27</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/my-new-computer/8786.rss">My New Computer</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My New Computer</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[King_Kaddo]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Mainboards do not really inflict on performance. They are all standardized at some level and only make out a performance differences in the range of 1-2% since they all use the same chipset with minor differences in Audio-,Lan- and controllerchips. If you’re not going to overclock it is meaningless to buy a K model Cpu nor a high class mainboard like the sabertooth. Don’t go for the shiny. Stick to good brands like Asus or Gigabyte. Don’t buy Asrock/Biostar/elitegroup/jetway.<br>
The first mainboard is very good.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/my-new-computer/8786/26">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/my-new-computer/8786/26</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 26 May 2012 10:35:56 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8786-26</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/my-new-computer/8786.rss">My New Computer</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My New Computer</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[lunertexcosmo]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="FunktasticLucky">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/f/3ec8ea/40.png" class="avatar"> FunktasticLucky:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>My Suggestions to you… Don’t get the 2600k.  Get the 2500k.  It is just as fast and it’s 100 dollars cheaper.  Put that 100 dollars towards a GTX 670 or a really nice aftermarket CPU cooler. You’ll want one of those to overclock the crap out of your 2500k.</p>
<p>2nd… Why did you buy a full tower case but then go for a Micro ATX motherboard??  Did you just find the cheapest Motherboard you could find?? bad idea.  The motherboard is just as important as the processor and the video card.  You get way skimpy on the motherboard you’re going to lose the performance of the entire system.</p>
<p>The Ram is good.  I didn’t get it because it sits WAY high and could cause interference with the larger aftermarket CPU coolers.  I suggest going with the G. Skill Ripjaws.  They look good and they are not really tall so they don’t interfere with coolers as badly.  8GB is good. Windows 7 LOVES lots of ram so it can cache programs in it to start them up faster.  so yes keep the 8GB.</p>
<p>Hard Drives as stated before are definitely a weak point here.  You bought a 1TB drive at 5900 RPM when seagate has a 1TB 7200 for cheaper.  I recommend looking through it again.</p>
<p>I’m just curious here.  What’s your budget if you don’t mind me asking?  1500? I’m just wondering.  If you have a little tech know how I’d say save yourself another 50 bux and just buy the windows 7 home premium upgrade.  There are lots of websites that tell you how to install a clean version and activate it later so that you dont’ have to have another version of windows installed to upgrade to windows 7. But if you reply to this and let me know a budget and what exactly this PC will be used for, we’ll see if we can whip something up for you.  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=9" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
<p>Edit: I decided to explain the processor thing.  The only real difference between the 2600k and the 2500k is hyperthreading.  But since most games and windows are not optimized for multi core, hyperthreading doesn’t do JACK.  I disabled mine and allowed it to run a little bit cooler.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Thanks for your advice.  I switched out the HDD for the 1 tb 7200 rpm that you suggested.  I was actually trying to find one of those in the first place but I guess I somehow missed it.  I’ve decided to stick with my i7 and GTX 570 for now.  However, I may upgrade (once I have the money) to an extreme edition and one of the higher levels of GTX cards.  As for the mobo, the one I picked out has five stars and I went with it because of its price/feedback ratio.  But there are two more mobo’s I’m considering now that you can take a look at.  And as for W7, thanks for the offer, but I’m going with the legit Windows club.  Some of the software I need only runs on MS copies  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=9" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"> .  And I never really had a budget to begin with.  I’ve always gone with the approach that if what I needed costed an X number of dollars, than that’s what I would have to pay to be happy.  But I’m trying not to go anywhere above $1450-1500 give or take.</p>
<p>Here’s my new possible mobo choices:</p>
<p>1.) <a href="https://www.newegg.com/Product/Product.aspx?Item=N82E16813131835" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">ASUS P8B75-V LGA 1155 Intel B75 SATA 6Gb/s USB 3.0 ATX Intel Motherboard</a></p>
<p>2.) <a href="https://www.newegg.com/Product/Product.aspx?Item=N82E16813131821" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">ASUS SABERTOOTH Z77 LGA 1155 Intel Z77 HDMI SATA 6Gb/s USB 3.0 ATX Intel Motherboard</a> (This one’s a beast.  But it looks like it may be worth it if I feel like upgrading to the third gen intel i7’s.  But the ones they have now are more than enough so I’m still debating.  Pricey, but nice)</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/my-new-computer/8786/25">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/my-new-computer/8786/25</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 26 May 2012 08:39:55 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8786-25</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/my-new-computer/8786.rss">My New Computer</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My New Computer</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[GuitarJim]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Plus one on the i5 2500K.</p>
<p>In addition I would recommend getting a good after market cooler like a Coolermaster Hyper 212 plus and upgrade to the GTX 670.</p>
<p>The 670 is a little better than the 580 in most games so will be a significant step up from the 570.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/my-new-computer/8786/24">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/my-new-computer/8786/24</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 26 May 2012 08:15:22 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8786-24</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/my-new-computer/8786.rss">My New Computer</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
