<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Emphasis on the Rocket Launch</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/emphasis-on-the-rocket-launch/10807</link>
    <description>So I just finished playing through Black Mesa, started playing about 4 days ago. So I thought I&#39;d give some of my thoughts.


AWESOME!!

Honestly, this has to be the best mod I have ever played in my life. To be honest I never actually played Half Life before this just read up about it but Black Mesa hooked its teeth into me pretty good.  :smiley: 

Now this being the internet and all negativity I feel like I should list just a few issues I have, but remember I&#39;m not complaining as I adore the game but I feel a few things could still be addressed. 

1. The rocket you fire at the end of [i]On a Rail[/i], I feel that [u]why[/u] you&#39;re setting off this rocket should be explained more. Because while I was setting it off I just kept wondering &quot;Why am I doing this? Whats the point of this? Whats on that rocket?&quot; it wasn&#39;t until later that I found out that there was a satellite on the rocket that some scientists tried to get into orbit but failed that would halt and reverse the Resonance Cascade. I found that out by going to the wiki. Was this ever explained at all in game? I feel like there should be more explanation on this.

2. By the time of the chapters [i]Surface Tension[/i]  and [i]Forget about Freeman[/i] the HECU are losing the battle against the aliens forcing the military to pull back and start heavy artillery strikes on Black Mesa. However in the mod I feel this also isnt shown well, in the few times you see the aliens fighting the military the military always seems to come out on top and that Gordon is the only thing really standing in their way. I feel that in the full release this should also be tweaked a bit where you really see more of how the HECU are getting pounded and destroyed against the alien forces. In the beginning when you first meet them in [i]We&#39;ve got Hostiles![/i] they are winning the fight, slaughtering any Black Mesa personal they see and containing the aliens and slowly through the chapters you see them get pushed back more and more due to both Freeman and the aliens and by the events of [i]Surface Tension [/i] they are losing the fight. You just don&#39;t really see that.

3. At the end of [i]Lambda Core[/i] they tell you that some creature on Xen is keeping the dimensional rip open and that Gordon has to go to Xen and kill it. So obviously the rocket you sent up into orbit a day earlier didn&#39;t work but they never even mention the rocket. I feel that they should at least mention it in passing like &quot;Unfortunately the satellite you sent up yesterday failed to close the dimensional rip but we still have one solution, we have discovered that a creature ...blah blah blah&quot; See? Simple and it addresses it.

Really just a few minor things but fantastic game nonetheless  :smiley: 

Can&#39;t wait for the full release with Xen and the rest of the chapters! Hope it doesn&#39;t take too long.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 20 Sep 2012 07:33:23 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>The Cafeteria</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/emphasis-on-the-rocket-launch/10807.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Emphasis on the Rocket Launch</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Artic_Xiongmao]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Yeah, the Lambda team could contact you via radio in the control room and explain the rocket launch in a bit of further detail. Just a sentence or two, before you can hit the button. It’d be wonderful.</p>
<p>And yes, I hope they fix the apparent scripted dominance of the HECU against the aliens.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/emphasis-on-the-rocket-launch/10807/36">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/emphasis-on-the-rocket-launch/10807/36</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 20 Sep 2012 07:33:23 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-10807-36</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/emphasis-on-the-rocket-launch/10807.rss">Emphasis on the Rocket Launch</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Emphasis on the Rocket Launch</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[MrFob]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I can definitely see where the OP is coming from.<br>
The rocket issue is just there because the explanation occurs quite some time before you actually do it. However, I remember this was way more of an issue in HL1 itself. IIRC, some guy shouts something about a rocket at you while you are riding by on a train car (and there was also some mention about it before the blast pit, I think) but when I first did it HL1, I hit the button and thought “Oh, look at that, I just launched a rocket into space … hm, that was cool …?!?”<br>
In Black Mesa, at least you can see some stuff on the monitors in launch control that hints at what it’s all really about. IMO it would have really been cool if the lambda core guys would contact you in the control room and tell you what you are doing and maybe talk you through a launch procedure that consists of a bit more than just pressing the ig red button (well, at least now we raise the thing out of the silo ourselves). I also agree, it would have been cool if the rocket would have been mentioned at the end.<br>
All that said, HK alsways told a large chunk of tit’s story by subtle hints in the environments rather than through dialogue or cutscenes or the like. BM does this even better since there such an awesome level of detail to pretty much everything in the game.</p>
<p>I (as well as many others) totally agree with the HECO vs. aliens issue. That seems to be one of the most widely accepted criticisms about an otherwise fantastic experience.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/emphasis-on-the-rocket-launch/10807/35">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/emphasis-on-the-rocket-launch/10807/35</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 20 Sep 2012 07:12:25 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-10807-35</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/emphasis-on-the-rocket-launch/10807.rss">Emphasis on the Rocket Launch</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Emphasis on the Rocket Launch</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[JJAB91]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Look we all know what the satellite did thats not the issue. The issue is that it is never explained in game. Doesn’t matter if it was explained in HL1 or its expansions it was never really explained in Black Mesa and thats the problem.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/emphasis-on-the-rocket-launch/10807/34">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/emphasis-on-the-rocket-launch/10807/34</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 20 Sep 2012 06:17:13 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-10807-34</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/emphasis-on-the-rocket-launch/10807.rss">Emphasis on the Rocket Launch</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Emphasis on the Rocket Launch</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Artic_Xiongmao]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Both, actually. The new satellite connects to the one from Black Mesa and closes the superportal.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/emphasis-on-the-rocket-launch/10807/33">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/emphasis-on-the-rocket-launch/10807/33</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 19 Sep 2012 22:18:50 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-10807-33</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/emphasis-on-the-rocket-launch/10807.rss">Emphasis on the Rocket Launch</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Emphasis on the Rocket Launch</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Ronster]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="kupocake">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/k/a87d85/40.png" class="avatar"> kupocake:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Isn’t the rocket explained in the PS2 Co-op mod, Decay?</p>
<p>“Once reunited with Keller, Cross and Green work to seal the dimensional tear to stop the invasion. The military arrive and try to remove all personnel as well as the alien force. After resetting key equipment to prevent a second dimensional rift, the two are tasked with preparing a satellite for launch. The satellite, which is launched by Freeman in Half-Life, is used in tandem with ground-based equipment to significantly weaken the effects of the resonance cascade.[10] Keller tasks Cross and Green with activating this set of prototype equipment, a displacement beacon, which through the satellite may be able to seal the dimensional rift. However, after activating the beacon, both characters are caught up in a “harmonic reflux”, a distortion caused by the rift. Despite this, Cross and Green are able to return safely and Keller congratulates them on their success.[11]”</p>
<p>(questionable canonically, but I was under the impression the major plot points such as this and the Black Ops nuke were checked with Valve).</p>
<p>Also, and my Half-Life lore is sketchy, but wasn’t the purpose of the HL2 Ep2 rocket to re-establish contact with the Satellite launched via the rocket in Half-Life 1?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>yes you are right on Decay… But Decay was like an addon by gearhouse, I am saying that I think “uplink” was originally intended to be contacting the sattalite you launch where as in “uplink” Demo you are told it is so he can get a door open to lambda core which is stupid and I think this was just for the demo and a simple story for the cut level.</p>
<p>That was not ever it’s original intention for creation atleast that is what I think</p>
<ol>
<li>
<p>because it’s at night like when you launch the rocket</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>They need to establish communications link with the sattalite</p>
</li>
</ol>
<p>3, You as the player were involved in stopping or trying to stop the portal tearing open wider and this was the 2nd part you had to play in it establishing the communication with the tool to stop the portal or diminish it.</p>
<p>So the demo changed that and made up some crap about it was to open a door  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/frowning.png?v=9" title=":frowning:" class="emoji" alt=":frowning:">  ultimatlely the sattalite failed anyway</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/emphasis-on-the-rocket-launch/10807/32">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/emphasis-on-the-rocket-launch/10807/32</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 19 Sep 2012 22:18:21 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-10807-32</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/emphasis-on-the-rocket-launch/10807.rss">Emphasis on the Rocket Launch</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Emphasis on the Rocket Launch</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[SiCaRiO]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>no, i think it was to close the new portal been made by the combine</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/emphasis-on-the-rocket-launch/10807/31">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/emphasis-on-the-rocket-launch/10807/31</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 19 Sep 2012 21:53:46 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-10807-31</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/emphasis-on-the-rocket-launch/10807.rss">Emphasis on the Rocket Launch</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Emphasis on the Rocket Launch</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[kupocake]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Isn’t the rocket explained in the PS2 Co-op mod, Decay?</p>
<p>“Once reunited with Keller, Cross and Green work to seal the dimensional tear to stop the invasion. The military arrive and try to remove all personnel as well as the alien force. After resetting key equipment to prevent a second dimensional rift, the two are tasked with preparing a satellite for launch. The satellite, which is launched by Freeman in Half-Life, is used in tandem with ground-based equipment to significantly weaken the effects of the resonance cascade.[10] Keller tasks Cross and Green with activating this set of prototype equipment, a displacement beacon, which through the satellite may be able to seal the dimensional rift. However, after activating the beacon, both characters are caught up in a “harmonic reflux”, a distortion caused by the rift. Despite this, Cross and Green are able to return safely and Keller congratulates them on their success.[11]”</p>
<p>(questionable canonically, but I was under the impression the major plot points such as this and the Black Ops nuke were checked with Valve).</p>
<p>Also, and my Half-Life lore is sketchy, but wasn’t the purpose of the HL2 Ep2 rocket to re-establish contact with the Satellite launched via the rocket in Half-Life 1?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/emphasis-on-the-rocket-launch/10807/30">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/emphasis-on-the-rocket-launch/10807/30</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 19 Sep 2012 19:08:44 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-10807-30</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/emphasis-on-the-rocket-launch/10807.rss">Emphasis on the Rocket Launch</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Emphasis on the Rocket Launch</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Ronster]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>The rocket launch was done very well… The mission was in 2 parts the launch and you also had to align a dish to communicate with the sattalite</p>
<p>It was cut from the original half life game but released as a stand alone demo called “uplink” you could mod half life to include the mission in the game but I don’t think it’s position is in the correct place after surface tension.</p>
<p>I think it should come directly after on a rail. because it’s at night and you get apprehended on your way to lamda core and end up in a dumpster.</p>
<p>The dish looked rubbish If it was re-imagined I would prefer to see it like a full parabolic dish. I mapped this dish into the source engine see below.</p>
<p><a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/File:Antenna_One_(Arthur)at_Goonhilly(side_view).jpg" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/File:Antenna_One_(Arthur)<em>at_Goonhilly</em>(side_view).jpg</a></p>
<p>It’s not only the first ever full parabolic dish but also part of the largest dish array in the world and is called King Arthur because it is in cornwall in the UK</p>
<p><a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/File:Antenna_One_(Arthur)at_Goonhilly(front_view).jpg" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/File:Antenna_One_(Arthur)<em>at_Goonhilly</em>(front_view).jpg</a></p>
<p>I imagined this to be a better substitute for the dish in uplink and it has a bit of history and is old design but looks cool especially all the walkways and it’s verticality</p>
<p><a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/File:Antenna_One_(Arthur)at_Goonhilly(rear_view).jpg" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/File:Antenna_One_(Arthur)<em>at_Goonhilly</em>(rear_view).jpg</a></p>
<p>So this is part of how I re-imagined uplink but to keep the dome that would lead to this structure outside of it.</p>
<p>Uplink had some good scripted sequences too but it was never properly intergrated into the original half life. It should of been directly after on a rail not surface tension… This is why it seemed to make no sense I guess. It was quite a short level but had some good fun momments in it like HECUS Burning VORTS. HECUS executing scientists combine style and also featured the GMAN and a GARG at the end.</p>
<p>I think after you launch the rocket Uplink starts but you would have to run to a different door under artillary fire and into the control room where you get given the mission and where it ends is back out to the launch site again and on to apprehension where you see GMAN walk through at the end of “Uplink” where the GARG also is will take you back to the launch site or atleast this way it would make sense because after “surface tension” made no sense</p>
<p><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=PO9Y-AUAaa0" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=PO9Y-AUAaa0</a></p>
<p><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=DpS_vkvC6Qg&amp;feature=relmfu" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=DpS_vkvC6Qg&amp;feature=relmfu</a></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/emphasis-on-the-rocket-launch/10807/29">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/emphasis-on-the-rocket-launch/10807/29</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 19 Sep 2012 17:13:05 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-10807-29</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/emphasis-on-the-rocket-launch/10807.rss">Emphasis on the Rocket Launch</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Emphasis on the Rocket Launch</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[JJAB91]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Pyro">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/p/71e660/40.png" class="avatar"> Pyro:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Apocryphal new race of aliens from Opposing Force. Supposedly, they came through via Xen, presumably fleeing the combine like the Xenians themselves, and tried to invade earth.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Odd when you consider we never heard from them again afterward. It leaves many questions. Who exactly were Race X? Where did they come from? What was their motivation? Why haven’t we seen them again? Where are they now? What was their relationship with the Xenians?</p>
<p>Although the HL1 expansions are kind of up in the air as far as canon is concerned. Although I believe they are generally regarded as canon. Are at least parts of it.(Like the destruction of Black Mesa with the nuke)</p>
<p>I don’t know if any of you are into the lore of Halo but the HL1 expansions kind of remind of the I Love Bees ARG that promoted Halo 2. The canonicity of it remains in debate and at least some parts of it seem to be canon while others simply can’t be. Although the good thing about Halo is after 11 years of games, novels and short stories everything all fits together perfectly with only a few small retcons and only that one ARG having canon up in the air. And one small non-canon story in Halo Legends played as satire.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/emphasis-on-the-rocket-launch/10807/28">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/emphasis-on-the-rocket-launch/10807/28</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 19 Sep 2012 15:46:19 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-10807-28</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/emphasis-on-the-rocket-launch/10807.rss">Emphasis on the Rocket Launch</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Emphasis on the Rocket Launch</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[JJAB91]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Pyro">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/p/71e660/40.png" class="avatar"> Pyro:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Yeah, the lack of marine/alien fights is definitely a fault. It’s been clearly explained before that quite a few areas of Surface Tension, where you would’ve seen the aliens start to win, were cut due to time constraints when a mapper quit.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I hope the maybe they can add that back in, maybe as a post release thing. Or at least change some of the AI imbalances that cause the marines to win everytime like the other guy mentioned.</p>
<p>They could tweak it til the Xenians win a majority of the fights for the Steam release and everyone would be happy.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/emphasis-on-the-rocket-launch/10807/27">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/emphasis-on-the-rocket-launch/10807/27</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 19 Sep 2012 15:38:43 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-10807-27</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/emphasis-on-the-rocket-launch/10807.rss">Emphasis on the Rocket Launch</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Emphasis on the Rocket Launch</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Pyroclase]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="GordonFreedman">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/g/76d3ee/40.png" class="avatar"> GordonFreedman:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>What is this?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Apocryphal new race of aliens from Opposing Force. Supposedly, they came through via Xen, presumably fleeing the combine like the Xenians themselves, and tried to invade earth.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/emphasis-on-the-rocket-launch/10807/26">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/emphasis-on-the-rocket-launch/10807/26</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 19 Sep 2012 15:03:07 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-10807-26</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/emphasis-on-the-rocket-launch/10807.rss">Emphasis on the Rocket Launch</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Emphasis on the Rocket Launch</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[David_VI]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Bloodshot">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/b/839c29/40.png" class="avatar"> Bloodshot:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Most of the battles where the HECU win are due to the AI imbalances though, as it is right now the HECU are too strong vs the Xenian forces. Since this is easily fixable in the skill.cfg, I have a feeling we will see more Xenian forces winning battles in the Steam release. Hell, I did some slight changes myself to make it a bit more like HL1 and the Agrunts are already kicking HECU ass at those points now.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Could you share some of these fixes? Is it the same as lowering reaction times and the power of the HECU guns?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/emphasis-on-the-rocket-launch/10807/25">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/emphasis-on-the-rocket-launch/10807/25</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 19 Sep 2012 14:53:10 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-10807-25</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/emphasis-on-the-rocket-launch/10807.rss">Emphasis on the Rocket Launch</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Emphasis on the Rocket Launch</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[GordonFreedman]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Devils barber">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Devils barber:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>The H.E.C.U Marines weren’t getting they’re asses kicked, the commander just didn’t wanna waste any more troops on black mesa. Its like the war with japan, sure the U.S could had eventually own japan by sending enough troops but decided to use the atom bomb instead so no more troops would die, this is the same with black mesa.</p>
<p>Even tho the H.E.C.U Marines were fighting 5 different enemies at the same time, gordon, BM Security, Black Ops, Xen, <span class="bbcode-b">Race X</span>, they could had still won if the commander wants to send enough troops.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>What is this?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/emphasis-on-the-rocket-launch/10807/24">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/emphasis-on-the-rocket-launch/10807/24</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 19 Sep 2012 14:39:03 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-10807-24</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/emphasis-on-the-rocket-launch/10807.rss">Emphasis on the Rocket Launch</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Emphasis on the Rocket Launch</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Bloodshot]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Most of the battles where the HECU win are due to the AI imbalances though, as it is right now the HECU are too strong vs the Xenian forces. Since this is easily fixable in the skill.cfg, I have a feeling we will see more Xenian forces winning battles in the Steam release. Hell, I did some slight changes myself to make it a bit more like HL1 and the Agrunts are already kicking HECU ass at those points now.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/emphasis-on-the-rocket-launch/10807/23">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/emphasis-on-the-rocket-launch/10807/23</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 19 Sep 2012 14:37:49 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-10807-23</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/emphasis-on-the-rocket-launch/10807.rss">Emphasis on the Rocket Launch</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Emphasis on the Rocket Launch</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Devils_barber]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="JJAB91">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/j/ebca7d/40.png" class="avatar"> JJAB91:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>So I just finished playing through Black Mesa, started playing about 4 days ago. So I thought I’d give some of my thoughts.</p>
<p>AWESOME!!</p>
<p>Honestly, this has to be the best mod I have ever played in my life. To be honest I never actually played Half Life before this just read up about it but Black Mesa hooked its teeth into me pretty good.  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/smiley.png?v=9" title=":smiley:" class="emoji" alt=":smiley:"></p>
<p>Now this being the internet and all negativity I feel like I should list just a few issues I have, but remember I’m not complaining as I adore the game but I feel a few things could still be addressed.</p>
<ol>
<li>
<p>The rocket you fire at the end of <span class="bbcode-i">On a Rail</span>, I feel that <span class="bbcode-u">why</span> you’re setting off this rocket should be explained more. Because while I was setting it off I just kept wondering “Why am I doing this? Whats the point of this? Whats on that rocket?” it wasn’t until later that I found out that there was a satellite on the rocket that some scientists tried to get into orbit but failed that would halt and reverse the Resonance Cascade. I found that out by going to the wiki. Was this ever explained at all in game? I feel like there should be more explanation on this.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>By the time of the chapters <span class="bbcode-i">Surface Tension</span>  and <span class="bbcode-i">Forget about Freeman</span> the HECU are losing the battle against the aliens forcing the military to pull back and start heavy artillery strikes on Black Mesa. However in the mod I feel this also isnt shown well, in the few times you see the aliens fighting the military the military always seems to come out on top and that Gordon is the only thing really standing in their way. I feel that in the full release this should also be tweaked a bit where you really see more of how the HECU are getting pounded and destroyed against the alien forces. In the beginning when you first meet them in <span class="bbcode-i">We’ve got Hostiles!</span> they are winning the fight, slaughtering any Black Mesa personal they see and containing the aliens and slowly through the chapters you see them get pushed back more and more due to both Freeman and the aliens and by the events of <span class="bbcode-i">Surface Tension </span> they are losing the fight. You just don’t really see that.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>At the end of <span class="bbcode-i">Lambda Core</span> they tell you that some creature on Xen is keeping the dimensional rip open and that Gordon has to go to Xen and kill it. So obviously the rocket you sent up into orbit a day earlier didn’t work but they never even mention the rocket. I feel that they should at least mention it in passing like “Unfortunately the satellite you sent up yesterday failed to close the dimensional rip but we still have one solution, we have discovered that a creature …blah blah blah” See? Simple and it addresses it.</p>
</li>
</ol>
<p>Really just a few minor things but fantastic game nonetheless  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/smiley.png?v=9" title=":smiley:" class="emoji" alt=":smiley:"></p>
<p>Can’t wait for the full release with Xen and the rest of the chapters! Hope it doesn’t take too long.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>The H.E.C.U Marines weren’t getting they’re asses kicked, the commander just didn’t wanna waste any more troops on black mesa. Its like the war with japan, sure the U.S could had eventually own japan by sending enough troops but decided to use the atom bomb instead so no more troops would die, this is the same with black mesa.</p>
<p>Even tho the H.E.C.U Marines were fighting 5 different enemies at the same time, gordon, BM Security, Black Ops, Xen, Race X, they could had still won if the commander wants to send enough troops.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/emphasis-on-the-rocket-launch/10807/22">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/emphasis-on-the-rocket-launch/10807/22</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 19 Sep 2012 14:35:06 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-10807-22</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/emphasis-on-the-rocket-launch/10807.rss">Emphasis on the Rocket Launch</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Emphasis on the Rocket Launch</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Pyroclase]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Yeah, the lack of marine/alien fights is definitely a fault. It’s been clearly explained before that quite a few areas of Surface Tension, where you would’ve seen the aliens start to win, were cut due to time constraints when a mapper quit.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/emphasis-on-the-rocket-launch/10807/21">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/emphasis-on-the-rocket-launch/10807/21</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 19 Sep 2012 14:28:23 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-10807-21</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/emphasis-on-the-rocket-launch/10807.rss">Emphasis on the Rocket Launch</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Emphasis on the Rocket Launch</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[nubber]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>HE<span class="bbcode-b">C</span>U: Hazardous Environment <span class="bbcode-b">C</span>ombat Unit please.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/emphasis-on-the-rocket-launch/10807/20">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/emphasis-on-the-rocket-launch/10807/20</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 19 Sep 2012 13:56:35 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-10807-20</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/emphasis-on-the-rocket-launch/10807.rss">Emphasis on the Rocket Launch</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Emphasis on the Rocket Launch</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[JJAB91]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="pinkribbonscars">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/p/a88e57/40.png" class="avatar"> pinkribbonscars:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>You can see during “Forget About Freeman” chapter. When you exit the facility there’s a huge war going on, and they’re retreating via Vtols.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>There is only two real major fights between the HESU and Xenian forces, one near the end of Surface tension before the tank and TOW missile part and another near the end of Forget about Freeman. In both cases the HESU won and decimated all Xenian forces.</p>
<p>EDIT: Actually I remember two more now, one where you first see a manta ray fly by and a small army of alien grunts show up…only to be bombed and killed by the HESU and then another time with a tank, marines, and alien grunts in a parking garage and the HESU won that too.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/emphasis-on-the-rocket-launch/10807/19">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/emphasis-on-the-rocket-launch/10807/19</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 19 Sep 2012 12:57:30 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-10807-19</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/emphasis-on-the-rocket-launch/10807.rss">Emphasis on the Rocket Launch</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Emphasis on the Rocket Launch</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[pinkribbonscars]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="JJAB91">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/j/ebca7d/40.png" class="avatar"> JJAB91:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Actually what I meant in my post was the marines being on top and then slowly losing is what it SHOULD have been but instead we got the marines being on top and never losing which is not how it should be.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>You can see during “Forget About Freeman” chapter. When you exit the facility there’s a huge war going on, and they’re retreating via Vtols.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/emphasis-on-the-rocket-launch/10807/18">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/emphasis-on-the-rocket-launch/10807/18</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 19 Sep 2012 12:46:52 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-10807-18</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/emphasis-on-the-rocket-launch/10807.rss">Emphasis on the Rocket Launch</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Emphasis on the Rocket Launch</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Artic_Xiongmao]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Yeah, the rocket should’ve been enough but “something big” is holding the portal open. We get that much, by the scientists at the Lambda teleporter. But it’d be nice to know that before launching the rocket itself, and maybe some “hey, thanks for the rocket launch” after.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/emphasis-on-the-rocket-launch/10807/17">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/emphasis-on-the-rocket-launch/10807/17</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 19 Sep 2012 12:35:21 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-10807-17</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/emphasis-on-the-rocket-launch/10807.rss">Emphasis on the Rocket Launch</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Emphasis on the Rocket Launch</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[ZindroVokun]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Yeah - I looked around for the storylines online, and it seems that satellites can close portals - like the one in Episode 2. So this’ll be the first attempt to close a portal by satellite, but of course it fails due to Nihilianth.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/emphasis-on-the-rocket-launch/10807/16">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/emphasis-on-the-rocket-launch/10807/16</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 19 Sep 2012 12:31:56 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-10807-16</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/emphasis-on-the-rocket-launch/10807.rss">Emphasis on the Rocket Launch</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Emphasis on the Rocket Launch</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Artic_Xiongmao]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I know that, obviously. It’s just that the game doesn’t explain it very well, if at all. We get a single sentence from a security guard who does not know what’s happening, and then, as far as I remember, nothing. Maybe the scientist who opens you the door to the Lambda Complex says something, but I’m pretty sure it’s nothing concrete.</p>
<p>I’m not asking for an overly-scientific explanation. But something more than “it’s to clean up this mess” would be wonderful, and some recognition for launching the rocket at the end, at the Lambda teleporter, would be nice too.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/emphasis-on-the-rocket-launch/10807/15">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/emphasis-on-the-rocket-launch/10807/15</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 19 Sep 2012 12:25:11 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-10807-15</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/emphasis-on-the-rocket-launch/10807.rss">Emphasis on the Rocket Launch</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Emphasis on the Rocket Launch</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[ysrael214]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Gordon was asked to send the rocket to space to serve as a satellite in closing the portal but they can’t close it because the Nihilianth is keeping it open so in Lambda Core, the Lambda Team asked Gordon to kill the being.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/emphasis-on-the-rocket-launch/10807/14">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/emphasis-on-the-rocket-launch/10807/14</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 19 Sep 2012 12:19:32 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-10807-14</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/emphasis-on-the-rocket-launch/10807.rss">Emphasis on the Rocket Launch</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Emphasis on the Rocket Launch</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Hyperbyte]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Artic Xiongmao">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Artic Xiongmao:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Good point about the intended ambiguity. But at least a reaction from the Lambda team would be nice  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/wink.png?v=9" title=":wink:" class="emoji" alt=":wink:"></p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Didn’t they?  I seem to recall the scientist who opens the small door after the huge fight with several alien grunts (beginning of Lambda Core) mentions the rocket.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/emphasis-on-the-rocket-launch/10807/13">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/emphasis-on-the-rocket-launch/10807/13</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 19 Sep 2012 12:15:17 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-10807-13</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/emphasis-on-the-rocket-launch/10807.rss">Emphasis on the Rocket Launch</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Emphasis on the Rocket Launch</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[JJAB91]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Artic Xiongmao">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Artic Xiongmao:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I had hoped they would emphasize the importance of the rocket launch, but unfortunately they did not. It was explained in passing both in the original and Black Mesa, and by an ignorant security guard no less. As it does happen with other things in the game, the dialogue should be expanded: we should get a deeper explanation of the rockets purpose <em>before</em> the launch by a surviving scientist, maybe in the control room itself, and maybe a comment on it once we arrive at the Lambda teleporter.</p>
<p>Also, they could add or change a few scripted sequences so that the Aliens start coming up on top against the marines. It looks as if Freeman is the sole reason they are pulling out. In the original this was partly true, too (“Forget about Freeman!” is the name of a whole chapter after all), but you could see that the HECU were losing the battle.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Well the chapter title makes sense, forget about Freeman as in the military has far more urgent matters than Gordon.</p>
<p>I’m REALLY hoping these things are fixed when Xen and the other chapters come out and its all one big nice package.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/emphasis-on-the-rocket-launch/10807/12">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/emphasis-on-the-rocket-launch/10807/12</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 19 Sep 2012 12:14:13 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-10807-12</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/emphasis-on-the-rocket-launch/10807.rss">Emphasis on the Rocket Launch</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
