<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>floating Marines</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/floating-marines/10887</link>
    <description>I have come across my fair share of nitpick Glitches, most of which are just so minor that they weren&#39;t worth mentioning in my opinion, or have been brought up by other members of the community to one end or another, this is just a glitch that I encountered that actually impeded the game sort of.

At the part of the game where you go outside to make your way to the manually loaded mounter rocket launcher....er....thingy....there is a helicopter that is constantly dropping marines into the area, when I played through this part I had a strange glitch where the repelling soldiers dropped out of the Helicopter and and just remained in a clump standing in the air, they don&#39;t shoot and I was unable to kill one of them, I ended up having to reload my save to stop them from floating and yelling about how I was right in front of them. you can see described hilarity in the screenshots I attached. While this was mostly just hilarious, it does impede progress since you need to destroy the helicopter that drops them off to continue, and in order for the helicopter to show up again all the Marines previously dropped need to die. It was still pretty fucking hilarious.

The mod was still worth the Years of waiting, the whole thing is amazing work, mad kudo&#39;s to the devs.
![2012-09-17_00001.jpg|690x500](upload://fXZHnZYpUC2xQQ9QMWpWlvp5BeD.jpeg)
![2012-09-17_00002.jpg|690x500](upload://vxkIMJpprqsTbEETZ2f0Xv9SDh5.jpeg)</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 20 Sep 2012 05:56:45 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>In-game Issues (Mod)</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/floating-marines/10887.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>floating Marines</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Batosai]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I have come across my fair share of nitpick Glitches, most of which are just so minor that they weren’t worth mentioning in my opinion, or have been brought up by other members of the community to one end or another, this is just a glitch that I encountered that actually impeded the game sort of.</p>
<p>At the part of the game where you go outside to make your way to the manually loaded mounter rocket launcher…er…thingy…there is a helicopter that is constantly dropping marines into the area, when I played through this part I had a strange glitch where the repelling soldiers dropped out of the Helicopter and and just remained in a clump standing in the air, they don’t shoot and I was unable to kill one of them, I ended up having to reload my save to stop them from floating and yelling about how I was right in front of them. you can see described hilarity in the screenshots I attached. While this was mostly just hilarious, it does impede progress since you need to destroy the helicopter that drops them off to continue, and in order for the helicopter to show up again all the Marines previously dropped need to die. It was still pretty fucking hilarious.</p>
<p>The mod was still worth the Years of waiting, the whole thing is amazing work, mad kudo’s to the devs.<br>
<div class="lightbox-wrapper"><a class="lightbox" href="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/original/2X/6/6fe8c44d180be1675886f2c0b8d3b146ce9dace7.jpeg" data-download-href="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/6fe8c44d180be1675886f2c0b8d3b146ce9dace7" title="2012-09-17_00001.jpg"><img src="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/original/2X/6/6fe8c44d180be1675886f2c0b8d3b146ce9dace7.jpeg" alt="2012-09-17_00001.jpg" data-base62-sha1="fXZHnZYpUC2xQQ9QMWpWlvp5BeD" width="690" height="500" data-small-upload="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/optimized/2X/6/6fe8c44d180be1675886f2c0b8d3b146ce9dace7_2_10x10.png"><div class="meta"><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-far-image svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#far-image"></use></svg><span class="filename">2012-09-17_00001.jpg</span><span class="informations">1278×719 89.8 KB</span><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-discourse-expand svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#discourse-expand"></use></svg></div></a></div><br>
<div class="lightbox-wrapper"><a class="lightbox" href="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/original/2X/d/dd08075820973fa7e6b5ff0c0ab22960a446d47f.jpeg" data-download-href="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/dd08075820973fa7e6b5ff0c0ab22960a446d47f" title="2012-09-17_00002.jpg"><img src="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/original/2X/d/dd08075820973fa7e6b5ff0c0ab22960a446d47f.jpeg" alt="2012-09-17_00002.jpg" data-base62-sha1="vxkIMJpprqsTbEETZ2f0Xv9SDh5" width="690" height="500" data-small-upload="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/optimized/2X/d/dd08075820973fa7e6b5ff0c0ab22960a446d47f_2_10x10.png"><div class="meta"><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-far-image svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#far-image"></use></svg><span class="filename">2012-09-17_00002.jpg</span><span class="informations">1278×719 72.7 KB</span><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-discourse-expand svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#discourse-expand"></use></svg></div></a></div></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/floating-marines/10887/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/floating-marines/10887/1</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 20 Sep 2012 05:56:45 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-10887-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/floating-marines/10887.rss">floating Marines</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
