<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Upgrading my rig, help wanted</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/upgrading-my-rig-help-wanted/8428</link>
    <description>My Core 2 isn&#39;t cutting it, and I&#39;m getting a decent sized tax return, so I&#39;m going to put some money into upgrading my computer, and would appreciate some help.  I&#39;ve never built my own, I think I know what to look for when getting a processor and mobo (socket type, RAM type, number of RAM slots, PCI and PCIe slots) but don&#39;t [i]really[/i] know.

The things I want to keep from my current build are the PSU, case, DVD drive, capture card, and GPU.  I&#39;m considering getting another GPU and SLIing them together, but my current GPU is a GTX 470, which is notorious for running hot.  How hard would it be (if it&#39;s even possible/advisable) to get a better cooling system for it?

I&#39;m not sure what model my case is, but [url=https://dl.dropbox.com/u/27262125/case.jpg]here[/url] is a picture of it.  It looks similar to some of the CoolerMaster cases I&#39;ve seen.

Anyway, here&#39;s my current parts list:
Intel Core 2 6600 (OC&#39;d to 2.9 GHz)
4x2 GB DDR2 400 MHz
GeForce GTX 470
AVerMedia C027 PCIe (capture card)
MSI P6N Platinum (MS-7350 according to CPU-Z)
1 TB 5200 RPM HDD (don&#39;t remember make/model, I&#39;d like to replace this and Ghost the data over to the new one)
CoolMax Green Power 700w (I&#39;d be willing to replace this if the manufacturer sucks, but it hasn&#39;t given me any trouble)
IDE DVD burner w/ LightScribe (I&#39;d be willing to replace this with a basic DVD burner if the new mobo doesn&#39;t have IDE)

I think that covers everything I have now  :stuck_out_tongue: 

I want to get at least 8 GB of RAM, and wouldn&#39;t mind having a dedicated sound card, I&#39;ve had onboard sound in every computer I&#39;ve owned, and wouldn&#39;t mind a bit more quality.  I also wouldn&#39;t mind suggestions for a new heatsink for the processor.  The processor would preferably be an i5 2500k or i7 2600k, and I&#39;d be willing to wait about a month if a new Intel processor is supposed to come out.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 24 Mar 2012 02:12:28 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Technology and Gaming</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/upgrading-my-rig-help-wanted/8428.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Upgrading my rig, help wanted</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[wheybags]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>My i5 idles at 31  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=9" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"></p>
<p>EDIT: Peaks at 60</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/upgrading-my-rig-help-wanted/8428/39">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/upgrading-my-rig-help-wanted/8428/39</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 24 Mar 2012 02:12:28 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8428-39</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/upgrading-my-rig-help-wanted/8428.rss">Upgrading my rig, help wanted</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Upgrading my rig, help wanted</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[BahamutBBob]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I just got finished re-mounting the cooler, and it is about 5 degrees cooler now.  Core 0 is about 66, and cores 1, 2, and 3 are about 70.  I have a bit less than what’s in the second set of pictures <a href="https://www.tomshardware.com/reviews/cooling-air-pressure-heatsink,3058-9.html" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">here</a>, and it doesn’t look nearly that pretty  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=9" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"></p>
<p>The first thing I noticed was the cooler was firmly in place when I tightened the bracket this time.  Before, it would still rotate when the screws were almost all the way in.</p>
<p>I would still like to get a new case eventually, but now I feel like I’m not going to break my processor by overclocking it.</p>
<p>Thanks for the help guys.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/upgrading-my-rig-help-wanted/8428/38">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/upgrading-my-rig-help-wanted/8428/38</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 21 Mar 2012 20:23:25 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8428-38</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/upgrading-my-rig-help-wanted/8428.rss">Upgrading my rig, help wanted</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Upgrading my rig, help wanted</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Kairouseki]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>What I did, and what the instructions told me to do, was put just a bit onto the CPU and spread it into a thin layer that covers the top of it. Then put another very small dab of thermal past right in the middle and then put the cooler on top of it. Works really well for me, ~40 C idle and 65 C while playing something like GTAIV.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/upgrading-my-rig-help-wanted/8428/37">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/upgrading-my-rig-help-wanted/8428/37</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 21 Mar 2012 02:19:21 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8428-37</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/upgrading-my-rig-help-wanted/8428.rss">Upgrading my rig, help wanted</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Upgrading my rig, help wanted</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[BahamutBBob]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>It’s likely that there is too much, then.</p>
<p>The person who helped me with the thermal paste (who I assumed knew what they were doing, since they’ve built a bunch of computers in the past) put a ton on there.  I’ll have to clean it off and get another tube of Arctic Silver, since I gave what I had left over to a friend.  I’ll use what you shared, Orpheon, when I go to do it.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/upgrading-my-rig-help-wanted/8428/36">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/upgrading-my-rig-help-wanted/8428/36</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 21 Mar 2012 02:11:41 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8428-36</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/upgrading-my-rig-help-wanted/8428.rss">Upgrading my rig, help wanted</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Upgrading my rig, help wanted</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Orpheon]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>The point of thermal paste is to fill in the very tiny gaps between the metal of the heatsink and the metal of the CPU heat spreader. Therefore you only want a thin layer. There’s a guide on applying it over on Tom’s Hardware, but the basic idea is to just have enough to cover up the words printed on the CPU. Either spread it on evenly with something flat like a credit card, or just drop a little dab somewhere about the size of a BB or a lentil, and then then smash it down by installing the heatsink. If you do it right there won’t be any extra, that is, none should squeeze out. If you happen to get some anywhere but the CPU, just use a cloth or a paper towel with some isopropyl alcohol to wipe it off. And of course, do not “re-use” the thermal paste - if you take the heatsink off, take all the paste off too with cloth/paper towel and alcohol.</p>
<p>EDIT: <a href="https://www.tomshardware.com/reviews/cooling-air-pressure-heatsink,3058.html" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">This is the article I mentioned.</a> Has more detailed instructions and pictures, and also has a lot more information about cooling your PC in general. <a href="https://www.tomshardware.com/reviews/cooling-airflow-heatsink,3053.html" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">See Part 1 also.</a></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/upgrading-my-rig-help-wanted/8428/35">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/upgrading-my-rig-help-wanted/8428/35</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 20 Mar 2012 22:07:29 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8428-35</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/upgrading-my-rig-help-wanted/8428.rss">Upgrading my rig, help wanted</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Upgrading my rig, help wanted</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[BahamutBBob]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I applied Arctic Silver when I put the cooler on the processor.  I know having too much can be a problem, how would I know how much is good, and how would I remove the extra?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/upgrading-my-rig-help-wanted/8428/34">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/upgrading-my-rig-help-wanted/8428/34</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 20 Mar 2012 20:11:04 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8428-34</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/upgrading-my-rig-help-wanted/8428.rss">Upgrading my rig, help wanted</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Upgrading my rig, help wanted</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Siggs]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Mine is pretty heavily overclocked, with air cooling it idles at about 35-40 and under load never seen it go over 62.</p>
<p>Check yours out, probably to do with the paste? was it pre applied stuff?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/upgrading-my-rig-help-wanted/8428/33">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/upgrading-my-rig-help-wanted/8428/33</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 20 Mar 2012 16:50:51 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8428-33</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/upgrading-my-rig-help-wanted/8428.rss">Upgrading my rig, help wanted</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Upgrading my rig, help wanted</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Kairouseki]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>My processor runs around 40 C while idle, though I don’t think it gets as high as yours does under stress. Yours is overclocked much more than mine is though. But it seems it’s a recent thing.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/upgrading-my-rig-help-wanted/8428/32">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/upgrading-my-rig-help-wanted/8428/32</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 20 Mar 2012 15:17:26 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8428-32</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/upgrading-my-rig-help-wanted/8428.rss">Upgrading my rig, help wanted</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Upgrading my rig, help wanted</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[BahamutBBob]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Bumping this real quick.</p>
<p>My processor temps seem a bit high (mid 40s while idling, would my video card running hot effect my processor’s ability to cool?  Running Prime95, the cores all get up to about 80, which I know is higher than I want to go, and almost immediately drop back down to 50 when I stop the tests, so I don’t think it’s a problem with the heatsink) and I think it may be my case.  It only has two fans built in, with no room for more.  Can anyone recommend me a nice case with good airflow?  I don’t have much of a budget right now, but recommend anything with a reasonable price, I can save up for it if needed.</p>
<p>Thanks.</p>
<p>Edit: backed my clock speed down a bit and ran Prime95 again, each core gets to about 75, which is still too high IMO.  Clock speed set to 4.0 GHz now instead of the 4.5 I had it at.  I want to try and get my temps under control before running a long stress test.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/upgrading-my-rig-help-wanted/8428/31">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/upgrading-my-rig-help-wanted/8428/31</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 20 Mar 2012 06:51:29 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8428-31</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/upgrading-my-rig-help-wanted/8428.rss">Upgrading my rig, help wanted</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Upgrading my rig, help wanted</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[BahamutBBob]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I would have moved the steamapps folder, but don’t have anything else in the house big enough to hold it  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=9" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:">   I guess I could have picked the larger games, moved them, and downloaded the smaller games again.  Oh well, no big deal.</p>
<p>On a side note, I’ve discovered Steam’s concurrent download limit.  It can only download 9 games at once, with any others sitting there with their GCF/NCF ready, but no download going.</p>
<p>Edit: <a href="https://dl.dropbox.com/u/27262125/WEI.jpg" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">putting my new Windows Experience Index here.</a>  I’ve done it a few times over the last 24 hours, and the HDD keeps getting a higher and higher score, so I’ll have to do it with no downloads going at some point, see if that makes a difference.  Also, I’ll do it again after OCing my CPU.</p>
<p>And Lukagerm, I hadn’t planned on messing with the RAM settings at all, thanks for pointing that out though, so I don’t mess it up.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/upgrading-my-rig-help-wanted/8428/30">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/upgrading-my-rig-help-wanted/8428/30</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 18 Feb 2012 16:21:59 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8428-30</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/upgrading-my-rig-help-wanted/8428.rss">Upgrading my rig, help wanted</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Upgrading my rig, help wanted</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Orpheon]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="BahamutBBob">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/b/e9bcb4/40.png" class="avatar"> BahamutBBob:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I played the ME3 demo before doing any hardware changes.  It looked great and ran well, I was surprised  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=9" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"></p>
<p>Then again, UE3 is starting to show it’s age, so that could be it.</p>
<p>I have one last question about this build.  I have my old HDD slaved up as the D drive, I’ll reformat it if that’s best, but I have a somewhat slow connection (peak is 300-400 KB/s) and don’t want to have to download all the Steam games I had installed again.  I know I can get Steam working properly by deleting everything from the folder but steam.exe and the steamapps folder, but is that recommended?  Will Steam automatically do everything it needs to for each game?  And can I remove my Windows install from that HDD?  Should I just delete it, or is there more to it than that?</p>
<p>Again, I’m willing to reformat, I’ve got almost everything important backed up.</p>
<p>Edit: I just reformatted.  The Windows folder was just over 20 gigs, and I didn’t want to waste that space.  I couldn’t find a way to remove it that worked.  Soon I can actually test some games on this thing  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=9" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"></p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>You could have just moved the steamapps folder, that’s mostly what you really need. A few games might need to download a little bit, but most of the download would be spared. Also you would need to make sure to move any saves from where they’re located (for example, Bioware stores their save game data in My Documents).</p>
<p>Oh, and yeah, I couldn’t stop with my build as it was. It was probably against my better judgment, but I nabbed an ASUS monitor that’s on sale right now on newegg - $150 plus a $20 rebate for a 23" 1080p 2ms monitor that won 3 customer choice awards. What can I say, it felt like a steal, even if it’s not a whole lot better than my 22" 1680x1050. But then, TOR and the ME3 demo didn’t run as well as I wanted, and since I was now upgrading my screen resolution, I decided I’d better get a new GPU, so I got a 560 ti too. I would’ve gone with something a little more powerful, but I was trying to hold back a little on money, and also keep the noise and temps down. Hopefully this’ll be the last major money I spend on this rig for a while, I’m supposed to be saving money so I can move out of the proverbial parent’s basement  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=9" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/upgrading-my-rig-help-wanted/8428/29">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/upgrading-my-rig-help-wanted/8428/29</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 18 Feb 2012 06:45:19 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8428-29</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/upgrading-my-rig-help-wanted/8428.rss">Upgrading my rig, help wanted</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Upgrading my rig, help wanted</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Lukagerm]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Bear in mind that you would ideally want to use 1.5v RAM with a Sandybridge cpu. 1.65v is at the top end of sandybridge’s limits. It should be ok but definitely don’t increase the voltage to your ram.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/upgrading-my-rig-help-wanted/8428/28">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/upgrading-my-rig-help-wanted/8428/28</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 18 Feb 2012 01:18:08 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8428-28</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/upgrading-my-rig-help-wanted/8428.rss">Upgrading my rig, help wanted</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Upgrading my rig, help wanted</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[BahamutBBob]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I played the ME3 demo before doing any hardware changes.  It looked great and ran well, I was surprised  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=9" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"></p>
<p>Then again, UE3 is starting to show it’s age, so that could be it.</p>
<p>I have one last question about this build.  I have my old HDD slaved up as the D drive, I’ll reformat it if that’s best, but I have a somewhat slow connection (peak is 300-400 KB/s) and don’t want to have to download all the Steam games I had installed again.  I know I can get Steam working properly by deleting everything from the folder but steam.exe and the steamapps folder, but is that recommended?  Will Steam automatically do everything it needs to for each game?  And can I remove my Windows install from that HDD?  Should I just delete it, or is there more to it than that?</p>
<p>Again, I’m willing to reformat, I’ve got almost everything important backed up.</p>
<p>Edit: I just reformatted.  The Windows folder was just over 20 gigs, and I didn’t want to waste that space.  I couldn’t find a way to remove it that worked.  Soon I can actually test some games on this thing  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=9" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/upgrading-my-rig-help-wanted/8428/27">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/upgrading-my-rig-help-wanted/8428/27</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Feb 2012 14:21:57 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8428-27</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/upgrading-my-rig-help-wanted/8428.rss">Upgrading my rig, help wanted</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Upgrading my rig, help wanted</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Orpheon]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Yeah, Windows saves data about the computer you installed it on, so it’ll cause problems if you try to put the hard drive in another computer and boot from it. If you have an OEM license, it’s supposed to be bound to the motherboard forever, but some people have had success getting the license freed by calling MS and telling them their old board died. Regular or upgrade licenses can be installed on any computer, but it may freak out if you activate it too many times. And of course, “special” licenses don’t follow any of those rules, lol.</p>
<p>Also, I finished my own build about a week ago, so far everything’s gone nice and smooth. Decided to keep onboard audio. Sounds pretty good to me, especially with new headphones. The only thing I’m still thinking about getting is an Ivy Bridge CPU when they come out (or a 2500k, if the price difference after it drops is significant), and maybe a new GPU. My Radeon 4890 is still trucking along for most games, but the Mass Effect 3 demo made it wheeze a little I think. Plus it is a bit loud and hot - a newer, better cooled card would be nice.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/upgrading-my-rig-help-wanted/8428/26">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/upgrading-my-rig-help-wanted/8428/26</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Feb 2012 08:35:07 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8428-26</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/upgrading-my-rig-help-wanted/8428.rss">Upgrading my rig, help wanted</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Upgrading my rig, help wanted</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[BahamutBBob]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Got my parts yesterday, and took this afternoon to assemble it.  It boots up fine, but unsurprisingly Windows freaks out when trying to boot from my old HDD.  Going to see if I can get this “special” copy installed tonight, if not I’ll bring my computer in to work tomorrow and install a copy of Enterprise with their license.</p>
<p>I’ll eventually buy my own license, just not right now.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/upgrading-my-rig-help-wanted/8428/25">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/upgrading-my-rig-help-wanted/8428/25</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Feb 2012 00:10:43 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8428-25</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/upgrading-my-rig-help-wanted/8428.rss">Upgrading my rig, help wanted</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Upgrading my rig, help wanted</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[CTID]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Yes, and by compatibility issues, I mean if the socket types aren’t the same then your processor isn’t going to plug into your motherboard and will be completely useless to you.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/upgrading-my-rig-help-wanted/8428/24">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/upgrading-my-rig-help-wanted/8428/24</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 13 Feb 2012 02:46:02 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8428-24</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/upgrading-my-rig-help-wanted/8428.rss">Upgrading my rig, help wanted</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Upgrading my rig, help wanted</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[BahamutBBob]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="CTID">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/user_avatar/leakfree.org/ctid/40/4984_2.png" class="avatar"> CTID:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>lolwut</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>:hmph: See below.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="CTID">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/user_avatar/leakfree.org/ctid/40/4984_2.png" class="avatar"> CTID:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>The only thing I can really think of having compatibility issues is your CPU and motherboard, but what do I know.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Or did you forget that you posted that?  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=9" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"></p>
<p>Reading reviews on the mobo, they bring up a good point.  The CPU socket is awfully close to the RAM slots.  I guess I could always return and replace the CPU cooler if it’s too big  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=9" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/upgrading-my-rig-help-wanted/8428/23">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/upgrading-my-rig-help-wanted/8428/23</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 12 Feb 2012 03:57:19 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8428-23</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/upgrading-my-rig-help-wanted/8428.rss">Upgrading my rig, help wanted</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Upgrading my rig, help wanted</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Siggs]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I couldn’t have recommended better paste myself  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=9" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/upgrading-my-rig-help-wanted/8428/22">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/upgrading-my-rig-help-wanted/8428/22</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 12 Feb 2012 02:17:04 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8428-22</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/upgrading-my-rig-help-wanted/8428.rss">Upgrading my rig, help wanted</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Upgrading my rig, help wanted</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[CTID]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="BahamutBBob">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/b/e9bcb4/40.png" class="avatar"> BahamutBBob:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I would hope with the motherboard and processor both being Intel, that they won’t have any compatibility problems.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>lolwut</p>
<p>Does the socket type on the motherboard match the processor’s? If not you’re fucked and have to return it/cancel and reorder.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/upgrading-my-rig-help-wanted/8428/21">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/upgrading-my-rig-help-wanted/8428/21</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 12 Feb 2012 01:12:13 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8428-21</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/upgrading-my-rig-help-wanted/8428.rss">Upgrading my rig, help wanted</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Upgrading my rig, help wanted</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[BahamutBBob]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Alright, I just put in the order, I went with the list I put above, with an i5, a Cooler Master Hyper 212 and some Arctic Silver thermal paste. (recommended by a guy at work)  I would hope with the motherboard and processor both being Intel, that they won’t have any compatibility problems.</p>
<p>Thanks for all the help everyone.  I’ll revive this thread if I need more help with the video card down the line somewhere.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/upgrading-my-rig-help-wanted/8428/20">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/upgrading-my-rig-help-wanted/8428/20</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 12 Feb 2012 00:01:56 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8428-20</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/upgrading-my-rig-help-wanted/8428.rss">Upgrading my rig, help wanted</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Upgrading my rig, help wanted</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[CTID]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>The only thing I can really think of having compatibility issues is your CPU and motherboard, but what do I know.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/upgrading-my-rig-help-wanted/8428/19">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/upgrading-my-rig-help-wanted/8428/19</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 11 Feb 2012 19:12:24 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8428-19</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/upgrading-my-rig-help-wanted/8428.rss">Upgrading my rig, help wanted</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Upgrading my rig, help wanted</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[BahamutBBob]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Got my federal return today, I’ll order parts today or tomorrow, I’ll post a final list here before ordering.  Is there a website I can go to to check compatibility issues for everything?  I want to make sure it’ll all work before I spend money on it.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/upgrading-my-rig-help-wanted/8428/18">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/upgrading-my-rig-help-wanted/8428/18</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 11 Feb 2012 18:25:51 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8428-18</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/upgrading-my-rig-help-wanted/8428.rss">Upgrading my rig, help wanted</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Upgrading my rig, help wanted</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[BahamutBBob]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Alright, thanks for the input guys.  I saw someone here, I think it was Collision, that got an i7 and said they disabled hyperthreading.</p>
<p>And I just measured the space between the mobo and the side of the case, it’s (almost) exactly 7 inches, so I can fit a Cooler Master Hyper 212 if I decide to go with one of those.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/upgrading-my-rig-help-wanted/8428/17">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/upgrading-my-rig-help-wanted/8428/17</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 02 Feb 2012 00:02:46 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8428-17</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/upgrading-my-rig-help-wanted/8428.rss">Upgrading my rig, help wanted</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Upgrading my rig, help wanted</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Orpheon]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="geekofalltrades">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/g/c2a13f/40.png" class="avatar"> geekofalltrades:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I have actually never heard of anybody disabling hyperthreading on their i7.  Then again, I don’t know many people with i7’s; the i5 is way more more than adequate for almost everybody.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>This. I haven’t heard of it either, but what it comes down to is that getting anything better than the i5 2500k is likely going to be a waste. Even the LGA2011 chips are hardly any better at gaming than a 2500k. Might as well save the dough and spend it on something else.</p>
<p><a href="https://www.tomshardware.com/reviews/gaming-cpu-review-overclock,3106-4.html" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">See here</a></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/upgrading-my-rig-help-wanted/8428/16">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/upgrading-my-rig-help-wanted/8428/16</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 01 Feb 2012 22:28:10 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8428-16</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/upgrading-my-rig-help-wanted/8428.rss">Upgrading my rig, help wanted</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Upgrading my rig, help wanted</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[geekofalltrades]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="BahamutBBob">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/b/e9bcb4/40.png" class="avatar"> BahamutBBob:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>And about my earlier question comparing i5 to i7, what’s the main difference aside from hyperthreading and price?  Why do people disable hyperthreading?  From my understanding, the way hyperthreading works essentially doubles the number of cores with very little loss, with the way it’s done these days.  Is it just because there isn’t any point right now, or are there performance concerns?  This is the biggest question I have about this build. (parts-wise)</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I have actually never heard of anybody disabling hyperthreading on their i7.  Then again, I don’t know many people with i7’s; the i5 is way more more than adequate for almost everybody.  I think the only other differences are that the i7 has a slightly larger cache and it comes with a higher clock speed out of the box.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/upgrading-my-rig-help-wanted/8428/15">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/upgrading-my-rig-help-wanted/8428/15</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 01 Feb 2012 21:56:48 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8428-15</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/upgrading-my-rig-help-wanted/8428.rss">Upgrading my rig, help wanted</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
