<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Internet problems</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/internet-problems/5870</link>
    <description>I have been experiencing several problems with my internet connections for a while.

Everything worked fine till we switched to fucking Tele2. Big Mistake.

Anyhow, first we had the a few problems such as the internet randomly losing connection. Plugging it out and back in would solve the problem. Seems like a small problem, but it happened pretty often and since it&#39;s one of those all in 1 thing it means that not only internet failed, but also the phone and the tv.

After a while of conversing with tele2 they sent us a new modem. 

Now the connection problem is gone, but all the old problems seem to have been replaced by new ones which are (at least for me) even more annoying.

The following things happen: I can no longer connect to my media server on my PS3. Well, I can, but it only shows half the video list till the letter H for some reason. Trying to play any video results in a black screen and then eventually a &#39;network error&#39;. Another problem is that my Itunes remote on my Iphone no longer works. It recognizes that code you have to enter, but can&#39;t find my library. The WIFI itself seems to work fine. 

And there&#39;s yet another problem. Though I no longer have any real connection trouble when surfing, my msn doesn&#39;t like this new router. I randomly lose connection, and often my messages don&#39;t arrive at all. 

Suffice to say that this is starting to get on my nerves. Those idiots at the Tele2 helpdesk haven&#39;t been able to say much useful either.

The setup in our home is as follows:
We have the modem downstairs, connected directly to the telephone line. Connected to that are the TV thing, our downstairs computer and a homeplug which is connected with 2 more homeplugs upstairs to my PS3 and PC. (Homeplugs are a way of connecting to the internet using the power net. You simply plug one in downstairs and connect it to the modem through a regular ethernet cable, and upstairs you connect it to your pc.)

Anyone have any idea how to solve this? Help is much appreciated.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2010 15:42:10 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Help and Support</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/internet-problems/5870.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Internet problems</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Daedalus]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I have been experiencing several problems with my internet connections for a while.</p>
<p>Everything worked fine till we switched to fucking Tele2. Big Mistake.</p>
<p>Anyhow, first we had the a few problems such as the internet randomly losing connection. Plugging it out and back in would solve the problem. Seems like a small problem, but it happened pretty often and since it’s one of those all in 1 thing it means that not only internet failed, but also the phone and the tv.</p>
<p>After a while of conversing with tele2 they sent us a new modem.</p>
<p>Now the connection problem is gone, but all the old problems seem to have been replaced by new ones which are (at least for me) even more annoying.</p>
<p>The following things happen: I can no longer connect to my media server on my PS3. Well, I can, but it only shows half the video list till the letter H for some reason. Trying to play any video results in a black screen and then eventually a ‘network error’. Another problem is that my Itunes remote on my Iphone no longer works. It recognizes that code you have to enter, but can’t find my library. The WIFI itself seems to work fine.</p>
<p>And there’s yet another problem. Though I no longer have any real connection trouble when surfing, my msn doesn’t like this new router. I randomly lose connection, and often my messages don’t arrive at all.</p>
<p>Suffice to say that this is starting to get on my nerves. Those idiots at the Tele2 helpdesk haven’t been able to say much useful either.</p>
<p>The setup in our home is as follows:<br>
We have the modem downstairs, connected directly to the telephone line. Connected to that are the TV thing, our downstairs computer and a homeplug which is connected with 2 more homeplugs upstairs to my PS3 and PC. (Homeplugs are a way of connecting to the internet using the power net. You simply plug one in downstairs and connect it to the modem through a regular ethernet cable, and upstairs you connect it to your pc.)</p>
<p>Anyone have any idea how to solve this? Help is much appreciated.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/internet-problems/5870/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/internet-problems/5870/1</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2010 15:42:10 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-5870-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/internet-problems/5870.rss">Internet problems</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
