<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>An intelgent dicussion regarding the &quot;7 hour war&quot;</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/an-intelgent-dicussion-regarding-the-7-hour-war/8370</link>
    <description>So I am new here on these forums, However I am not new to Half Life. It was one of the first FPS games I can remember playing as a kid and I loved it. But that&#39;s not too important now except know that YES I have played Half Life 1 and 2.

Now in Half Life 2 it is a pretty well known historical event that the Combine destroyed the entire Earth military in 7 hours. Hence &quot;7 hour war&quot;. Which is pretty awesome. However If I&#39;m not mistaken weren&#39;t the Xen aliens already causing havoc on Earth as well as zombie outbreak? 

Also the Portal Storms themselves could have easy been equivalent to a nuke or at least an EMP. Which means Earths forces were fighting aliens already and zombies THEN they were probably shocked and destroyed by the Portal Storms.

And then BAM an entire Combine army comes strolling in on an already damaged, weakened and probably dismantled army. For example if Portal Storms had any nuclear or EMP similar effects most of Earths defensive weapons, air support, radars, satellites, tanks, AA&#39;s and so on would be &quot;off&quot; and useless. 

So my question is this:  Lets say there were no Xen aliens, no zombies and lets say Portals were just portals and didn&#39;t cause any damage at all and lets say us Humans were fully aware of what was coming WOULD the Combine still be able to take us over in 7 hours. Would we destroy them without a problem, Or would the combine still win but take longer.

Thank you.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 24 Apr 2012 23:17:07 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Half-Life Series</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/an-intelgent-dicussion-regarding-the-7-hour-war/8370.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>An intelgent dicussion regarding the &quot;7 hour war&quot;</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[DEATH_eVADER]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>The way I see it, Earth was defeated because the military was so disorganised and couldn’t form into a coherrent fighting force.</p>
<p>The majority of Earths Military forces were at peacetime readiness at the time the Portal Storms commenced I would imagine. As soon as the Portal Storms hit a lot of NCOs and COs were probably decimated by alien entities such as the headcrabs. This caused the already established military hierarchy to be screwed beyond comprehension, war assets never even used, because their operators either were never given orders, got killed or even never at the right place at the right time.</p>
<p>Also don’t forget half the world was at nighttime, soldiers on leave were probably boozing/sleeping and totally caught of guard. Probably explains why there seems to be more American accents ingame because the other half of the world are dead from sleeping</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/an-intelgent-dicussion-regarding-the-7-hour-war/8370/133">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/an-intelgent-dicussion-regarding-the-7-hour-war/8370/133</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 24 Apr 2012 23:17:07 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8370-133</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/an-intelgent-dicussion-regarding-the-7-hour-war/8370.rss">An intelgent dicussion regarding the &quot;7 hour war&quot;</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>An intelgent dicussion regarding the &quot;7 hour war&quot;</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[David]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I just think the first thing the combine did was send either a small group, or a single advisor through, to act as a scout to learn about earth; that advisor was able to accumluate enough knowledge to know where the capitals of a few strong countries are; so they just prepared the invasion force, and as soon as they went through, they went to different capitals and just smashed them (especially if they could teleport in where ever they wanted)</p>
<p>At that point, advisors would just start probing the memories of the officials in the cities, learning about major military installments and crushing them to, and repeating this over and over until the only fighting force left would be people who owned guns, and they would not be hard to get rid of</p>
<p>Breen probably negotiated for the people of Earth kept alive as lab rats, possible synths, etc; and the combine agreed since Earth works as a nice stepping stone into a new part of the universe</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/an-intelgent-dicussion-regarding-the-7-hour-war/8370/132">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/an-intelgent-dicussion-regarding-the-7-hour-war/8370/132</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 Apr 2012 00:12:21 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8370-132</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/an-intelgent-dicussion-regarding-the-7-hour-war/8370.rss">An intelgent dicussion regarding the &quot;7 hour war&quot;</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>An intelgent dicussion regarding the &quot;7 hour war&quot;</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[dblkion]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I’m amazed by the amout of bullcrap people come up with when trying to explain stuff the game’s devs emselves didnt even think about.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/an-intelgent-dicussion-regarding-the-7-hour-war/8370/131">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/an-intelgent-dicussion-regarding-the-7-hour-war/8370/131</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 Mar 2012 23:22:59 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8370-131</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/an-intelgent-dicussion-regarding-the-7-hour-war/8370.rss">An intelgent dicussion regarding the &quot;7 hour war&quot;</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>An intelgent dicussion regarding the &quot;7 hour war&quot;</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[MRPolo]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>What I believe has happened is:<br>
When Gordon Freeman has managed to kill the controller, portal storms broke out all across the globe, except for certain parts of Russia which would make sense as it’s nearly on the other side of globe to USA. It is obvious from one of the newspapers showing a skyscraper being obliterated that the combines used some sort of super weapon that could easily destroy whole cities. However, this weapon would be inefficient if it was single use and so it must have been a cannon of some sort. Many people fled to Russia and of course after the war many more were imported there. Though the 7 hour scenario is the one presumed the war had to last at least twice the amount because of the units that hid around forests and countryside leaving the combine with a “cleaning up” job. It was obvious that an invasion force was incapable of keeping Earth by itself and so the combine decided to create an army of humans and half humans that would serve as normal police and soldiers. After, presumably, around 6-7 years, as we all know, Gordon Freeman returns, greeted, surprisingly as a hero, not a villain and that where Half Life 2 kicks off.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/an-intelgent-dicussion-regarding-the-7-hour-war/8370/130">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/an-intelgent-dicussion-regarding-the-7-hour-war/8370/130</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 Mar 2012 20:10:43 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8370-130</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/an-intelgent-dicussion-regarding-the-7-hour-war/8370.rss">An intelgent dicussion regarding the &quot;7 hour war&quot;</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>An intelgent dicussion regarding the &quot;7 hour war&quot;</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[JohnWorfin]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Dias">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/d/4491bb/40.png" class="avatar"> Dias:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Also how the packet was sent out at the end of Episode 1…</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>SCIENCE!!!111!!!1!!!</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/an-intelgent-dicussion-regarding-the-7-hour-war/8370/129">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/an-intelgent-dicussion-regarding-the-7-hour-war/8370/129</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 Mar 2012 04:07:01 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8370-129</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/an-intelgent-dicussion-regarding-the-7-hour-war/8370.rss">An intelgent dicussion regarding the &quot;7 hour war&quot;</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>An intelgent dicussion regarding the &quot;7 hour war&quot;</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Dias]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Also how the packet was sent out at the end of Episode 1…</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/an-intelgent-dicussion-regarding-the-7-hour-war/8370/128">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/an-intelgent-dicussion-regarding-the-7-hour-war/8370/128</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 15 Mar 2012 21:14:12 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8370-128</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/an-intelgent-dicussion-regarding-the-7-hour-war/8370.rss">An intelgent dicussion regarding the &quot;7 hour war&quot;</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>An intelgent dicussion regarding the &quot;7 hour war&quot;</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[BahamutBBob]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Well, the portal did open before Gordon blew the mechanism.  I would think they would have realized something went wrong when it suddenly and violently closed.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/an-intelgent-dicussion-regarding-the-7-hour-war/8370/127">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/an-intelgent-dicussion-regarding-the-7-hour-war/8370/127</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 14 Mar 2012 22:00:17 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8370-127</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/an-intelgent-dicussion-regarding-the-7-hour-war/8370.rss">An intelgent dicussion regarding the &quot;7 hour war&quot;</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>An intelgent dicussion regarding the &quot;7 hour war&quot;</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[JohnWorfin]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>If the speculation is true, breen didn’t die. He was given a host body.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/an-intelgent-dicussion-regarding-the-7-hour-war/8370/126">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/an-intelgent-dicussion-regarding-the-7-hour-war/8370/126</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 14 Mar 2012 05:43:10 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8370-126</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/an-intelgent-dicussion-regarding-the-7-hour-war/8370.rss">An intelgent dicussion regarding the &quot;7 hour war&quot;</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>An intelgent dicussion regarding the &quot;7 hour war&quot;</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Katana]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I was thinking about why that message wouldn’t be sent out during the “one week” inbetween the Entanglement and Anticitizen One chapters.<br>
Maybe Breen didn’t even think to send out the message early on. Actually, it would all tie in well with him trying to win Eli’s cooperation at the end of Half-Life 2…he decided NOT to report to his superiors, so he could show how awesome humanity is (that is, the trans-human soldiers) by destroying the entire resistance on his own. Once Breen died, the remaining Combine and any advisors still in the citadel decided “Fuck it, Breen was an idiot, we’re calling for help.” and started preparing that communication.</p>
<p>I think it’s entirely possible that, if we assume just COMMUNICATING between such distance worlds is a hassle, maybe the real Combine don’t even know that humanity destroyed the Citadel and everything. They’ll get back from conquering several other worlds and be all “BREEEEEEEN!!! I leave you to babysit ONE race and look what happens!!!”</p>
<p>Actually kind of helps make the advisors’ names make more sense. If upper management was going to assign some new race (humans, Dr. Breen) to a position of authority, they’d want some of their own kind watching over him and making sure he’s not screwing everything up or betraying them at the last minute.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/an-intelgent-dicussion-regarding-the-7-hour-war/8370/125">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/an-intelgent-dicussion-regarding-the-7-hour-war/8370/125</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 14 Mar 2012 03:18:58 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8370-125</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/an-intelgent-dicussion-regarding-the-7-hour-war/8370.rss">An intelgent dicussion regarding the &quot;7 hour war&quot;</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>An intelgent dicussion regarding the &quot;7 hour war&quot;</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[amazingcomedy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Tosser Sloth">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Tosser Sloth:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Trumpets blared nightmarishly<br>
because fallopian tubes<br>
farmed earthworms hydroponically,<br>
and brobdingnagian squelchers<br>
upholstered their clogs.</p>
<p>Colossal togs were opened<br>
wide!<br>
“Gadzooks!”<br>
proclaimed Chief Freezing-Their-Bazookas-Off,<br>
while raggedly clad<br>
atop sweet gum tree.</p>
<p>Headcrabs, cavorting wildly,<br>
plow the turnpike green<br>
with limes, zucchini, spinach,<br>
slime and Xenians.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Lol, nice.</p>
<p>Personally, and someone else said this earlier, I think the Combine just got overconfident and decided to let Breen handle things on his own. Once they saw how shit was starting to go down on Earth, they wanted to bring in their reinforcements to take care of the resistance, and they were going to, until the gateway to their homeworld was shut down in EP2. Now, the remaining Combine forces are stranded, and all they have now is what they left Breen with.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/an-intelgent-dicussion-regarding-the-7-hour-war/8370/124">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/an-intelgent-dicussion-regarding-the-7-hour-war/8370/124</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 14 Mar 2012 03:05:15 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8370-124</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/an-intelgent-dicussion-regarding-the-7-hour-war/8370.rss">An intelgent dicussion regarding the &quot;7 hour war&quot;</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>An intelgent dicussion regarding the &quot;7 hour war&quot;</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Tosser_Sloth]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I wrote a poem about the seven hour war.</p>
<p>Trumpets blared nightmarishly<br>
because fallopian tubes<br>
farmed earthworms hydroponically,<br>
and brobdingnagian squelchers<br>
upholstered their clogs.</p>
<p>Colossal togs were opened<br>
wide!<br>
“Gadzooks!”<br>
proclaimed Chief Freezing-Their-Bazookas-Off,<br>
while raggedly clad<br>
atop sweet gum tree.</p>
<p>Headcrabs, cavorting wildly,<br>
plow the turnpike green<br>
with limes, zucchini, spinach,<br>
slime and Xenians.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/an-intelgent-dicussion-regarding-the-7-hour-war/8370/123">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/an-intelgent-dicussion-regarding-the-7-hour-war/8370/123</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 13 Mar 2012 20:39:04 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8370-123</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/an-intelgent-dicussion-regarding-the-7-hour-war/8370.rss">An intelgent dicussion regarding the &quot;7 hour war&quot;</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>An intelgent dicussion regarding the &quot;7 hour war&quot;</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[BahamutBBob]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Nihilanth wasn’t part of the Combine during Half-Life.  He went to Xen <span class="bbcode-i">because</span> the Combine couldn’t go there.  It seems like he was a slave of the Combine at one point, but was in hiding during HL1, and took the opportunity that the resonance cascade gave him to try and get one step further from the Combine.</p>
<p>And the Advisors are definitely part of the Combine.  Are they the original race, or mostly the original race?  Who knows.  Are they in a position of power within the group?  Definitely.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/an-intelgent-dicussion-regarding-the-7-hour-war/8370/122">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/an-intelgent-dicussion-regarding-the-7-hour-war/8370/122</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 08 Mar 2012 22:31:08 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8370-122</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/an-intelgent-dicussion-regarding-the-7-hour-war/8370.rss">An intelgent dicussion regarding the &quot;7 hour war&quot;</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>An intelgent dicussion regarding the &quot;7 hour war&quot;</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[sloshedtrain]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>If you guys remeber Hl1, the aliens (Vorts, headcrabs, bullsquid, etc…) teleported at random locations, who’s to say the combine didn’t do the same? Also remember the vortigaunts were also slaves to the Nihilanth who was in turn slave to the combine, perhaps the already weakend military, didn’t stand a chance when the actual combine appeared.<br>
G-man was behind combine coming to Earth, EP 2 Eli tells Gordon, that Gman was the one who gave him the Xen crystal. But, then Gman turns against the combine, in favor of another “employer” thus “Point Insertion”. Who his current employer is, won’t probably be revealed until HL3?<br>
Dr.Breen knew about Gordon’s “Employment” to Gman, at the HL2 Dr.Breen tells Gordon “Did you know your contract was open to the highest bidder?” But other than that he doesn’t tell you much mainly because, Gordon pretty much kills him.<br>
The Advisors are probably the Combine, or at least a part of it, Dr.Breen is seen negotiating with them just before the elevator at the end of the game.<br>
it could be that the Combine is more like a unification of alien races kinda like the Covenant from Halo (without the religious part of course)? Though I don’t have much proof of this though.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/an-intelgent-dicussion-regarding-the-7-hour-war/8370/121">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/an-intelgent-dicussion-regarding-the-7-hour-war/8370/121</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 08 Mar 2012 18:51:45 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8370-121</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/an-intelgent-dicussion-regarding-the-7-hour-war/8370.rss">An intelgent dicussion regarding the &quot;7 hour war&quot;</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>An intelgent dicussion regarding the &quot;7 hour war&quot;</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[lunertexcosmo]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Mephmage">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/m/85f322/40.png" class="avatar"> Mephmage:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>There’s absolutely no chance whatsoever that humanity could’ve lasted any significant amount of time.<br>
From a purely scientific perspective, we’re nothing but ants in comparison to what kind of uniform race the combine appears to be.</p>
<p>To put it in perspective, we’re a type 0 civilization that has yet to stop fighting amongst ourselves. The combine is a type 3 civilization, an immortal race with technology reaching far beyond anything we have, stretching across what I imagine would be several galaxies.<br>
Our most powerful weapon, the nuke, has an energy output of what… 1%? That’s our most powerful weapon.</p>
<p>The combine has most likely mastered weaponized anti-matter, which gives them weapons with an energy output of 100%, that is… They can wipe out our entire planet before anyone can even say “Fuck’s that beeping noise?”.</p>
<p>Which of course poses a few other questions… Why would the combine even be interested in our planet? For our water? Water is commonplace in space, it exists in abundance. Oxygen? Gold? …Proteins? Hell, I don’t know.<br>
And why would a race as superior as the combine even talk to humans? Would you ever walk up to anthill and spend 7 hours trampling them, then come to the conclusion that Ant no. 4128921 should represent you from atop a giant pillar rammed into the anthill?</p>
<p>The story of half life 2 makes little sense. But I actually like the idea of a “7 hour war” just to show how arrogant we are with our primitive chemical weapons.<br>
Anyone who can travel anywhere in space, can conquer us, because we’re nothing but apes waving torches at the stars.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I would say Breen’s teleporation and the Gman.  It’s obvious he has plans for Gordon.  Who’s to say he didn’t help the combine come here and set up shop?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/an-intelgent-dicussion-regarding-the-7-hour-war/8370/120">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/an-intelgent-dicussion-regarding-the-7-hour-war/8370/120</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 08 Mar 2012 05:01:25 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8370-120</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/an-intelgent-dicussion-regarding-the-7-hour-war/8370.rss">An intelgent dicussion regarding the &quot;7 hour war&quot;</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>An intelgent dicussion regarding the &quot;7 hour war&quot;</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[OrderOfDagon]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>For all we know that could have been how long it took for the Combine to get to the major cities and force a surrender.</p>
<p>It was 7 hours of fighting – I doubt it means that the Combine killed all opposition in 7 hours.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/an-intelgent-dicussion-regarding-the-7-hour-war/8370/119">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/an-intelgent-dicussion-regarding-the-7-hour-war/8370/119</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 07 Mar 2012 22:24:58 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8370-119</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/an-intelgent-dicussion-regarding-the-7-hour-war/8370.rss">An intelgent dicussion regarding the &quot;7 hour war&quot;</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>An intelgent dicussion regarding the &quot;7 hour war&quot;</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[JohnWorfin]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Marooner">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/m/76d3ee/40.png" class="avatar"> Marooner:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Even if they managed to occupy all larger cities in Europe - I can’t agree to a war just lasting 7 hours in total, I mean even the movements of the troops takes time, and I’m not going to speak of the guerrilla fights occurring normally in city streets.<br>
Maybe it took seven hours to destroy Washington and Brussel or something like that so the USA and the NATO and all the others lsot contact to each other, but the actual war would have lasted way longer.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Valve said the war lasted 7 hours.  Thats why its called the "7 hour war’</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/an-intelgent-dicussion-regarding-the-7-hour-war/8370/118">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/an-intelgent-dicussion-regarding-the-7-hour-war/8370/118</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 07 Mar 2012 20:16:03 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8370-118</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/an-intelgent-dicussion-regarding-the-7-hour-war/8370.rss">An intelgent dicussion regarding the &quot;7 hour war&quot;</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>An intelgent dicussion regarding the &quot;7 hour war&quot;</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Marooner]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Even if they managed to occupy all larger cities in Europe - I can’t agree to a war jsut lasting 7 hours in total, I mean even the movements of the troops takes time, and I’m not going to speak of the guerilla fights occurring normally in city streets.<br>
Maybe it took seven hours to destroy Washington and Brussel or something like that so the USA and the NATO and all the others lsot contact to eachother, but the actual war would have lasted way longer.</p>
<p>I like the idea of the Combine forces moving away after the successfull invasion of Earth, so they leave beack a “few” troops organizing the Cities and the resource gathering. I don’t think that the actual Combine army is that weak, they just create soldiers for each specific environment they have to deal with, and on earth the troops weren’t as strong as on their homeplanet.<br>
We never saw them on their own planet, so there’s no clue on their actual force.<br>
And when I think of the Cities with all the wasteland around, the broken and destroyed buildings and the starving people, it really looks like the Combine’s best days on earth are over. The sea’s drained, and mainly all ressources are gathered, so they called back to troops and left Breen and his troops back in City 17 to maintain the city until they loose interest in earth.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/an-intelgent-dicussion-regarding-the-7-hour-war/8370/117">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/an-intelgent-dicussion-regarding-the-7-hour-war/8370/117</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 07 Mar 2012 19:39:17 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8370-117</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/an-intelgent-dicussion-regarding-the-7-hour-war/8370.rss">An intelgent dicussion regarding the &quot;7 hour war&quot;</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>An intelgent dicussion regarding the &quot;7 hour war&quot;</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[OrderOfDagon]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="MysticJ">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/m/839c29/40.png" class="avatar"> MysticJ:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I personally envision the War as a series of massive destructive blasts. Bang! There goes New York. Bang! The Alps just disappeared. Seats of Power would be probably eliminated simply because rulers tend to be located in largest cities, and these should be easily detectable even by someone who doesn’t speak our language or decode our broadcasts. So, within few minutes, it is entirely possible that there was not a single RULER on the entire planet. As such, when Breen contacted (no doubt with G-man’s help) the invaders, he might have been the only one doing such thing, and so they agreed to his surrender, in order to preserve the valuable resources they wanted to exploit. Subsequently, Breen has sent a broadcast explaining to all humans that Earth surrendered and that we must not fight back, Combine placed an occupational garrison (Synths) on Earth and appointed Breen as the administrator, they placed the citadel on Earth, and went on to conquer other worlds.</p>
<p>End of story.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Well, we know that New York didn’t go “bang” because the United Nations building is where the surrender took place.</p>
<p>Also, I doubt the Combine just banged up Earth with explosions if they needed resources; but I doubt they came to Earth for resources. I’m sure they took plenty while they were campaigning on Earth, but they’re not called the Combine for nothing. They probably took Earth for the same reason they conquer all planets and dimensions – desired control and combination-evolution. They probably spared humanity to gain insight to portal technology. This is why you hear Breen and Mossman constantly bickering about it before Judith turned.</p>
<p>And if you were implying that the Gman represents humanity, I don’t think you should make such assertions just yet – his motives and whereabouts are still a mystery.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/an-intelgent-dicussion-regarding-the-7-hour-war/8370/116">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/an-intelgent-dicussion-regarding-the-7-hour-war/8370/116</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 05 Mar 2012 02:29:46 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8370-116</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/an-intelgent-dicussion-regarding-the-7-hour-war/8370.rss">An intelgent dicussion regarding the &quot;7 hour war&quot;</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>An intelgent dicussion regarding the &quot;7 hour war&quot;</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[MysticJ]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="X_Mastershot_X">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/x/c5a1d2/40.png" class="avatar"> X_Mastershot_X:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Imagine it like this,<br>
Portal storms happen----&gt; There’s chaos everywhere, governments even detonate nukes in cities to help stop headcrab or antlion infestations. People who are in remote places disappear. Everybody flees to the nearby cities and all of them become major population centers with lots fo military firepower,this probably even led to dictatorships so people are supressed and depressed even before Our benefactors arrive----&gt;</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Really? You think that any sane government would nuke cities just because several unknown non-intelligent lifeforms appear and start melee-attacking civilians??? What the hell for? Give me a well-supplied platoon of 100 soldiers and I’ll clean any city of antlions and headcrabs in couple of days. What’s so difficult about it?</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="X_Mastershot_X">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/x/c5a1d2/40.png" class="avatar"> X_Mastershot_X:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Combine discover the rift between Xen and Earth—Out of nowhere superportals appear (maybe charge itself a little bit)  And Aliens start pouring out of them like mad. Earth military, who is dealing with shit ton of issues. Are caught by suprise. (If an EMP occured they are in much deeper shit.) Again out of nowhere giant boxes fall out of the sky and millions of aliens start pouring out of them, too<br>
----&gt;</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>It is hinted throughout HL2 and Episodes that The Black Mesa Incident made Combine aware of Earth’s location, and they were able to use Xen to “slingshot” to Earth, because Xen, the borderworld, is a place between dimensions, thus significantly shortening distances. Imagine it this way:</p>
<p>Take a piece of paper and draw two dots near opposite corners. What’s the shortest distance between the two dots? Normally, people answer “a straight line”, but that’s not entirely true. A borderworld slingshot, in effect, serves as a shortcut, similar to bending the paper in such a way that the two dots “touch”.</p>
<p>The BM portal to Xen shortened the distance from BM to Xen to ZERO, making it feasible for Combine to invade Earth.</p>
<p>Therefore, even though G-man informs Gordon at the end of HL1 that “The borderworld, Xen, is in our control - thanks to you.” … that control didn’t last long, probably, or alternatively, Earth’s government didn’t last long enough to enjoy that control, once the Combine started their invasion.</p>
<p>Nihilanth’s death had the effect of creating portalstorms on Earth. Combine calibrated their technology to use Xen as slingshot and were able to teleport to Earth.</p>
<p>I personally envision the War as a series of massive destructive blasts. Bang! There goes New York. Bang! The Alps just disappeared. Seats of Power would be probably eliminated simply because rulers tend to be located in largest cities, and these should be easily detectable even by someone who doesn’t speak our language or decode our broadcasts. So, within few minutes, it is entirely possible that there was not a single RULER on the entire planet. As such, when Breen contacted (no doubt with G-man’s help) the invaders, he might have been the only one doing such thing, and so they agreed to his surrender, in order to preserve the valuable resources they wanted to exploit. Subsequently, Breen has sent a broadcast explaining to all humans that Earth surrendered and that we must not fight back, Combine placed an occupational garrison (Synths) on Earth and appointed Breen as the administrator, they placed the citadel on Earth, and went on to conquer other worlds.</p>
<p>End of story.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/an-intelgent-dicussion-regarding-the-7-hour-war/8370/115">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/an-intelgent-dicussion-regarding-the-7-hour-war/8370/115</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 27 Feb 2012 20:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8370-115</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/an-intelgent-dicussion-regarding-the-7-hour-war/8370.rss">An intelgent dicussion regarding the &quot;7 hour war&quot;</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>An intelgent dicussion regarding the &quot;7 hour war&quot;</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Dias]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Mented">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/m/9de0a6/40.png" class="avatar"> Mented:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>They can just conjur that up from thin air? The citadel is made in a giant element combining machine?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>The whole universe has more resources than anything could ever need. All that’s needed to produce just about anything is energy, which they have giant dark-engery reactors to power, labor which they have robots for &amp; elements, which can be turned into one another through nuclear fusion/fission provided by the reactors. Hell, I’m sure we could accomplish the same in real life if money didn’t control the world.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Mented">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/m/9de0a6/40.png" class="avatar"> Mented:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I do wonder though, if they travel between dimensions, do they travel from one, to the another to go back to the original but in a different place on a different planet? That makes sense right?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>If the little peek we got of the dimension breen was going to travel to is any indicator, showing a bunch of citadels in close proximity, they could all connect to a homeworld or possibly to some kind of hub-worlds.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/an-intelgent-dicussion-regarding-the-7-hour-war/8370/114">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/an-intelgent-dicussion-regarding-the-7-hour-war/8370/114</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 18 Feb 2012 07:07:57 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8370-114</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/an-intelgent-dicussion-regarding-the-7-hour-war/8370.rss">An intelgent dicussion regarding the &quot;7 hour war&quot;</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>An intelgent dicussion regarding the &quot;7 hour war&quot;</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Kelesh]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>They are from different dimension, yes. But that doesn’t mean that their is Soo different from ours. For instance, the resources they take from Earth can be found in their own dimension but in the other end of their galaxy, so we the better source.</p>
<p>The game takes place Autumn if you ask me. Look around the countryside of City 17. Also, if it was an 20 year monoseason winter/autumn, the vegetation should’ve been in less diversity than we see now. Maybe the presence of the Combine have brought a new mini-iceage over the planet, by changing our climate. But surely there should be some kind of short summer.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/an-intelgent-dicussion-regarding-the-7-hour-war/8370/113">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/an-intelgent-dicussion-regarding-the-7-hour-war/8370/113</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 11 Feb 2012 19:28:16 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8370-113</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/an-intelgent-dicussion-regarding-the-7-hour-war/8370.rss">An intelgent dicussion regarding the &quot;7 hour war&quot;</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>An intelgent dicussion regarding the &quot;7 hour war&quot;</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[BahamutBBob]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Mented">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/m/9de0a6/40.png" class="avatar"> Mented:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I do wonder though, if they travel between dimensions, do they travel from one, to the another to go back to the original but in a different place on a different planet? That makes sense right?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Sounds a lot like the Xen relay to me.</p>
<p>On the topic of resources: if the Combine are from another dimension, it’s possible that the elements are different there.  Not likely, since all of their tech seems to work fine on Earth, which means the same or similar laws of physics and the same common elements, but possible.  That could explain why the water level in the oceans is lower.  Another possible explanation could be that it does seem like the climate is a bit cooler than Earth today, causing the polar ice caps to grow, then again we don’t know what month HL2 is supposed to take place in.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/an-intelgent-dicussion-regarding-the-7-hour-war/8370/112">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/an-intelgent-dicussion-regarding-the-7-hour-war/8370/112</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 11 Feb 2012 19:08:40 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8370-112</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/an-intelgent-dicussion-regarding-the-7-hour-war/8370.rss">An intelgent dicussion regarding the &quot;7 hour war&quot;</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>An intelgent dicussion regarding the &quot;7 hour war&quot;</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Mented]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Mephmage">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/m/85f322/40.png" class="avatar"> Mephmage:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Regardless of their travelling capabilities, I’d assume they live in a universe that is built the same way as ours. And all the resources you can find on our planet, exists in abundance in the cosmos. All you have to do is get out in space, and start harvesting asteroids, planets, moons, and comets. Put solar panels in space and you’ve got unlimited power from the sun.</p>
<p>So… In his defense, there’s nothing on our planet that they could possibly want that doesn’t already exist everywhere else in their own dimension. Neighbouring planet, moons, their sun… Given their vastly superior technology, then applying our own technological development and evolution, you can only come to the conclusion that not only have they reached the space age, but they’ve most likely already conquered their own solar system and probably beyond.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I don’t think people actually realise the problems with gathering and using resources between planets in a solar system. I also don’t think people realise the amount of distance there is between solar systems and how difficult it would actually be to traverse space with all the needed equipment to mine a planet, then send the materials back. The Combine have clearly found a much more suitable option to their technological level. They don’t need to traverse space, they can just send it through a portal. So literally any planet is up for grabs. I wouldn’t say they need to conquer for conquering sake, but they have the ability to easily take over the planet and it’s not like it costs them anything with the return. It’s cost effective simply put.</p>
<p>People are saying ‘Why would they?’. Well why not? They are completely unopposed morally, ethically and politically. Think manifest destiny.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/an-intelgent-dicussion-regarding-the-7-hour-war/8370/111">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/an-intelgent-dicussion-regarding-the-7-hour-war/8370/111</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 11 Feb 2012 11:06:43 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8370-111</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/an-intelgent-dicussion-regarding-the-7-hour-war/8370.rss">An intelgent dicussion regarding the &quot;7 hour war&quot;</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>An intelgent dicussion regarding the &quot;7 hour war&quot;</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Zuul]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Maybe it was just a good old pre-emptive strike? They might of thought that we were planning an attack 'cause of the teleportation tech. Maybe they didn’t know so much about us, so they went all in. And once they were here, they said “Fuck it. Let’s use them instead of wiping them out completely.”</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/an-intelgent-dicussion-regarding-the-7-hour-war/8370/110">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/an-intelgent-dicussion-regarding-the-7-hour-war/8370/110</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 11 Feb 2012 09:09:56 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8370-110</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/an-intelgent-dicussion-regarding-the-7-hour-war/8370.rss">An intelgent dicussion regarding the &quot;7 hour war&quot;</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>An intelgent dicussion regarding the &quot;7 hour war&quot;</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Bah]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Everyone is assuming that there was actually fighting during the Seven Hour War, it is possible that it was a Cold War style stand off, eventually ending in Earth’s surrender and disarmament at the negotiation table.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/an-intelgent-dicussion-regarding-the-7-hour-war/8370/109">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/an-intelgent-dicussion-regarding-the-7-hour-war/8370/109</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 11 Feb 2012 02:49:54 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8370-109</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/an-intelgent-dicussion-regarding-the-7-hour-war/8370.rss">An intelgent dicussion regarding the &quot;7 hour war&quot;</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
