<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>IBM Model M2 Problem</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/ibm-model-m2-problem/12703</link>
    <description>I recently discovered my Dad&#39;s old IBM keyboard laying around in the attic. I&#39;m a raging hipster and really like the feel of the keys so I&#39;ve been using it with my keyboard, but recently I just unplugged and then re set up my rig in, as far as I can tell, the exact same manner just with another monitor plugged in. Except now when I hold down a key, press another key, and then let go of the second key, the keyboard stops registering that the first key is still held down. For example, in CS:GO, if I&#39;m moving forward with the W key, and then press space to jump while still holding down W, the character stops moving after I let go of space and the jump is finished, but he will keep moving until I let go of space.

I really don&#39;t know how to google this problem so I figured I&#39;d give here a shot. The keyboard is plugged in to a ps2 to USB converter.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 26 Oct 2013 22:06:32 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Help and Support</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/ibm-model-m2-problem/12703.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>IBM Model M2 Problem</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[garrthbarrttinn]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>It’s as acade said, and it applies outside of video games, I tested it in m$ word.</p>
<p>Edit: so I’m doing all this with an external keyboard on my laptop. The issue doesn’t seem to appear on the keyboard’s internal keyboard or my other external keyboard (logitech g11).</p>
<p>Also, I tried a test:<br>
Hold shift, then hold W, then let go of shift.</p>
<p>Internal keyboard:<br>
WWWWWWWWWWWWWWWWWWWWWWwwwwwwwwwwwwwwwwwwwwww</p>
<p>Model M2:<br>
WWWWWWWWWWWWWWWWWWWWWWWWWWWWWWWWWWWWwwwwwwwwwwwwwwwwwwwww</p>
<p>The same result, however with the model M2 there is a good 1 second delay in the stream of w’s when I let go of shift while on the internal keyboard there is no delay, I am assuming this is the source of the problem. Any ideas for a resolution?</p>
<p>Also, I had been using it plugged directly into my desktop’s PS2 port for quite some time without issue and into my laptop’s USB converter for about a week before the problem emerged.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/ibm-model-m2-problem/12703/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/ibm-model-m2-problem/12703/5</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 26 Oct 2013 22:06:32 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12703-5</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/ibm-model-m2-problem/12703.rss">IBM Model M2 Problem</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>IBM Model M2 Problem</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[danielsangeo]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I’m merely asking if this happens outside of games.  It might be a limitation of the keyboard itself.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/ibm-model-m2-problem/12703/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/ibm-model-m2-problem/12703/4</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 26 Oct 2013 17:10:57 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12703-4</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/ibm-model-m2-problem/12703.rss">IBM Model M2 Problem</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>IBM Model M2 Problem</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[papernick]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>It’s not that he cannot press both simultaneously, the problem is that when he lets go of one of them, the other also stops being registered.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/ibm-model-m2-problem/12703/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/ibm-model-m2-problem/12703/3</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 26 Oct 2013 17:03:20 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12703-3</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/ibm-model-m2-problem/12703.rss">IBM Model M2 Problem</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>IBM Model M2 Problem</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[danielsangeo]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Does the keyboard allow you to press multiple keys simultaneously outside of CS:GO?  Can you do CTRL-ALT-DEL (in Windows) or other commands that require multiple simultaneous key presses?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/ibm-model-m2-problem/12703/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/ibm-model-m2-problem/12703/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 26 Oct 2013 15:30:56 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12703-2</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/ibm-model-m2-problem/12703.rss">IBM Model M2 Problem</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>IBM Model M2 Problem</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[garrthbarrttinn]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I recently discovered my Dad’s old IBM keyboard laying around in the attic. I’m a raging hipster and really like the feel of the keys so I’ve been using it with my keyboard, but recently I just unplugged and then re set up my rig in, as far as I can tell, the exact same manner just with another monitor plugged in. Except now when I hold down a key, press another key, and then let go of the second key, the keyboard stops registering that the first key is still held down. For example, in CS:GO, if I’m moving forward with the W key, and then press space to jump while still holding down W, the character stops moving after I let go of space and the jump is finished, but he will keep moving until I let go of space.</p>
<p>I really don’t know how to google this problem so I figured I’d give here a shot. The keyboard is plugged in to a ps2 to USB converter.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/ibm-model-m2-problem/12703/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/ibm-model-m2-problem/12703/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 26 Oct 2013 05:01:45 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12703-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/ibm-model-m2-problem/12703.rss">IBM Model M2 Problem</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
