<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Several things to improve.</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/several-things-to-improve/10422</link>
    <description>Hi guys!

First of all, I would like to say that Black Mesa is really amazing. You have done a great job. I say it as a gamer who played Half-Life for the first time 8 years ago and I have had regular contact with it since then.

I have played Black Mesa for a few hours already and these are things I have noticed, things that could improve the game:

1) Normal difficulty is too difficult. I am an experienced gamer and while playing on this difficulty I had about 1-5 HP most of the time and had to keep on reloading the game. I changed the difficulty level to easy at one point and since then it was way more enjoyable to play BM. The easy level is the most balanced one. Actually, the easy difficulty should be the normal difficulty, and the normal difficulty should  be the hard difficulty.
Also, what I have noticed and I think it&#39;s very important about the difficulty level is that the enemy soldiers shoot you instantly when they see you (the player has less than half a second to react), they almost always if not always hit you at first sight and also when you do not move. In other words, their accuracy is way to high at first sight situations and when the player does not move (but this might seem natural). Another thing about the AI is that after you shoot or do something that could alarm them, they immediately know where you are. There is no way to surprise them. Connected with their first sight accuracy, there are many situations, when your location is somehow discovered and you are shot immediately. It&#39;s obviously wrong. It should look like this, that for example you shoot with your weapon from behind a cover, they are alarmed, but don&#39;t know where you are, they try to search for you, and when you move out of the cover, they should be surprised, thus not shoot you immediately, but take some time to react.

2) I don&#39;t know the chapter&#39;s name, but when you see a soldier for the first time, that soldier kills a scientist. You see this scene from above. There is a container which seems could be dropped on the soldier&#39;s head by pressing a button, but the button did not work for me. There was no reaction while pressing it.

3) Jumping is quite troublesome. It&#39;s not that bad, because it seems more realistic, nevertheless I think the classic jumping style was better.

4) The glock pistol lacks the quick fire mode that we had in Half-Life.

5) I really like the way you zoom the view with a revolver. Regardless some people might say, I am convinced this should be copied to other weapons as well.

6) It is amazing how the scientists&#39; looks differ so much, but it would be twice that good, if every single one would look different. I know this might be a hard and demanding thing to do, but it would make a huge impression on players (I know because I had this impression until I realised some scientists look the same). Oh, and I loved those women in Black Mesa.

7) The ability to walk slowly (without making any noise) like in Half-Life would be nice and useful in some situations.

8. The way your suit and weapons become covered in blood is fantastic.

9) I would like to see things written on blackboards and generally other written things that you could read in game to be in higher resolution. Those are things that attract player&#39;s attention and it&#39;s a little disappointing when you can&#39;t read them well because of the low resolution textures. It also makes the game less realistic (seeing pixels does it).

11) It is almost impossible to avoid bullsquid&#39;s long range attack (he shoots acid I guess). In Half-Life it was quite an easy thing to avoid it. I think it was better in Half-Life, because in Black Mesa he always hits you and it&#39;s just irritating.

12) I hope you will be updating Black Mesa using automatic Steam updates. I guess some non Steam download mirrors will also be necessary, but Steam updates are the priority.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 18 Sep 2012 20:36:46 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>In-game Issues (Mod)</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/several-things-to-improve/10422.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Several things to improve.</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Rafiraf]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I’ve found more things to fix:</p>
<ul>
<li>shooting fans makes the sound like shooting glass,</li>
<li>zooming with the crossbow drops the number of FPS significantly,</li>
</ul>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/several-things-to-improve/10422/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/several-things-to-improve/10422/4</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 18 Sep 2012 20:36:46 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-10422-4</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/several-things-to-improve/10422.rss">Several things to improve.</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Several things to improve.</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Rafiraf]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Yeah, these are not some serious issues, maybe except the AI reaction times and accuracy. The lack of serious issues only shows how good Black Mesa is. I’ve presented my feelings about the game, things I’d like to see improved, simply because I really love the game and would like to see it even better.</p>
<p>On the second thought, you’re right about glock. Since you can shoot it fast by pressing the fire button rapidly, the quick fire mode seems pointless.</p>
<p>Well, I could dodge bullsquid’s attacks only a few times, while in Half-Life he would very rarely hit me. It’s a fact that in Black Mesa his acid (I guess it’s acid) flies way faster, too fast in my opinion.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/several-things-to-improve/10422/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/several-things-to-improve/10422/3</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 17 Sep 2012 07:53:56 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-10422-3</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/several-things-to-improve/10422.rss">Several things to improve.</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Several things to improve.</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[flipdarkfuture]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>This sound more like niggles rather then actual problems.</p>
<p>I’ve run into a few problems with jumping myself, but apparently you need to hold down the crouch key after jumping, that’s how you get on top of boxes and stuff.</p>
<p>And if you hold down the fire button while using the glock, it quick-fires. Or you could just click it really fast.</p>
<p>I personally find it fairly easy to dodge the Bullsquid spit. Just sprint and slide as it reaches the height of it’s arc.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/several-things-to-improve/10422/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/several-things-to-improve/10422/2</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 17 Sep 2012 04:06:20 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-10422-2</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/several-things-to-improve/10422.rss">Several things to improve.</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Several things to improve.</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Rafiraf]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Hi guys!</p>
<p>First of all, I would like to say that Black Mesa is really amazing. You have done a great job. I say it as a gamer who played Half-Life for the first time 8 years ago and I have had regular contact with it since then.</p>
<p>I have played Black Mesa for a few hours already and these are things I have noticed, things that could improve the game:</p>
<ol>
<li>
<p>Normal difficulty is too difficult. I am an experienced gamer and while playing on this difficulty I had about 1-5 HP most of the time and had to keep on reloading the game. I changed the difficulty level to easy at one point and since then it was way more enjoyable to play BM. The easy level is the most balanced one. Actually, the easy difficulty should be the normal difficulty, and the normal difficulty should  be the hard difficulty.<br>
Also, what I have noticed and I think it’s very important about the difficulty level is that the enemy soldiers shoot you instantly when they see you (the player has less than half a second to react), they almost always if not always hit you at first sight and also when you do not move. In other words, their accuracy is way to high at first sight situations and when the player does not move (but this might seem natural). Another thing about the AI is that after you shoot or do something that could alarm them, they immediately know where you are. There is no way to surprise them. Connected with their first sight accuracy, there are many situations, when your location is somehow discovered and you are shot immediately. It’s obviously wrong. It should look like this, that for example you shoot with your weapon from behind a cover, they are alarmed, but don’t know where you are, they try to search for you, and when you move out of the cover, they should be surprised, thus not shoot you immediately, but take some time to react.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>I don’t know the chapter’s name, but when you see a soldier for the first time, that soldier kills a scientist. You see this scene from above. There is a container which seems could be dropped on the soldier’s head by pressing a button, but the button did not work for me. There was no reaction while pressing it.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Jumping is quite troublesome. It’s not that bad, because it seems more realistic, nevertheless I think the classic jumping style was better.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>The glock pistol lacks the quick fire mode that we had in Half-Life.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>I really like the way you zoom the view with a revolver. Regardless some people might say, I am convinced this should be copied to other weapons as well.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>It is amazing how the scientists’ looks differ so much, but it would be twice that good, if every single one would look different. I know this might be a hard and demanding thing to do, but it would make a huge impression on players (I know because I had this impression until I realised some scientists look the same). Oh, and I loved those women in Black Mesa.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>The ability to walk slowly (without making any noise) like in Half-Life would be nice and useful in some situations.</p>
</li>
</ol>
<ol start="8">
<li>The way your suit and weapons become covered in blood is fantastic.</li>
</ol>
<ol start="9">
<li>
<p>I would like to see things written on blackboards and generally other written things that you could read in game to be in higher resolution. Those are things that attract player’s attention and it’s a little disappointing when you can’t read them well because of the low resolution textures. It also makes the game less realistic (seeing pixels does it).</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>It is almost impossible to avoid bullsquid’s long range attack (he shoots acid I guess). In Half-Life it was quite an easy thing to avoid it. I think it was better in Half-Life, because in Black Mesa he always hits you and it’s just irritating.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>I hope you will be updating Black Mesa using automatic Steam updates. I guess some non Steam download mirrors will also be necessary, but Steam updates are the priority.</p>
</li>
</ol>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/several-things-to-improve/10422/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/several-things-to-improve/10422/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 16 Sep 2012 23:49:03 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-10422-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/several-things-to-improve/10422.rss">Several things to improve.</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
