<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>How to be nicer</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/how-to-be-nicer/7210</link>
    <description>I think I&#39;m going to make a conscious effort to be a nicer, better person. The way I see it is, I&#39;m opinionated, if I disagree with somebody, I&#39;m most likely going to let them know it and try to prove them wrong. I try as hard as I can to not be wrong, but I will admit it when I am. I&#39;m usually a complete asshole to people I disagree with, and like to make people feel stupid.

I guess I&#39;m nice to people I feel bad for, and generally try to defend them or be their friend, but that&#39;s not really enough. I don&#39;t think I&#39;m a happy person, and I really only am happy when I&#39;m laughing from making fun of somebody, or when I prove myself right.

Any advice on how to be a nicer person? I realized today that I&#39;m a self-superior asshole and want to change that.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 26 May 2011 23:03:12 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Off Topic</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/how-to-be-nicer/7210.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>How to be nicer</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Mango_Assassin]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>We all go through shit times, be it lasting of many months to years, when I was 16 I never looked forward to anything, I went on holiday with two of my best mates, I wasn’t even excited or anything, regardless I had a great time in the end.</p>
<p>I use to insult people for general amusement and laughs a lot, I wouldn’t even saying ‘joking’ etc, I’d just insult and leave at that, I was always fucking miserable.</p>
<p>Right now, I’m having a shit time, a girl that led me for a while to believe she wanted something serious fucked off with another guy, I’ve worked the same job for 4 years this November and hate it, My mates place recently got robbed and I lost a few centimental of value objects, I’m having to try to occupy my mind on something else. Right now I’m just full of hate and anger, It’s generally how I deal with being sad.</p>
<p>Now take everything I’ve said above, and at the end of it, even after anything has happened to me, I realised I still have what matters to me and they will always be there for me, my friends I’m proud to call my brothers.</p>
<p>(<a class="mention" href="/u/fuskox">@Fuskox</a>, from what I’ve seen of you on here, you seem like a pretty cool guy.)</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/how-to-be-nicer/7210/42">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/how-to-be-nicer/7210/42</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 May 2011 23:03:12 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7210-42</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/how-to-be-nicer/7210.rss">How to be nicer</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How to be nicer</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Actonide]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="DansonDelta40">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/d/bbce88/40.png" class="avatar"> DansonDelta40:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>The Hitchhiker’s Guide shaped my worldview</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I do not want my mattress to be sentient, and I never forget to hit the ground when I fall…<br>
It would be cool, though.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/how-to-be-nicer/7210/41">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/how-to-be-nicer/7210/41</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 May 2011 20:26:27 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7210-41</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/how-to-be-nicer/7210.rss">How to be nicer</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How to be nicer</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[CTID]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Fancy Pants">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Fancy Pants:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>like no really<br>
you dont WANT to be nice<br>
like believe it or not im super super nice irl and i have problems saying no to anybody and i get taken advantage of a lot<br>
i have people seriously trying to teach me how to tell people to fuck off when they ask me for shit<br>
if you can be a dick to ppls faces do it</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>This. Same with me.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="OldDirtyBastard">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/o/dec6dc/40.png" class="avatar"> OldDirtyBastard:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Seriously, if you want to be 100%, genuinely, Jesus-like nice to <span class="bbcode-b"><em>everyone</em></span> - you can forget about it.<br>
But this:</p>
<p>Is simply a matter of self-control and keeping your fucking mouth shut.<br>
Work on it.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>And this.</p>
<p>There are few advantages to being nice to people, people see an advantage to others being nice because they’re easy to take advantage. Seriously, fuck people. They suck.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/how-to-be-nicer/7210/40">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/how-to-be-nicer/7210/40</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 May 2011 20:20:44 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7210-40</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/how-to-be-nicer/7210.rss">How to be nicer</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How to be nicer</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[xalener]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>The HHGG movie should have been 4 hours long to contain the epic social commentary the book had. It missed a lot of it (but it was still kinda there between the lines).</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/how-to-be-nicer/7210/39">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/how-to-be-nicer/7210/39</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 May 2011 20:11:04 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7210-39</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/how-to-be-nicer/7210.rss">How to be nicer</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How to be nicer</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[DansonDelta40]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I agree with danielsangeo and xalener. The Hitchhiker’s Guide shaped my worldview as much as Pratchett’s Discworld Novels did.</p>
<p>After reading them, you might see things from a much different perspective and find yourself a more understanding, open-minded individual.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/how-to-be-nicer/7210/38">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/how-to-be-nicer/7210/38</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 May 2011 09:06:10 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7210-38</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/how-to-be-nicer/7210.rss">How to be nicer</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How to be nicer</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[xalener]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="danielsangeo">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/user_avatar/leakfree.org/danielsangeo/40/4347_2.png" class="avatar"> danielsangeo:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>The Bible didn’t really make me nicer.  What helped me was…believe it or not, the Hitchhiker’s Guide to the Galaxy.</p>
<p>Now, before you call “bullshit” on me, the books espouse a view of the universe which, I feel, is much more realistic than any scripture and editorializes and anthropomorphizes our life into an easily understandable and, well, entertaining nugget.  It doesn’t take itself seriously (how can you when you have a robot programmed to be depressed talking to an exuberant sentient mattress?), but, inside all the silliness is a great worldview.</p>
<p>I suggest reading that.   <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=9" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>HHGG is better than the bible in terms of “self help”</p>
<p>It’s true.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/how-to-be-nicer/7210/37">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/how-to-be-nicer/7210/37</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 May 2011 02:17:09 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7210-37</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/how-to-be-nicer/7210.rss">How to be nicer</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How to be nicer</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Fuskox]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I agree with that weed part, yes it does. So easy to talk and have a great time. Gonna check out the link.</p>
<p>Very true link, I never really get how things work out that way.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/how-to-be-nicer/7210/36">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/how-to-be-nicer/7210/36</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 May 2011 02:05:28 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7210-36</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/how-to-be-nicer/7210.rss">How to be nicer</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How to be nicer</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Ibanez]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>This thread makes me happy. I love seeing people actually express genuine emotions on the internet, it makes me feel better about humanity. I’ve always been “the nice guy” that friends rip on, or that girls pass over for the asshole they can screw over. Over the last year or so, I’ve met people who changed me completely in a very, very good way. It’s given me a much more laid back attitude about life, and that’s what it really boils down to: how much of a fuck you give. If you care too much about other peoples’ opinions of you and so on, it’ll never work. You need to find the middle ground between being a nice guy pussyface, and a normal person who doesn’t give a rats ass about what other people think of them. Gain confidence in things that you know you can do that other people can’t do. Pertaining to being a ‘nice guy’, I found this lovely link on my facebook wall today, it was fairly uplifting, you might enjoy it: <a href="https://www.stumbleupon.com/su/26inxf/www.stwing.upenn.edu/%257Ejenf/writing/rant04.html" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://www.stumbleupon.com/su/26inxf/www.stwing.upenn.edu/%257Ejenf/writing/rant04.html</a>.</p>
<p>As for being less mean and more nice; smoke weed! (No, I’m not trying to start that argument again, I genuinely mean it.) Don’t smoke weed by yourself, find people you can have good conversation with and smoke with them. Weed conversation beats the shit out of a lot of other kinds of conversation you could have, and the act of smoking with friends and having a lil pow-wow mellows you out and does a great job of making you think objectively, as opposed to subjectively. That’s what the other people are there for, to make you stop thinking about yourself and how your problems relate to you.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/how-to-be-nicer/7210/35">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/how-to-be-nicer/7210/35</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 May 2011 02:04:13 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7210-35</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/how-to-be-nicer/7210.rss">How to be nicer</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How to be nicer</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[robot_deodorant]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Murder everyone that’s ever pissed you off and then make sure to never kill again. From then on every action you take in life will be “nice”.</p>
<p>“Remember that time I murdered that guy? Hmm? Yeah. I’m a nice person now.”</p>
<p>But seriously… being nice is easy.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/how-to-be-nicer/7210/34">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/how-to-be-nicer/7210/34</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 May 2011 01:44:32 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7210-34</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/how-to-be-nicer/7210.rss">How to be nicer</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How to be nicer</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Someonerandm]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="DansonDelta40">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/d/bbce88/40.png" class="avatar"> DansonDelta40:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Then voice your opinion like you so eloquently manage to do on this forum every now and then, especially when being criticized.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>You mean swear a ton and then use bad grammar? That might actually work.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/how-to-be-nicer/7210/33">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/how-to-be-nicer/7210/33</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 May 2011 01:36:37 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7210-33</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/how-to-be-nicer/7210.rss">How to be nicer</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How to be nicer</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[DansonDelta40]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Fancy Pants">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Fancy Pants:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>i need to be meaner but i caaaaaaaaaaaaaaant</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Just try to imagine the next guy who asks you to do something for him is one of us forum fuckwads you don’t give a damn about.</p>
<p>Then voice your opinion like you so eloquently manage to do on this forum every now and then, especially when being criticized.</p>
<p>If it helps, shut your eyes that same moment and pretend you are typing and shout out loudly what you are typing.</p>
<p>Just be a little like you act on these forums, and you will accomplish your goal.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/how-to-be-nicer/7210/32">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/how-to-be-nicer/7210/32</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 May 2011 00:06:52 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7210-32</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/how-to-be-nicer/7210.rss">How to be nicer</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How to be nicer</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Fuskox]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Sounds like a good idea Nightmare, might try it out.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/how-to-be-nicer/7210/31">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/how-to-be-nicer/7210/31</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 May 2011 20:37:06 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7210-31</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/how-to-be-nicer/7210.rss">How to be nicer</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How to be nicer</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Nightmare470]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>This worked for me, find someone who’s an optimistic and happy person and talk to them, get to know them and hang around with them. Don’t be mean to them though, but kinda watch what they do and somewhat mimic it and try to look at things the way they do, it helped me. I used to have a “we’re all gonna die what’s the point to anything” view but my friend always says that we’ll only die once, so die with someone you like, and she made it her job to make it so there was plenty of people she liked and who liked her back. I adopted this attitude more or less and I’m a happier person and usually being happy leads to being nice, or at least it makes being nicer easier!</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/how-to-be-nicer/7210/30">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/how-to-be-nicer/7210/30</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 May 2011 20:15:36 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7210-30</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/how-to-be-nicer/7210.rss">How to be nicer</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How to be nicer</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Fuskox]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I’m 16, and I’m hoping to be nicer because I’m just not really happy. Thinking about it today, I think it’s probably just looking on the bright side of life that would make me a nicer, happier person. So far, I think I’m succeeding at it. I don’t think I yelled at somebody once today, and didn’t tell people they’re stupid or demean anyone. I still got angry, but managed to hold it in. <span class="bbcode-i">By a very small amount</span> =)</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/how-to-be-nicer/7210/29">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/how-to-be-nicer/7210/29</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 May 2011 19:09:14 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7210-29</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/how-to-be-nicer/7210.rss">How to be nicer</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How to be nicer</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Marb]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>There’s a lot of truth to the saying “Nice guys finish last.”  When you spend too much time worrying about <span class="bbcode-b">not </span>offending or upsetting people and worrying about what other people are thinking of you and your actions, then it can severely cut into your ability to just be yourself.  And yes, it sets yourself up to be “walked all over” if you let it get to that point.</p>
<p>I’m basically the “nice guy.”  At this point in life, I’m ok with it for the most part.  I think I’ve attained just enough of the “don’t give a fuck” attitude to prevent getting walked on yet still remain a nice enough of a guy.  My online persona is generally my IRL persona as well.  If anything, I’m probably a little nicer online … if not a <span class="bbcode-i">little </span>more out-going…</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/how-to-be-nicer/7210/28">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/how-to-be-nicer/7210/28</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 May 2011 15:13:12 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7210-28</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/how-to-be-nicer/7210.rss">How to be nicer</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How to be nicer</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[deadjosh]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I can quite literally feel your pain as my father is a raging alcoholic. My mother was a heroin addict. The two divorced when I was just a little tyke and my father, brother and I had to move to Alaska (from California) to get away from her. (She used to kidnap my brother and I and hold us for ransom so she could get her next fix.)</p>
<p>Growing up I held a lot of resentment for my father because I always felt he chose alcohol over his kids. I still feel that way to this day. I haven’t spoken to him in over a year, mostly because he is a total recluse and doesn’t really want to have anything to do with his children. I sincerely hope this end is not in store for your family, because I miss my father and worry about him.</p>
<p>For me, the Bible went a long way toward curbing my anger. It wasn’t only my dad that I was angry with either. I let it bleed-over to <span class="bbcode-i">all</span> my relationships. I’m 36 now and still trying to recover from a lifetime spent hating pretty much everyone, including myself.</p>
<p>I hope and pray that your mom <span class="bbcode-i">does</span> quit drinking, but there’s no way to force it. Either she makes the choice to quit or she doesn’t. It’s pretty much as simple as that. It <span class="bbcode-i">cannot</span> be made for her.</p>
<p>Feel free to PM me if you want…and good luck, it’s rare to see anyone who genuinely wants to better themselves, and 'tis a noble goal.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/how-to-be-nicer/7210/27">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/how-to-be-nicer/7210/27</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 May 2011 13:24:28 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7210-27</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/how-to-be-nicer/7210.rss">How to be nicer</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How to be nicer</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Maxey]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>People need to have a balance of niceness and rudeness so they don’t become too boring and predictable.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/how-to-be-nicer/7210/26">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/how-to-be-nicer/7210/26</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 May 2011 11:33:56 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7210-26</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/how-to-be-nicer/7210.rss">How to be nicer</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How to be nicer</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[DrasarSalman]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I wouldn’t call myself nice… not mean either. Probably just a little offensive.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/how-to-be-nicer/7210/25">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/how-to-be-nicer/7210/25</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 May 2011 10:48:16 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7210-25</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/how-to-be-nicer/7210.rss">How to be nicer</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How to be nicer</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Raziel_ZV]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Look, you don´t need to be nicer…you are who you are…and that makes you cool person  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=9" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:">  …It´s not that you are not nice to people, but people aren´t nice to you because of todays society…rotten society…  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=9" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/how-to-be-nicer/7210/24">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/how-to-be-nicer/7210/24</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 May 2011 10:40:57 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7210-24</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/how-to-be-nicer/7210.rss">How to be nicer</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How to be nicer</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[taxi_evil]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Can I ask how old the OP is? If you’re still a teenager you go through sometimes long periods of feeling angry and hostile.</p>
<p>I have a few alcoholics in my family. Luckily we live further away from them, but we sort of let them get on with it. Tried helping them, but ultimately if they don’t want to help themselves then it’s a losing battle.</p>
<p>Lastly, maybe try talking about things you don’t feel superior about to other people? You could meet a guy, talk to him about computers (say) and he wouldn’t have a clue. But he might be an expert at fixing cars or particle physics (I genuinely met a physicist in the pub a while ago, he bought me and my mate a drink and we talked about Higg’s Boson  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=9" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"> )</p>
<p>You can get into a lot of trouble being nasty to everyone, especially when alcohol gets involved. A bit of courtesy and being nice, and I’ve never been involved in a bar fight</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/how-to-be-nicer/7210/23">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/how-to-be-nicer/7210/23</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 May 2011 08:49:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7210-23</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/how-to-be-nicer/7210.rss">How to be nicer</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How to be nicer</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[danielsangeo]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>The Bible didn’t really make me nicer.  What helped me was…believe it or not, the Hitchhiker’s Guide to the Galaxy.</p>
<p>Now, before you call “bullshit” on me, the books espouse a view of the universe which, I feel, is much more realistic than any scripture and editorializes and anthropomorphizes our life into an easily understandable and, well, entertaining nugget.  It doesn’t take itself seriously (how can you when you have a robot programmed to be depressed talking to an exuberant sentient mattress?), but, inside all the silliness is a great worldview.</p>
<p>I suggest reading that.   <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=9" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/how-to-be-nicer/7210/22">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/how-to-be-nicer/7210/22</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 May 2011 05:21:08 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7210-22</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/how-to-be-nicer/7210.rss">How to be nicer</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How to be nicer</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[_rot_fodder]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I find just being aware of my feelings is a great start to gain neutural ground. If you find yourself eccessively angry at someone or something, sit for a moment, close your eyes and concentrate on what the anger feels like, in a purely physical sense. As in, concentrate on the burning feeling in your chest, and ignore what is causing it. The feeling will go away the longer you concentrate on it, and you will find your mind clearer to think in a non biased manner. It works for me, as long as I can actually keep concentrating on the physical feeling instead of what is bothering me. Fun Fact: It also helps with wounds/bruises/etc.</p>
<p>One thing that just helps me be a nicer person in general, and I’m going to get 103 bullshits for this but whatever, is read a bible. Try it or not, believe it or not, I don’t give a shit. I’m just saying what works for me. I’m not saying study it like some sort of scolar writing down every law and name, just some light reading.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/how-to-be-nicer/7210/21">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/how-to-be-nicer/7210/21</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 May 2011 05:08:17 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7210-21</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/how-to-be-nicer/7210.rss">How to be nicer</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How to be nicer</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[danielsangeo]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Sometimes, someone can be too nice.</p>
<p>I see it on the road.  Someone waits until the last minute to get into a traffic jam, sometimes even riding the shoulder to get ahead…then someone lets this jackass in, furthering the jam.  “I’m just being nice/courteous” would be their excuse if you questioned them.   They’re not being nice or courteous because they’ve exacerbated the problem and rewarded rule-breakers.</p>
<p>“Nice” would be to be what some would consider ‘mean’ and not let the jackhole in.  He broke the rules, now he has to live with the consequences…even if it means sitting in the shoulder for 10 minutes.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/how-to-be-nicer/7210/20">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/how-to-be-nicer/7210/20</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 May 2011 05:07:18 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7210-20</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/how-to-be-nicer/7210.rss">How to be nicer</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How to be nicer</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Fuskox]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>ODB, I don’t think you understand. We tried for 6 years straight, and couldn’t win. I talk to my dad about it all the time, he’s the one who wanted the divorce, and he still worries about her. I talk to her boyfriend about it every time I see him, he can’t stop it either. I’ve tried to help her, I still do, I just can’t win.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/how-to-be-nicer/7210/19">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/how-to-be-nicer/7210/19</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 May 2011 05:02:25 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7210-19</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/how-to-be-nicer/7210.rss">How to be nicer</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How to be nicer</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[OldDirtyBastard]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>And I think seeing the failure that my mother is in life has also changed me, I don’t know whether or not for the better or worse. Watching her alcoholism break up my parents’ marriage, and now seeing it slowly destroy both her business and family life, make me probably more angry than I’ve ever been in my entire life, but nothing I say changes a thing. I think my mother’s problems have made me a less happy person, but I think I see life on a more realistic level because of them, even though it’s a very pessimistic view.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Well that’s a whole fucking another prospect.<br>
Really, why wouldn’t you start by helping your mom through.<br>
Do yourself a favor and set a goal for yourself. <span class="bbcode-i">Force </span>her to stop, do something about it.<br>
There’s plenty of ways.</p>
<p>Go.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/how-to-be-nicer/7210/18">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/how-to-be-nicer/7210/18</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 May 2011 04:46:23 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7210-18</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/how-to-be-nicer/7210.rss">How to be nicer</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
