<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Rebuilding BM&#39;s Soundcache (for use in custom scripts/sounds in it)</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/rebuilding-bms-soundcache-for-use-in-custom-scripts-sounds-in-it/11835</link>
    <description>Bah. I&#39;ve looked in every fuckin&#39; nook and cranny in the internet. Can&#39;t find anything that&#39;s worked for me.

Basically, what I&#39;m trying to do is import a few of HL2&#39;s sounds and the related scripts into BM. Now, I managed to get so far as to get it to recognize the scripts I&#39;m using and the engine seems to detect (partially) the directories for the sounds.

... here&#39;s the partially, the issue pops in when I try to play it using the &quot;play&quot; convar, the engine doesn&#39;t recognize the wav name, yet when I whack, say a zombie with the new sound scripts, I don&#39;t get the error. (just doesn&#39;t play the sound).

I&#39;m stumped. Any ideas?</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 11 Dec 2012 15:20:04 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Help!</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/rebuilding-bms-soundcache-for-use-in-custom-scripts-sounds-in-it/11835.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Rebuilding BM&#39;s Soundcache (for use in custom scripts/sounds in it)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Chickenprotector]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Bah. I’ve looked in every fuckin’ nook and cranny in the internet. Can’t find anything that’s worked for me.</p>
<p>Basically, what I’m trying to do is import a few of HL2’s sounds and the related scripts into BM. Now, I managed to get so far as to get it to recognize the scripts I’m using and the engine seems to detect (partially) the directories for the sounds.</p>
<p>… here’s the partially, the issue pops in when I try to play it using the “play” convar, the engine doesn’t recognize the wav name, yet when I whack, say a zombie with the new sound scripts, I don’t get the error. (just doesn’t play the sound).</p>
<p>I’m stumped. Any ideas?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/rebuilding-bms-soundcache-for-use-in-custom-scripts-sounds-in-it/11835/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/rebuilding-bms-soundcache-for-use-in-custom-scripts-sounds-in-it/11835/1</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 11 Dec 2012 15:20:04 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11835-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/rebuilding-bms-soundcache-for-use-in-custom-scripts-sounds-in-it/11835.rss">Rebuilding BM&#39;s Soundcache (for use in custom scripts/sounds in it)</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
