<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Missing bm_c2a4d.bsp?</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/missing-bm-c2a4d-bsp/14577</link>
    <description>Hey, just picked up Black Mesa on Steam and I&#39;ve run into a rather serious problem in Residue Processing.  When changing levels from bm_c2a4c (climbing up the red-lit ladder) the game just unceremoniously dumps me to the desktop with no error message.  I did a bunch of trouble shooting, verified my local file integrity, even reinstalled the game and nothing fixed it.  So I figured in a pinch I&#39;d just skip to map bm_c2a4d using the console (which I believe is the next in progression based on some googling).  Low and behold, it says that map doesn&#39;t exist.  I went into the directory where the game is installed and sure enough that .bsp file is missing.

So, should that bsp be there?  I assume this is why I&#39;m crashing.  I know BM is still sort early access so things might be changing.
Again, verified my local files several times and got a clean bill of health, and did a fresh install.  So if that file is indeed missing, I&#39;m not sure how to get Steam to install it.

Hopefully the collective wisdom here can help me out, as a long-time half-life loyalist I&#39;m pumped to get back into it!</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 10 Jan 2016 08:17:52 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>In-game Issues</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/missing-bm-c2a4d-bsp/14577.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Missing bm_c2a4d.bsp?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Racket_Man]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Dr Cohen">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Dr Cohen:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I went back to a much earlier save in the level, and loading map bm_c2a4e worked.  A console dump of the crash was spitting this out:</p>
<p>Ignoring unreasonable position (-720.419128,-2886.475098,-16399.529297) from vphysics! (entity prop_physics)<br>
---- Host_Changelevel ----<br>
WARNING! Field mapName is using the wrong FIELD_ type!<br>
Fix this or you’ll see a crash.<br>
WARNING! Field mapName is using the wrong FIELD_ type!<br>
Fix this or you’ll see a crash.</p>
<p>I assume something I had done in the level was making it cry.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I was playing BMS today (I have not had a chance since the Crossfire update) and I saw a LOT of the above messages on the console</p>
<p>No crash or anything, but I have not seen this message/error before.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/missing-bm-c2a4d-bsp/14577/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/missing-bm-c2a4d-bsp/14577/5</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 10 Jan 2016 08:17:52 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14577-5</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/missing-bm-c2a4d-bsp/14577.rss">Missing bm_c2a4d.bsp?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Missing bm_c2a4d.bsp?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Dr_Cohen]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I went back to a much earlier save in the level, and loading map bm_c2a4e worked.  A console dump of the crash was spitting this out:</p>
<p>Ignoring unreasonable position (-720.419128,-2886.475098,-16399.529297) from vphysics! (entity prop_physics)<br>
---- Host_Changelevel ----<br>
WARNING! Field mapName is using the wrong FIELD_ type!<br>
Fix this or you’ll see a crash.<br>
WARNING! Field mapName is using the wrong FIELD_ type!<br>
Fix this or you’ll see a crash.</p>
<p>I assume something I had done in the level was making it cry.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/missing-bm-c2a4d-bsp/14577/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/missing-bm-c2a4d-bsp/14577/4</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 09 Jan 2016 06:36:30 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14577-4</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/missing-bm-c2a4d-bsp/14577.rss">Missing bm_c2a4d.bsp?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Missing bm_c2a4d.bsp?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Dr_Cohen]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Ok, good to know I’m not missing any files.  Tried to load bm_c2a4e and same problem.  Drops me to the desktop.  Weird.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/missing-bm-c2a4d-bsp/14577/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/missing-bm-c2a4d-bsp/14577/3</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 09 Jan 2016 06:29:40 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14577-3</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/missing-bm-c2a4d-bsp/14577.rss">Missing bm_c2a4d.bsp?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Missing bm_c2a4d.bsp?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[danielsangeo]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I loaded up bm_c2a4c on my version (I’m on the beta opt-in so I don’t know if that changes things), and just no-clipped to the end.</p>
<p>I transitioned fine while going up the ladder.  Might be a problem with the vanilla version of the Steam version.</p>
<p>Until they fix it (or offer a fix), temporarily you can load the next map by going to bm_c2a4e.  (There is no bm_c2a4d.)</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/missing-bm-c2a4d-bsp/14577/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/missing-bm-c2a4d-bsp/14577/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 09 Jan 2016 04:32:41 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14577-2</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/missing-bm-c2a4d-bsp/14577.rss">Missing bm_c2a4d.bsp?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Missing bm_c2a4d.bsp?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Dr_Cohen]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Hey, just picked up Black Mesa on Steam and I’ve run into a rather serious problem in Residue Processing.  When changing levels from bm_c2a4c (climbing up the red-lit ladder) the game just unceremoniously dumps me to the desktop with no error message.  I did a bunch of trouble shooting, verified my local file integrity, even reinstalled the game and nothing fixed it.  So I figured in a pinch I’d just skip to map bm_c2a4d using the console (which I believe is the next in progression based on some googling).  Low and behold, it says that map doesn’t exist.  I went into the directory where the game is installed and sure enough that .bsp file is missing.</p>
<p>So, should that bsp be there?  I assume this is why I’m crashing.  I know BM is still sort early access so things might be changing.<br>
Again, verified my local files several times and got a clean bill of health, and did a fresh install.  So if that file is indeed missing, I’m not sure how to get Steam to install it.</p>
<p>Hopefully the collective wisdom here can help me out, as a long-time half-life loyalist I’m pumped to get back into it!</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/missing-bm-c2a4d-bsp/14577/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/missing-bm-c2a4d-bsp/14577/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 09 Jan 2016 04:05:08 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14577-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/missing-bm-c2a4d-bsp/14577.rss">Missing bm_c2a4d.bsp?</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
