<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Soooooo...</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/soooooo/13703</link>
    <description>Helloooooo

First of all you will have to excuse me if this topic has been discussed recently/lately and I sort of &quot;re-opened&quot; the discussion again.
Second of all you will have to excuse me if this isn&#39;t the right section.

So...

I&#39;ve been waiting for AGGGEEEEEEESSSSSS (You&#39;re not the only guy waiting, so stop this!) for black mesa to get released.

Basically because I loved the first part, and then after because I want to redevelop  :lambda: L2dm maps in bm form, since I like to map even if it wasn&#39;t that good of a map at the end, I continue updating it, BECAUSE I ENJOY IT.

So, if this has been answered already, then you&#39;ll have to excuse me, and if you are getting tired of the word excuse, then you will have to excuse me.

[i][b]How much percent is done for the final product?[/b][/i]

I don&#39;t mean to sound offensive but I know that the BM team does NOT want to disappoint their huge fanbase &amp; valve, and because of that they want to produce their product in the ultimate form then update it casually,

But... I really hope you&#39;re not overexaggerating your expectations.

Too much time &amp; work can lead to loss of interest, unless there are other side plans that you are not showing on the surface.

I&#39;d rather get everyday change (update) for the game rather than waiting for a beautiful conclusion, but that just might be my opinion.


Thanks.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2015 21:03:47 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>The Cafeteria</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/soooooo/13703.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Soooooo...</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Bulik]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="ShogoMoe">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 ShogoMoe:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Helloooooo<br>
I’d rather get everyday change (update) for the game rather than waiting for a beautiful conclusion, but that just might be my opinion.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I’d be careful what you wish for.  Take a few recent game releases as an example (ACU, etc.), and even some early access stuff.  It seems better to have a fully polished product out of the gate than the alternative, especially for a “AAA indie” game like this.  Either way, it’ll be done when it’s done.  More than that, nobody can say (At least, to the public).</p>
<p>Do keep making those updates though, Chon!  Really good to have some insight to what’s cooking under our radar.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/soooooo/13703/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/soooooo/13703/3</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2015 21:03:47 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13703-3</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/soooooo/13703.rss">Soooooo...</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Soooooo...</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[TextFAMGUY1]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>The team is in full throttle. We’re as eager to get the game out there as you are. We don’t do percentages or estimates as we’ve made that mistake before.</p>
<p>It’s coming. For sure. Don’t worry about that. The Steam Release won’t be the end either, there’ll be plenty of free updates and changes after that, too.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/soooooo/13703/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/soooooo/13703/2</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2015 17:31:32 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13703-2</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/soooooo/13703.rss">Soooooo...</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Soooooo...</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Humam]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Helloooooo</p>
<p>First of all you will have to excuse me if this topic has been discussed recently/lately and I sort of “re-opened” the discussion again.<br>
Second of all you will have to excuse me if this isn’t the right section.</p>
<p>So…</p>
<p>I’ve been waiting for AGGGEEEEEEESSSSSS (You’re not the only guy waiting, so stop this!) for black mesa to get released.</p>
<p>Basically because I loved the first part, and then after because I want to redevelop  :lambda: L2dm maps in bm form, since I like to map even if it wasn’t that good of a map at the end, I continue updating it, BECAUSE I ENJOY IT.</p>
<p>So, if this has been answered already, then you’ll have to excuse me, and if you are getting tired of the word excuse, then you will have to excuse me.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-i"><span class="bbcode-b">How much percent is done for the final product?</span></span></p>
<p>I don’t mean to sound offensive but I know that the BM team does NOT want to disappoint their huge fanbase &amp; valve, and because of that they want to produce their product in the ultimate form then update it casually,</p>
<p>But… I really hope you’re not overexaggerating your expectations.</p>
<p>Too much time &amp; work can lead to loss of interest, unless there are other side plans that you are not showing on the surface.</p>
<p>I’d rather get everyday change (update) for the game rather than waiting for a beautiful conclusion, but that just might be my opinion.</p>
<p>Thanks.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/soooooo/13703/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/soooooo/13703/1</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2015 17:13:49 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13703-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/soooooo/13703.rss">Soooooo...</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
