<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Lighting issues and immediate crash at bm_c1a4e</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/lighting-issues-and-immediate-crash-at-bm-c1a4e/10844</link>
    <description>I&#39;ve had issues with my game in regards to the flashlight being on inside the offices (when you come off the elevator to the electrical wire dangling about). Now that I&#39;ve cleared out the missile Silo and proceeded down, I cannot look down at all unless I wish for the game to crash instantly for doing so. Bbefore I had issues with the lighting so I assume it may be that, or it could be a texture error with whatever is down there at the bottom of the silo or in the water.

Any known fixes for any of these?
I&#39;m also running in an SLI configuration for anyone asking for hardware.
EDIT: I disabled SLI and tried to head down the Silo, error occurred.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 20 Sep 2012 11:18:21 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>In-game Issues (Mod)</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/lighting-issues-and-immediate-crash-at-bm-c1a4e/10844.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Lighting issues and immediate crash at bm_c1a4e</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[lexa2]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Could you please elaborate more on your hardware and software config? “I have SLI-enabled setup” is just not enough to really be able to give you any advice.</p>
<p>You mention flashlight-related problems. What exactly problems they were? Had you fixed them in any way? Also, had you read the sticky FAQ thread? If you’ve got SLI-based setup with older nVIDIA cards from 7xxx series - there’s a known driver bug, you would have to fallback into 28x.xx series of the driver (or even earlier - you would have to test what works best for you).</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/lighting-issues-and-immediate-crash-at-bm-c1a4e/10844/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/lighting-issues-and-immediate-crash-at-bm-c1a4e/10844/2</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 20 Sep 2012 11:18:21 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-10844-2</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/lighting-issues-and-immediate-crash-at-bm-c1a4e/10844.rss">Lighting issues and immediate crash at bm_c1a4e</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Lighting issues and immediate crash at bm_c1a4e</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[DesuTroyah]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I’ve had issues with my game in regards to the flashlight being on inside the offices (when you come off the elevator to the electrical wire dangling about). Now that I’ve cleared out the missile Silo and proceeded down, I cannot look down at all unless I wish for the game to crash instantly for doing so. Bbefore I had issues with the lighting so I assume it may be that, or it could be a texture error with whatever is down there at the bottom of the silo or in the water.</p>
<p>Any known fixes for any of these?<br>
I’m also running in an SLI configuration for anyone asking for hardware.<br>
EDIT: I disabled SLI and tried to head down the Silo, error occurred.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/lighting-issues-and-immediate-crash-at-bm-c1a4e/10844/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/lighting-issues-and-immediate-crash-at-bm-c1a4e/10844/1</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 19 Sep 2012 18:04:29 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-10844-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/lighting-issues-and-immediate-crash-at-bm-c1a4e/10844.rss">Lighting issues and immediate crash at bm_c1a4e</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
