<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>HeadCrab Spawning Bug</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/headcrab-spawning-bug/12541</link>
    <description>So, I was playing and eventually got to the part in &quot;Unforeseen Concequences&quot; where you go down a lift and some HeadCrabs start spawning above you and fall on you. Well, after activating the lift, I saw there was a Health device inside the office right in front of the lift, so I jumped off it and went to the office to get my free health. Then, I dropped down to the lift and started to wait for the HeadCrabs to spawn, but they didn&#39;t. I&#39;m guessing they only spawn if you stay on the lift at all times, right?</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 08 Sep 2013 03:19:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>In-game Issues (Mod)</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/headcrab-spawning-bug/12541.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>HeadCrab Spawning Bug</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Antidermis]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>So, I was playing and eventually got to the part in “Unforeseen Concequences” where you go down a lift and some HeadCrabs start spawning above you and fall on you. Well, after activating the lift, I saw there was a Health device inside the office right in front of the lift, so I jumped off it and went to the office to get my free health. Then, I dropped down to the lift and started to wait for the HeadCrabs to spawn, but they didn’t. I’m guessing they only spawn if you stay on the lift at all times, right?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/headcrab-spawning-bug/12541/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/headcrab-spawning-bug/12541/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 08 Sep 2013 03:19:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12541-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/headcrab-spawning-bug/12541.rss">HeadCrab Spawning Bug</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
