<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>dxlevel</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/dxlevel/13837</link>
    <description>Loving the new Steam release so far but had a question or two.  I usually use Steam library to add launch options like +mat_dxlevel 98 but when I use it on BMS it never shows up in the advanced video options.  I tried using -dxlevel 98 but that didn&#39;t work either.  I tried 95 instead of 98 for both and still no success.  I tried to add the command to autoexec.cfg with no success either.  Clearly this is operator error.  The game works fine on dxlevel 90 but I would like to force to 98 like I&#39;ve been able to do with any other Source title.
I have to disagree with the day one performance fix.  I forced my embedded graphics card instead of the integrated card and forced triple buffering.  I didn&#39;t enable the FPS counter in the console but there was a clear performance boost even with all advanced options ticked.  Easily getting 4x FPS with no more audio stutter.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 06 May 2015 15:00:11 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Help!</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/dxlevel/13837.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>dxlevel</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Larz1695]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Loving the new Steam release so far but had a question or two.  I usually use Steam library to add launch options like +mat_dxlevel 98 but when I use it on BMS it never shows up in the advanced video options.  I tried using -dxlevel 98 but that didn’t work either.  I tried 95 instead of 98 for both and still no success.  I tried to add the command to autoexec.cfg with no success either.  Clearly this is operator error.  The game works fine on dxlevel 90 but I would like to force to 98 like I’ve been able to do with any other Source title.<br>
I have to disagree with the day one performance fix.  I forced my embedded graphics card instead of the integrated card and forced triple buffering.  I didn’t enable the FPS counter in the console but there was a clear performance boost even with all advanced options ticked.  Easily getting 4x FPS with no more audio stutter.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/dxlevel/13837/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/dxlevel/13837/1</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 06 May 2015 15:00:11 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13837-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/dxlevel/13837.rss">dxlevel</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
