<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Second Garg &amp; Tactical Map</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/second-garg-tactical-map/11307</link>
    <description>I&#39;ve played up to the end of Surface Tension, and I just played through the part from the vent-shooting to the tactical map. What really struck me how the game really changed at this point, quality-wise.

Many things happened simultaneously:

1. The soldiers shoot the vent, and it sort of crumbles in a quite unrealistic way
1. You expect the soldiers to keep shooting you, yet you find a Garg shooting them instead, what? Where was that giant monster just 2 seconds ago?
1. The garg starts chasing you, and kind of just walks through cars that explode, it&#39;s almost impossible to see that it&#39;s actually pushing them to the side at all, in HL1 this was quite spectacular, here it&#39;s just a bit messy and weird
1. The framerate drops to like 5fps (the rest of the game was smooth as butter)
1. You exit the tunnel and you arrive to the outdoor area, at which point I quickly hid in the water
1. What do I see? The garg attacking one of the towers and ignoring me... WTF?
1. Then I realized that you&#39;re supposed to climb that tower, of course… but the Garg is scripted to attack the tower, regardless of whether you&#39;re on it or not
1. The tactical map was a pain in the ***: you can barely see what&#39;s on it, and it took me ages to figure out that I was meant to click with the mouse to set a point, instead of using the &quot;Use&quot; key. Not to mention the whole thing is vibrating as the Garg attacks the whole tower, and the frame rate is at 5fps.


Did anyone else feel like this part was quite poor quality, especially compared to the very high level of detail of the rest of the game?</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 09 Oct 2012 01:00:35 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>The Cafeteria</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/second-garg-tactical-map/11307.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Second Garg &amp; Tactical Map</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[UnhingedMouse0]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Another thing that I found weird about this section, is that I could actually push cars around when I was running through the tunnel, like they weighed no more than a normal wooden crate or something. I suppose this was so the garg can kick them about, but it’s awkward. I’d rather have it completely scripted as to where he hits them and where they go and not have the player be able to move them.</p>
<p>I agree with all the other points raised as well.</p>
<p>Yeah Bjossi, that really bothered me. Another place I noticed this, (at least I think so, I only checked quickly so maybe I’m mistaken) was when you enter the building to launch the rocket. You go up the ladder behind the servers, or whatever they are, but if you turn around, the hatch you just came through is mysteriously gone and there is just floor there. Ummm, WHAT?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/second-garg-tactical-map/11307/37">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/second-garg-tactical-map/11307/37</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 09 Oct 2012 01:00:35 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11307-37</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/second-garg-tactical-map/11307.rss">Second Garg &amp; Tactical Map</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Second Garg &amp; Tactical Map</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[JezMM]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I too dived straight in the water and was killed by the Garg pretty easily when I FINALLY managed to get close enough to notice the ladder on the tower.  I couldn’t beat the section without retrying back to the start of the chase, which… isn’t that much time but the amount of time I spent exploring the water and non-garg areas made it feel annoying.</p>
<p>Altogether I do think the section to be reworked.  I know once you’re up on the tower the Garg doesn’t attack you, but I think it would be a better payoff if there was an earlier section where we have to use an airstrike panel.</p>
<p>I do imagine it’d be awesome to be introduced to the airstrikes seperately and just be all “oh that was neat”, and then shortly after, the Garg chase happens and you find another panel, and right away you’re like “…AWESOME 8D” when you realise the implications.  I also wonder if I would have “got” the airstrike panel for the first time under pressure like that if I wasn’t already familiar with the concept from HL1.</p>
<p>Funnily enough I didn’t even notice the jump pad either.  I wasn’t even aware BM had them, and since I’m not a HL1 buff I forgot they even existed until I replayed HL: Source the other day to compare with my BM experience.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/second-garg-tactical-map/11307/36">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/second-garg-tactical-map/11307/36</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 08 Oct 2012 20:50:54 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11307-36</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/second-garg-tactical-map/11307.rss">Second Garg &amp; Tactical Map</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Second Garg &amp; Tactical Map</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Bjossi]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I agree with pretty much everything in the original post, and I want to add my own two unimportant things that I noticed:</p>
<ol>
<li>
<p>There is an invisible wall that prevents you from going back into the garage you ran out of with the Garg behind you earlier. While I knew pretty well by then that the BM level designers hate backtracking with a passion by magically closing doors and gates behind Gordon’s every other step when there is no enemy alive to do so, this one time the level designer didn’t even bother to create a sensible obstacle, it is just an invisible wall that prevents you from going where you were minutes earlier. Why not make the ceiling crash down or maybe have the Garg leave a car in the way? If you’re going to arbitrarily prevent the player from visiting old areas if s/he so wishes, the least you can do is give a good reason for it being impossible to go back.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>The mortar effects are awfully unimpressive. HL1’s was far louder and more fun to watch/hear. In general the explosives in BM are absolutely <span class="bbcode-b"><span class="bbcode-i">horrible</span></span>, aesthetically speaking. There is no punch to the explosion sounds whatsoever, but in this scene it hit me the hardest. I see this point as a strange anomaly because literally everything else sounds great, guns, ambience…</p>
</li>
</ol>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/second-garg-tactical-map/11307/35">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/second-garg-tactical-map/11307/35</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 06 Oct 2012 23:37:03 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11307-35</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/second-garg-tactical-map/11307.rss">Second Garg &amp; Tactical Map</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Second Garg &amp; Tactical Map</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[AWildHeadcrabAppears]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>If you look out the grating on the side of the vent as the soldiers shoot it, you can see the Garg prying open the doors behind them. Though I do agree that it was a jarring transition between the snark vent part to the Garg fight.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/second-garg-tactical-map/11307/34">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/second-garg-tactical-map/11307/34</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 06 Oct 2012 22:31:23 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11307-34</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/second-garg-tactical-map/11307.rss">Second Garg &amp; Tactical Map</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Second Garg &amp; Tactical Map</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[k3nny1550]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Yeah, probably should just use an OnTouching output trigger for the top of the tower to trigger the scripted_sequence for the Garg shake.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/second-garg-tactical-map/11307/33">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/second-garg-tactical-map/11307/33</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 06 Oct 2012 21:11:54 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11307-33</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/second-garg-tactical-map/11307.rss">Second Garg &amp; Tactical Map</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Second Garg &amp; Tactical Map</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[jesse1994]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Yeah, like maybe have the guard attack the tower only if you’re on it</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/second-garg-tactical-map/11307/32">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/second-garg-tactical-map/11307/32</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 06 Oct 2012 20:07:49 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11307-32</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/second-garg-tactical-map/11307.rss">Second Garg &amp; Tactical Map</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Second Garg &amp; Tactical Map</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[RossBondReturns]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Duzftz9wZYo" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Duzftz9wZYo</a></p>
<p>Recorded last night with headphones on. On my Compaq Presario as a comparative video to the one from my actual Let’s Play of the same segment in my Let’s Play.</p>
<p>Pretty much my cleanest run of that segment yet. Still have yet to have the targetting screen glitch on me.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/second-garg-tactical-map/11307/31">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/second-garg-tactical-map/11307/31</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 06 Oct 2012 18:37:32 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11307-31</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/second-garg-tactical-map/11307.rss">Second Garg &amp; Tactical Map</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Second Garg &amp; Tactical Map</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Ibanez]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I don’t get why they didn’t use the Xen jump pads more than the one time in Forget about Freeman…</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/second-garg-tactical-map/11307/30">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/second-garg-tactical-map/11307/30</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 06 Oct 2012 18:21:50 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11307-30</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/second-garg-tactical-map/11307.rss">Second Garg &amp; Tactical Map</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Second Garg &amp; Tactical Map</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[GordonReturns]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I always thought the soldiers heard you rumbling around in the vent and when you make that drop that makes a nice audible thunk, they start shooting.  You could argue that in the original, the soldiers “magically” heard you and started shooting everything.  Then Mr. Garg knocked on the doors and plows over the soldiers.  I ran like hell and ran straight to the tower because I played the original, then took a few seconds to figure out the map and killed him before he even got to humping the tower.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/second-garg-tactical-map/11307/29">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/second-garg-tactical-map/11307/29</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 06 Oct 2012 18:10:49 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11307-29</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/second-garg-tactical-map/11307.rss">Second Garg &amp; Tactical Map</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Second Garg &amp; Tactical Map</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[k3nny1550]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I just used a Xen jump pad to get up to the tower and nuke the Garg.</p>
<p>EDIT: ^ In the original HL. BM has a ladder on the tower, I just booked it up that and spent about a minute fumbling with the touch screen while the Garg shaked the tower with me on it.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/second-garg-tactical-map/11307/28">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/second-garg-tactical-map/11307/28</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 06 Oct 2012 17:44:10 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11307-28</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/second-garg-tactical-map/11307.rss">Second Garg &amp; Tactical Map</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Second Garg &amp; Tactical Map</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Unit24]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Gregorovich!">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Gregorovich!:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>The main problem with the Garg, IMO, is that in the original, you had to run down into the water, with him following you, and quickly climb up the ladder, race back to the tower and call a mortar strike on him before he got up the ramp leading to the tower. But this time, all you have to do is jump up onto the tower and click on him.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Actually, you didn’t have to run into the water in the original. I never did that and still managed to beat him.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/second-garg-tactical-map/11307/27">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/second-garg-tactical-map/11307/27</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 06 Oct 2012 12:41:08 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11307-27</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/second-garg-tactical-map/11307.rss">Second Garg &amp; Tactical Map</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Second Garg &amp; Tactical Map</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Gregorovich]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>The main problem with the Garg, IMO, is that in the original, you had to run down into the water, with him following you, and quickly climb up the ladder, race back to the tower and call a mortar strike on him before he got up the ramp leading to the tower. But this time, all you have to do is jump up onto the tower and click on him.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/second-garg-tactical-map/11307/26">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/second-garg-tactical-map/11307/26</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 06 Oct 2012 10:54:24 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11307-26</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/second-garg-tactical-map/11307.rss">Second Garg &amp; Tactical Map</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Second Garg &amp; Tactical Map</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Chickenprotector]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Artic Xiongmao">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Artic Xiongmao:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>They heard it coming? Unless it’s supposed to have teleported into the room, it does not make sense. They shoot at you, and literally two seconds later the Garg is right next to the soldiers.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Actually, if you look to your left out the vent while the soldiers are shooting it, you can see the Garg forcing open the doors behind it in the scene.</p>
<p>I did experience FPS drops while outside, no where else, beyond that I went straight for the tower, but I decided to climb the ladder on the other side of the jump pad… wasn’t all that visible.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/second-garg-tactical-map/11307/25">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/second-garg-tactical-map/11307/25</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 06 Oct 2012 10:20:27 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11307-25</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/second-garg-tactical-map/11307.rss">Second Garg &amp; Tactical Map</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Second Garg &amp; Tactical Map</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[elivance]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Hi<br>
+1 for another who thought that diving in that sewer was a good idea,<br>
then I got back and I saw the Garg shaking that tower…<br>
A real anti-climax moment…</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/second-garg-tactical-map/11307/24">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/second-garg-tactical-map/11307/24</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 06 Oct 2012 08:37:30 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11307-24</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/second-garg-tactical-map/11307.rss">Second Garg &amp; Tactical Map</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Second Garg &amp; Tactical Map</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Marb]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>+1 for another who thought jumping in the water was a good idea… “SWIMMING STRICTLY FORBIDDEN.” Duh, what was I thinking :retard:<br>
After playing a little flame-tag (and losing), I reloaded and got through just fine the second time.</p>
<p>The tactical map was very glitchy for me and hard to use.  And I too didn’t initially realize it was supposed to be “fired,” instead of “used.”</p>
<p>I’m kind of surprised that this was the only instance in the game thus far when your fire button disconnects from whatever weapon that you’re holding.  It wouldn’t have been such an issue if there were other interfaces in the game where this sort of mechanism took place.  You know, like computer terminals or other things like that.  Or some sort of visual clue would have been nice, like the crosshair changing in some way.  Or maybe even having to “use” the map and then get into firing mode, similar to the 50cal or TOW.</p>
<p>The “disconnect from weapon-in-hand” mode is kind of a cool feature though, if used correctly. It could potentially be put to good use in other parts of the game as well where direct fighting isn’t involved.</p>
<p>As for the map itself: subsequent playthroughs resulted in the tactical map working normal with no glitchiness at all.  Also, I too was disappointed at nothing else being destroyable with the strikes.  All in all, I still enjoyed this part of the mod very much.</p>
<p>EDIT: Wait, I just realized I had the crowbar equipped every time I used the tactical map for fear of firing off on it… I don’t actually know whether the crosshair changes or not <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/confused.png?v=9" title=":confused:" class="emoji" alt=":confused:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/second-garg-tactical-map/11307/23">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/second-garg-tactical-map/11307/23</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 06 Oct 2012 07:19:49 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11307-23</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/second-garg-tactical-map/11307.rss">Second Garg &amp; Tactical Map</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Second Garg &amp; Tactical Map</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[warpedfreeman]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>i knew what to do with the tactical map because i read the change for a mortar in the BM Wiki many moths ago  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=9" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:">  although when you r in the tower there is a shake that is little anoying but is fine cause it should not be easy to target the garg</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/second-garg-tactical-map/11307/22">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/second-garg-tactical-map/11307/22</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2012 22:35:18 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11307-22</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/second-garg-tactical-map/11307.rss">Second Garg &amp; Tactical Map</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Second Garg &amp; Tactical Map</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[eligitine]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I kinda had an interesting experience. As soon as I heard soldiers, I chucked a few grenades through the vents, killing the soldiers. That triggered the garg to break through and start rampaging around. When I got to the vent, it was still <em>shot</em> by something, and I had the unique experience of the garg being already at the end of the chase, waiting for me.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/second-garg-tactical-map/11307/21">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/second-garg-tactical-map/11307/21</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2012 22:06:15 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11307-21</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/second-garg-tactical-map/11307.rss">Second Garg &amp; Tactical Map</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Second Garg &amp; Tactical Map</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[TextFAMGUY1]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Yeah I agree - Surface Tension was the least well done part of the game for me. The parts which were good, were really good. The vent shooting and the Garg chase was just awkward. It worked fine if you played it as intended - not looking back, going straight up the tower. But I jumped in the water, and the Garg just started attacking the tower. It was certainly an awkward scene.</p>
<p>If they were able to fix it up a bit for their steam update it could have a lot of potential to be really exciting. There also need to be way more scripted fights between the HECU and the aliens, so we can see them losing and thus having a reason to pull out. This Garg chase is a good place to start. Perhaps you could be legging it alongside loads of other marines also running away from the Garg. Kind of like in HL2 in Nova Prospekt where the mother Antlion appears, and you and the Combine briefly forget your differences and try to kill it. It could be like that - you’re running away for dear life alongside them, and they’re being crushed and killed all around you while you’re all trying to get away. Could be a very exciting and poignant scene.</p>
<p>Oh and the monitor was really glitchy for me too.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/second-garg-tactical-map/11307/20">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/second-garg-tactical-map/11307/20</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2012 21:13:45 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11307-20</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/second-garg-tactical-map/11307.rss">Second Garg &amp; Tactical Map</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Second Garg &amp; Tactical Map</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Artic_Xiongmao]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>They heard it coming? Unless it’s supposed to have teleported into the room, it does not make sense. They shoot at you, and literally two seconds later the Garg is right next to the soldiers.</p>
<p>But anyway. It’s not only about making sense; mostly, it is about pacing. The vent shooting should feel like its own great little scene, instead of being instantly overshadowed by the chase scene.</p>
<p>And again, the garg chase (mostly because of its music) overshadows the iconic “Forget about Freeman!” line.</p>
<p>It’s just… strange pacing throughout that section.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/second-garg-tactical-map/11307/19">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/second-garg-tactical-map/11307/19</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2012 19:50:11 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11307-19</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/second-garg-tactical-map/11307.rss">Second Garg &amp; Tactical Map</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Second Garg &amp; Tactical Map</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[FERGUS]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Did you people never look towards where the bullets come from? The Garg breaks up the door behind the marines as soon as they start shooting. They didn’t know he was there.</p>
<p>Though, it doesn’t take away the feeling that the garg hunt was sort of an anticlimax.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/second-garg-tactical-map/11307/18">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/second-garg-tactical-map/11307/18</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2012 19:47:56 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11307-18</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/second-garg-tactical-map/11307.rss">Second Garg &amp; Tactical Map</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Second Garg &amp; Tactical Map</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Xeoxer]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I shat a brick when I saw the garg breaking through the door, then I ran like hell without looking back, then I used the trampoline-like thing to jump up the tower (instead of hiding in water, like almost all other ppl) then I tried to break the wall and the door like in HL, but then it turned out you must only destroy the pillar and open the door by hand -.- I had framedrop here as well.</p>
<p>Maybe the soldiers heard something moving inside the vent and shot at it, but then they suddenly heard garg coming and they focused on a larger threat ;p that kinda makes sense.</p>
<p>This section is one of the best twists from original HL, where player expects to fall to the garage with some soldiers instead of fucking garg, and thet’s why it’s so shocking. I didn’t look back at garg, so I didn’t see the clipping glitches, but only because I played it like the devs expected it to be played. So it should be corrected a bit.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/second-garg-tactical-map/11307/17">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/second-garg-tactical-map/11307/17</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2012 18:48:27 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11307-17</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/second-garg-tactical-map/11307.rss">Second Garg &amp; Tactical Map</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Second Garg &amp; Tactical Map</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Dr_Karamazov]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I experienced no frame rate drop, so I guess it’s purely down to individual systems.</p>
<p>I also did the same thing as OP and ran past the tower.  When I turned around he was hammering it.  It was pretty amusing.<br>
So I decided that I may as well try and climb it since that was obviously where I was supposed to be…and then he one shotted me.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/second-garg-tactical-map/11307/16">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/second-garg-tactical-map/11307/16</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2012 10:18:36 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11307-16</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/second-garg-tactical-map/11307.rss">Second Garg &amp; Tactical Map</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Second Garg &amp; Tactical Map</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Ronster]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I think they should keep it like it was in half life… They have to do bug fixing in the map files anyway they should just try to update the maps now with the missing content.</p>
<p>It’s really only a small amount in the game that is missing.</p>
<p>I am glad they released what they had… But the beauty of modding is they can expand it and improve it all they want.</p>
<p>surface tension should be restored to it’s former glory… On a rail perhaps a little exapnsion here but not much an extra track and junction would do.</p>
<p>Nissing content from office complex like the zombie behind the door and the big fan that chops up the headcrabs and the scene with the alien grunt pulling the doors open in lambda core should also be in.</p>
<p>It’s actually not all that much that got dropped. I am sure they can find and recruit mappers / animation scripters to work on these parts now the mod is hugely successfull</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/second-garg-tactical-map/11307/15">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/second-garg-tactical-map/11307/15</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2012 08:27:14 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11307-15</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/second-garg-tactical-map/11307.rss">Second Garg &amp; Tactical Map</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Second Garg &amp; Tactical Map</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[k3nny1550]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>If I get the BM SDK set up sometime this century, I’ll try decompiling the garg map to look at the entity work in it. I have an idea about tweaking the vent shot scene. I’d add the garage sequence back in but modify it so that the garg tunnel is relatively close to the garage workshop. Perhaps the shooting sequence would take place after the player has moved through most of the air vent, and instead of the bottom falling out the duct splits and the player falls backwards into the garage to add to the disorienting feeling.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/second-garg-tactical-map/11307/14">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/second-garg-tactical-map/11307/14</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2012 05:51:28 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11307-14</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/second-garg-tactical-map/11307.rss">Second Garg &amp; Tactical Map</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Second Garg &amp; Tactical Map</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Artic_Xiongmao]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Lemonz&amp;oranges">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Lemonz&amp;oranges:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>and i agree the HECU soldiers didnt have logical consistancy in that scene</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>That is my main concern. Make those events separate, in two different sections. Not only will it flow better, it will make SENSE. In HL you heard the soldiers first, and the vents made a lot of sound… so they shot at it. In the current version, what is happening exactly? “Oh, look, we have a loud, big Garg right here trying to kill us… wait a sec, we have magically noticed there’s someone inside that vent… why don’t we focus on that and then completely forget about it two seconds later?”</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/second-garg-tactical-map/11307/13">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/second-garg-tactical-map/11307/13</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 03 Oct 2012 23:18:57 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11307-13</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/second-garg-tactical-map/11307.rss">Second Garg &amp; Tactical Map</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
