<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Power Up - Indifferent Gargantua</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/power-up-indifferent-gargantua/9865</link>
    <description>At the start of Power Up, after the soldiers are dead, the Gargantua comes to the doorway and refuses to move. If I&#39;m in just the right place, he may flame the hallway (cool effect btw, thanks for that), but generally he&#39;s pretty indifferent to me.

In fact, I can&#39;t get right in his face while he just stands there.

[url]https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=96400707[/url]

Sometimes I can even whack him on the nose with my crowbar without any retaliation.

It appears as though he&#39;s blocking the doorway so I was afraid to approach, and I assumed that some AI behavior would cause him to move and provide an opportunity to pass, but he didn&#39;t move and I just cautiously approached.

If he keeps this up, I may put a leash on him, give him a treat, and take him for a walk.

..Easy difficulty. Maybe too easy.

Perhaps the level AI thought process is that I will have entered the room before the marines die, but that was not the case. As you can see in the screenshot (barely), GMan hasn&#39;t even left yet.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 15 Sep 2012 23:32:22 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>In-game Issues (Mod)</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/power-up-indifferent-gargantua/9865.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Power Up - Indifferent Gargantua</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[ArleeJ]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Searching for a solution to what I thought was a bug where I could not kill Gargantua kept bringing me to this thread. My issue was an issue with not completing all the tasks, after forum searching I dug up this <a href="https://forums.blackmesasource.com/showthread.php?t=12918" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">post</a> which solved the whole thing.</p>
<p>(Sorry it’s not 100% Related, I just spent 45min looking for a solution, hopefully this will save half an hour for someone else.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/power-up-indifferent-gargantua/9865/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/power-up-indifferent-gargantua/9865/8</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 15 Sep 2012 23:32:22 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9865-8</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/power-up-indifferent-gargantua/9865.rss">Power Up - Indifferent Gargantua</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Power Up - Indifferent Gargantua</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[xplodwild]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Same here. Upon arriving in the first hallway, he blocked the door, waiting for me. I tried to move around, throw some grenades, he’d whistle a bit but stay here. I rushed on the opposite side of the room, lost quite some health, but made it.</p>
<p>Then after doing my job around to bring on power, when I returned he was staying in front of the big tunnel that leads to the place where you have to kill him. He wouldn’t move from there either, once again I sprinted as fast as I could, he hit me a bit, but that was the only way. Then, arrived on the console, I noticed I had to plug the two cords. I went down the ladder, and he started to fire right between the two plugs, right in front of the ladder, and it would never stop until he made me some damages (it’s like he starts and stops ONLY when it deals 60HP to you).<br>
I had full health and full energy, only 20 health after all of this, and I’m not sure I beat it the way it’s supposed to be beaten, but there is definitely some AI flaws here.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/power-up-indifferent-gargantua/9865/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/power-up-indifferent-gargantua/9865/7</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 15 Sep 2012 21:20:22 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9865-7</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/power-up-indifferent-gargantua/9865.rss">Power Up - Indifferent Gargantua</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Power Up - Indifferent Gargantua</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[spawner]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>agreed</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/power-up-indifferent-gargantua/9865/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/power-up-indifferent-gargantua/9865/6</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 15 Sep 2012 20:36:48 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9865-6</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/power-up-indifferent-gargantua/9865.rss">Power Up - Indifferent Gargantua</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Power Up - Indifferent Gargantua</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[OCDMonkey]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>what I found annoying is that first, it took me a while to find out why I couldn’t press the button to blow him up, and before that I actually had to work to lead him into the room (I guess I was running too fast or something, because he just left the room). I also did experience him blocking the door, as well as him refusing to move away from the tunnel leading to his death sentence (just stayed there, making it impossible for me to pass).</p>
<p>Him leaning into the doorway to try and get you though is a really cool addition. Plus the animation of him dieing was so amazing it made up for any annoyances. Actually, the Gargantua himself looks amazingly good.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/power-up-indifferent-gargantua/9865/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/power-up-indifferent-gargantua/9865/5</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 15 Sep 2012 16:20:36 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9865-5</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/power-up-indifferent-gargantua/9865.rss">Power Up - Indifferent Gargantua</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Power Up - Indifferent Gargantua</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Malidictus]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>There seems to be an AI quirk where the Gargantua will ignore the player if the player is outside of its designated area, which is the large railway crossing chamber. In the original, the Gargantua followed the player regardless of where he went, leading to a moment where he’d stand right next to the “power up” button, making it hard to press. This one appears intentionally programmed to ignore anything that isn’t in the large open space.</p>
<p>He’ll actually do the same when you go into the generator room to kill him. He’ll chase you and shoot at you while you’re downstairs, but as soon as you climb up the ladder, he ignores you. You can walk up to the railing and stick your tongue out to him - nothing. You can stand on top of the console in full view and in line of fire - nothing. He’ll only shoot at you if you inch ahead far enough to be in his “chamber,” technically.</p>
<p>This does make the encounter SIGNIFICANTLY easier since the thing will ignore you most of the time, but it also makes it very non-threatening.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/power-up-indifferent-gargantua/9865/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/power-up-indifferent-gargantua/9865/4</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 15 Sep 2012 15:30:25 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9865-4</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/power-up-indifferent-gargantua/9865.rss">Power Up - Indifferent Gargantua</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Power Up - Indifferent Gargantua</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[RiscIt]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Getting past him isn’t a problem. There’s ample space between him and the door frame and he doesn’t deal much damage. I’m more concerned that I can stand there and whack him with a crowbar and he doesn’t even react.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/power-up-indifferent-gargantua/9865/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/power-up-indifferent-gargantua/9865/3</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 15 Sep 2012 15:23:25 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9865-3</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/power-up-indifferent-gargantua/9865.rss">Power Up - Indifferent Gargantua</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Power Up - Indifferent Gargantua</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Nolife_Demon]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I just made a thread about the exact same issue, I just found a solution though, If you run back around the corner and wait a moment he will walk off, you then need to sprint run to the next room, you will take minor damage, but as soon as you double back into the corridor with the door he blocks he will come at the door again, this is the only current way I have found to get past him.</p>
<p>Hope this helps  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=9" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/power-up-indifferent-gargantua/9865/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/power-up-indifferent-gargantua/9865/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 15 Sep 2012 14:40:12 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9865-2</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/power-up-indifferent-gargantua/9865.rss">Power Up - Indifferent Gargantua</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Power Up - Indifferent Gargantua</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[RiscIt]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>At the start of Power Up, after the soldiers are dead, the Gargantua comes to the doorway and refuses to move. If I’m in just the right place, he may flame the hallway (cool effect btw, thanks for that), but generally he’s pretty indifferent to me.</p>
<p>In fact, I can’t get right in his face while he just stands there.</p>
<p><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=96400707" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=96400707</a></p>
<p>Sometimes I can even whack him on the nose with my crowbar without any retaliation.</p>
<p>It appears as though he’s blocking the doorway so I was afraid to approach, and I assumed that some AI behavior would cause him to move and provide an opportunity to pass, but he didn’t move and I just cautiously approached.</p>
<p>If he keeps this up, I may put a leash on him, give him a treat, and take him for a walk.</p>
<p>…Easy difficulty. Maybe too easy.</p>
<p>Perhaps the level AI thought process is that I will have entered the room before the marines die, but that was not the case. As you can see in the screenshot (barely), GMan hasn’t even left yet.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/power-up-indifferent-gargantua/9865/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/power-up-indifferent-gargantua/9865/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 15 Sep 2012 13:58:21 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9865-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/power-up-indifferent-gargantua/9865.rss">Power Up - Indifferent Gargantua</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
