<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Scientist in freezer is driving me insane.</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/scientist-in-freezer-is-driving-me-insane/13263</link>
    <description>I like how the source engine brings so much interaction with the environment yet the mod tries to limit player interactions.

I started playing trough the mod yet again and this time I decided to try to save as much people as possible I managed to save 3 barneys and 1 scientist and then I saw a scientist in the freezer in the office complex. I tried interacting with the scientist and make her follow me so I can rescue her too but she didn&#39;t do anything. I met scientists like this in the mod before but they at least told me they were too scared to go and would prefer to stay and wait while this one just asked me if there were any safe places to get away from the monsters and then nothing else.


 So there she was not doing anything and it was like the game was telling me that for some reason Gordon did not want to talk to the scientist and I had no control over that even though the game didn&#39;t tell me that I should not bother since the scientist didn&#39;t say anything about staying there and waiting and my character was silent for no reason which drives me mad because in the original half-life you could interact with them and they would follow.

 And yes I do understand that when a person doesn&#39;t want to come with me I shouldn&#39;t expect a reaction but she didn&#39;t say that she doesn&#39;t want to come and I felt my character was being a prick not helping the scientist against his own will.

You could at least give her a line to say like &quot;Now that you have dealt with the monsters I think I would stay here&quot; or &quot;Can you leave me alone&quot; and I will at least understand why she won&#39;t come.

Or if you are scared that players will just tell her to follow and then go trough the vents where it&#39;s un accessible for npc&#39;s you could make her say &quot;I don&#39;t want to risk going trough there I think I&#39;ll stay here&quot; you already did something like that at the chapter &quot;forget about freeman&quot; where the guard says that he doesn&#39;t want to follow you and he will find another way.

And now I feel like the game has taken control out of my hands for no real reason than to make me mad and the scientist is just staying there won&#39;t even react when I shoot at her.

Please if you can do something about it because this is seriously breaking the immersion of this great mod. To people who don&#39;t care about the npc&#39;s this wont mean much but for a guy like me who likes interaction and wants to actually rescue them this is abysmal.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2014 12:12:22 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>The Cafeteria</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/scientist-in-freezer-is-driving-me-insane/13263.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Scientist in freezer is driving me insane.</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[MysticJ]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="snark567">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/s/bbe5ce/40.png" class="avatar"> snark567:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I do have vent crawling but as I said If the npc can’t do it they can make it so she abandons you.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>That won’t help anything.</p>
<p>Because it would still mean she is willingly staying IN THE FREEZER which has sub-zero temperature.</p>
<p>The only possible behavior that would not break immersion is for her to ask whether it is safe in the pre-freezer area, and go hide there. Otherwise, she is doomed to freeze to death.</p>
<p>You should report this as a “bug” or “wish for the final release”.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/scientist-in-freezer-is-driving-me-insane/13263/20">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/scientist-in-freezer-is-driving-me-insane/13263/20</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2014 12:12:22 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13263-20</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/scientist-in-freezer-is-driving-me-insane/13263.rss">Scientist in freezer is driving me insane.</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Scientist in freezer is driving me insane.</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Lestat_cv]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I have a sad news for you: They all die in the end, Black Mesa is destroyed by a nuclear warhead, you could not save them OP</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/scientist-in-freezer-is-driving-me-insane/13263/19">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/scientist-in-freezer-is-driving-me-insane/13263/19</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2014 18:58:46 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13263-19</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/scientist-in-freezer-is-driving-me-insane/13263.rss">Scientist in freezer is driving me insane.</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Scientist in freezer is driving me insane.</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[snark567]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="danielsangeo">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/user_avatar/leakfree.org/danielsangeo/40/4347_2.png" class="avatar"> danielsangeo:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I think the original point of this thread was that the scientist in the freezer does not have a response line as the other scientists do, not whether NPCs can follow you through obstacles, the number of NPCs that can follow, or anything like that.</p>
<p>The OP wanted to know why the scientist in the freezer didn’t have any response after the NPC completed its programmed path.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Yes I still hope that some time in the future it will at least get fixed but looks like people don’t really care that much and writing more on this topic wont change a thing so I’ll just leave it at here.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/scientist-in-freezer-is-driving-me-insane/13263/18">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/scientist-in-freezer-is-driving-me-insane/13263/18</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2014 13:56:33 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13263-18</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/scientist-in-freezer-is-driving-me-insane/13263.rss">Scientist in freezer is driving me insane.</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Scientist in freezer is driving me insane.</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypt]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>It probably didn’t have a line because either the devs didn’t think to include one, thought that it’s such a minute detail and not worth recording for, or possibly even had spacial concerns.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/scientist-in-freezer-is-driving-me-insane/13263/17">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/scientist-in-freezer-is-driving-me-insane/13263/17</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2014 12:58:29 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13263-17</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/scientist-in-freezer-is-driving-me-insane/13263.rss">Scientist in freezer is driving me insane.</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Scientist in freezer is driving me insane.</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Maxey]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>It still doesn’t matter tho…</p>
<p>Ok, I’m out, sorry.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/scientist-in-freezer-is-driving-me-insane/13263/16">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/scientist-in-freezer-is-driving-me-insane/13263/16</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2014 12:51:48 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13263-16</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/scientist-in-freezer-is-driving-me-insane/13263.rss">Scientist in freezer is driving me insane.</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Scientist in freezer is driving me insane.</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[danielsangeo]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I think the original point of this thread was that the scientist in the freezer does not have a response line as the other scientists do, not whether NPCs can follow you through obstacles, the number of NPCs that can follow, or anything like that.</p>
<p>The OP wanted to know why the scientist in the freezer didn’t have any response after the NPC completed its programmed path.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/scientist-in-freezer-is-driving-me-insane/13263/15">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/scientist-in-freezer-is-driving-me-insane/13263/15</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2014 12:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13263-15</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/scientist-in-freezer-is-driving-me-insane/13263.rss">Scientist in freezer is driving me insane.</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Scientist in freezer is driving me insane.</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Maxey]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>You do realize what you’re doing is futile in the long term, right? You’ll eventually reach places where you both won’t be able to take the NPCs with you and go back to the previous chapter. Do you think the game keeps track of what the NPCs you left behind are doing? No, they’re literally wiped from memory and you don’t get a special commendation or award in the end. It literally doesn’t matter.</p>
<p>Now, do you really think the devs will give that aspect of the game any special attention? That’s likely way way on their list of priorities.</p>
<p>It’s the kind of minutae detail that concerns you because that’s all you choose to focus on but in the grand scheme of things it’s as terrible an omission as the lack of actual 3D modelled roaches, that is, not very terrible at all.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/scientist-in-freezer-is-driving-me-insane/13263/14">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/scientist-in-freezer-is-driving-me-insane/13263/14</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2014 11:39:48 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13263-14</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/scientist-in-freezer-is-driving-me-insane/13263.rss">Scientist in freezer is driving me insane.</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Scientist in freezer is driving me insane.</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[snark567]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Maxey">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/user_avatar/leakfree.org/maxey/40/4358_2.png" class="avatar"> Maxey:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>First the floating stage emitters thread and now this. What’s next? A thread asking why you can’t pee in the bathroom?</p>
<p>Are we getting invaded by the pedantic army? Get a reality check guys, this is a sci-fi action game not a scientifically correct social simulator…</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Things like this break the immersion if you are all about run and gun without giving a damn then good for you but everyone views things differently.</p>
<p>Plus it doesn’t need to be a “scientifically” correct social simulator to give the npc a simple line like “I don’t want to come” It’s like if you are working at a store and suddenly a guy comes running to you saying “Damn I had a really bad day and now I had to run away from the rain” And then he just stands there infront of you and you tell him that the stuff he want’s to buy will cost 5 dollars but he does nothing but stay like a statue until people decide to lift him up and move him outside where he will just stay there because someone forgot to “script” the interaction.</p>
<p>I realise that I sound weird when talking about this stuff but it really is annoying stuff like the guard at the surface tension where the creators didn’t think that the player will save them in time and didn’t add interactions and when you kill the sniper before he kills them the scientist just stands there doing nothing.</p>
<p>At least I hope that simple stuff like this will be fixed for the steam release.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/scientist-in-freezer-is-driving-me-insane/13263/13">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/scientist-in-freezer-is-driving-me-insane/13263/13</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2014 10:32:17 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13263-13</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/scientist-in-freezer-is-driving-me-insane/13263.rss">Scientist in freezer is driving me insane.</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Scientist in freezer is driving me insane.</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Maxey]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>First the floating stage emitters thread and now this. What’s next? A thread asking why you can’t pee in the bathroom?</p>
<p>Are we getting invaded by the pedantic army? Get a reality check guys, this is a sci-fi action game not a scientifically correct social simulator…</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/scientist-in-freezer-is-driving-me-insane/13263/12">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/scientist-in-freezer-is-driving-me-insane/13263/12</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2014 08:36:56 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13263-12</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/scientist-in-freezer-is-driving-me-insane/13263.rss">Scientist in freezer is driving me insane.</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Scientist in freezer is driving me insane.</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[snark567]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="toxyn">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/t/c6cbf5/40.png" class="avatar"> toxyn:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>How is she gonna follow you out of that hell hole anyways? don’t you have vent crawling to do after you meet her? life moves on whether you bring the lady with you or not. Its just a game yo, they probably gave her some lines in the final release anyways. I feel bad for you if you feel you should rescue them because you abandon them near an elevator shaft and they don’t say much then either. They just turn to stone.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I do have vent crawling but as I said If the npc can’t do it they can make it so she abandons you.<br>
Also as I said even though I can do the vent crawling I can easily open the door that leads to the freezer in the first place and take her to the other side and leave her then I can proceed with the vent crawling I can go to the other side and open the door for her.</p>
<p>Plus even though I leave them they would be a team of people which will increase their survival at least for a while plus maybe I just want to group all npc’s into one place.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/scientist-in-freezer-is-driving-me-insane/13263/11">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/scientist-in-freezer-is-driving-me-insane/13263/11</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2014 23:29:39 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13263-11</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/scientist-in-freezer-is-driving-me-insane/13263.rss">Scientist in freezer is driving me insane.</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Scientist in freezer is driving me insane.</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Swaggless]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="sersoft">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/user_avatar/leakfree.org/sersoft/40/5837_2.png" class="avatar"> sersoft:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Only Alyx can crawl through vents like Gordon can.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I was about to say that you never see her do that, then I remembered the first turret battle in Nova Prospekt.</p>
<p>But seriously, Snark. If this 1 scientist not talking to ruins the entirety of this awesome game for you, than you have nothing but discontent ahead of you. That’s sad. Not everything needs to be perfect, man.</p>
<p>NOTE: This isn’t to say “If you see a problem in a game, let it go!”, this is saying “Don’t get all bent out-of-shape over a minor flaw in an entire game.” The only element of BM I would consider rage-inducing is the Soldier AI, not 1 mute scientist in a feezer.[/SIZE]</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/scientist-in-freezer-is-driving-me-insane/13263/10">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/scientist-in-freezer-is-driving-me-insane/13263/10</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2014 23:14:20 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13263-10</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/scientist-in-freezer-is-driving-me-insane/13263.rss">Scientist in freezer is driving me insane.</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Scientist in freezer is driving me insane.</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[sersoft]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Only Alyx can crawl through vents like Gordon can.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/scientist-in-freezer-is-driving-me-insane/13263/9">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/scientist-in-freezer-is-driving-me-insane/13263/9</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2014 22:38:32 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13263-9</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/scientist-in-freezer-is-driving-me-insane/13263.rss">Scientist in freezer is driving me insane.</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Scientist in freezer is driving me insane.</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[RK1]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Jack Freeman">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Jack Freeman:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>You can only have four people following you at a time. You already had three security guards and one scientist.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Not true; I can distinctly remember having three scientists and two guards following me at the end of the chapter.</p>
<p>It might be that a flag got unchecked, minor 2 second fix if they do fix it. Not like it matters too much, since she can’t navigate back anyways, and she might be going into shock or something and that would be why she doesn’t respond.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/scientist-in-freezer-is-driving-me-insane/13263/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/scientist-in-freezer-is-driving-me-insane/13263/8</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2014 21:31:07 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13263-8</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/scientist-in-freezer-is-driving-me-insane/13263.rss">Scientist in freezer is driving me insane.</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Scientist in freezer is driving me insane.</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Toxyn]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>How is she gonna follow you out of that hell hole anyways? don’t you have vent crawling to do after you meet her? life moves on whether you bring the lady with you or not. Its just a game yo, they probably gave her some lines in the final release anyways. I feel bad for you if you feel you should rescue them because you abandon them near an elevator shaft and they don’t say much then either. They just turn to stone.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/scientist-in-freezer-is-driving-me-insane/13263/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/scientist-in-freezer-is-driving-me-insane/13263/7</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2014 20:53:42 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13263-7</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/scientist-in-freezer-is-driving-me-insane/13263.rss">Scientist in freezer is driving me insane.</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Scientist in freezer is driving me insane.</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[snark567]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="darkone">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/user_avatar/leakfree.org/darkone/40/4296_2.png" class="avatar"> darkone:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>you can have more then four people following you Jack.</p>
<p>A note, the freezer scientist is just to scared to follow the player… that and there is no way for them to follow the player.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>You are just making up your own stuff are you? She is scared but she says nothing about being too scared to come with me at least they could have made her say “I’m too scared to come with you” when I press E but they didn’t and she just stands there like a robot.</p>
<p><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=6ptSTogUdNw" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=6ptSTogUdNw</a></p>
<p>and that’s where the problem is if she told me that she didn’t want to follow I wouldn’t be here asking for a fix.<br>
And if you listen to her you will see that she is indeed scared and she realised that the place she is in is not safe but that’s where the conversation ends and she does nothing by the looks of it it’s like she would prefer to go with Gordon than to stay there but the game doesn’t allow for the interaction to happen.</p>
<p>And there is a way to follow If the game gave me the option I could have backtracked with her and then when I went trough the other side I would meet her again.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/scientist-in-freezer-is-driving-me-insane/13263/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/scientist-in-freezer-is-driving-me-insane/13263/6</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2014 20:20:10 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13263-6</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/scientist-in-freezer-is-driving-me-insane/13263.rss">Scientist in freezer is driving me insane.</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Scientist in freezer is driving me insane.</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[darkone]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>you can have more then four people following you Jack.</p>
<p>A note, the freezer scientist is just to scared to follow the player… that and there is no way for them to follow the player.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/scientist-in-freezer-is-driving-me-insane/13263/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/scientist-in-freezer-is-driving-me-insane/13263/5</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2014 19:25:15 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13263-5</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/scientist-in-freezer-is-driving-me-insane/13263.rss">Scientist in freezer is driving me insane.</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Scientist in freezer is driving me insane.</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[snark567]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Jack Freeman">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Jack Freeman:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>You can only have four people following you at a time. You already had three security guards and one scientist.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Actually when i found the scientist In the freezer I was alone since I made the npc’s wait.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/scientist-in-freezer-is-driving-me-insane/13263/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/scientist-in-freezer-is-driving-me-insane/13263/4</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2014 18:57:52 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13263-4</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/scientist-in-freezer-is-driving-me-insane/13263.rss">Scientist in freezer is driving me insane.</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Scientist in freezer is driving me insane.</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Jack_Freeman]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>You can only have four people following you at a time. You already had three security guards and one scientist.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/scientist-in-freezer-is-driving-me-insane/13263/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/scientist-in-freezer-is-driving-me-insane/13263/3</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2014 17:06:46 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13263-3</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/scientist-in-freezer-is-driving-me-insane/13263.rss">Scientist in freezer is driving me insane.</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Scientist in freezer is driving me insane.</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Maxey]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Please, consult a doctor to treat your ridiculous OCD.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/scientist-in-freezer-is-driving-me-insane/13263/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/scientist-in-freezer-is-driving-me-insane/13263/2</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2014 15:43:49 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13263-2</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/scientist-in-freezer-is-driving-me-insane/13263.rss">Scientist in freezer is driving me insane.</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Scientist in freezer is driving me insane.</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[snark567]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I like how the source engine brings so much interaction with the environment yet the mod tries to limit player interactions.</p>
<p>I started playing trough the mod yet again and this time I decided to try to save as much people as possible I managed to save 3 barneys and 1 scientist and then I saw a scientist in the freezer in the office complex. I tried interacting with the scientist and make her follow me so I can rescue her too but she didn’t do anything. I met scientists like this in the mod before but they at least told me they were too scared to go and would prefer to stay and wait while this one just asked me if there were any safe places to get away from the monsters and then nothing else.</p>
<p>So there she was not doing anything and it was like the game was telling me that for some reason Gordon did not want to talk to the scientist and I had no control over that even though the game didn’t tell me that I should not bother since the scientist didn’t say anything about staying there and waiting and my character was silent for no reason which drives me mad because in the original half-life you could interact with them and they would follow.</p>
<p>And yes I do understand that when a person doesn’t want to come with me I shouldn’t expect a reaction but she didn’t say that she doesn’t want to come and I felt my character was being a prick not helping the scientist against his own will.</p>
<p>You could at least give her a line to say like “Now that you have dealt with the monsters I think I would stay here” or “Can you leave me alone” and I will at least understand why she won’t come.</p>
<p>Or if you are scared that players will just tell her to follow and then go trough the vents where it’s un accessible for npc’s you could make her say “I don’t want to risk going trough there I think I’ll stay here” you already did something like that at the chapter “forget about freeman” where the guard says that he doesn’t want to follow you and he will find another way.</p>
<p>And now I feel like the game has taken control out of my hands for no real reason than to make me mad and the scientist is just staying there won’t even react when I shoot at her.</p>
<p>Please if you can do something about it because this is seriously breaking the immersion of this great mod. To people who don’t care about the npc’s this wont mean much but for a guy like me who likes interaction and wants to actually rescue them this is abysmal.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/scientist-in-freezer-is-driving-me-insane/13263/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/scientist-in-freezer-is-driving-me-insane/13263/1</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2014 14:44:07 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13263-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/scientist-in-freezer-is-driving-me-insane/13263.rss">Scientist in freezer is driving me insane.</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
