<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>About some gameplay and design choices of Black Mesa</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/about-some-gameplay-and-design-choices-of-black-mesa/11602</link>
    <description>I created this thread because there are some things I would like to comment on that really bothered me in black mesa, and perhaps may warrant some discussion.   

The first thing, and to me, the most important was the lack of introduction of new gameplay elements.  To save time, I will copy some of what I have written before.  
In all half life games, every new concept is introduced in its basic functions, and gradually shows you how to apply the concept in a new and unique way. In fact this is part of what makes half life so great for many people.
In black mesa, I believe a major problem with is it&#39;s reliance on the player&#39;s knowledge from playing hl2 or episodes, eschewing some of the sequences that introduce to the concept and allow you to become familiar with it.  It is for this reason that Im not fond of the anomalous materials sequence, especially the placement of the crowbar. Valve had already designed the pacing and progression of the gameplay to a very high standard, but talking  specifically about the crowbar, its location in bm seems to have come from the goal of changing it to surprise veterans, rather than for the actual improvement of that section.

 I&#39;ll explain:

In the beginning of the game, the tram sequence is used to allow player to familiarize himself with basic movement, offering the the player the freedom to walk around and observe, among other things. He gets off, and along the way to the test labs, he learns to interact with people, and push buttons and pick up stuff.

Shit goes down in the test lab, You push a button, you utilize the crouching and jumping abilities to navigate hazards (like evading lasers), and you move debris blocking your way. At this point in normal hl, you are introduced to the crowbar, who&#39;s basic function is to break stuff and interact with some obstacles in the environment. You use it to break a window, allowing you to pass. Only after you learn that the crowbar is used for breaking stuff, did the game throw enemies at you. 

In bm, you witness a set piece and then are forced to rely on a guard with crappy ai (or just wait and watch him die from general retardedness.) The actual area where you get the crowbar, (and you might already have a pistol,) its when you know that you will have to fight the enemies as soon as you pick it up (new players might not even know they can dislodge the crowbar between the doors an even pick it up.) This does not allow the player to experiment and become familiar with the crowbar before being forced to use it.  It also removes a lot of the interaction actual interaction before that sequence, reducing mainly to a series of set pieces or scripted events.  I personally find that needlessly boring, and even annoying, considering the amount of enemies in that area

While there are flares which one can use to light some enemies on fire, they
are not well introduced or explained, and actually aren&#39;t used at all after that sequence, which would make it seem kind of redundant.
It may sound stupid, but for new player, that subtle difference of crowbar placement can make a huge difference.  

In regards to this issue, the crowbar isn&#39;t the only example, though it is the one that sticks out the most in my mind.

Somewhat related to my previous point are some things like the crouch jumping, the charging time of the vorts, and the accuracy of the marines.  However those have been discussed in abundance, so I won&#39;t talk about those. 

The other thing that bothered me was the omitting of some of the visual design used in all the hl games.  Perhaps some areas are so detailed that just finding an objective may be difficult.  In general the problem seems to be use of green and red lights with objects which the player cannot interact with.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Nov 2012 01:47:54 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>The Cafeteria</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/about-some-gameplay-and-design-choices-of-black-mesa/11602.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>About some gameplay and design choices of Black Mesa</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[BendyBread]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="pRopaaNS">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/p/3ec8ea/40.png" class="avatar"> pRopaaNS:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Lack of atmosphere is one of BMs flaws. Thanks for pointing out one of reasons why this atmosphere was lacking.<br>
This is what I wrote in my early review:</p>
<p>So, in other words, levels weren`t organized in chronological order gameplay wise, by correctly introducing new weapons and giving environment to try out  and experiment with those weapons, which players would normallly want to do after picking up a weapon for the first time.</p>
<p>So, in that sense, we picked up magnum instead of shotgun, but after leaving area bunch of Vortigaunts spawned and mangnums slow fire rate and inablility to drop them with a single shot unless it<code>s a headshot made a bad first impression for this newly picked up gun. It wasn</code>t an appropiate situation to use this weapon and, honestly, magnum isn<code>t even suited against xen creatures, but against hecus, which is why it originally was indroduced when we were leaving blast pit. Shotgun itself was introduced right before running into literally horde of Houndeyes, whose numbers were too much to handle if you</code>re not already familiar with this gun and if you weren<code>t already expecting such a big pack of enemies there.  Could analyze all other guns as well, but I don</code>t remember that much and I don`t really have time to write all this neither.</p>
<p>p.s. and yeah, it isn<code>t just about weapons, but can be refered to other things as well. For example, as I mentioned meeting this horde of houndeyes after picking up shotgun, which was completely unexcepted and didn</code>t follow any flow.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Never thought of that, but you make an excellent point! I played HL: Source just before playing BM, so I was wondering why we got the shotgun so late. The only “worthy” Xen creature to use the magnum on is Vortigaunts, to be fair, because you want to kill them quickly as possible in my opinion since they charge so damn quickly now.</p>
<p>I did notice that though. I could easily quit the game and not go “oh maybe 30 minutes more”. It was just a “do or dont”, easy decision. Original HL had this weird hold on me, like it was urging me to keep going, to reach victory.</p>
<p>I also found the HECU fights made me want to quit. If I could tell what was coming, or I had retried a particular area too much, I was more inclined to quit than persist and succeed just because the HECU personally feel harder.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/about-some-gameplay-and-design-choices-of-black-mesa/11602/27">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/about-some-gameplay-and-design-choices-of-black-mesa/11602/27</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 06 Nov 2012 01:47:54 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11602-27</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/about-some-gameplay-and-design-choices-of-black-mesa/11602.rss">About some gameplay and design choices of Black Mesa</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>About some gameplay and design choices of Black Mesa</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[pRopaaNS]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Lack of atmosphere is one of BMs flaws. Thanks for pointing out one of reasons why this atmosphere was lacking.<br>
This is what I wrote in my early review:</p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>…although game is great, but it lacks atmoshpere and anticipation, as I could quit game any moment without feeling any particular motivation to keep playing.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>So, in other words, levels weren`t organized in chronological order gameplay wise, by correctly introducing new weapons and giving environment to try out  and experiment with those weapons, which players would normallly want to do after picking up a weapon for the first time.</p>
<p>So, in that sense, we picked up magnum instead of shotgun, but after leaving area bunch of Vortigaunts spawned and mangnums slow fire rate and inablility to drop them with a single shot unless it<code>s a headshot made a bad first impression for this newly picked up gun. It wasn</code>t an appropiate situation to use this weapon and, honestly, magnum isn<code>t even suited against xen creatures, but against hecus, which is why it originally was indroduced when we were leaving blast pit. Shotgun itself was introduced right before running into literally horde of Houndeyes, whose numbers were too much to handle if you</code>re not already familiar with this gun and if you weren<code>t already expecting such a big pack of enemies there.  Could analyze all other guns as well, but I don</code>t remember that much and I don`t really have time to write all this neither.</p>
<p>p.s. and yeah, it isn<code>t just about weapons, but can be refered to other things as well. For example, as I mentioned meeting this horde of houndeyes after picking up shotgun, which was completely unexcepted and didn</code>t follow any flow.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/about-some-gameplay-and-design-choices-of-black-mesa/11602/26">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/about-some-gameplay-and-design-choices-of-black-mesa/11602/26</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 05 Nov 2012 14:24:23 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11602-26</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/about-some-gameplay-and-design-choices-of-black-mesa/11602.rss">About some gameplay and design choices of Black Mesa</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>About some gameplay and design choices of Black Mesa</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[MaxTheLimit]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Johnathan Welsh ( Cpl.1nsane ) I think.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/about-some-gameplay-and-design-choices-of-black-mesa/11602/25">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/about-some-gameplay-and-design-choices-of-black-mesa/11602/25</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 03 Nov 2012 03:16:35 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11602-25</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/about-some-gameplay-and-design-choices-of-black-mesa/11602.rss">About some gameplay and design choices of Black Mesa</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>About some gameplay and design choices of Black Mesa</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[arizzi]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Who was in charge of designing this level?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/about-some-gameplay-and-design-choices-of-black-mesa/11602/24">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/about-some-gameplay-and-design-choices-of-black-mesa/11602/24</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 03 Nov 2012 00:30:05 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11602-24</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/about-some-gameplay-and-design-choices-of-black-mesa/11602.rss">About some gameplay and design choices of Black Mesa</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>About some gameplay and design choices of Black Mesa</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Dr_Maxwell]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Actually, I’m stuck playing HL1, which I don’t mind.   <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=9" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/about-some-gameplay-and-design-choices-of-black-mesa/11602/23">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/about-some-gameplay-and-design-choices-of-black-mesa/11602/23</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 03 Nov 2012 00:02:26 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11602-23</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/about-some-gameplay-and-design-choices-of-black-mesa/11602.rss">About some gameplay and design choices of Black Mesa</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>About some gameplay and design choices of Black Mesa</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[MaxTheLimit]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Can’t please everyone. Guess you are stuck going back and making it the way you like yourself.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/about-some-gameplay-and-design-choices-of-black-mesa/11602/22">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/about-some-gameplay-and-design-choices-of-black-mesa/11602/22</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Nov 2012 23:55:48 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11602-22</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/about-some-gameplay-and-design-choices-of-black-mesa/11602.rss">About some gameplay and design choices of Black Mesa</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>About some gameplay and design choices of Black Mesa</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Dr_Maxwell]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>The fact that they aren’t going to change it doesn’t make me happy with it.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/about-some-gameplay-and-design-choices-of-black-mesa/11602/21">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/about-some-gameplay-and-design-choices-of-black-mesa/11602/21</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Nov 2012 23:17:51 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11602-21</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/about-some-gameplay-and-design-choices-of-black-mesa/11602.rss">About some gameplay and design choices of Black Mesa</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>About some gameplay and design choices of Black Mesa</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Dotard]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>The game is out, they won’t rework the third chapter just because you aren’t happy with the crowbar placement.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/about-some-gameplay-and-design-choices-of-black-mesa/11602/20">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/about-some-gameplay-and-design-choices-of-black-mesa/11602/20</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Nov 2012 15:05:10 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11602-20</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/about-some-gameplay-and-design-choices-of-black-mesa/11602.rss">About some gameplay and design choices of Black Mesa</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>About some gameplay and design choices of Black Mesa</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Dr_Maxwell]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="darkone">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/user_avatar/leakfree.org/darkone/40/4296_2.png" class="avatar"> darkone:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>thing is it would take away alot from the mod, if you put it in lets say where it was, tehy would have to remake or put in triggers are aren’t needed for the elevator, you would also have to deal with A holes that would kill the guard on sight for a pistol. which would break game flow. the crowbar where it is fits the remake of the area.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I’d say that my idea is a nice solution to getting the crowbar before combat begins while still keeping the elevator crash crowbar-free.  Also, while my idea would help alleviate the killing-the-guard problem because it would bond the player more with the guard before the player has a chance to kill them, <span class="bbcode-b">you already don’t have to deal with assholes like that because Black Mesa isn’t a multiplayer game</span>.  Further, if you want to talk about breaking game flow, then how about a flare-only section - the only section with that concentration of flares in the game with no explanation, training the player to do the wrong thing, and irritating the player/breaking immersion by having a guard with horrible AI, which, depending on the difficulty level, either demonstrates that he’s invincible or gets him killed, in the latter case making the <span class="bbcode-i">pistol</span> Gordon’s first weapon?  Hell, I’m speaking in horrible run-on sentences now, but that’s because there’s just so much wrong with this sequence, and the justifications for changing it to its current state are so poor, with the only one I really sympathize with being the improvement that the elevator scene gets with the removal of the crowbar - and my idea manages to get that in while not breaking the game the way Black Mesa does.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/about-some-gameplay-and-design-choices-of-black-mesa/11602/19">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/about-some-gameplay-and-design-choices-of-black-mesa/11602/19</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Nov 2012 23:28:56 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11602-19</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/about-some-gameplay-and-design-choices-of-black-mesa/11602.rss">About some gameplay and design choices of Black Mesa</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>About some gameplay and design choices of Black Mesa</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[darkone]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>thing is it would take away alot from the mod, if you put it in lets say where it was, tehy would have to remake or put in triggers are aren’t needed for the elevator, you would also have to deal with A holes that would kill the guard on sight for a pistol. which would break game flow. the crowbar where it is fits the remake of the area.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/about-some-gameplay-and-design-choices-of-black-mesa/11602/18">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/about-some-gameplay-and-design-choices-of-black-mesa/11602/18</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Nov 2012 22:42:55 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11602-18</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/about-some-gameplay-and-design-choices-of-black-mesa/11602.rss">About some gameplay and design choices of Black Mesa</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>About some gameplay and design choices of Black Mesa</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[arizzi]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>The whole reason I am discussing this is because I think it would have made the scene better.  You can apply that sort of reasoning to anything, but I can say for me it would have been “more fun” if the crowbar had been introduced earlier instead of having us rely on flares or the guard.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/about-some-gameplay-and-design-choices-of-black-mesa/11602/17">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/about-some-gameplay-and-design-choices-of-black-mesa/11602/17</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Nov 2012 17:20:19 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11602-17</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/about-some-gameplay-and-design-choices-of-black-mesa/11602.rss">About some gameplay and design choices of Black Mesa</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>About some gameplay and design choices of Black Mesa</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[bur]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Look, it’s a game. There’s no point in overthinking this stuff. If it’s fun and doesn’t break immersion completely, who cares?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/about-some-gameplay-and-design-choices-of-black-mesa/11602/16">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/about-some-gameplay-and-design-choices-of-black-mesa/11602/16</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Nov 2012 14:16:29 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11602-16</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/about-some-gameplay-and-design-choices-of-black-mesa/11602.rss">About some gameplay and design choices of Black Mesa</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>About some gameplay and design choices of Black Mesa</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Dr_Maxwell]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I think it should’ve gotten to the player much earlier than it did in Black Mesa, as I disagree with the concept of the flare section for a variety of reasons, but I love the way that the lack of a crowbar forces the player to kill the people in the elevator himself via button.  Here’s my idea for the ideal redesign:</p>
<p>You get up to the elevator and there’s no way to get the door open except to push the button, killing the people in the elevator in a horrifying scene just like the one in Black Mesa (but without the ability to break open the elevator door with a chair; that’s just weak).  The player then climbs up to the top of the elevator, where the guard is fighting with zombies… behind a jammed glass elevator door.  The guard speaks to Gordon, muffled, through the crack in the door, telling him to try to find a way to break through.  The player can then go around investigating… and by climbing down, he’ll discover that all along, the crowbar was on top of the crashed elevator.  He retrieves it… at which point a crowbar teleports in.  The player may choose to fight it, or simply to run straight for the ladder, to get back to the jammed elevator door, which he breaks open to join the guard (who, on hard mode, will often be dead by this point).</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/about-some-gameplay-and-design-choices-of-black-mesa/11602/15">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/about-some-gameplay-and-design-choices-of-black-mesa/11602/15</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Nov 2012 03:42:02 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11602-15</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/about-some-gameplay-and-design-choices-of-black-mesa/11602.rss">About some gameplay and design choices of Black Mesa</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>About some gameplay and design choices of Black Mesa</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[BendyBread]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I really really liked the flares. I mean apart from “SET EVERYTHING ON FIRE MWAHAHA”, it was just fun to use them as a general thing. Not only that, but I liked the idea of the crowbar actually being introduced later as a “proper” placement to jam the door.<br>
In HL1 it was just lying around randomly. I always did think that was a bit odd.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/about-some-gameplay-and-design-choices-of-black-mesa/11602/14">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/about-some-gameplay-and-design-choices-of-black-mesa/11602/14</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Nov 2012 03:13:41 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11602-14</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/about-some-gameplay-and-design-choices-of-black-mesa/11602.rss">About some gameplay and design choices of Black Mesa</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>About some gameplay and design choices of Black Mesa</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[arizzi]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="MaxTheLimit">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/m/0ea827/40.png" class="avatar"> MaxTheLimit:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I know you didn’t say anything about it. I did. It is quite clear that section of the game is supposed to create tension. I’m saying that giving you more options to make the section easier lessens the effectiveness of the atmosphere created by the areas directly after resonance cascade.</p>
<p>When you find the crowbar it becomes part of your arsenal. It is no longer using items found in your surroundings as a weapon. It is just the melee weapon in your armoury. It isn’t something you have to look for.</p>
<p>I know you said you’d have both. I’m saying that is worse.</p>
<p>BTW - No more red text please.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>On the contrary, using the crowbar is actually harder/more involved than throwing a flare.</p>
<p>I also really dont see how it diminishes the tension in any way, not that there is much in the first place, since the enemies are easy to dispatch either way.  Getting up close and personal with the enemies with a melee weapon really gives the sense that you are fighting for your life.  But maybe instead of tension you meant something else, maybe horror or atmosphere.</p>
<p>For the purpose of the story/atmoshpere, the crowbar really isn’t any different from another improvised weapon, the only difference being that it is, as you said, added to your arsenal.  Both items are put right into your path, so your never really forced to, “look” for items.  Now that I think of it, teaching the player to pick up and throw items at enemies might lead them to doing so with items that aren’t flares, which we know doesn’t damage them at all.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/about-some-gameplay-and-design-choices-of-black-mesa/11602/13">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/about-some-gameplay-and-design-choices-of-black-mesa/11602/13</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 31 Oct 2012 17:03:16 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11602-13</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/about-some-gameplay-and-design-choices-of-black-mesa/11602.rss">About some gameplay and design choices of Black Mesa</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>About some gameplay and design choices of Black Mesa</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[darkone]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>think the guard AI for the first after shit hits fan guard should be changed a bit.</p>
<ol>
<li>
<p>he should try to beat zombies with his pistol if they get to close (all guards should have melee secondary just in case). or atleast be able to push them back.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>he should have and use the flares. (give him 2 that are on his belt, the first he tosses at a zombie saying something like lets hope they burn, the second would just be for looks)</p>
</li>
</ol>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/about-some-gameplay-and-design-choices-of-black-mesa/11602/12">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/about-some-gameplay-and-design-choices-of-black-mesa/11602/12</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 31 Oct 2012 04:46:44 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11602-12</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/about-some-gameplay-and-design-choices-of-black-mesa/11602.rss">About some gameplay and design choices of Black Mesa</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>About some gameplay and design choices of Black Mesa</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[MaxTheLimit]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="arizzi">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/a/b19c9b/40.png" class="avatar"> arizzi:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I never said anything about tension. This section’s purpose was to show people how bad shit just got, as well as introduce them to new enemies,(and in the original hl, to get them familiar with navigating the environment and using the crowbar.) It gives them something more interesting to do, and which relies more on the user’s input.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I know you didn’t say anything about it. I did. It is quite clear that section of the game is supposed to create tension. I’m saying that giving you more options to make the section easier lessens the effectiveness of the atmosphere created by the areas directly after resonance cascade.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="arizzi">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/a/b19c9b/40.png" class="avatar"> arizzi:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I never said anything about removing it. I specifically said before that I would keep both if it were up to me. How is a crowbar not something that you have just found in the local environment and put to improvised use. Thats kind of why the crowbar is made out to be such a big part of Gordon’s image. Every weapon in hl has a specific role, as well as advantages and disadvantages versus certain targets.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>When you find the crowbar it becomes part of your arsenal. It is no longer using items found in your surroundings as a weapon. It is just the melee weapon in your armoury. It isn’t something you have to look for.</p>
<p>I know you said you’d have both. I’m saying that is worse.</p>
<p>BTW - No more red text please.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/about-some-gameplay-and-design-choices-of-black-mesa/11602/11">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/about-some-gameplay-and-design-choices-of-black-mesa/11602/11</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 31 Oct 2012 00:08:16 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11602-11</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/about-some-gameplay-and-design-choices-of-black-mesa/11602.rss">About some gameplay and design choices of Black Mesa</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>About some gameplay and design choices of Black Mesa</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Conti]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Why bother use the crowbar a bit sooner in Unforeseen Consequences – only to break a glass and kill a few headcrabs/zombies – if you’ll have the whole damn game after that to use that same crowbar?<br>
I agree with Max. No need for explanations about how to use the crowbar; if you know what it does in RL, you’ll know what it can do in-game. But if you don’t know… well… use your brain! The breakthrough in HL (and subsequent sequels) was making the players think about how to solve a puzzle instead of only breaking/shooting things.</p>
<p>For me, the crowbar placement in BM is perfect as it is. And it tells a history (in a subtle manner): Someone desperate tried to escape from the zombies, found a crowbar, but instead of being brave and kill some zombies with it, prefered to use it to block a door. If that guy survived or not, doesn’t matter… Here comes Freeman which sees that crowbar and  – voilá! – finds a better use for it, killing zombies and other critters like a true hero.</p>
<p>So… If you want a purpose for the crowbar placement in BM, there it is^. Better than in HL, where it is conveniently lying on the ground just waiting for you to pick it up.</p>
<p>As for the flare, unfortunately I think it was under-used in BM. I would love to see more uses for it in other chapters than only in UC. Not just to burn zombies… but to use it as a way to unlock some level puzzles.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/about-some-gameplay-and-design-choices-of-black-mesa/11602/10">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/about-some-gameplay-and-design-choices-of-black-mesa/11602/10</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 30 Oct 2012 23:50:14 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11602-10</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/about-some-gameplay-and-design-choices-of-black-mesa/11602.rss">About some gameplay and design choices of Black Mesa</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>About some gameplay and design choices of Black Mesa</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[arizzi]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="MaxTheLimit">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/m/0ea827/40.png" class="avatar"> MaxTheLimit:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>It’s a crowbar. All of this seems quite unnecessary.</p>
<p>[COLOR=‘Red’]Those are among the reasons why it was placed where it was in the original, as well as why it might play better if it were moved.</p>
<p>I have no problem with the guard ai. Definitely not human. Far from it. But about as capable as most other following ai in fps games.</p>
<p>I think the whole argument that the crowbar is something you learn to effectively use is silly. Once you see the timing after the first 4-5 swings, then you got it.</p>
<p>[COLOR=‘red’] I never claimed that it was something vital, fact of the matter is; what I am saying is that it provides better gameplay (and I might argue better atmosphere, for lack of a better term to describe it.  I think its much cooler to swing a crowbar than throw a flare.)</p>
<p>I also don’t see how giving a player another weapon early makes for better tension early in the game. Arguments can be made for effectiveness and then enemies you face, but I don’t see how providing ANOTHER weapon makes this sequence better in any real way.</p>
<p>[COLOR=‘red’]I never said anything about tension.  This section’s purpose was to show people how bad shit just got, as well as introduce them to new enemies,(and in the original hl, to get them familiar with navigating the environment and using the crowbar.)  It gives them something more interesting to do, and which relies more on the user’s input.</p>
<p>Because you lose a small section of combat that is restricted to what you can find in the local environment, rather than the arsenal you have with you. All I see is some unique gameplay that is lost. The reason you suggest for removing it is because it is more convenient and players may need to get accustomed to using a crowbar. I have trouble imagining a person that needs more than a swing or two to understand the mechanics of the crowbar fully.</p>
<p>[COLOR=‘red’]I never said anything about removing it.  I specifically said before that I would keep both if it were up to me. How is a crowbar not something that you have just found in the local environment and put to improvised use.  Thats kind of why the crowbar is made out to be such a big part of Gordon’s image.  Every weapon in hl has a specific role, as well as advantages and disadvantages versus certain targets.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/about-some-gameplay-and-design-choices-of-black-mesa/11602/9">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/about-some-gameplay-and-design-choices-of-black-mesa/11602/9</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 30 Oct 2012 23:33:06 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11602-9</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/about-some-gameplay-and-design-choices-of-black-mesa/11602.rss">About some gameplay and design choices of Black Mesa</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>About some gameplay and design choices of Black Mesa</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[MaxTheLimit]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="arizzi">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/a/b19c9b/40.png" class="avatar"> arizzi:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>It’s not as much about being taught, but about familiarizing the player with the crowbar before having to use it against enemies, as well as establishing its role, discovering what enemies its effective against, and encouraging the player to discover effective tactics</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>It’s a crowbar. All of this seems quite unnecessary.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="arizzi">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/a/b19c9b/40.png" class="avatar"> arizzi:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Sticking with the guards has always proven to be a bad idea for me, as they generally dont shoot at things that are close to them, leading them to be defenseless when the zomies are hitting them. A few other ai flaws really ruin this sequence if you follow the guard.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I have no problem with the guard ai. Definitely not human. Far from it. But about as capable as most other following ai in fps games.</p>
<p>I think the whole argument that the crowbar is something you learn to effectively use is silly. Once you see the timing after the first 4-5 swings, then you got it.</p>
<p>I also don’t see how giving a player another weapon early makes for better tension early in the game. Arguments can be made for effectiveness and then enemies you face, but I don’t see how providing ANOTHER weapon makes this sequence better in any real way.</p>
<p>Because you lose a small section of combat that is restricted to what you can find in the local environment, rather than the arsenal you have with you. All I see is some unique gameplay that is lost. The reason you suggest for removing it is because it is more convenient and players may need to get accustomed to using a crowbar. I have trouble imagining a person that needs more than a swing or two to understand the mechanics of the crowbar fully.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/about-some-gameplay-and-design-choices-of-black-mesa/11602/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/about-some-gameplay-and-design-choices-of-black-mesa/11602/8</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 30 Oct 2012 23:09:08 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11602-8</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/about-some-gameplay-and-design-choices-of-black-mesa/11602.rss">About some gameplay and design choices of Black Mesa</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>About some gameplay and design choices of Black Mesa</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Dotard]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>2 things:</p>
<ol>
<li>An introducing scripted sequence of the Guard throwing a flare into the gas, setting a zombie aflame would be nice.</li>
<li>Improved AI for both the Guards and HECU, them using a melee attack at close and then stepping backwards to get some distance from their target.</li>
</ol>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/about-some-gameplay-and-design-choices-of-black-mesa/11602/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/about-some-gameplay-and-design-choices-of-black-mesa/11602/7</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 30 Oct 2012 22:55:24 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11602-7</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/about-some-gameplay-and-design-choices-of-black-mesa/11602.rss">About some gameplay and design choices of Black Mesa</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>About some gameplay and design choices of Black Mesa</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[arizzi]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I think the best balance would be just to have both</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/about-some-gameplay-and-design-choices-of-black-mesa/11602/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/about-some-gameplay-and-design-choices-of-black-mesa/11602/6</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 30 Oct 2012 22:53:04 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11602-6</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/about-some-gameplay-and-design-choices-of-black-mesa/11602.rss">About some gameplay and design choices of Black Mesa</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>About some gameplay and design choices of Black Mesa</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[RossBondReturns]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I found the flares exciting.</p>
<p>I mean I had to help out the guard and protect myself by utilizing the flares to either directly set zombies on fire and ignite plumes of gas.</p>
<p>I had no real problem with the guards A.I. on my first playthrough he died which was a nice change to him being invincible.</p>
<p>The other times I’ve played we’ve both survived by working as a team.</p>
<p>Oh and I use flares often…because I like to see other things in the game burn.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/about-some-gameplay-and-design-choices-of-black-mesa/11602/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/about-some-gameplay-and-design-choices-of-black-mesa/11602/5</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 30 Oct 2012 22:51:29 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11602-5</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/about-some-gameplay-and-design-choices-of-black-mesa/11602.rss">About some gameplay and design choices of Black Mesa</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>About some gameplay and design choices of Black Mesa</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[arizzi]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="MaxTheLimit">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/m/0ea827/40.png" class="avatar"> MaxTheLimit:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>What kind of person needs to be taught that you can use a heavy crowbar to smash things? How much do you need to learn about how to use one?</p>
<p>[COLOR=‘Red’]It’s not as much about being taught, but about familiarizing the player with the crowbar before having to use it against enemies, as well as establishing its role, discovering what enemies its effective against, and encouraging the player to discover effective tactics</p>
<p>Are you not given a prompt to pick up flares? I can’t recall. But this section is key to teach a player how to utilize guards for help in certain sections.</p>
<p>[COLOR=‘red’]Sticking with the guards has always proven to be a bad idea for me, as they generally dont shoot at things that are close to them, leading them to be defenseless when the zomies are hitting them.  A few other ai flaws really ruin this sequence if you follow the guard.</p>
<p>It also is more effective at building tension in this section because you are forced to improvise more to use the flares as weapons. It makes you vulnerable, which makes the whole sequence more intense. You indicate that leaving the player unarmed makes the sequence less exciting, but I don’t see how. I actually prefer the pacing as it is now. In BM you are left unarmed longer. Sure you can get a gun from a guard earlier, but generally you get it far later than in HL1. This makes the initial portions of the game better because after the event you are scrambling for your life.</p>
<p>[COLOR=‘red’]I guess it comes down to preferences, I never really thought that throwing flares at zombies gives the idea that you are scambling for your life any more than using a crowbar, less so in fact.  Plus do to the crappy ai of the guard, your probably going to end up with a pistol immediately afterward anyway. But in regards to what I said before about establishing the role of the crowbar, and all the other stuff I already mentioned, it seems to me that the crowbar was better placed where it was in hl.  I mean, valve did choose to put it there for a reason</p>
<p>It does make a big difference, and I think it is better. Let’s face it, the headcrabs and zombies are weak enemies, and once you have the crowbar they drop like flies. Forcing a player to use tools at hand ( guards / flares ) makes the gameplay more dynamic so far as I can tell.</p>
<p>[COLOR=‘red’]They drop all the same when you throw flares at them in fact its even easier since you dont even have to dodge their attacks.  As I mentioned before, At least with the crowbar, the player learns to use it effectively by developing their own tactics with it as opposed to just throwing it, also as I mentioned before, learning to use the crowbar will help you later in the game as opposed to flares.  Also, the zombies really dont walk fast or anything, you can just sprint through them which is what I usually do because I find the flares kind of annoying to use, the crowbar is much more convenient for dealing with them in the end.</p>
<p>Yes, after you get proper weapons flares aren’t really useful. I sort of hoped that the player would get more opportunity to use them in RP when you aren’t armed again, but no dice. That being said without disarming the player it would be quite difficult to encourage a player to use such a limited utility. I mean why use flares when you have a shotgun, or grenades?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/about-some-gameplay-and-design-choices-of-black-mesa/11602/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/about-some-gameplay-and-design-choices-of-black-mesa/11602/4</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 30 Oct 2012 22:29:15 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11602-4</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/about-some-gameplay-and-design-choices-of-black-mesa/11602.rss">About some gameplay and design choices of Black Mesa</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>About some gameplay and design choices of Black Mesa</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[darkone]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>reason to use flares when you have a gun.1. ammo conservation, its alot more important than in half life. 2. burning things.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/about-some-gameplay-and-design-choices-of-black-mesa/11602/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/about-some-gameplay-and-design-choices-of-black-mesa/11602/3</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 30 Oct 2012 21:08:58 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11602-3</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/about-some-gameplay-and-design-choices-of-black-mesa/11602.rss">About some gameplay and design choices of Black Mesa</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
