<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Small map bug in On A Rail</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/small-map-bug-in-on-a-rail/12500</link>
    <description>I&#39;m running through your remake for the first time, and I got to the missile launch facility in On A Rail. Got inside the complex, killed the two guards, and then I didn&#39;t notice the launch button in the room on the upper level, and expected there to be another room to go to. Couldn&#39;t get through the door at the other side of the room but I noticed it was breakable, so I broke it. Couldn&#39;t get through it, so I broke the upper side, found a trash can, hopped on the trash can and then through the door into the hallway. From there I saw a blast door to my left, and another breakable glass door to my right. So I grabbed the trash can, and repeated the procedure with the new door, and hopped through. Found myself outside your maps. You should probably make those glass doors unbreakable in a future release.  :slight_smile:</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 25 Aug 2013 22:45:56 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>In-game Issues (Mod)</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/small-map-bug-in-on-a-rail/12500.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Small map bug in On A Rail</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Jonny_B_Goode]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I’m running through your remake for the first time, and I got to the missile launch facility in On A Rail. Got inside the complex, killed the two guards, and then I didn’t notice the launch button in the room on the upper level, and expected there to be another room to go to. Couldn’t get through the door at the other side of the room but I noticed it was breakable, so I broke it. Couldn’t get through it, so I broke the upper side, found a trash can, hopped on the trash can and then through the door into the hallway. From there I saw a blast door to my left, and another breakable glass door to my right. So I grabbed the trash can, and repeated the procedure with the new door, and hopped through. Found myself outside your maps. You should probably make those glass doors unbreakable in a future release.  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=9" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/small-map-bug-in-on-a-rail/12500/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/small-map-bug-in-on-a-rail/12500/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 25 Aug 2013 22:45:56 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12500-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/small-map-bug-in-on-a-rail/12500.rss">Small map bug in On A Rail</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
