<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Steam Account Security - Top ways to stay safe</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/steam-account-security-top-ways-to-stay-safe/1471</link>
    <description>There seems to be a lot confusion about account security.  What should it be, what shouldn&#39;t it be.  Is the user or the steam program really doing its part in maintaining the security of your steam account, blah blah blah....

This is just a reminder to everyone that security is still owned by the user, not the software/program.  For most of the userbase, (95% or higher) simple and basic computer security practices will keep your account safe and out of harms way.  This is just a list of some of those basics to keep in mind.

-----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------

1)  [b]E-Mail Verification[/b] USE IT FOR GOODNESS SAKE!
Verifying your email address with Steam improves the security of your Steam Account. Once you&#39;ve verified your email address with Steam, both your Steam Account password and access to your email account are required in order to make any changes to your Steam Account credentials, such as your password, secret question and answer, and contact email address. This helps further protect your Steam Account from being stolen by a potential phisher.  

There is absolutly no reason you should not be doing this.  Go here for more info:

https://support.steampowered.com/kb_article.php?ref=5151-RUAS-1543

-----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------

2)  [b]Protect your steam account login/password info with your life[/b]. The only places you should be keying your password into is one of three places, the steam interface itself, or two specific websites [b]that you typed into the url address bar YOURSELF[/b]. That would be the Steam store [url]https://store.steampowered.com/login[/url] or the Steam Community [url]https://steamcommunity.com[/url] (notice the S in https for SECURITY!)  

Remember, just because it says [url=&#39;https://www.google.com&#39;]https://steamcommunity.com[/url] doesnt mean it really is [url=&#39;https://www.t-arty.com/images/designslarge/noob.jpg&#39;]https://steamcommunity.com[/url].  Amirite!? Right! 

So .........


* Don&#39;t click links. Type it in if you want to go somewhere on the net.
* VALVe/STEAM/VAC Employees will NEVER use free email providers such as gmail, hotmail or msn and they never contact you out of the blue.  Never. NEVER EVER.
* VALVe/STEAM/VAC Employees will NEVER ask for passwords.  Never. NEVER EVER.
* Do NOT use the same username/password as what you have on other websites/forums. 
* DO NOT give your key or password out.  NOT EVEN TO:

Your mom, brother, dad, sister or other relatives
* Your friends, pretend friends, bestest bestest friends in the whole wide world
* People in Im&#39;s, Pm&#39;s, or other messaging systems ANYWHERE
* Anyone offering [b]free games[/b] or free [b]anything[/b].  There are websites that LOOK like a Steam website, but they are fake and phish for account details rather well. So be careful...Especially &quot;links&quot; sent to you through a &quot;friend&quot; that take you to a fake website that [b]LOOKS[/b] like the steam community.  Remember, once your account is hijacked, the first thing the diptwad does is pull up your friends list and then starts sending pms to them to see who else might click the provided link and login to the fake steam site.

-----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------

3) [b]Be careful of outside programs that could compromise your account.[/b]
Viruses, keyloggers, spyware... all of that is a potential issue for your steam account so be sure you have programs (PLURAL) to keep you clean and clean often!  I can&#39;t stress this enough folks! Just cuz &quot;Malwarebites&quot; doesn&#39;t find a Trojan doesn&#39;t mean you are clean.  It may be that &quot;Adaware&quot; or &quot;AVG&quot; find something that others don&#39;t find.  There are enough free programs out there... USE THEM! and use them often!

-----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------

4) [b]Cheats [/b]or [b]Modified core game files.[/b]

If you have done either of these things then you need to stay away from vac secured servers.

Example: You install and play PARANOIA or BLOOM MOD which are mods that clearly announce that they use a modified opengl32.dll file. This is not a &quot;cheat&quot;, however because it uses a modified game file... and if you do not switch it back to the original game file before going on a vac secured server... you WILL BE FLAGGED FOR A VAC BAN. No it will not be unbanned.  VAC bans for specific code behaviors, not [i]intentions[/i].

-----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------

5) [b]&quot;No thank you!&quot;[/b] Be careful who you accept gifts from!  Be VERY careful!  
Example:  Joe Shmoe is a Smuck.  He stole his best friends mom&#39;s credit card and went out and purchased a bunch of games with it.  He then turned around and either gave them away via the &quot;gift&quot; system or he SOLD the games.  The unsuspecting person receives this gift or game and assigns it to his uber leet kewl steam account that has over $200 dollars worth of games on it.  A month later Steam revokes access to that game due to credit card fraud.  You are out your money, so take care of where you get your games from!  

[url=&#39;https://support.steampowered.com/kb_article.php?ref=5854-QWLN-2621&#39;]My Gift Has Been Revoked[/url]
[quote]
I received the following error:
Your recent gift of &lt; Steam Game &gt; from &lt; Steam Gifter &gt; has been revoked due to a problem processing payment for this item.  The games associated with this gift can no longer be played as a result. If you would like to purchase this item, visit the Steam Store. Otherwise, you may choose to delete the local content associated with this gift.
[/quote]
  

[url=&#39;https://support.steampowered.com/kb_article.php?ref=5406-WFZC-5519&#39;]Reasons for Disabled Accounts[/url]
[quote]
REDEEMING FRAUDULENT GIFTS
Never accept a gift from an unknown user. Any accounts tied to a redeemed gift from a fraudulent source may be disabled.
[/quote]

-----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------

6) [b]&quot;OMG! I have been hijacked!&quot;[/b] If for some reason your account IS stolen from you:

[b]Screenshot Instructions[/b]
[INDENT][url]https://www.catzeyes93.com/images/SteamAccountHijackHelp/HELP.html[/url][/INDENT]

[b]Text Instructions[/b]
You have a **steam account** to play games on
You have a **steam forum** account to post on the steam forums
You have a **steam support** account for times you are having issues with your steam account

1) Register a steam support account here: [url=&#39;https://support.steampowered.com/register.php&#39;]https://support.steampowered.com/register.php[/url]
2) Then go to create a support ticket here: [url=&#39;https://support.steampowered.com/newticket.php&#39;]https://support.steampowered.com/newticket.php[/url]
3) Be sure to give them as much information about your steam account and what happened.
4) Be prepared to offer them proof of ownership. (Purchase receipt, CC billing statement, jpg scan of cd key or other proof of purchase) 
5) You will be using your steam support account to check on the status of your ticket here [url]https://support.steampowered.com/ticketlist.php[/url] as well as sending any additional requested info.



[b]Note: Tickets are answered in the order they are received and many times within 24 hours for hijacked accounts.  The official time frame for tickets are 3 - 5 business days though.[/b]

-----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------

While you are waiting on your ticket here are some popular topics to read: 
* [url=&#39;https://support.steampowered.com/cgi-bin/steampowered.cfg/php/enduser/std_adp.php?p_faqid=197&#39;]Reclaiming a Hijacked Steam Account[/url]
* [url=&#39;https://support.steampowered.com/cgi-bin/steampowered.cfg/php/enduser/std_adp.php?p_faqid=294&#39;]Contacting VALVe Billing and Support[/url]
* [url=&#39;https://support.steampowered.com/cgi-bin/steampowered.cfg/php/enduser/std_adp.php?p_faqid=301&#39;]Account Security Recommendations[/url]
* [url=&#39;https://support.steampowered.com/kb_article.php?ref=7849-RADZ-6869&#39;]Valve Anti-Cheat System (VAC)[/url]
* [url=&#39;https://support.steampowered.com/kb_article.php?ref=4044-QDHJ-5691&#39;]I&#39;ve Been Banned[/url]
* [url=&#39;https://support.steampowered.com/kb_article.php?ref=5406-WFZC-5519&#39;]Disabled Steam Account[/url]
* [url=&#39;https://support.steampowered.com/kb_article.php?ref=8830-EOBN-8013&#39;]Cheaters, Abusive Admins, New Cheats, and Cheat Websites[/url]
* [url=&#39;https://store.steampowered.com/subscriber_agreement/&#39;]STEAM™ SUBSCRIBER AGREEMENT[/url] (sometimes referred to as the End User License Agreement / EULA)
* [url=&#39;https://store.steampowered.com/online_conduct/&#39;]STEAM™ ONLINE CONDUCT[/url]

-----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 08 Aug 2010 22:34:21 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Help and Support</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/steam-account-security-top-ways-to-stay-safe/1471.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Steam Account Security - Top ways to stay safe</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[kewl]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Dias">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/d/4491bb/40.png" class="avatar"> Dias:</div>
<blockquote>
<p><span alt="" class="broken-image" title="This image is broken"><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-unlink svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#unlink"></use></svg></span><br>
I received a fun little message just a few minutes ago. The guy’s joined 70 groups, solely for the reason of messaging people, and has 14 friends, most of which have gibberish names. (presumably alt-accounts)</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I think I’ve been spammed by that same guy. :fffuuu:</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/steam-account-security-top-ways-to-stay-safe/1471/72">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/steam-account-security-top-ways-to-stay-safe/1471/72</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 08 Aug 2010 22:34:21 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-1471-72</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/steam-account-security-top-ways-to-stay-safe/1471.rss">Steam Account Security - Top ways to stay safe</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Steam Account Security - Top ways to stay safe</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Dias]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><span alt="" class="broken-image" title="This image is broken"><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-unlink svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#unlink"></use></svg></span><br>
I received a fun little message just a few minutes ago. The guy’s joined 70 groups, solely for the reason of messaging people, and has 14 friends, most of which have gibberish names. (presumably alt-accounts)</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/steam-account-security-top-ways-to-stay-safe/1471/71">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/steam-account-security-top-ways-to-stay-safe/1471/71</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 08 Aug 2010 19:46:46 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-1471-71</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/steam-account-security-top-ways-to-stay-safe/1471.rss">Steam Account Security - Top ways to stay safe</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Steam Account Security - Top ways to stay safe</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Katana]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>This is why you should always be careful accepting gifts; Steam has the right to disable your WHOLE account if something you’ve received was attained illegally. They don’t always do it, but you should assume they will.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/steam-account-security-top-ways-to-stay-safe/1471/70">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/steam-account-security-top-ways-to-stay-safe/1471/70</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 11 May 2010 22:25:06 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-1471-70</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/steam-account-security-top-ways-to-stay-safe/1471.rss">Steam Account Security - Top ways to stay safe</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Steam Account Security - Top ways to stay safe</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[CatzEyes93]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I have seen two scenarios happen on the steam forums:</p>
<ol>
<li>
<p>Schmuck steals a card from his friend or where ever and purchases a bunch of games on a disposable steam account, and then ‘gifts’ them to people that pay him on the side at a discount rate. Those folks go get their ‘gift’ and attach it to their longstanding account.  A month later the card had been reported stolen and all the original purchases are reversed.  The chargeback causes the ‘gift’ <span class="bbcode-i">game </span>to be revoked.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>All the above accept in some cases, I have seen this also get the <span class="bbcode-i">whole account</span> disabled.</p>
</li>
</ol>
<p>(VAC is actually something else entirely and deals only with cheating infractions.)</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/steam-account-security-top-ways-to-stay-safe/1471/69">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/steam-account-security-top-ways-to-stay-safe/1471/69</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 11 May 2010 19:41:56 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-1471-69</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/steam-account-security-top-ways-to-stay-safe/1471.rss">Steam Account Security - Top ways to stay safe</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Steam Account Security - Top ways to stay safe</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[The_Minotaur]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="CatzEyes93">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/user_avatar/leakfree.org/catzeyes93/40/4402_2.png" class="avatar"> CatzEyes93:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>yup! And then those folks could possibly risk losing the whole account on the basis of fraud.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Maybe, but you don’t get the money back I think, and they could gift it to random people. Perhaps in exchange for a legitimately bought game? Just pretend they didn’t mean to buy it or something.</p>
<p>Those people would get their accounts banned, and the person who did it would get off with a bunch of free games.</p>
<p>Anyway, I agree that you should have to have the card present, even if it’s simply so you don’t accidently buy something with the wrong card. I’ve done that before.  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=9" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/steam-account-security-top-ways-to-stay-safe/1471/68">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/steam-account-security-top-ways-to-stay-safe/1471/68</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 11 May 2010 19:30:44 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-1471-68</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/steam-account-security-top-ways-to-stay-safe/1471.rss">Steam Account Security - Top ways to stay safe</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Steam Account Security - Top ways to stay safe</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[CatzEyes93]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>yup! And then those folks could possibly risk losing the whole account on the basis of fraud.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/steam-account-security-top-ways-to-stay-safe/1471/67">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/steam-account-security-top-ways-to-stay-safe/1471/67</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 11 May 2010 15:22:31 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-1471-67</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/steam-account-security-top-ways-to-stay-safe/1471.rss">Steam Account Security - Top ways to stay safe</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Steam Account Security - Top ways to stay safe</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Katana]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>See, another thing I really think they need to look into is the CCV code for credit cards. Basically, even when it remembers account information, at LEAST ask for that so they know that your card is physically there.<br>
Otherwise, someone stealing the account could load up 15 games from the store, and gift them to another account.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/steam-account-security-top-ways-to-stay-safe/1471/66">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/steam-account-security-top-ways-to-stay-safe/1471/66</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 11 May 2010 13:03:06 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-1471-66</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/steam-account-security-top-ways-to-stay-safe/1471.rss">Steam Account Security - Top ways to stay safe</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Steam Account Security - Top ways to stay safe</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[CatzEyes93]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>the email verification should make it tons harder to hijack the account.  If you folks have not already done this I suggest you do it.  It was only made available just late last year.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/steam-account-security-top-ways-to-stay-safe/1471/65">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/steam-account-security-top-ways-to-stay-safe/1471/65</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 21 Apr 2010 12:32:58 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-1471-65</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/steam-account-security-top-ways-to-stay-safe/1471.rss">Steam Account Security - Top ways to stay safe</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Steam Account Security - Top ways to stay safe</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Carlton]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>^lol my college does it every four months, but i always end up forgetting the one i chage it to, then having to call to get it reset to the default password. i think i’ve had to do that like three times now.</p>
<p>i got jacked once. funny thing was he didn’t steal any of my unredeemed gifts. don’t accept and friend or even sometimes group invites, and don’t click on any links from people you don’t trust. even if they are your legit friend, still be careful. and never log in if someone links you the steam homepage.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/steam-account-security-top-ways-to-stay-safe/1471/64">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/steam-account-security-top-ways-to-stay-safe/1471/64</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 21 Apr 2010 00:33:18 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-1471-64</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/steam-account-security-top-ways-to-stay-safe/1471.rss">Steam Account Security - Top ways to stay safe</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Steam Account Security - Top ways to stay safe</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Katana]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>It’s kinda funny how my college is so adamant about account security, even forcing us to change our account passwords every 3 months. And yet there is one huge freaking vulnerability;</p>
<p>People are expected to enter their password into as many as 15 different-looking sites at RIT.</p>
<p>The worst part? People can create their own sites on the RIT network. So for instance, if I use my Website Design class’ webspace to make a site at people.rit.edu/myname/authrequired and say “Enter your RIT username and password” honestly no one would think twice. It’s really dumb.</p>
<p>I actually have to admit I did once fall for a “steamtournament.ca” address and entered my password; but about a second later, I realized my horrible mistake, immediately changed my password and never looked back on the old one.</p>
<p>Honestly, with around 175 games in my account, I really think Steam should be thinking about verification that goes beyond a simple password.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/steam-account-security-top-ways-to-stay-safe/1471/63">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/steam-account-security-top-ways-to-stay-safe/1471/63</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 21 Apr 2010 00:06:48 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-1471-63</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/steam-account-security-top-ways-to-stay-safe/1471.rss">Steam Account Security - Top ways to stay safe</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Steam Account Security - Top ways to stay safe</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[lambda]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>This scares me… i dont wanna get hacked!</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/steam-account-security-top-ways-to-stay-safe/1471/62">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/steam-account-security-top-ways-to-stay-safe/1471/62</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 20 Apr 2010 16:02:45 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-1471-62</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/steam-account-security-top-ways-to-stay-safe/1471.rss">Steam Account Security - Top ways to stay safe</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Steam Account Security - Top ways to stay safe</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[CatzEyes93]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Oh hai! I got those!</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/steam-account-security-top-ways-to-stay-safe/1471/61">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/steam-account-security-top-ways-to-stay-safe/1471/61</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 12 Mar 2010 03:14:13 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-1471-61</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/steam-account-security-top-ways-to-stay-safe/1471.rss">Steam Account Security - Top ways to stay safe</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Steam Account Security - Top ways to stay safe</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[FireTime]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/smiley.png?v=9" title=":smiley:" class="emoji only-emoji" alt=":smiley:"></p>
<p>don’t forget the <a href="https://www.pennridge.org/works/outlet%20safety.jpg" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">outlet covers</a> :3</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/steam-account-security-top-ways-to-stay-safe/1471/60">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/steam-account-security-top-ways-to-stay-safe/1471/60</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 12 Mar 2010 02:06:02 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-1471-60</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/steam-account-security-top-ways-to-stay-safe/1471.rss">Steam Account Security - Top ways to stay safe</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Steam Account Security - Top ways to stay safe</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[CatzEyes93]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="FireTime">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/f/ba8739/40.png" class="avatar"> FireTime:</div>
<blockquote>
<p><em>tear</em> :’(</p>
<p>lol, thats fine. I was mostly posting the information because of how easy it was to find it. It was about 4% hacking, 6% view source, 80% google searches, and 10% whois queries.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Hey there, no worries buddy. I just wanna make sure everything is on the up and up and that we don’t encourage things that <span class="bbcode-i">could </span>get messy.</p>
<p>I guess you could say this particular thread is about emulating some of the basic steam rules? One of which is to minimize the advertizment of bad links, as well as minimize the need to hunt someone down and “make them pay!! GARG BAHHH! GRRRRrr1~~~@!!!”</p>
<p>All is good tho. You have honorable intentions.  I am simply trying to keep it all safe for all the children in the home.  :luv4you:</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/steam-account-security-top-ways-to-stay-safe/1471/59">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/steam-account-security-top-ways-to-stay-safe/1471/59</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 12 Mar 2010 01:13:50 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-1471-59</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/steam-account-security-top-ways-to-stay-safe/1471.rss">Steam Account Security - Top ways to stay safe</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Steam Account Security - Top ways to stay safe</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[coldroll]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I’ve been getting the same message as Lord Grievous every month.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/steam-account-security-top-ways-to-stay-safe/1471/58">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/steam-account-security-top-ways-to-stay-safe/1471/58</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 12 Mar 2010 01:12:04 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-1471-58</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/steam-account-security-top-ways-to-stay-safe/1471.rss">Steam Account Security - Top ways to stay safe</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Steam Account Security - Top ways to stay safe</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Spartan911]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Wow Id better think twice  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=9" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:">  Good Thread  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=9" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:">  Alot Of ppl have been doing this and accepting many GIFT fraud  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/frowning.png?v=9" title=":frowning:" class="emoji" alt=":frowning:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/steam-account-security-top-ways-to-stay-safe/1471/57">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/steam-account-security-top-ways-to-stay-safe/1471/57</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 11 Mar 2010 22:09:52 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-1471-57</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/steam-account-security-top-ways-to-stay-safe/1471.rss">Steam Account Security - Top ways to stay safe</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Steam Account Security - Top ways to stay safe</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[sudpuzzer]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Whoops, sorry I meant to disable those links, but I see Catz is on the ball.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/steam-account-security-top-ways-to-stay-safe/1471/56">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/steam-account-security-top-ways-to-stay-safe/1471/56</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 11 Mar 2010 21:32:25 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-1471-56</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/steam-account-security-top-ways-to-stay-safe/1471.rss">Steam Account Security - Top ways to stay safe</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Steam Account Security - Top ways to stay safe</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[FireTime]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>[COLOR=‘Red’]Edit: CatzEyes93</p>
<p>I am really sorry FireTime, but I dont want this thread to turn into a witch hunt.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p><em>tear</em> :’(</p>
<p>lol, thats fine. I was mostly posting the information because of how easy it was to find it. It was about 4% hacking, 6% view source, 80% google searches, and 10% whois queries.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/steam-account-security-top-ways-to-stay-safe/1471/55">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/steam-account-security-top-ways-to-stay-safe/1471/55</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 11 Mar 2010 08:50:45 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-1471-55</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/steam-account-security-top-ways-to-stay-safe/1471.rss">Steam Account Security - Top ways to stay safe</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Steam Account Security - Top ways to stay safe</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[bigfan421]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I wouldn’t worry about it too much.<br>
oh if you get an email that says that the steam servers have been hacked don’t believe it. I got suckered into a week without a steam account b/c i believed that load of BS</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/steam-account-security-top-ways-to-stay-safe/1471/54">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/steam-account-security-top-ways-to-stay-safe/1471/54</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 11 Mar 2010 05:27:38 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-1471-54</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/steam-account-security-top-ways-to-stay-safe/1471.rss">Steam Account Security - Top ways to stay safe</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Steam Account Security - Top ways to stay safe</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[sudpuzzer]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>Never tell your password to anyone.<br>
mrCSS. JUST GOT L4D2 FREE!!!: Hey, I just got free L4D2 and HL2:EP3, Want it? If you have ati <a data-bbcode="true">https://~burp~/</a> and if you have nvidia http:~burp~/<br>
mrCSS. JUST GOT L4D2 FREE!!!: Hey, I just got free L4D2 and HL2:EP3, Want it? If you have ati <a data-bbcode="true">https://~burp~/</a> and if you have nvidia <a data-bbcode="true">https://~burp~/</a><br>
sudpuzzer: ummm no<br>
mrCSS. JUST GOT L4D2 FREE!!!: oh ok<br>
mrCSS. JUST GOT L4D2 FREE!!!: sorry then<br>
sudpuzzer: it was a good try though. site looks real<br>
mrCSS. JUST GOT L4D2 FREE!!!: what?<br>
mrCSS. JUST GOT L4D2 FREE!!!: it is…<br>
sudpuzzer: psh. really. just cuz all the links work and it conveniently tells me that all download slots are full when I type in random stuff in the login / password boxes? hahaha<br>
mrCSS. JUST GOT L4D2 FREE!!!: -_-<br>
mrCSS. JUST GOT L4D2 FREE!!! is now Offline.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I’m kinda afraid I pissed him off and I’m gonna get hacked now. :FFFUUU:</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/steam-account-security-top-ways-to-stay-safe/1471/53">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/steam-account-security-top-ways-to-stay-safe/1471/53</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 11 Mar 2010 05:21:25 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-1471-53</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/steam-account-security-top-ways-to-stay-safe/1471.rss">Steam Account Security - Top ways to stay safe</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Steam Account Security - Top ways to stay safe</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[CatzEyes93]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Please see the first post and contact steam support to create a ticket.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/steam-account-security-top-ways-to-stay-safe/1471/52">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/steam-account-security-top-ways-to-stay-safe/1471/52</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 12 Feb 2010 18:20:39 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-1471-52</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/steam-account-security-top-ways-to-stay-safe/1471.rss">Steam Account Security - Top ways to stay safe</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Steam Account Security - Top ways to stay safe</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[nubber]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>hi,<br>
my steam just said that my account wos deactivated,<br>
but i never did any kind of cheating or something,<br>
i dont know what made them deactivate my account…<br>
this is really disappointing -.-<br>
help pls<br>
-Nubber</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/steam-account-security-top-ways-to-stay-safe/1471/51">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/steam-account-security-top-ways-to-stay-safe/1471/51</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 12 Feb 2010 18:06:56 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-1471-51</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/steam-account-security-top-ways-to-stay-safe/1471.rss">Steam Account Security - Top ways to stay safe</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Steam Account Security - Top ways to stay safe</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Trigger_Proximity]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Holy crap. Was I right with the packet loss thing? That was just a humongous guess! Yet somehow logical.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/steam-account-security-top-ways-to-stay-safe/1471/50">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/steam-account-security-top-ways-to-stay-safe/1471/50</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 12 Feb 2010 10:00:49 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-1471-50</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/steam-account-security-top-ways-to-stay-safe/1471.rss">Steam Account Security - Top ways to stay safe</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Steam Account Security - Top ways to stay safe</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Door]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I only get the message with SEVERE packet loss(usually about 67% and higher) which I get courtesy of my ISP.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/steam-account-security-top-ways-to-stay-safe/1471/49">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/steam-account-security-top-ways-to-stay-safe/1471/49</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 12 Feb 2010 09:59:36 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-1471-49</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/steam-account-security-top-ways-to-stay-safe/1471.rss">Steam Account Security - Top ways to stay safe</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Steam Account Security - Top ways to stay safe</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Lord_Grievous]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>That would explain why I don’t always get it, it just happens once in a while (once to be exact).</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/steam-account-security-top-ways-to-stay-safe/1471/48">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/steam-account-security-top-ways-to-stay-safe/1471/48</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 12 Feb 2010 09:55:58 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-1471-48</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/steam-account-security-top-ways-to-stay-safe/1471.rss">Steam Account Security - Top ways to stay safe</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
