<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Budget Gaming PC?</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/budget-gaming-pc/8923</link>
    <description>Hi, i was looking at this computer [url]https://www.newegg.ca/Product/Product.aspx?Item=N82E16883229285[/url] and this [url]https://www.newegg.com/Product/Product.aspx?Item=N82E16834246328[/url] laptop what would be a better choice for price and gaming,  or if i can do better for cheaper or same price, gotta be from a canadian site though  :slight_smile:  What kinda games can these rigs run though ?</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 18 Jun 2012 04:50:50 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Help and Support</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/budget-gaming-pc/8923.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Budget Gaming PC?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[amf66]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I would be very weary of that prebuilt PC. The cheaper prebuilts will come with dirt cheap, piece of shit power supplies and that’s the last place you want to cut corners on. Tell us your price range and we might be able to find you something better.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/budget-gaming-pc/8923/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/budget-gaming-pc/8923/5</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 Jun 2012 04:50:50 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8923-5</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/budget-gaming-pc/8923.rss">Budget Gaming PC?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Budget Gaming PC?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Gasher]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I know, that was a mouthful… some good ideas for others to consider though. Taking a couple weeks off, and a little bored… Too bad BMS isn’t ready. <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/frowning.png?v=9" title=":frowning:" class="emoji" alt=":frowning:"></p>
<p>I will just add that even a $400 HP Pavilion from BestBuy (like my wife’s) is a flimsy p.o.s. and is cobbled togther with what appears to be plastic, tin and solder. And I highly doubt I could squeeze a huge card like GTX570 etc in there… This is one of the reasons I like Extended ATX cases.</p>
<p>Give us a brief report/review after you have it couple days.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/budget-gaming-pc/8923/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/budget-gaming-pc/8923/4</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 Jun 2012 04:02:03 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8923-4</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/budget-gaming-pc/8923.rss">Budget Gaming PC?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Budget Gaming PC?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[moehog0]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Alright, that really helped a lot, but yea its hard to find used stuff here and just easiest to by a pre built system. Ive been researching a lot though. I looked at all the parts in that Cyber power pc and theyll do what i want its pretty cheap for the stuff i get in it, im pretty sure thatll be the pc i buy. In the future i may upgrade but a quad core processor, 8 gb ram, Radeon 6670 1gb, should all be enough for the stuff i want to do for awhile into the future. So thanks for your reply, helped me understand what i want haha!<br>
Cheers!</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/budget-gaming-pc/8923/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/budget-gaming-pc/8923/3</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 17 Jun 2012 23:45:37 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8923-3</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/budget-gaming-pc/8923.rss">Budget Gaming PC?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Budget Gaming PC?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Gasher]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>My personal opinion: This may sound counter-intuitive to some, but if I were on a tight budget and wanted the absolute best bang for my buck, I would try to get a <span class="bbcode-b">used</span> high-end pc that is about 1.5-2 years old. There are many things on a <span class="bbcode-b">nice</span> pc from a couple years ago that are not likely to become obsolete any time soon, and when picked up at a discount, will really be handy as you upgrade. For instance, a really nice mid or full tower <span class="bbcode-i">extended atx </span>case with at least 600W power supply (pref 750+). It is certainly within the realm of possibility to find something with a great case, 600W+, SLI-ready motherboard, Dual Core 3Ghz (or better) CPU, 4GB+ of RAM, 500GB+ HD and something like a nVidia GTX460 video card… for around $500US. To me, this is a better $500 spent. I would much rather buy something like what I have outlined, built by an enthusiast, than on some factory-built-cookie-cutter pc, put together by slave labor. I have been building my own pcs for eons (always dual-processor workstations actually) and would not have it any onther way.</p>
<p>But you either need to do your homework or make sure you know someone (or forums) to run shit up flagpole before you purchase, so that you don’t unknowingly end up buying some turd. And do not get a laptop for gaming… that is plain silly imho.</p>
<p>Of course, if you live way out in the boonies in CA and do not have many listed on craigslist etc within driving distance, then forget everything I just said.</p>
<p>Good luck bro</p>
<p>Edit: That CyberPower (cyber… really? hehe) does have decent specs for $571 and it does come with win7 x64 (something to always consider in cost of DIY pc), but jesus that thing looks flimsy… yikes! Of course, I have a Lian Li case that was over $500… so I am not an authority on low-end systems. And do not be fooled by their use of the word ULTRA… there is nothing ULTRA about that pc. These types of bargain pcs are always built with the absolute cheapest parts. No one here will disagree with that, I am fairly sure.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/budget-gaming-pc/8923/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/budget-gaming-pc/8923/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 17 Jun 2012 02:32:13 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8923-2</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/budget-gaming-pc/8923.rss">Budget Gaming PC?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Budget Gaming PC?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[moehog0]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Hi, i was looking at this computer <a href="https://www.newegg.ca/Product/Product.aspx?Item=N82E16883229285" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://www.newegg.ca/Product/Product.aspx?Item=N82E16883229285</a> and this <a href="https://www.newegg.com/Product/Product.aspx?Item=N82E16834246328" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://www.newegg.com/Product/Product.aspx?Item=N82E16834246328</a> laptop what would be a better choice for price and gaming,  or if i can do better for cheaper or same price, gotta be from a canadian site though  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=9" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:">  What kinda games can these rigs run though ?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/budget-gaming-pc/8923/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/budget-gaming-pc/8923/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 16 Jun 2012 20:22:24 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8923-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/budget-gaming-pc/8923.rss">Budget Gaming PC?</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
