<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Supreme Commander 2 to run on Steam</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/supreme-commander-2-to-run-on-steam/2518</link>
    <description>
[quote]
Taylor announced another improvement to the game, this time affecting multiplayer: SupCom 2 will be completely supported and integrated into Steam and utilise Valve&#39;s superior server browser. GPG net will not be making the transition. 
[/quote]
As the quote above states, Chris Taylor has announced that SupCom2 will follow the way of Modern Warfare2 and require steam. Heres the link to the [url=&#39;https://pc.ign.com/articles/105/1058207p1.html&#39;]full article[/url]. I am happy to hear this personally, and hope they offer SupCom1 on Steam aswell, (I only have Forged Alliance). 

I am a little wary of their changes to resource aquisition and usage. Sure the resources are a bit difficult for the beginner to pick up, but they aren&#39;t to difficult once you play for a bit. I liked that fact that I only had to manage 2 resources and I couldn&#39;t run out of either. SupCom2 sounds amazing, but I hope they don&#39;t make what made SupCom1 great watered down just to appeal to a broader audience. Thoughts?</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 08 Jan 2010 09:59:52 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Technology and Gaming</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/supreme-commander-2-to-run-on-steam/2518.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Supreme Commander 2 to run on Steam</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Sitten_duck]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>Taylor announced another improvement to the game, this time affecting multiplayer: SupCom 2 will be completely supported and integrated into Steam and utilise Valve’s superior server browser. GPG net will not be making the transition.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>As the quote above states, Chris Taylor has announced that SupCom2 will follow the way of Modern Warfare2 and require steam. Heres the link to the <a href="https://pc.ign.com/articles/105/1058207p1.html" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">full article</a>. I am happy to hear this personally, and hope they offer SupCom1 on Steam aswell, (I only have Forged Alliance).</p>
<p>I am a little wary of their changes to resource aquisition and usage. Sure the resources are a bit difficult for the beginner to pick up, but they aren’t to difficult once you play for a bit. I liked that fact that I only had to manage 2 resources and I couldn’t run out of either. SupCom2 sounds amazing, but I hope they don’t make what made SupCom1 great watered down just to appeal to a broader audience. Thoughts?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/supreme-commander-2-to-run-on-steam/2518/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/supreme-commander-2-to-run-on-steam/2518/1</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Jan 2010 09:59:52 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2518-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/supreme-commander-2-to-run-on-steam/2518.rss">Supreme Commander 2 to run on Steam</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
