<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Ladders, audio normalization, and other nuisance bugs</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/ladders-audio-normalization-and-other-nuisance-bugs/10146</link>
    <description>The only thing that drives me nuts about this game is ladders.  I&#39;ve died and lost more health more times trying to get both on and off ladders (at both the top of a ladder and bottom) that I&#39;ve lost count.  There is little to no rhyme or reason as to what key combination/direction will work to get me on and off a ladder.  Jumping works sometimes, using WASD works sometimes, but mostly I just end up falling 20 stories and break both legs.  The effect is complete with bone crushing sound effects.  And death follows after that.  Who knows - headcrabs might zombify me.

So far I&#39;ve avoided having to be in a major battle while attempting to get off of a ladder and then humiliatingly fall down and die.  Stairs seem to be a constant of every major battle so far.

The music in this game is nice, but for some reason is REALLY loud compared to the rest of the in-game audio.  That could just be my audio settings though.  However I&#39;m pretty sure I&#39;m using the default audio settings.  Some of the voice acting seems a bit quiet too compared to other voices, so it might be a good idea to evaluate each audio track and normalize the audio so it is all at a similar volume in-game for the default game audio settings.

The crowbar response time, when it isn&#39;t attacking anything, is rather sluggish given the short distance it travels on screen.  When it is attacking something, it speeds up significantly even though it travels a longer distance.  It sucks when I miss a flying headcrab and then have to wait for the crowbar to reset to just barely miss the next one.  Then again, headcrabs only cost a couple health.  It has been forever since I touched HL1, maybe it did the same thing, but it feels weird.

Jumping and jump-crouching are occasionally very flaky.  Especially jumping onto pipes and other irregularly shaped objects.

Sight shooting doesn&#39;t work any better than crosshair shooting.  It actually feels worse, IMO.

The game occasionally crashes back to Windows.  This might have to do with the version of the SDK being used.  The automatic quick saves really help a lot to get back into the game and not feel like a crash is a terrible fail.  I remember HL2 crashing and thus forcing me to redo entire sections all over again because distances between automatic saves were few and far between.

Quick saves occasionally happen at very inopportune times.  When a player has less than 35 health, they probably don&#39;t want a quick save to happen unless the next section is a cakewalk and/or contains a lot of health kits.  I&#39;ve survived an extended 15 health quick save reload but only barely (4 health left before finding a medkit).

Other than those issues, this remake is awesome and your team did a very, very good job.  The attention to detail is incredible.  I was only expecting some cheesy little rendition of a few scenes of HL1 and instead we&#39;ve all been treated to a damn awesome game.  Plus, it is free.  For what I paid for it, I really should not be complaining, so take these gripes with a grain of salt and this last paragraph is really what matters  :slight_smile:</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 16 Sep 2012 11:11:02 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>In-game Issues (Mod)</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/ladders-audio-normalization-and-other-nuisance-bugs/10146.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Ladders, audio normalization, and other nuisance bugs</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[cobalt358]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>some things here i have to agree with.</p>
<p>for some reason the iron sights on the revolver feels off, there have been more than a few times when i thought something was lined up perfectly only to miss, maybe i’m not as good an aim as i thought i was but i’ve found normal crosshair aim to be much more accurate in gereral.</p>
<p>the music has been bugging out on me too, i’ve got it turned all the way down (i like to keep the atmosphere as realistic as possible, my gordon doesn’t own an ipod) but occasionally it’s turns on by itself, i have to quit the game and restart to get rid of it. not game breaking, but immersion killing for sure (the music itself is great, but i would rather listen to it separately).</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/ladders-audio-normalization-and-other-nuisance-bugs/10146/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/ladders-audio-normalization-and-other-nuisance-bugs/10146/6</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 16 Sep 2012 11:11:02 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-10146-6</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/ladders-audio-normalization-and-other-nuisance-bugs/10146.rss">Ladders, audio normalization, and other nuisance bugs</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Ladders, audio normalization, and other nuisance bugs</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[fdisk]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I may have just gotten used to the frustrating ladder mechanic as it has been present in EVERY Half-Life game since Half-Life 1 and most mods too. Pressing E (or use if you’ve reassigned it) is a nice tip however I find here and there you get off the ladder the wrong way, most notably in Power Up when you climb up to meet the turret after the security guard tells you there are “things” in the way. Audio normalization is a peeve of mine and I find it often destroys dynamic content. Most of the times the music comes on at a time when sound cues are not too important. If you have a nice speaker set or a good set of in-ear monitors or headphones it makes a huge difference as I find the soundtrack’s abstract qualities to fit the game very well. I recall the crowbar always being slower when striking nothing as well, something to be aware of if you want to use your crowbar like Barry Bonds, it’s all about timing or you will be fated to scrambling around trying to find where it landed (the crowbar is especially useful on the lift in Unforeseen Consequences). I find jumping, especially crouch-jumping to be a flaky move in the first place so I have no opinion there. I do have to agree on the sight-shooting it’s not very useful at all, HOWEVER it is a hell of a lot of fun to feel like you’re blowing away aliens and evil Marines behind those tritium sights and seeing the revolver action. That makes the mechanic well worth it IMO.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/ladders-audio-normalization-and-other-nuisance-bugs/10146/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/ladders-audio-normalization-and-other-nuisance-bugs/10146/5</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 16 Sep 2012 08:21:24 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-10146-5</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/ladders-audio-normalization-and-other-nuisance-bugs/10146.rss">Ladders, audio normalization, and other nuisance bugs</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Ladders, audio normalization, and other nuisance bugs</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Executor]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I’m not sure what this ladder issue is that keeps being mentioned, for me they work just like in HL2.  I can mount the ladder just by walking toward it (even at the top of the ladder), and dismount either by jumping off or just continuing to walk forward when I reach the top/bottom of the ladder.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/ladders-audio-normalization-and-other-nuisance-bugs/10146/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/ladders-audio-normalization-and-other-nuisance-bugs/10146/4</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 16 Sep 2012 07:41:23 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-10146-4</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/ladders-audio-normalization-and-other-nuisance-bugs/10146.rss">Ladders, audio normalization, and other nuisance bugs</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Ladders, audio normalization, and other nuisance bugs</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[sourcegamer101]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>The devs either need to switch the ladder method to Counter-Strike Source’s, or add a tip called:</p>
<p>E - Mount/Dismount from ladder</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/ladders-audio-normalization-and-other-nuisance-bugs/10146/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/ladders-audio-normalization-and-other-nuisance-bugs/10146/3</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 16 Sep 2012 05:20:57 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-10146-3</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/ladders-audio-normalization-and-other-nuisance-bugs/10146.rss">Ladders, audio normalization, and other nuisance bugs</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Ladders, audio normalization, and other nuisance bugs</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Lazy_Figure]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Do you use the “E” key with ladders?  I don’t have too much trouble when pressing “E” while facing a ladder to climb, then pressing “E” again while facing in the direction I want to get off.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/ladders-audio-normalization-and-other-nuisance-bugs/10146/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/ladders-audio-normalization-and-other-nuisance-bugs/10146/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 16 Sep 2012 04:49:52 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-10146-2</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/ladders-audio-normalization-and-other-nuisance-bugs/10146.rss">Ladders, audio normalization, and other nuisance bugs</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Ladders, audio normalization, and other nuisance bugs</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[mrcrashbug]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>The only thing that drives me nuts about this game is ladders.  I’ve died and lost more health more times trying to get both on and off ladders (at both the top of a ladder and bottom) that I’ve lost count.  There is little to no rhyme or reason as to what key combination/direction will work to get me on and off a ladder.  Jumping works sometimes, using WASD works sometimes, but mostly I just end up falling 20 stories and break both legs.  The effect is complete with bone crushing sound effects.  And death follows after that.  Who knows - headcrabs might zombify me.</p>
<p>So far I’ve avoided having to be in a major battle while attempting to get off of a ladder and then humiliatingly fall down and die.  Stairs seem to be a constant of every major battle so far.</p>
<p>The music in this game is nice, but for some reason is REALLY loud compared to the rest of the in-game audio.  That could just be my audio settings though.  However I’m pretty sure I’m using the default audio settings.  Some of the voice acting seems a bit quiet too compared to other voices, so it might be a good idea to evaluate each audio track and normalize the audio so it is all at a similar volume in-game for the default game audio settings.</p>
<p>The crowbar response time, when it isn’t attacking anything, is rather sluggish given the short distance it travels on screen.  When it is attacking something, it speeds up significantly even though it travels a longer distance.  It sucks when I miss a flying headcrab and then have to wait for the crowbar to reset to just barely miss the next one.  Then again, headcrabs only cost a couple health.  It has been forever since I touched HL1, maybe it did the same thing, but it feels weird.</p>
<p>Jumping and jump-crouching are occasionally very flaky.  Especially jumping onto pipes and other irregularly shaped objects.</p>
<p>Sight shooting doesn’t work any better than crosshair shooting.  It actually feels worse, IMO.</p>
<p>The game occasionally crashes back to Windows.  This might have to do with the version of the SDK being used.  The automatic quick saves really help a lot to get back into the game and not feel like a crash is a terrible fail.  I remember HL2 crashing and thus forcing me to redo entire sections all over again because distances between automatic saves were few and far between.</p>
<p>Quick saves occasionally happen at very inopportune times.  When a player has less than 35 health, they probably don’t want a quick save to happen unless the next section is a cakewalk and/or contains a lot of health kits.  I’ve survived an extended 15 health quick save reload but only barely (4 health left before finding a medkit).</p>
<p>Other than those issues, this remake is awesome and your team did a very, very good job.  The attention to detail is incredible.  I was only expecting some cheesy little rendition of a few scenes of HL1 and instead we’ve all been treated to a damn awesome game.  Plus, it is free.  For what I paid for it, I really should not be complaining, so take these gripes with a grain of salt and this last paragraph is really what matters  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=9" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/ladders-audio-normalization-and-other-nuisance-bugs/10146/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/ladders-audio-normalization-and-other-nuisance-bugs/10146/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 16 Sep 2012 04:30:50 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-10146-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/ladders-audio-normalization-and-other-nuisance-bugs/10146.rss">Ladders, audio normalization, and other nuisance bugs</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
