<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Guitarists! Report for duty.</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/guitarists-report-for-duty/4315</link>
    <description>I want some advice on recording interfaces for the computer, I figured some guitarists might know about it. Rather than buy expensive hardware effects pedals, I want to route the signal into my computer so I can apply VST effects to it. I know for example there&#39;s Line6 pod, but it&#39;s kind of expensive I think. 

Also, if anyone needs a cheap guitar stand, PM me.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 07 Jun 2010 12:57:53 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Show Off</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/guitarists-report-for-duty/4315.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Guitarists! Report for duty.</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[MikeyCgangster]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I use the Native Instruments Session I/O along with Guitar Rig 3 XE.  I also have an M-Audio midi-to-USB interface.  Both are excellent.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/guitarists-report-for-duty/4315/22">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/guitarists-report-for-duty/4315/22</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 07 Jun 2010 12:57:53 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-4315-22</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/guitarists-report-for-duty/4315.rss">Guitarists! Report for duty.</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Guitarists! Report for duty.</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Deimos]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Thank you sir.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p><img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=9" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji only-emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
<p>What do you play? acoustic, electric? What do you prefer?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I mostly play electric as i am quite the metal head, i have 3 electrics and an acoustic because i enjoy john butler trio and stuff like that.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/guitarists-report-for-duty/4315/21">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/guitarists-report-for-duty/4315/21</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 07 Jun 2010 12:24:24 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-4315-21</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/guitarists-report-for-duty/4315.rss">Guitarists! Report for duty.</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Guitarists! Report for duty.</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[_amp_955_hlberg]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Deimos">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/d/5f9b8f/40.png" class="avatar"> Deimos:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>reporting for duty sir!</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Epic Avatar you got thar…</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/guitarists-report-for-duty/4315/20">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/guitarists-report-for-duty/4315/20</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 06 Jun 2010 08:16:50 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-4315-20</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/guitarists-report-for-duty/4315.rss">Guitarists! Report for duty.</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Guitarists! Report for duty.</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Note-anator]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=9" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji only-emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
<p>What do you play? acoustic, electric? What do you prefer?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/guitarists-report-for-duty/4315/19">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/guitarists-report-for-duty/4315/19</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 05 Jun 2010 20:25:29 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-4315-19</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/guitarists-report-for-duty/4315.rss">Guitarists! Report for duty.</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Guitarists! Report for duty.</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Deimos]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>reporting for duty sir!</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/guitarists-report-for-duty/4315/18">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/guitarists-report-for-duty/4315/18</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 05 Jun 2010 14:43:34 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-4315-18</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/guitarists-report-for-duty/4315.rss">Guitarists! Report for duty.</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Guitarists! Report for duty.</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Note-anator]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>EXCELLENT choice with the JX-8P</p>
<p>I did an eight month tour across Canada with a JX-8P, and that keyboard kicked ass in the tough department. It was amazing.</p>
<p>Well, you are well on your way it seems, and that is most excellent.</p>
<p>Some of the DVDs are better than others of course, and that is why a public Library may be worth considering. The one I (cough) watched, was nothing more than some guy tryign to blow smoke up my ass. NOt a whole lot in there are all. The other few, rocked. One fellow worked on teh Thriller album, and he KNEW his game. Impressive. I wish I could rememeber his name now.</p>
<p>Thanks for the update on the Proteus - that is seriously cool. I have been out of the music thing for a while, so have obviously fallen behind the times.</p>
<p>The joys of getting old.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/guitarists-report-for-duty/4315/17">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/guitarists-report-for-duty/4315/17</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jun 2010 05:44:21 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-4315-17</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/guitarists-report-for-duty/4315.rss">Guitarists! Report for duty.</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Guitarists! Report for duty.</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[mattemuse]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I’ve been playing keyboard for maybe 6 months. Got a couple of books on music theory that I’m still trying to work though. I’ll give the DVD lessons a shot sometime, Youtube video lessons tend to be shit.</p>
<p>About the JV1080/proteus, that’s the type of thing that can be done purely in software. In fact I believe E-mu sells the Proteus sound banks as a standalone software instrument. Some of their modules’ banks are available for free on their website!</p>
<p>If space is an issue for you, sell a couple of your extras! You might be surprised how easy it is to get a good price for that kind of stuff on eBay, and you seem to  have a few workstations that are covering the same territory. My current enthusiasm is 100% financed by eBay sales of music gear I never used.</p>
<p>Space is an issue for me as well, but my next acquisition may be a JX-8p - very similar to your -3p, except the 8p has a solid midi implementation so it can be edited with software as opposed to needing a hardware editor expansion which is just as expensive as the synth. If I get an 8p I’ll really have to get rid of my ESQ, I’m limiting myself to a total of one controller keyboard to hook up to the PC and one “color” keyboard to keep myself entertained. I’ll have a garage-full of these things if I let myself slip.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/guitarists-report-for-duty/4315/16">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/guitarists-report-for-duty/4315/16</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jun 2010 04:57:35 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-4315-16</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/guitarists-report-for-duty/4315.rss">Guitarists! Report for duty.</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Guitarists! Report for duty.</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Note-anator]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="mattemuse">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/m/dc4da7/40.png" class="avatar"> mattemuse:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I’ve always been more interested in keyboards that sound like “themselves” rather than ones that accurately emulate other instruments, and for that intangible quality I don’t think the highest bit depth or the best A/D converter can substitute for the “character” of certain vintage sound architecture.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I SO agree. I love the old stuff too, but it is a room thing for me. Still, as you say… The Ensoniq was/is an EXCELLENT keyboard. I was considering that one as well. There is so many ways a person can go.</p>
<p>Since your current Keyboard is also able to be used as a controller, one thing that may be of interest, would be to consider say … an old Proteus Module. Depending on which one a person gets, they come pre-loaded with a shit load of high quality sound, are inexpensive, compact, multitimberal out the ass, are upgradable, and have some rather funky wave editing, and sound scaping to play with. If I were to find one in good shape, I would SO be all over that. (Used ot have one, and I still get wet dreams over the sound quality that thing could push out) Once you have that hooked up, it is simply a matter of adding the extras.</p>
<p>That is what I have the JV-1080 for this point (Again, I am not playing at this point, but moduals are well worth having - especially for live gigging. It is loaded out the ass with expansions, and has the same sort of features as the Proteus. Only, the Proteus eats it alive for accurate accustiv instrument sounds, but not even close with sound architecturing.</p>
<p>AS for the Waveform structing, that is what I bought the Wave station for. Mine needs a new transformer though - The keyboard works very well, but it has a buzz. They were known for that - The internal transformers all have this goofy vibration thing that gets worse as they get older. They start out silent.as time goes on, the main insulation board that seprates the coils comes a bit loose, and begins to buzz. No real biggy, but drives me mental.</p>
<p>The joys of old gear. I would love to get my hands on some of the varous old gear.</p>
<p>Oh, DUH… I also have a JX-3P. I just about wet my pants when I got this one… I used to have one, it was the first one I ever Bought. I sold it (along with some other old tasty gear -Yes, I still have the bruises from kicking myself in teh ass) to upgrade. Anyways, I love the old thing. I also want to get the old old programer box that was a hands on fast programming tool, but again, I am not so much into it anymore. One day, but just not today.</p>
<p>So, enough of my prattle - How long have you been playing for?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/guitarists-report-for-duty/4315/15">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/guitarists-report-for-duty/4315/15</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jun 2010 04:31:10 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-4315-15</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/guitarists-report-for-duty/4315.rss">Guitarists! Report for duty.</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Guitarists! Report for duty.</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[mattemuse]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Ok wow, you added a ton of info after I replied. Lets see, where to start… By “chops” I mean playing ability. It’s quite possible to compose music without being able to physically play an instrument in real time, but I eventually found it limiting creatively and I’m trying to correct my limitation there.</p>
<p>About gear, it’s a weakness of mine. Eventually I figured out most of the electronic instruments I had could be emulated 99-100% accuracy with hardware, and sold it all. Now I’m focused on obtaining instruments which have voice architecture that can’t be accurately emulated in software. For example your DW-8000 has components which cause soft overdrive/distortion in various parts of the signal path, and it has a voltage-controled resonant filter which saturates (adds harmonic content to) the audio output in ways that are difficult/expensive to imitate in software.</p>
<p>I’m guessing that’s one of yours that needs a battery replacement, eh? I’ve done some research into that instrument, with dead batteries they sell for peanuts - very enticing for bargain hunters. My current keyboard, an Ensoniq, is quite similar to that Korg but more oriented towards sound design. So much so that I find myself learning subtractive synthesis more often than I’m learn how to play the damn thing.<br>
So I may end up trading it in for a simpler and older Juno-60 clone (or more likely I’ll keep both &gt; <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/frowning.png?v=9" title=":frowning:" class="emoji" alt=":frowning:"> )</p>
<p>I’ve always been more interested in keyboards that sound like “themselves” rather than ones that accurately emulate other instruments, and for that intangible quality I don’t think the highest bit depth or the best A/D converter can substitute for the “character” of certain vintage sound architecture.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/guitarists-report-for-duty/4315/14">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/guitarists-report-for-duty/4315/14</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jun 2010 04:00:06 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-4315-14</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/guitarists-report-for-duty/4315.rss">Guitarists! Report for duty.</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Guitarists! Report for duty.</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Note-anator]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I am not sure what you mean by chops? (Sorry, I am a bit slow with the terms)</p>
<p>I am assuming you are meaning music arrangement, or computer editing of said recordings?</p>
<p>This may sound a bit gay, but it is well worth doing.</p>
<p>I have a lot of natural ability in music. Have an amazing ear for hearing things. I do not read music, but can play most things i decide to. After playing lots and lots, I realized that my total ability was somewhat rather lacking - so, I went to eh Library, and took out some teaching DVD’s from varoius keyboard pros - Learned lots of neat licks and such. The blues DVD Rocked - Very helpful. (I did the same sort of thing with Photography - I took out basic learning, even though I do alright  - Amazed at what I didn’t know…)</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/guitarists-report-for-duty/4315/13">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/guitarists-report-for-duty/4315/13</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jun 2010 03:09:12 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-4315-13</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/guitarists-report-for-duty/4315.rss">Guitarists! Report for duty.</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Guitarists! Report for duty.</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[mattemuse]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Ah, “players” synths  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/smiley.png?v=9" title=":smiley:" class="emoji" alt=":smiley:">  I’ve always been more interested in composition/sound design, but I’m making a concerted effort to learn some chops. Any advice?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/guitarists-report-for-duty/4315/12">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/guitarists-report-for-duty/4315/12</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jun 2010 02:47:37 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-4315-12</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/guitarists-report-for-duty/4315.rss">Guitarists! Report for duty.</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Guitarists! Report for duty.</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Note-anator]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I have a few - Some of them need some work, but I am so busy with Railroading, photography and gardening, it is hard to find time to make it worth the fixes - Batteries likely need replacing on a few and such. Besides, with Reason (And a few other lesser plug ins and such) so much of the old gear is not worth setting up. If a person wants say … an old korg  M1, add in and away we go - One controller, and power machine can replace all the old stuff. Though, to be honest, I LOVE playing the Kurziel - I may end up trading it all in on one of their newer work stations. Then again, there are sme POWERFUL machines for a reasonable dollar. The Emax was a 16 bit machine. For the most part, I thik most CDs are pressed with 16 encoding - so the extra 8 bit a person may get out of a higher end machine is still compressed at mix down, so am not too sure if there is a gain.</p>
<p>As well, it is the A/D converters that really is where the rubber hits the road. Some folks go for the whole - “Yeah, but this thing has 52X oversample” (Add a few hundred bucks onto the player/machine/instrument) Ummm So? Oversample only helps to improve accuracy - If it read right with one sample, (Which most do) then a person pays for the needless 51X… I would think that it is better to get a higher quality A/D conver… Just sayin’.</p>
<p>The Toy list…</p>
<p>Korg Wave Station<br>
Roland Xp-50<br>
Kurziel 2000<br>
Roland Jv-1080<br>
Roland JX-3p<br>
Korg DW-8000</p>
<p>Ovation Model 1617 (Old, but amazing)<br>
Ibenez electric / Peavy amp<br>
VS-880 EX</p>
<p>Microphones</p>
<p>Sennheiser MD431 (An amazing mic - The Sure SM-58s (at the time I bought my mic) were mesuring 25% distortion at 125 db. Mine does not even begin to measure it until close to the same levels. I did a bunch of touring here are there, and had a lot of fun doing it, but eventually, guilty pleasures have to be abandon at some point.)</p>
<p>AKG C3000 (For a cheeper studio mic, this thing kicks major ass - it is amazingly sensitive - I was messing around with it some time back, and while recording, I was getting this goofy micro slap back of sound - it turned out to be the mic picking up an echo off the wall - it was a small room)</p>
<hr>
<p> One day I will get back into it, but for now, too much going on.</p>
<p>(Heh… was muzing about if I were to attempt a sound track from Black Mesa (I am rather good with composing) what kind of track would the MOD need? I can see a HUGE orchestra score - but then, i am rather busy…</p>
<p>(I was going to go into music in a pro way, but so far, too many other things have gotten in the way - good things, so no complaints.)</p>
<p>What gear do you have?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/guitarists-report-for-duty/4315/11">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/guitarists-report-for-duty/4315/11</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jun 2010 02:40:05 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-4315-11</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/guitarists-report-for-duty/4315.rss">Guitarists! Report for duty.</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Guitarists! Report for duty.</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[mattemuse]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>no worries, i’m more or less on top of it, just hoping for some recommendations since using my computer’s line in and an adapter cable isn’t cutting it anymore.</p>
<p>What “old synths” do you have? I know the title says “guitarists” but synths were actually the inspiration for this thread.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/guitarists-report-for-duty/4315/10">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/guitarists-report-for-duty/4315/10</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jun 2010 00:28:36 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-4315-10</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/guitarists-report-for-duty/4315.rss">Guitarists! Report for duty.</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Guitarists! Report for duty.</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Note-anator]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Cool.</p>
<p>Hmmm can ask a buddy of mine what his take is, as he was right into/still keeps up with/was a pro sound engineer.</p>
<p>Yeah - the usb2 latency thing can bite sometimes.</p>
<p>Wish I could help more - If I get yacking with him, I will see what he thinks.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/guitarists-report-for-duty/4315/9">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/guitarists-report-for-duty/4315/9</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jun 2010 00:23:19 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-4315-9</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/guitarists-report-for-duty/4315.rss">Guitarists! Report for duty.</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Guitarists! Report for duty.</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[mattemuse]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Note-anator">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/n/c2a13f/40.png" class="avatar"> Note-anator:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I use a VS-880EX as an interface .</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I can’t find much information on that thing, it looks like a self-contained multitrack recorder. It obviously interfaces with a computer somehow if you’re using it in conjunction with Reason, but what I’m looking for might be a little simpler - just one or two line-ins and midi in/out with a decent pre-amp that sends audio data with very little latency to my computer through a USB2 connection.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/guitarists-report-for-duty/4315/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/guitarists-report-for-duty/4315/8</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jun 2010 00:14:23 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-4315-8</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/guitarists-report-for-duty/4315.rss">Guitarists! Report for duty.</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Guitarists! Report for duty.</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Note-anator]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Hmmm</p>
<p>I use a VS-880EX as an interface (When I record - and that is not often) with Reason software for mixing. You can get a VS-880 EX dirt cheep, and the signal to noise ratio is around 0.05% Not bad for an older 16 bit machine.</p>
<p>I have lots of other toys (Old Synths and such) but Reason has lots of mixer, VST, wynth plug ins - Routing is a breeze - bang for the buck, it is a good way to fly. A bit pricey for the start up, but lots of value.</p>
<p>Old stuff, but it works well.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/guitarists-report-for-duty/4315/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/guitarists-report-for-duty/4315/7</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 31 May 2010 23:41:19 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-4315-7</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/guitarists-report-for-duty/4315.rss">Guitarists! Report for duty.</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Guitarists! Report for duty.</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Diabol]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I’m also using Toneport GX, really good stuff.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/guitarists-report-for-duty/4315/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/guitarists-report-for-duty/4315/6</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 31 May 2010 21:48:08 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-4315-6</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/guitarists-report-for-duty/4315.rss">Guitarists! Report for duty.</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Guitarists! Report for duty.</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Bolteh]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I don’t really notice any noise + it has a noisegate anyway.</p>
<p>Not sure if they still make the GX, but I’m sure they have an equivalent for the same hardware/price</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/guitarists-report-for-duty/4315/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/guitarists-report-for-duty/4315/5</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 31 May 2010 21:09:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-4315-5</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/guitarists-report-for-duty/4315.rss">Guitarists! Report for duty.</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Guitarists! Report for duty.</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Shadi]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Bolteh">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/b/ecae2f/40.png" class="avatar"> Bolteh:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I’m using a €60-70 Toneport GX (Line 6) to get the signal in. It comes with its own software (Gearbox, but I don’t like it that much), but works perfectly with any other amp-sim software (Amplitube, Guitar Rig… I prefer Guitar Rig). But I’m sure you can find some USB interfaces that don’t come with their own software for less.</p>
<p>Lately I’ve been, messing around with the amp designer in Logic Pro, can get some nice effects with that as well, but it’s not that good at simulating real amps (Guitar Rig beats everything else at that aspect, tbh).</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>once again…you spoiled bastard xO</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/guitarists-report-for-duty/4315/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/guitarists-report-for-duty/4315/4</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 31 May 2010 20:09:17 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-4315-4</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/guitarists-report-for-duty/4315.rss">Guitarists! Report for duty.</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Guitarists! Report for duty.</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[mattemuse]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>That’s a very reasonable price, I’m surprised. Is the noise floor adequate? The interface I’m looking most closely at is a M-audio fast track for around the same price, although i can’t decide if i need an interface that also has MIDI I/O.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/guitarists-report-for-duty/4315/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/guitarists-report-for-duty/4315/3</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 31 May 2010 20:01:15 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-4315-3</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/guitarists-report-for-duty/4315.rss">Guitarists! Report for duty.</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Guitarists! Report for duty.</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Bolteh]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I’m using a €60-70 Toneport GX (Line 6) to get the signal in. It comes with its own software (Gearbox, but I don’t like it that much), but works perfectly with any other amp-sim software (Amplitube, Guitar Rig… I prefer Guitar Rig). But I’m sure you can find some USB interfaces that don’t come with their own software for less.</p>
<p>Lately I’ve been, messing around with the amp designer in Logic Pro, can get some nice effects with that as well, but it’s not that good at simulating real amps (Guitar Rig beats everything else at that aspect, tbh).</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/guitarists-report-for-duty/4315/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/guitarists-report-for-duty/4315/2</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 31 May 2010 19:28:05 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-4315-2</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/guitarists-report-for-duty/4315.rss">Guitarists! Report for duty.</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Guitarists! Report for duty.</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[mattemuse]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I want some advice on recording interfaces for the computer, I figured some guitarists might know about it. Rather than buy expensive hardware effects pedals, I want to route the signal into my computer so I can apply VST effects to it. I know for example there’s Line6 pod, but it’s kind of expensive I think.</p>
<p>Also, if anyone needs a cheap guitar stand, PM me.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/guitarists-report-for-duty/4315/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/guitarists-report-for-duty/4315/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 30 May 2010 19:24:07 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-4315-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/guitarists-report-for-duty/4315.rss">Guitarists! Report for duty.</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
