<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>I&#39;ve messed up with portals</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/ive-messed-up-with-portals/11760</link>
    <description>Hi

First of all :bms: is do awesome.

I&#39;ve got a crash when I was amazed on lucky pick of needed vent hole on big fan fly (bm_c1a4c)
I started to load-game and try another ones. Then I realised a portal behaviour.. So, I &#39;noclipped&#39; and fly to take a look. And, looks like it was in some actual portal place — I&#39;ve got a crash, giggled, and I would never write about it, but they said to tell a programmer  :smiley: 
[img]https://dl.dropbox.com/u/1846455/temp/BM/TOO.png[/img]

[url]https://dl.dropbox.com/u/1846455/temp/BM/hl2_4104_crash_2012_11_28T20_40_4C0.mdmp[/url]

Keep it up, you&#39;re the greatest (I&#39;m serious, you are)

Source SDK Base 2007 (all original installs)
Win7x64
Core2duo e4600 2.4G
GeForce GTX 460

PS I&#39;ve got some issues with an alternate ways-to-see in the game (you know like.. wow &quot;you have found a secret area&quot;) so, when I took a look at different vents I saw plenty of red lights and only one, on the top, with bright lamp (which is unreachable, I even tried to fly up from the very fan, and just then I assumed to use a damn cheat). So first of all I decided to examine the wrong ones, if there is some goodies..
I play [b]Black Mesa[/b] for a first time, slow and nice, checking every detail (cool details) So I hoped - one way is the correct, others are false or labyrinths, and maybe the hardest to get is &#39;the secret area&#39; one.
..I&#39;m sure plenty of oldskool gamers did just the same</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2012 21:51:25 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>In-game Issues (Mod)</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/ive-messed-up-with-portals/11760.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>I&#39;ve messed up with portals</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[sersoft]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I admit I thought there would be a secret vent there, but they all lead exactly where you need to go so it’s not a big deal.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/ive-messed-up-with-portals/11760/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/ive-messed-up-with-portals/11760/2</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2012 21:51:25 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11760-2</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/ive-messed-up-with-portals/11760.rss">I&#39;ve messed up with portals</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>I&#39;ve messed up with portals</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[ClockworkBastard]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Hi</p>
<p>First of all :bms: is do awesome.</p>
<p>I’ve got a crash when I was amazed on lucky pick of needed vent hole on big fan fly (bm_c1a4c)<br>
I started to load-game and try another ones. Then I realised a portal behaviour… So, I ‘noclipped’ and fly to take a look. And, looks like it was in some actual portal place — I’ve got a crash, giggled, and I would never write about it, but they said to tell a programmer  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/smiley.png?v=9" title=":smiley:" class="emoji" alt=":smiley:"><br>
<span alt="" class="broken-image" title="This image is broken"><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-unlink svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#unlink"></use></svg></span></p>
<p><a href="https://dl.dropbox.com/u/1846455/temp/BM/hl2_4104_crash_2012_11_28T20_40_4C0.mdmp" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://dl.dropbox.com/u/1846455/temp/BM/hl2_4104_crash_2012_11_28T20_40_4C0.mdmp</a></p>
<p>Keep it up, you’re the greatest (I’m serious, you are)</p>
<p>Source SDK Base 2007 (all original installs)<br>
Win7x64<br>
Core2duo e4600 2.4G<br>
GeForce GTX 460</p>
<p>PS I’ve got some issues with an alternate ways-to-see in the game (you know like… wow “you have found a secret area”) so, when I took a look at different vents I saw plenty of red lights and only one, on the top, with bright lamp (which is unreachable, I even tried to fly up from the very fan, and just then I assumed to use a damn cheat). So first of all I decided to examine the wrong ones, if there is some goodies…<br>
I play <span class="bbcode-b">Black Mesa</span> for a first time, slow and nice, checking every detail (cool details) So I hoped - one way is the correct, others are false or labyrinths, and maybe the hardest to get is ‘the secret area’ one.<br>
…I’m sure plenty of oldskool gamers did just the same</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/ive-messed-up-with-portals/11760/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/ive-messed-up-with-portals/11760/1</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2012 21:03:54 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11760-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/ive-messed-up-with-portals/11760.rss">I&#39;ve messed up with portals</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
