<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Everybody Draw Muhammad Day</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/everybody-draw-muhammad-day/4196</link>
    <description>A fun new pseudo-holiday has arrived at last! Depending on your time zone, that is. May 20th is Everybody Draw Muhammad Day.

So post your very own depiction of the prophet Muhammad :3

[img]https://fc03.deviantart.net/fs71/f/2010/139/a/3/a387a401f628180c102db0ae5073f4e1.png[/img]</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 20 May 2010 11:38:55 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Show Off</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/everybody-draw-muhammad-day/4196.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Everybody Draw Muhammad Day</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[CatzEyes93]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>1 post participating, 22 posts of folks arguing over the offensiveness of it.  I think this was more lame than offensive, but I will take the hit and close it.</p>
<p>Remember folks… the “report” button is for times you are offended or a troll needs to be taken care of.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/everybody-draw-muhammad-day/4196/25">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/everybody-draw-muhammad-day/4196/25</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 20 May 2010 11:38:55 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-4196-25</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/everybody-draw-muhammad-day/4196.rss">Everybody Draw Muhammad Day</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Everybody Draw Muhammad Day</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Hyperbyte]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="King_Kaddo">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/k/bcef8e/40.png" class="avatar"> King_Kaddo:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Yeah ok I know that people don’t like muslims</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Don’t generalize please.  Many people don’t mind Muslims. <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=9" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="King_Kaddo">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/k/bcef8e/40.png" class="avatar"> King_Kaddo:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>In the rules it isn’t even allowed to make any picture of him.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>What you have to understand, is that these are the rules that <span class="bbcode-i">you</span> have chosen to live by.  This doesn’t mean that <span class="bbcode-i">other</span> people also have to follow these rules.  Other people may choose to follow completely different rules.  This is what living in a free society is all about. <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=9" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
<p>Has anyone in here told you “You know, in the rules I believe in, Muslim religion isn’t allowed. You should change your religion”?  In general, people wouldn’t consider saying that, because you are given freedom to believe in what you want.  If you want to believe in God, hey - <span class="bbcode-i">you can</span>!  If you want to believe in Allah - <span class="bbcode-i">fine</span>!  If you want to believe in Sunday morning breakfast - <span class="bbcode-i">go ahead</span>!</p>
<p>But do not tell other poeple how to live.  This is not fair.  People give you your freedom to believe what you want.  This is a form of respect.  Return this respect by giving others the same freedom.</p>
<p>I agree however that freedom of speech and freedom of expression does not give one the right to freely offend people.  But, hey - <span class="bbcode-i">you</span> have chosen to visit this thread.  When I saw the title, “Draw Muhammad Day”, I knew for 100% certain that this thread would contain content that offends Muslims.  Yet here you are.  Why?  What brings you to this thread?  What moves you to visit this thread, knowing you are going to be offended?</p>
<p>My point is, basically, you are <span class="bbcode-i">choosing</span> to be offended.  The thread title contained plenty of warning.  If a Christian goes to a Goth concert, there’s a 100% chance they will be offended… they know this, so they don’t go.  This makes sense.</p>
<p>Yet here you are, seeking out the material which offends you, and then you start telling people “it is not allowed to make pictures” of <span class="bbcode-i">your</span> prophet because it offends you.  This makes absolutely no sense to me.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="King_Kaddo">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/k/bcef8e/40.png" class="avatar"> King_Kaddo:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>You are offending Mohammed and that’s what we don’t like.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I do very much appreciate this sentence.  You don’t <span class="bbcode-i">like</span> it.  That’s a very good way to argue your case and will actually get people to listen. <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=9" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:">  Many of your fellow Muslims start making threats, but this only fuels anger in people to create more and more offensive things for Muslims.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="King_Kaddo">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/k/bcef8e/40.png" class="avatar"> King_Kaddo:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>And srsly why do you people don’t just get it? You know nothing about Mohammed and draw caricatures of him. Where is the joke?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Honestly, I have no idea where the joke in this is.  I think it’s more about making a statement than actually making a joke.  Many Muslims try to force their view of things and their rules, onto other people.  It is a very natural defence mechanism for people to rebel once they feel their freedom is being taken away.</p>
<p>Lastly… obviously we live in a very modern society. A society where there is lots and lots of offensive material. There are many advertisements which offend people, there are many things being said that offend people.  This doesn’t just happen to Muslims. It also happens to Christians, atheïsts, children, women, men, you, me - everybody!  It is <span class="bbcode-i">your</span> job and your job alone to create a shield against these things and react appropriately.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/everybody-draw-muhammad-day/4196/24">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/everybody-draw-muhammad-day/4196/24</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 20 May 2010 11:34:27 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-4196-24</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/everybody-draw-muhammad-day/4196.rss">Everybody Draw Muhammad Day</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Everybody Draw Muhammad Day</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Trigger_Proximity]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Ok. I’ll start off by saying I’m agnostic. Just to absolve myself of any further religious flaming. Now onto the important stuff.<br>
Although this may of not been such a good idea in hindsight and when you think about it, it IS very offensive to some people but why should the opinion of one affect another? For example I don’t like Death Metal, it Doesn’t affect Elpants opinion of it. So therefore your opinion of what is offensive is not the same of what others find offensive. If you don’t like the content of something and you’re the MINORITY it would most likely be better for you to just leave and not pay attention to what’s going on there. In short, we do have the right to do what we want to do. Say what we want to say AND more importantly be as offensive as we want. That is the power of freedom of speech.<br>
Now I highly suggest you Cease and Desist 'less you become the target of a religious outburst.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/everybody-draw-muhammad-day/4196/23">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/everybody-draw-muhammad-day/4196/23</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 20 May 2010 10:56:44 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-4196-23</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/everybody-draw-muhammad-day/4196.rss">Everybody Draw Muhammad Day</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Everybody Draw Muhammad Day</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[nubber]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>im a muslim myself and even though im not very religious to be honest, i think its just<br>
rude to draw/publish these kind of art/humour or whatever you want to say to that.<br>
not that im hurt or soemthing, but i would never ever draw something like this, just for the sake of  politeness and respect of other people, even if i dont respect their religion.<br>
thats my opinion to that.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/everybody-draw-muhammad-day/4196/22">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/everybody-draw-muhammad-day/4196/22</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 20 May 2010 10:23:01 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-4196-22</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/everybody-draw-muhammad-day/4196.rss">Everybody Draw Muhammad Day</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Everybody Draw Muhammad Day</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Jerakal]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I think we all get your point, “I have the right to be as offensive as I want to be.”</p>
<p>The only question is, What do you gain from it?  A slight feeling of superiority over the “Easily offended masses”?  Yeah some people are uptight, yeah it gets annoying.  But purposely goading them is just as bad, if not more obnoxious.</p>
<p>Hell I’m not even disagreeing with you, I think censorship is wrong, but I also don’t like purposely pissing people off, who really haven’t done anything to me.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/everybody-draw-muhammad-day/4196/21">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/everybody-draw-muhammad-day/4196/21</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 20 May 2010 10:19:11 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-4196-21</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/everybody-draw-muhammad-day/4196.rss">Everybody Draw Muhammad Day</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Everybody Draw Muhammad Day</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Bolteh]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Maybe I just want to take a swing to shake them up a bit without hitting them?</p>
<p>Also, is it my fault of they lean towards me when I’m taking a swing?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/everybody-draw-muhammad-day/4196/20">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/everybody-draw-muhammad-day/4196/20</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 20 May 2010 10:10:01 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-4196-20</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/everybody-draw-muhammad-day/4196.rss">Everybody Draw Muhammad Day</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Everybody Draw Muhammad Day</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Jerakal]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>That doesn’t mean you have to aim for them.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/everybody-draw-muhammad-day/4196/19">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/everybody-draw-muhammad-day/4196/19</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 20 May 2010 10:08:35 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-4196-19</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/everybody-draw-muhammad-day/4196.rss">Everybody Draw Muhammad Day</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Everybody Draw Muhammad Day</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Bolteh]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>And some people’s noses are far bigger than others.</p>
<p>Same goes for toes, some toes are way longer than others.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/everybody-draw-muhammad-day/4196/18">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/everybody-draw-muhammad-day/4196/18</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 20 May 2010 10:03:36 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-4196-18</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/everybody-draw-muhammad-day/4196.rss">Everybody Draw Muhammad Day</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Everybody Draw Muhammad Day</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Jerakal]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>“The right to swing my fist ends where the other man’s nose begins.”</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/everybody-draw-muhammad-day/4196/17">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/everybody-draw-muhammad-day/4196/17</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 20 May 2010 09:56:15 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-4196-17</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/everybody-draw-muhammad-day/4196.rss">Everybody Draw Muhammad Day</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Everybody Draw Muhammad Day</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Bolteh]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>It may be a cheesy line, but it’s still a value of the western society. Everything in this world, everything we do, everything we say can and -will- offend someone. So what?</p>
<p>You guys saying that freedom of speech is bullshit and doesn’t apply to this situation are effectively offending those that firmly believe in freedom of speech. It’s the exact same situation, only difference is that the tables have turned and that the ones on the receiving end aren’t as uptight as you are.</p>
<p>And to answer your initial question: on Belgian television, racial slurs are used in shows and movies, and while explicit porn isn’t shown during daytime TV, there is the occasional boob/nipple/pubic hair that pops up during commercials or whatever. It’s not because the US (“land of freedom”) censorspretty much everything, that <span class="bbcode-i">my </span>country does.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/everybody-draw-muhammad-day/4196/16">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/everybody-draw-muhammad-day/4196/16</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 20 May 2010 09:54:21 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-4196-16</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/everybody-draw-muhammad-day/4196.rss">Everybody Draw Muhammad Day</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Everybody Draw Muhammad Day</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Neon_Knight]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Bolteh, I really don’t think you understand.</p>
<p>It’s not “censoring freedom of speech” to be considerate of people around you.<br>
Is it “censoring freedom of speech” when it’s socially unacceptable to use racial slurs in public?  Is it “censoring freedom of speech” when you can’t show porn on daytime TV or swear on a children’s TV show?</p>
<p>No, of course it’s not.  Don’t be a complete idiot.   It’s just being considerate of your audience and of those around you.</p>
<p>…freedom of speech, honestly… not everything has to be some lame political statement, you know…  and contrary to popular belief, “political correctness” isn’t actually evil.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/everybody-draw-muhammad-day/4196/15">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/everybody-draw-muhammad-day/4196/15</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 20 May 2010 09:45:56 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-4196-15</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/everybody-draw-muhammad-day/4196.rss">Everybody Draw Muhammad Day</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Everybody Draw Muhammad Day</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[brokenfridgehinge]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>It’s like those Dutch cartoonist guys that drew Mo in the newspaper or something and got assassinated by some Islam radicals. I guess they just don’t understand or accept the Western sense of humour.</p>
<p>edit: Ninja’d by Bolteh.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/everybody-draw-muhammad-day/4196/14">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/everybody-draw-muhammad-day/4196/14</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 20 May 2010 09:33:25 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-4196-14</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/everybody-draw-muhammad-day/4196.rss">Everybody Draw Muhammad Day</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Everybody Draw Muhammad Day</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Bolteh]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="King_Kaddo">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/k/bcef8e/40.png" class="avatar"> King_Kaddo:</div>
<blockquote>
<p><em>facepalm</em></p>
<p>You missed the point. That has nothing to do with mohammed caricatures. It isn’t our personal believe. We know that he existed.</p>
<p>It also doesn’t have to do something with the rules in our religion.<br>
Yeah ok I know that people don’t like muslims and have a lot prejudices but it’s not ok to draw pictures of Mohammed like that. (In the rules it isn’t even allowed to make any picture of him) You are offending Mohammed and that’s what we don’t like.</p>
<p>And srsly why do you people don’t just get it? You know nothing about Mohammed and draw caricatures of him. Where is the joke?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>It isn’t OK for Muslims. But why wouldn’t it be OK for us? The only reason why it wouldn’t be OK for us, is that we could risk our lives to a deranged fool like Osama.</p>
<p>I can somewhat understand why Muslims are upset with “The” Danish Muhammad cartoon (actually I don’t, since not a single Muslim seems to get the concept behind the cartoon, but I can see why they would think it was offensive). But this?</p>
<p>Anyway, I’m not religious myself, so my very essence, my very existence offends Allah/Muhammad/God/Buddah/Ganesha/martians. Should I stop living now?</p>
<p>Oh, and it isn’t about a joke. It’s specifically about depicting Muhammad. Not making fun of him or making him a terrorist or whatever. The very idea behind this pseudo-holiday is to show the world that we should stick to the freedom of speech, and not censor ourselves because a certain group of people might take offense to something they don’t understand.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/everybody-draw-muhammad-day/4196/13">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/everybody-draw-muhammad-day/4196/13</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 20 May 2010 09:30:29 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-4196-13</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/everybody-draw-muhammad-day/4196.rss">Everybody Draw Muhammad Day</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Everybody Draw Muhammad Day</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Shadi]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>meh, Bolteh don’t take the wrong Idea, maybe you don’t mean to offend or insult anyone, but it hurts the feelings of many, I for one, I find it offensive, but like what brokenfridgehinge said : this is the internet and shit happens everywhere in it, Raptor-Jesus, bomb-head Muhammad, and…are there any offensive sketches of Moses or even Buddha ?  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=9" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"> , whatever there are many other offensive stuff other than this, check this one for instance</p>
<p><a href="https://www.inminds.co.uk/img/hebron.graffiti.3.jpg" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://www.inminds.co.uk/img/hebron.graffiti.3.jpg</a></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/everybody-draw-muhammad-day/4196/12">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/everybody-draw-muhammad-day/4196/12</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 20 May 2010 09:10:13 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-4196-12</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/everybody-draw-muhammad-day/4196.rss">Everybody Draw Muhammad Day</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Everybody Draw Muhammad Day</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[King_Kaddo]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Bolteh">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/b/ecae2f/40.png" class="avatar"> Bolteh:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I find your avatar, name, signature, join date and location offensive and insulting.</p>
<p>It’s against my personal believe that someone has a pencil sketch as avatar, has a name with 2 Z’s in it, has a silly WoW-meme as signature, has joined earlier than me and lives in Dutchland (see how retarded your point is, yet?)[/SIZE]</p>
<p>But you don’t hear me crying for a ban or removal of your posts?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p><em>facepalm</em></p>
<p>You missed the point. That has nothing to do with mohammed caricatures. It isn’t our personal believe. We know that he existed.</p>
<p>It also doesn’t have to do something with the rules in our religion.<br>
Yeah ok I know that people don’t like muslims and have a lot prejudices but it’s not ok to draw pictures of Mohammed like that. (In the rules it isn’t even allowed to make any picture of him) You are offending Mohammed and that’s what we don’t like.</p>
<p>And srsly why do you people don’t just get it? You know nothing about Mohammed and draw caricatures of him. Where is the joke?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/everybody-draw-muhammad-day/4196/11">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/everybody-draw-muhammad-day/4196/11</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 20 May 2010 09:08:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-4196-11</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/everybody-draw-muhammad-day/4196.rss">Everybody Draw Muhammad Day</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Everybody Draw Muhammad Day</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Bolteh]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I find your avatar, name, signature, join date and location offensive and insulting.</p>
<p>It’s against my personal believe that someone has a pencil sketch as avatar, has a name with 2 Z’s in it, has a silly WoW-meme as signature, has joined earlier than me and lives in Dutchland (see how retarded your point is, yet?)[/SIZE]</p>
<p>But you don’t hear me crying for a ban or removal of your posts?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/everybody-draw-muhammad-day/4196/10">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/everybody-draw-muhammad-day/4196/10</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 20 May 2010 08:56:25 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-4196-10</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/everybody-draw-muhammad-day/4196.rss">Everybody Draw Muhammad Day</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Everybody Draw Muhammad Day</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Hazzmat]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Bolteh so what it’s still insulting</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/everybody-draw-muhammad-day/4196/9">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/everybody-draw-muhammad-day/4196/9</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 20 May 2010 08:53:12 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-4196-9</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/everybody-draw-muhammad-day/4196.rss">Everybody Draw Muhammad Day</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Everybody Draw Muhammad Day</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Bolteh]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>We aren’t insulting your religion or being disrespectful.</p>
<p>The law/rule of not depicting Muhammad only counts for Muslims. Seeing as most of us aren’t, we’re free to depict him. Nobody’s forcing you to watch the depictions anyway.</p>
<p>Why should <span class="bbcode-i">we </span>follow rules of <span class="bbcode-i">your </span>religion?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/everybody-draw-muhammad-day/4196/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/everybody-draw-muhammad-day/4196/8</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 20 May 2010 08:52:23 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-4196-8</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/everybody-draw-muhammad-day/4196.rss">Everybody Draw Muhammad Day</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Everybody Draw Muhammad Day</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[King_Kaddo]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I’m also for a closing. This is dumb and not respectful. You are just insulting our religion and we don’t want that. We keep our religion serious and can’t stand it when other people make fun of it.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/everybody-draw-muhammad-day/4196/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/everybody-draw-muhammad-day/4196/7</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 20 May 2010 08:50:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-4196-7</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/everybody-draw-muhammad-day/4196.rss">Everybody Draw Muhammad Day</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Everybody Draw Muhammad Day</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[brokenfridgehinge]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Is anyone here actually offended? I’m not, and even if you were Muslim you would know not to take internet threads such as this one seriously. But it anyone has a personal beef with it, I’ll close this.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/everybody-draw-muhammad-day/4196/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/everybody-draw-muhammad-day/4196/6</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 20 May 2010 08:49:23 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-4196-6</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/everybody-draw-muhammad-day/4196.rss">Everybody Draw Muhammad Day</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Everybody Draw Muhammad Day</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Bolteh]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Hazzmat">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/h/8dc957/40.png" class="avatar"> Hazzmat:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>This thread is very offending. Can a mod close this please?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>:facepalm:</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/everybody-draw-muhammad-day/4196/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/everybody-draw-muhammad-day/4196/5</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 20 May 2010 08:43:46 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-4196-5</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/everybody-draw-muhammad-day/4196.rss">Everybody Draw Muhammad Day</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Everybody Draw Muhammad Day</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Hazzmat]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>This thread is very offending. Can a mod close this please?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/everybody-draw-muhammad-day/4196/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/everybody-draw-muhammad-day/4196/4</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 20 May 2010 08:37:55 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-4196-4</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/everybody-draw-muhammad-day/4196.rss">Everybody Draw Muhammad Day</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Everybody Draw Muhammad Day</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Shadi]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Ramirezoid">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/r/ba9def/40.png" class="avatar"> Ramirezoid:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>A fun new pseudo-holiday has arrived at last! Depending on your time zone, that is. May 20th is Everybody Draw Muhammad Day.</p>
<p>So post your very own depiction of the prophet Muhammad :3</p>
<p><span alt="" class="broken-image" title="This image is broken"><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-unlink svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#unlink"></use></svg></span></p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>is that a hybrid chicken or ?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/everybody-draw-muhammad-day/4196/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/everybody-draw-muhammad-day/4196/3</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 20 May 2010 07:21:20 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-4196-3</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/everybody-draw-muhammad-day/4196.rss">Everybody Draw Muhammad Day</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Everybody Draw Muhammad Day</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Ballsopt]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>why only Muhammad. might as well do every religious prophet. <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/expressionless.png?v=9" title=":expressionless:" class="emoji" alt=":expressionless:"></p>
<p>also, this is drifting into</p>
<p><span alt="" class="broken-image" title="This image is broken"><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-unlink svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#unlink"></use></svg></span></p>
<p>territory</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/everybody-draw-muhammad-day/4196/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/everybody-draw-muhammad-day/4196/2</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 20 May 2010 06:22:45 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-4196-2</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/everybody-draw-muhammad-day/4196.rss">Everybody Draw Muhammad Day</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Everybody Draw Muhammad Day</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Ramirezoid]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>A fun new pseudo-holiday has arrived at last! Depending on your time zone, that is. May 20th is Everybody Draw Muhammad Day.</p>
<p>So post your very own depiction of the prophet Muhammad :3</p>
<p><span alt="" class="broken-image" title="This image is broken"><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-unlink svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#unlink"></use></svg></span></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/everybody-draw-muhammad-day/4196/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/everybody-draw-muhammad-day/4196/1</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 20 May 2010 06:17:21 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-4196-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/everybody-draw-muhammad-day/4196.rss">Everybody Draw Muhammad Day</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
