<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Non talking NPC scientist</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/non-talking-npc-scientist/10189</link>
    <description>I&#39;m not sure if this is really considered a bug, but I&#39;m at the part where you start dealing with the military soldiers. There are 2 scientist who have the face and one of them says, &quot;I&#39;m the man that knows everything, take me with you!&quot; Then they run and get shot by the soldiers in the next room.

Well you can bypass that by throwing a grenade in the room with the soldiers, the scientists run towards you and don&#39;t get killed. However they also don&#39;t talk. Once you walk into the room, the scientists run and do that sequence. Right now, I&#39;ll see if I can prevent them from being killed.

It would be a chance for some dialog, like when you are able to save the scientist from getting shot by the soldier coming down the elevator, right before it. One of those scientists should be changed so they aren&#39;t the same model.

Edit: I was able to save 1 scientist. I threw 2 more grenades which made them move farther back where I then closed the fire door on them, trapping them. I then sprinted and killed the first two soldiers, 1 above and behind on the skywalk and one to the left on the upper floor. I then ran towards the barnacle and had it latch onto me and killed it. I then proceeded to take out the other soldiers.

No matter what, those scientist do that sequence after you walk right into that room, somehow going right through the fire door (I know it&#39;s a scripted event lol). So I was able to save one and clear the room, NPC still didn&#39;t talk. I didn&#39;t use cheats either. It&#39;s freaking hard to pull it off, I had to practice and learn the soldiers positions and get everything right. It would be worthy of an achievement.

bm_c1a3b.HL1.

[code]
Loading game from SAVE\autosave.sav...
Loading game from //MOD/SAVE/bm_c1a3b.HL1...
Failed to load sound &quot;bms_ambience\room_ambience\r_ambience_med2.wav&quot;, file probably missing from disk/repository
Redownloading all lightmaps
CSceneEntity Take me with you! unable to find actor named &quot;!enemy&quot;
Physics queue not empty, error!
[/code]

A side note: Wouldn&#39;t it be easier to use Google Code or another issue reporting tool instead of forum posts, at least it&#39;s easier to keep track of bugs and merge duplicates.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 16 Sep 2012 09:11:52 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>In-game Issues (Mod)</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/non-talking-npc-scientist/10189.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Non talking NPC scientist</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Executor]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Another bug like this is in Apprehension.  If you kill the first Ichthyosaur before going up to talk to the scientist and get the crossbow, that scientist won’t say a word to you, even if you ‘use’ him.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/non-talking-npc-scientist/10189/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/non-talking-npc-scientist/10189/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 16 Sep 2012 09:11:52 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-10189-2</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/non-talking-npc-scientist/10189.rss">Non talking NPC scientist</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Non talking NPC scientist</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[sevenalive]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I’m not sure if this is really considered a bug, but I’m at the part where you start dealing with the military soldiers. There are 2 scientist who have the face and one of them says, “I’m the man that knows everything, take me with you!” Then they run and get shot by the soldiers in the next room.</p>
<p>Well you can bypass that by throwing a grenade in the room with the soldiers, the scientists run towards you and don’t get killed. However they also don’t talk. Once you walk into the room, the scientists run and do that sequence. Right now, I’ll see if I can prevent them from being killed.</p>
<p>It would be a chance for some dialog, like when you are able to save the scientist from getting shot by the soldier coming down the elevator, right before it. One of those scientists should be changed so they aren’t the same model.</p>
<p>Edit: I was able to save 1 scientist. I threw 2 more grenades which made them move farther back where I then closed the fire door on them, trapping them. I then sprinted and killed the first two soldiers, 1 above and behind on the skywalk and one to the left on the upper floor. I then ran towards the barnacle and had it latch onto me and killed it. I then proceeded to take out the other soldiers.</p>
<p>No matter what, those scientist do that sequence after you walk right into that room, somehow going right through the fire door (I know it’s a scripted event lol). So I was able to save one and clear the room, NPC still didn’t talk. I didn’t use cheats either. It’s freaking hard to pull it off, I had to practice and learn the soldiers positions and get everything right. It would be worthy of an achievement.</p>
<p>bm_c1a3b.HL1.</p>
<pre><code class="lang-auto">Loading game from SAVE\autosave.sav...
Loading game from //MOD/SAVE/bm_c1a3b.HL1...
Failed to load sound "bms_ambience\room_ambience\r_ambience_med2.wav", file probably missing from disk/repository
Redownloading all lightmaps
CSceneEntity Take me with you! unable to find actor named "!enemy"
Physics queue not empty, error!</code></pre>
<p>A side note: Wouldn’t it be easier to use Google Code or another issue reporting tool instead of forum posts, at least it’s easier to keep track of bugs and merge duplicates.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/non-talking-npc-scientist/10189/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/non-talking-npc-scientist/10189/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 16 Sep 2012 08:37:56 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-10189-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/non-talking-npc-scientist/10189.rss">Non talking NPC scientist</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
