<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Weapon Textures Suddenly gone!</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/weapon-textures-suddenly-gone/13765</link>
    <description>Just last night I was playing Black Mesa up to the end of the &quot;Questionable Ethics&quot; Chapter and everything was working just fine. I left from there, rejoined the game this morning and suddenly, ALL my weapons textures have changed to the purple and black checkerboard (missing textures). I checked the game files and the weapon texture files are all still there. The only thing I did between last night and this morning was verify my integrity for Source SDK Base 2007, and I also put &#39;-dxlevel 9.0&#39; in the Set Launch Options for Black Mesa. Did doing any of those REALLY cause my weapons to lose their textures?!?!?!</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Apr 2015 01:18:43 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>In-game Issues (Mod)</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/weapon-textures-suddenly-gone/13765.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Weapon Textures Suddenly gone!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Auz]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Just last night I was playing Black Mesa up to the end of the “Questionable Ethics” Chapter and everything was working just fine. I left from there, rejoined the game this morning and suddenly, ALL my weapons textures have changed to the purple and black checkerboard (missing textures). I checked the game files and the weapon texture files are all still there. The only thing I did between last night and this morning was verify my integrity for Source SDK Base 2007, and I also put ‘-dxlevel 9.0’ in the Set Launch Options for Black Mesa. Did doing any of those REALLY cause my weapons to lose their textures?!?!?!</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/weapon-textures-suddenly-gone/13765/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/weapon-textures-suddenly-gone/13765/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 25 Apr 2015 01:18:43 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13765-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/weapon-textures-suddenly-gone/13765.rss">Weapon Textures Suddenly gone!</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
