<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Halo: Reach VGA Trailer</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/halo-reach-vga-trailer/2136</link>
    <description>Since I know this is OBVIOUSLY the best place to host this topic, since I know you ALL love the Halo franchise [/sarcasm][/SIZE], I would like to discuss last night&#39;s VGA trailer for Halo: Reach.

[url]https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=kco1sYXGwYE&amp;feature=sub[/url]

First of all, if Bungie isn&#39;t pulling any of that CGI bullshit like they have done in the past, I will shit bricks. The detail on the SPARTAN armor is incredible, and the way they walk doesn&#39;t look as cartoony as before.

Also, I have noticed that Mary O&#39;Donnel is back to being the John Williams of video games as always. The music in the trailer is nothing short of epic. Though I hope some of the slow, beautiful tracks from the New Mombasa levels in ODST return for Reach, though I have no idea on how they would work since what was great about the music was the fact that you&#39;re alone, in the dark, and everyone wants to kill you. If you&#39;re a SPARTAN, you can handle all of that because YOU&#39;RE A FUCKING SPARTAN!

So yeah, this game looks like another awesome Halo game. It&#39;s great that Bungie is releasing a Beta for the game with ODST, especially since it eases the kick in the balls Microsoft gave us for charging full price for 3/4 of a &quot;full&quot; game.

But, I know I&#39;m stupid for starting a thread in the BMS forums, where everyone is a PC fanboy. This thread will probably be driven off topic to an offense [i](Halo sux lol!)[/i] defense [i](no, Halo rullllzzzz! lol!)[/i] [i]&quot;debate&quot;[/i] by Page 2. Imonfire and Collision will do that &quot;HAHAHAHAHA&quot; shit and all of the Halo fans in the forums will desperately try to stay on topic, but will be too busy fending off trolls when obviously they shouldn&#39;t even be reading this topic since they don&#39;t like Halo.

Also, WOO-HOO! ELITES ARE BACK! FUCK YEAH!</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 03 Jan 2010 22:20:20 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Technology and Gaming</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/halo-reach-vga-trailer/2136.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Halo: Reach VGA Trailer</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[xalener]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Cover system+fps= a bounty of more exploitable glitches and just assness all around.</p>
<p>The only way you can do that is to pull out to third person, and I’m not sure if that’s happening. the director of content for Halo 3 was a different guy as all the other games+reach. He sucked. Bungie knows it. No more Halo3-esque ideas.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/halo-reach-vga-trailer/2136/111">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/halo-reach-vga-trailer/2136/111</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 03 Jan 2010 22:20:20 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2136-111</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/halo-reach-vga-trailer/2136.rss">Halo: Reach VGA Trailer</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Halo: Reach VGA Trailer</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Soup]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="loony636">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/l/6bbea6/40.png" class="avatar"> loony636:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I’d also like to see a decent cover system, rather than your normal “crouch behind random crates” system that’s present in a lot of these games. I didn’t play ODST, but IIRC there’s no Gears of War style cover system in any of the Halo games, which I’d really like to see, because I liked it a lot.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>A cover system in an FPS is what you make of it. What you’re proposing doesn’t really make sense.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/halo-reach-vga-trailer/2136/110">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/halo-reach-vga-trailer/2136/110</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 03 Jan 2010 16:09:58 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2136-110</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/halo-reach-vga-trailer/2136.rss">Halo: Reach VGA Trailer</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Halo: Reach VGA Trailer</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[loony636]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="xalener">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/x/cc9497/40.png" class="avatar"> xalener:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I have high hopes for the game visually. It may not look too impressive, but they’ve got one of the pioneers of visual 3d design on that team. Just like with Halo 3, there will be some techniques that no one’s used before/ or use rarely and it ends up being applied to something that is SUPPOSED to look cartoony. Thus it is ridiculed for looking fake.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I have no doubt that it’ll look amazing. All the Halo games have. I just hope that it doesn’t stop there, since that’s the problem that every other Halo (and most FPS games) game has done; they spend a lot of money on visuals and gameplay, and then skimp out on story/characters/plot/dialogue/etc.</p>
<p>I’d also like to see a decent cover system, rather than your normal “crouch behind random crates” system that’s present in a lot of these games. I didn’t play ODST, but IIRC there’s no Gears of War style cover system in any of the Halo games, which I’d really like to see, because I liked it a lot.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/halo-reach-vga-trailer/2136/109">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/halo-reach-vga-trailer/2136/109</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 03 Jan 2010 07:57:31 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2136-109</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/halo-reach-vga-trailer/2136.rss">Halo: Reach VGA Trailer</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Halo: Reach VGA Trailer</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[xalener]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>4x anti aliasing instead of 16x?</p>
<p>Maybe a slightly lower framerate?</p>
<p>That’s it probably. Unless they pull a Halo 3 and retexture everything real quick before release.</p>
<p>…</p>
<p>But seriously. We haven’t even seen everything this engine can do. I mean, on the bungie publications (lighting to be exact) They talk about lighting things from ABOVE THE FUCKING ATMOSPHERE. And then proceeds to show some rough terrain with a blue aura over it <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/confused.png?v=9" title=":confused:" class="emoji" alt=":confused:"></p>
<p>I have high hopes for the game visually. It may not look too impressive, but they’ve got one of the pioneers of visual 3d design on that team. Just like with Halo 3, there will be some techniques that no one’s used before/ or use rarely and it ends up being applied to something that is SUPPOSED to look cartoony. Thus it is ridiculed for looking fake.</p>
<p>yeah, we need more realistic games like COD out there. Let’s put all concept artists out of business! Devs don’t need to come up with their own shit! They can just copy life! See how hard I worked on this texture I took of my porch out back? I’M SO FUCKING ARTISTIC WITH MY FUCKING PICTURES OF A FUCKING WALL.</p>
<p><em>cougchHL2cougch</em></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/halo-reach-vga-trailer/2136/108">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/halo-reach-vga-trailer/2136/108</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 03 Jan 2010 01:54:23 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2136-108</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/halo-reach-vga-trailer/2136.rss">Halo: Reach VGA Trailer</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Halo: Reach VGA Trailer</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[dky.tehkingd.u]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Last Bungie game of the Halo series, and probably the last decent Halo game that will ever be made, since I consider Bungie to be the only devs who know what they’re doing with the franchise. I mean look at Halo Wars…  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/frowning.png?v=9" title=":frowning:" class="emoji" alt=":frowning:"></p>
<p>Anyway, graphics are real nice in that trailer. My only doubt about the trailer is the fact that, even though they used the Reach engine to render it, the trailer was put together using a frame-dump… so I dunno about how the final product will look.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/halo-reach-vga-trailer/2136/107">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/halo-reach-vga-trailer/2136/107</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 02 Jan 2010 21:05:20 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2136-107</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/halo-reach-vga-trailer/2136.rss">Halo: Reach VGA Trailer</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Halo: Reach VGA Trailer</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[xalener]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Alright.</p>
<p>“Shut up and get behind me…sir.”-Halo 1 checkpoint name</p>
<p>“CAN’T…RUN…WITH…THING…ON…BACK”</p>
<p>“I know what the ladies like”</p>
<p>Cortana:“Cheif <em>ping</em> <em>ping</em> ping* wake up!”</p>
<p>“No one panic! EXCEPT FOR ME!!! AyAyAyAYAYAyAYAyAYAYA!!!” -Halo 2 elite</p>
<p><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=rlGr_vdxKlc" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=rlGr_vdxKlc</a></p>
<p><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=U3Hxq6lM9tY" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=U3Hxq6lM9tY</a></p>
<p><img src="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/original/2X/7/7b55b9cd748c12099b320b6ce2139bfc17a8d52d.png" alt="" data-base62-sha1="hB4owoTUWBNvLv5KBAzBj4iv1y5" width="443" height="330"></p>
<p>But fucking SERIOUSLY…</p>
<p>Is this SSC? I need to know. Please can someone who knows about this shit chime in?</p>
<p><a href="https://www.405th.com/reach/reach%201151.jpg" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://www.405th.com/reach/reach%201151.jpg</a></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/halo-reach-vga-trailer/2136/106">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/halo-reach-vga-trailer/2136/106</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 02 Jan 2010 20:33:11 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2136-106</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/halo-reach-vga-trailer/2136.rss">Halo: Reach VGA Trailer</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Halo: Reach VGA Trailer</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Acristoff]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Look at the trailer that this thread is about and say that halo doesn’t take itself seriously.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/halo-reach-vga-trailer/2136/105">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/halo-reach-vga-trailer/2136/105</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 02 Jan 2010 20:13:41 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2136-105</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/halo-reach-vga-trailer/2136.rss">Halo: Reach VGA Trailer</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Halo: Reach VGA Trailer</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[xalener]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>The universe does I mean…</p>
<p>It’s mostly the humor of it all and how seriously it DOESN’T take itself. Starship Troopers (first one) is the closest thing I can equate it to when I say “soul”.</p>
<p>But yeah, I really wish they’d try harder with the characters. Halo does so much right in the way of the experience that the stuff it does wrong (immersion) just amplifies disappointment.</p>
<p>More on topic: Wait a minute… Is that Subsurface scattering I see? or is it an illusion? Fuck.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/halo-reach-vga-trailer/2136/104">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/halo-reach-vga-trailer/2136/104</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 02 Jan 2010 20:10:14 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2136-104</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/halo-reach-vga-trailer/2136.rss">Halo: Reach VGA Trailer</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Halo: Reach VGA Trailer</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Soup]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Oh come on, Halo isn’t anywhere near “sci-fi in its purest form”. It’s sci-fi in its Hollywood form.</p>
<p>I’m not saying it’s bad, I’m not saying I didn’t love it, but it’s nowhere near “sci-fi in its purest form”. Science fiction by definition has technology based on current technology or theory and is always at least partially explained.</p>
<p>Also, it has an extremely bland and unoriginal story with a fairly predictable twist. The characters are flat and uninteresting and the only gripping parts were the bits with the flood in the first one.</p>
<p>I’ll say again, I enjoyed it. And a hell of a lot. This was because it was just plain fun. But soul? It ain’t got it.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/halo-reach-vga-trailer/2136/103">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/halo-reach-vga-trailer/2136/103</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 02 Jan 2010 20:05:52 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2136-103</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/halo-reach-vga-trailer/2136.rss">Halo: Reach VGA Trailer</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Halo: Reach VGA Trailer</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Acristoff]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Halo’s “got soul”? I have no idea what you mean by that.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/halo-reach-vga-trailer/2136/102">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/halo-reach-vga-trailer/2136/102</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 02 Jan 2010 19:49:21 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2136-102</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/halo-reach-vga-trailer/2136.rss">Halo: Reach VGA Trailer</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Halo: Reach VGA Trailer</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[xalener]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Picklesworth">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/p/df788c/40.png" class="avatar"> Picklesworth:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I, uhm, really don’t understand why people are so excited over this video from the graphics standpoint. It looks pretty much on par with any other video game trailer, maybe a bit <span class="bbcode-i">less</span> pretty than the norm on PCs.</p>
<p>And the “hey, it’s rendered on our game engine!” claim is bullshit anyway. It most probably isn’t rendered in real time, it isn’t how <span class="bbcode-i">the game</span> is. Maybe a close approximation.</p>
<p>It’s not that I think the game will be bad; it’ll probably be pretty good, as far as Halo is concerned. But my, how our standards have shortened!</p>
<p>“Hey, that video has some kind of script! The different cuts are related! The cuts are each longer than 3 seconds! I’M IN LOVE”</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-i">I hate their faces.</span> Check out the person at 1:07. She’s made of wood.</p>
<p>And what’s with that guy that’s all dressed up in costume, with the reddish armour and the skull painted over his face? (Yah, that looks like a practical choice for when you’ll be trying to aim a rifle at the bad guys, dumbass).</p>
<p>Then the squad leader guy telling our protagonist guy to “leave that loan wolf stuff behind” while he has that other moron in the squad who is obviously completely out of uniform.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>lol. Halo’s always had a satirical impractical Paul Verhoeven-esque universe. Characters in this game have license to do shit just to look cool. It fits the style…<br>
Anyway, this Isn’t realtime, but it IS a framedump. It’s in engine. But it’s got more anti aliasing than the actual game will. Words straight from Bungie. That being said, all assets in the trailer is what’s being used in the game. That alone is impressive. I can’t believe how high poly these charactes look. And how huge the textures are. I know Bungie uses lots of detail maps, but still. The wrinkles on Carter’s forehead look way more complex than the crappy noise maps they’ve used before.</p>
<p>BTW: Who gives a flying shit if a game isn’t revolutionary?</p>
<p>That shitty Jurassic Park FPS that came out BEFORE HL was possibly the most revolutionary game since Doom, and it was ASS.</p>
<p>Half Life is a mix between an 80’s action movie and a 50’s/ 60’s sci fi movie in the form of a shooter. Those whose “puzzles” get a lot of praise, but are about as challenging as a 4 piece jigsaw.</p>
<p>Halo is…well… Sci fi in it’s purest form… Supersoldiers, space marines, deadly parasites, crazy religious aliens… It’s got it all.</p>
<p>I love sci fi, so I like Half Life AND Halo, but I like Halo a bit more because well… It’s got soul, really. I like Half life 1 better than Halo’s sequels (Haf life 2 was a necessary step up, but it was lackluster compared to the episodes), But Halo CE remains my favourite game ever.</p>
<p>That all being said, Reach is going to be Bungie’s last Halo before 343 industries takes over. I know Bungie as a company very well, I’ve been faithful to them since Marathon. I know they’ll do everything they can to send this series out with a bang before it gets Spyro the dragon’d up, if you know what I mean.</p>
<p>And To soup:</p>
<p>Epic Win.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/halo-reach-vga-trailer/2136/101">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/halo-reach-vga-trailer/2136/101</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 02 Jan 2010 19:21:21 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2136-101</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/halo-reach-vga-trailer/2136.rss">Halo: Reach VGA Trailer</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Halo: Reach VGA Trailer</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Soup]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Eric Fong">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Eric Fong:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>And that would be end of bungle.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p><div class="lightbox-wrapper"><a class="lightbox" href="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/original/2X/2/2dd67b18932ff72e17f6294f2b5a03113c72f9c2.jpeg" data-download-href="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/2dd67b18932ff72e17f6294f2b5a03113c72f9c2" title=""><img src="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/original/2X/2/2dd67b18932ff72e17f6294f2b5a03113c72f9c2.jpeg" alt="" data-base62-sha1="6xv0zAAkkCeWYhnf2PjgylHRGOm" width="387" height="500" data-small-upload="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/optimized/2X/2/2dd67b18932ff72e17f6294f2b5a03113c72f9c2_2_10x10.png"><div class="meta"><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-far-image svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#far-image"></use></svg><span class="filename"></span><span class="informations">423×546 90.1 KB</span><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-discourse-expand svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#discourse-expand"></use></svg></div></a></div></p>
<p>Poor Bungle.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/halo-reach-vga-trailer/2136/100">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/halo-reach-vga-trailer/2136/100</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 02 Jan 2010 18:15:48 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2136-100</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/halo-reach-vga-trailer/2136.rss">Halo: Reach VGA Trailer</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Halo: Reach VGA Trailer</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Someonerandm]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>And you should get them in the orange box, so it was twenty for both episodes. And they are still episodes, and so should not be expected to revolutionize gaming as Half Life 2 did, even over time, although with the amount of time Episode 3 is taking, I’m not sure if they forgot they were doing episodes. As a side note the Fallout 3 addons cost 50 dollars and they didn’t advance the game play concept. Some would say some of them took away from it.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/halo-reach-vga-trailer/2136/99">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/halo-reach-vga-trailer/2136/99</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Dec 2009 17:16:40 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2136-99</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/halo-reach-vga-trailer/2136.rss">Halo: Reach VGA Trailer</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Halo: Reach VGA Trailer</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[JohnKiller118]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>It was part of what was supposed to be a full game with each episode costing $20 at launch. So if you want every part of the Half-Life 2 Episodes, you need to pay $60 over time.</p>
<p>Though Episode 1 got a price cut, so now it’s $50 total for all Episodes. Still, that’s a full priced PC game.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/halo-reach-vga-trailer/2136/98">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/halo-reach-vga-trailer/2136/98</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Dec 2009 13:59:20 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2136-98</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/halo-reach-vga-trailer/2136.rss">Halo: Reach VGA Trailer</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Halo: Reach VGA Trailer</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Someonerandm]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Plus episode two wasn’t a sequel, it was an episode…</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/halo-reach-vga-trailer/2136/97">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/halo-reach-vga-trailer/2136/97</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Dec 2009 13:02:35 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2136-97</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/halo-reach-vga-trailer/2136.rss">Halo: Reach VGA Trailer</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Halo: Reach VGA Trailer</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[JamestheDoc]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I dunno, it’s just that Halo was always really generic and never really seemed to innovate so much, and making a fifth game is just really stretching this one out.</p>
<p>Halo: Awesome for it’s time, a good shooter for Microsoft’s new console.</p>
<p>Halo 2: Campaign is short and disappointing, multiplayer makes up for it.</p>
<p>Halo 3: Campaign is short and disappointing, pretty much the same multiplayer.</p>
<p>ODST: Campaign is short and disappointing, horde-based co-op mode, multiplayer IS Halo 3’s multiplayer</p>
<p>Halo Reach: _______________</p>
<p>Spartans, Covenant, and shooting we can expect and know will be present.  And I’m not expecting a ton more…</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/halo-reach-vga-trailer/2136/96">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/halo-reach-vga-trailer/2136/96</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Dec 2009 11:38:15 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2136-96</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/halo-reach-vga-trailer/2136.rss">Halo: Reach VGA Trailer</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Halo: Reach VGA Trailer</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[JohnKiller118]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><span class="bbcode-b">OR</span> it’s the fact that it’s another Halo game, which means it’s in a similar style of, oh I don’t know, A HALO GAME!</p>
<p>The gameplay difference between Half-Life 2: Episode 2 and Half-Life 2 are minuscule, yet Episode 2 was far better than Half-Life 2. Think of that before posting <span class="bbcode-i">“omg this is da same game lol”</span></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/halo-reach-vga-trailer/2136/95">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/halo-reach-vga-trailer/2136/95</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Dec 2009 10:05:36 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2136-95</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/halo-reach-vga-trailer/2136.rss">Halo: Reach VGA Trailer</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Halo: Reach VGA Trailer</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[JamestheDoc]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Everything in the trailer reminds me of all the Halos I’ve played before… <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/confused.png?v=9" title=":confused:" class="emoji" alt=":confused:"></p>
<p>I’m just seeing this cash-cow shrivel and twitch…</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/halo-reach-vga-trailer/2136/94">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/halo-reach-vga-trailer/2136/94</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Dec 2009 09:01:02 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2136-94</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/halo-reach-vga-trailer/2136.rss">Halo: Reach VGA Trailer</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Halo: Reach VGA Trailer</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Dust]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>^This</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/halo-reach-vga-trailer/2136/93">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/halo-reach-vga-trailer/2136/93</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Dec 2009 08:15:11 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2136-93</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/halo-reach-vga-trailer/2136.rss">Halo: Reach VGA Trailer</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Halo: Reach VGA Trailer</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Someonerandm]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I agree. Your post is an Epic Win.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/halo-reach-vga-trailer/2136/92">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/halo-reach-vga-trailer/2136/92</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Dec 2009 06:40:01 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2136-92</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/halo-reach-vga-trailer/2136.rss">Halo: Reach VGA Trailer</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Halo: Reach VGA Trailer</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Ibanez]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>A picture which consisted of ‘epic win’ as a stand-alone sentence. I hate it when people use ‘epic’ as prefixes to anything, too. It’s just… so goddamn lame.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/halo-reach-vga-trailer/2136/91">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/halo-reach-vga-trailer/2136/91</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Dec 2009 04:10:28 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2136-91</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/halo-reach-vga-trailer/2136.rss">Halo: Reach VGA Trailer</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Halo: Reach VGA Trailer</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[JohnKiller118]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Ibanez">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/i/a4c791/40.png" class="avatar"> Ibanez:</div>
<blockquote>
<p><img src="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/optimized/2X/3/3f92080d1b528379eda5e19264bf0f34e7fd3c3d_2_295x500.png" alt="" data-base62-sha1="94mWZRqOi7PFGE2ZFVHvXTgZma1" width="295" height="500" srcset="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/optimized/2X/3/3f92080d1b528379eda5e19264bf0f34e7fd3c3d_2_295x500.png, https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/optimized/2X/3/3f92080d1b528379eda5e19264bf0f34e7fd3c3d_2_442x750.png 1.5x, https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/optimized/2X/3/3f92080d1b528379eda5e19264bf0f34e7fd3c3d_2_590x1000.png 2x" data-small-upload="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/optimized/2X/3/3f92080d1b528379eda5e19264bf0f34e7fd3c3d_2_10x10.png"></p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I didn’t use “Win” or “Fail” in complete sentences. I used a :jizz: smiley and posted a picture.</p>
<p>Though it is a funny comic, and very true.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/halo-reach-vga-trailer/2136/90">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/halo-reach-vga-trailer/2136/90</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Dec 2009 00:33:40 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2136-90</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/halo-reach-vga-trailer/2136.rss">Halo: Reach VGA Trailer</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Halo: Reach VGA Trailer</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Master_Chef]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Picklesworth">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/p/df788c/40.png" class="avatar"> Picklesworth:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>loan wolf</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>You heard it here first, folks. The new Halo title will be centered on forcing alien troops and suburban homeowners to accept insecure investments under threats of violence.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/halo-reach-vga-trailer/2136/89">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/halo-reach-vga-trailer/2136/89</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Dec 2009 00:16:15 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2136-89</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/halo-reach-vga-trailer/2136.rss">Halo: Reach VGA Trailer</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Halo: Reach VGA Trailer</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Acristoff]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I too hate it when people say lol, win, fail, or epic.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/halo-reach-vga-trailer/2136/88">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/halo-reach-vga-trailer/2136/88</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 24 Dec 2009 23:44:49 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2136-88</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/halo-reach-vga-trailer/2136.rss">Halo: Reach VGA Trailer</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Halo: Reach VGA Trailer</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[HyperCorruption]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I plan to get this game when it comes out. Trailer looks pretty nice too.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/halo-reach-vga-trailer/2136/87">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/halo-reach-vga-trailer/2136/87</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 24 Dec 2009 18:03:30 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2136-87</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/halo-reach-vga-trailer/2136.rss">Halo: Reach VGA Trailer</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
