<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Which Headset?</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/which-headset/11484</link>
    <description>I&#39;m pretty much deciding between these two:

[b]The Sennheiser PC 350[/b]: [url]https://www.sennheiserusa.com/noise-cancelling-headset-computer-gamer-headset-skype-voip_502141[/url]


[b]The Steelseries 7H[/b]: [url]https://steelseries.com/us/products/audio/steelseries-7h[/url]


I&#39;ll probably be buying a sound card too.  Despite what some may say, I think a separate sound card is quite a bit better than just using the sound chip on my mobo.  Probably something from Creative, as I really want the THX True Studio virtual surround features that come with it.  I&#39;ve never really been much of an audio guy, but I really need a nice headset since my Sony headphones I&#39;ve been using are dying in one ear.  So if you have any other suggestions feel free to let me know.

[b]EDIT:[/b] If any of you are audiophiles and have direct experience with using headsets with both on board sounds and discrete sound cards and have an opinion, feel free to let me know because a decent sound card from Creative is a little pricey.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 14 Oct 2012 09:10:19 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Technology and Gaming</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/which-headset/11484.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Which Headset?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[johnyo]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <blockquote>
<p>audiophiles<br>
using headsets<br>
pick one.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>Seriously though, if gaming is all you need your headphones for, then a headset will probably work just fine, but if you care about high quality music, then get headphones and attach a mic to them. ATH M50 or DT770 Pro (80 Ohm) are often recommended.<br>
A dedicated card <span class="bbcode-i">will</span> make a difference (for games get one with EAX3.0), but don’t forget there are many ways to configure signal processing in software so it’s not like you can’t get decent sound quality (or even binaural effects) unless you dish out $100 on a dedicated maxpro gaymen sound card.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/which-headset/11484/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/which-headset/11484/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 14 Oct 2012 09:10:19 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11484-2</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/which-headset/11484.rss">Which Headset?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Which Headset?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[lunertexcosmo]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I’m pretty much deciding between these two:</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">The Sennheiser PC 350</span>: <a href="https://www.sennheiserusa.com/noise-cancelling-headset-computer-gamer-headset-skype-voip_502141" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://www.sennheiserusa.com/noise-cancelling-headset-computer-gamer-headset-skype-voip_502141</a></p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">The Steelseries 7H</span>: <a href="https://steelseries.com/us/products/audio/steelseries-7h" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://steelseries.com/us/products/audio/steelseries-7h</a></p>
<p>I’ll probably be buying a sound card too.  Despite what some may say, I think a separate sound card is quite a bit better than just using the sound chip on my mobo.  Probably something from Creative, as I really want the THX True Studio virtual surround features that come with it.  I’ve never really been much of an audio guy, but I really need a nice headset since my Sony headphones I’ve been using are dying in one ear.  So if you have any other suggestions feel free to let me know.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">EDIT:</span> If any of you are audiophiles and have direct experience with using headsets with both on board sounds and discrete sound cards and have an opinion, feel free to let me know because a decent sound card from Creative is a little pricey.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/which-headset/11484/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/which-headset/11484/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 14 Oct 2012 05:34:13 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11484-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/which-headset/11484.rss">Which Headset?</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
