<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Reflection of Modern Games</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/reflection-of-modern-games/8768</link>
    <description>[b]The tl;dr summary is at the bottom, but I suggest reading the actual events instead.
[/b]
It all started last weekend when my father called me about something interesting he was given on a job (he moves furniture and drives a truck). He was given an original Atari 2600 with a bunch of controllers and games, with a Nintendo 64 with much of the same. He said that I should come over and get it because he knows I&#39;m into that sorta stuff. So Anyways, I drove up to his house yesterday to take a look at what he got...

When I arrived, I took a seat and talked with my father for a while -- eventually we got to the Atari. When he brought me to it, all of the wires and devices were cramped in a single cardboard box about as big as filing cabinet, which probably means it hadn&#39;t been touched in a while. So I dissected the box of all it&#39;s components and went to my dad&#39;s basement to grab an old CRT television that could handle the old hardware correctly. When I finally got color and everything else working, my dad started playing [i]Kaboom[/i]; one of my dad&#39;s old favorites. Being born in the late 80s, I didn&#39;t really get too much time on the Atari before focusing on Sega and Nintendo, so some of the titles I recognized first hand, but the rest I had just seen or heard of through AVGN or basic internet surfing. Anyways, when my dad was done with his nostalgic play-through of his favorite classics, he popped in a game called [i]Combat[/i], which he told me all Ataris came with back when they were being sold. I had never heard of the game, or at least couldn&#39;t recall it. 

So he popped it in and there we were controlling two separate, colored tanks on opposite ends of the screen. The rules were simple - utilize cover and shoot each other. But regardless of the simple concept, me and my dad found each other going at this game for about 25 minutes. After that time had passed, I rose up and said something like, [i]&quot;..well, that&#39;s enough of this game. I forgot how simple games were back then...&quot;[/i] But then my dad laughed and told me to keep my pants on as he stood up and started fiddling with some lever on the Atari. 

As he did this, the the map started changing with every button press; the obstacles would change, the colors, the bullets bounced off walls now, and there was even an airplane version where you got to fire your rockets and then guide them into the other player (apparently called Heat-seeker or something). When my dad started running me through the rotations of different game modes, my dad and I ended up being there on that single game for about 3 [i]1/2[/i] [/SIZE]hours. We were laughing hysterically the whole time as he kicked my ass at these old games. We then went on to play other games - we played Frogger, Pacman, Warlord (or something), centipede, space invaders, etc.    

After a long day of fun on the system, I said goodnight to my dad and went home, letting him hold on to the system for another couple of weeks in the hopes that he would get some joy out of it. On the drive home, all I was thinking about was how badly I ate my words and ended up playing those simple games for so long. Then I started thinking, how come no games are as innovative as the Atari games these days? Essentially, most games in the past 15 years have either been a third person shooter, over-the-shoulder shooter, FPS, or RTS -- or a variation of one of the 4. 

I suddenly felt so sick of the four mundane game styles that I had been fed for the last 15 years that I started going out of my way to look into older games -- and I&#39;m a classic gamer, so I had to go back to my [i]PS1[/i] and [i]Sega[/i] emulators. Eventually, it made sense why game publishers like [i][b]PopCap[/b][/i] made so much money off simple little games; it doesn&#39;t take amazing graphics or a compelling story to make a game good -- it just takes pure [u]fun[/u].

What do you guys think? Do you think games these days tend to focus more on story, graphics, and money than on fun and relaxed competition? And if you have an opinion, which do you prefer?

[b]TL;DR:[/b] [i]Time on the Atari made me realize that simple games can actually be more fun than complicated graphics and story. Do you think that game publishers should take a step back and think about the fun-factor more? [/i]</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 20 May 2012 07:28:27 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Technology and Gaming</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/reflection-of-modern-games/8768.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Reflection of Modern Games</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[k3nny1550]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>BioShock got tiresome for me after the initial ten hours because of a dreadful escort mission, the upcoming shitty ending fork, and the realization that I would never fight more than four different types of enemies.</p>
<p>Human Revolution was more or less my game of 2011. Wonderfully designed, masterfully written, ambitious in it’s scope, and one of the best treatments of the moral and societal implications of transhumanism in recent memory. As soon as school is out I’m going to replay that game.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/reflection-of-modern-games/8768/32">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/reflection-of-modern-games/8768/32</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 20 May 2012 07:28:27 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8768-32</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/reflection-of-modern-games/8768.rss">Reflection of Modern Games</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Reflection of Modern Games</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[OrderOfDagon]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I completely agree.</p>
<p>You know, Deus Ex: Human Revolution was a Cyberpunk game that wasn’t really as story deep as I thought it would be, nor did it have a relatively long length, but it was still the funnest game I have played in almost 5 years. Before DE:HM, Bioshock held the title for me as funnest game of the next gens, but Human Revolution takes the cake. Prototype is a close third, with Alien Vs Predator coming in at fourth. These games didn’t have amazing stories (Bioshock and Deus Ex had good ones, though - especially Bioshock) yet they were fun as hell and kept me playing longer than any other game.</p>
<p>Aliens vs Predator was only fun for its multiplayer, which is quite a twist for me. It was fun because the combat took some skill and then you took a style. But after a few updates and patches, the game had these exploits where people would just assassinate everyone instead of fighting, and fighting had an exploit where you could hit the enemy in a timed fashion and prevent them from fighting back – that’s when that game stopped being fun.</p>
<p>Gamers don’t like to be forced to play a certain way to succeed, they want to rebel and find their own style and not have to worry about lagging behind – this is why I love old style fighting games like Capcom Vs Snk and NeoGeo Battle Colosseum.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/reflection-of-modern-games/8768/31">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/reflection-of-modern-games/8768/31</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 20 May 2012 04:59:48 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8768-31</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/reflection-of-modern-games/8768.rss">Reflection of Modern Games</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Reflection of Modern Games</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[IronManLok]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>imo it’s all about the process of gaming industry shifting from a hobby to a business</p>
<p>before, games were simple and required not much money to make… they were based on what those early developers felt it was fun… with those simpler games, few ppl started to make big bucks</p>
<p>this attracted the “corporate” minds, and they decided to create a business out of it, and hence, games started being based on business concepts… instead of being based on fun, now its based on marketing apeal, shiping on schedule, reutilization of resources, ideas and IPs, profits maximization, etc… being fun is just a colateral effect, not the main focus, as long as it sells, it doesnt matter… let me give some examples:</p>
<ul>
<li>
<p>have u noticed how games become shorter and shorter with every passing year? nowadays games developers pride themselves when their games go past 15 hours of play time… 10 years ago this would be a joke… gosh, there are even games with 4 hours of play time now… u wanna know why? they noticed that ppl will buy less games if they spend too much time on a single game… so the business men started demanding that developers make shorter games… thats profit maximization affecting the game content</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>have you notice that there’s always a genre of the moment? it takes one game to make huge success and all other companies go make something on the same genre of that game so they can be in the same boat… how many MMOs started poping up after WoW?</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>as I said, as long as it sells, it doenst matter being fun… thats why they focus more on graphics, cause it’s shiny and ppl likes to buy shiny things… it’s like fashion, usually ppl doesn’t buy clothes based on technical arguments like “is this cloth durable” or “will it protect me”, they buy because of looks and desire… games are the same, most of the ppl buy games based on looks and desires, not if the game is fun or not…</p>
</li>
</ul>
<p>I’m not saying u can’t have fun with modern games, I’m just saying it’s not the focus anymore</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/reflection-of-modern-games/8768/30">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/reflection-of-modern-games/8768/30</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 20 May 2012 01:20:14 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8768-30</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/reflection-of-modern-games/8768.rss">Reflection of Modern Games</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Reflection of Modern Games</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[OrderOfDagon]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>You’re getting it, but I wasn’t saying one should take over the other industry, I was simply talking about fun and was wondering if people thought games should strive to be more fun.</p>
<p>You actually gave an opinion that related to that, and now I’m satisfied; you said you don’t think they need to, and I completely accept your answer and take it into consideration.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/reflection-of-modern-games/8768/29">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/reflection-of-modern-games/8768/29</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 20 May 2012 00:04:08 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8768-29</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/reflection-of-modern-games/8768.rss">Reflection of Modern Games</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Reflection of Modern Games</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Kairouseki]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>Time on the Atari made me realize that simple games can actually be  more fun than complicated graphics and story. Do you think that game  publishers should take a step back and think about the fun-factor more</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Simple games can be fun. Complicated games can be fun. Simple games are not inherently more fun than complicated games, and “fun” in and of itself is subjective. I do not think that game makers need to step back and think about the fun-factor more, because I myself have fun with games coming out now. Do I sometimes like to play a simple game like Tetris over a complex game like Stalker? Sure. But to say that a game having amazing graphics and a complex story makes it less fun than a game like Combat, which you used in the OP, is an incredible overgeneralization and relies on you being the one making the argument. Nine times out of ten, I would choose to play Stalker or Crysis over Combat. iOS, XBLA, and indie games are the games nowadays that do what you’re talking about, prioritize gameplay and “fun” over graphics or story, so you can’t say that all games coming out now are of the complex graphics and story variety. I don’t care if people prefer indie games to AAA (or whatever) games, but just like how the industry shouldn’t be all games prioritizing graphics over gameplay, neither should it be oversaturated with games not using the technology we have now for good graphics. There is a market for both kinds of games and neither should push the other out of the industry.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/reflection-of-modern-games/8768/28">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/reflection-of-modern-games/8768/28</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 19 May 2012 23:57:31 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8768-28</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/reflection-of-modern-games/8768.rss">Reflection of Modern Games</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Reflection of Modern Games</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[OrderOfDagon]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>You put words in my mouth and disagreed with points I never made.</p>
<p>I was talking about games made for fun (I used actual events on how I got to the thought) and what I hoped for was a discussion about what might make games fun, and how simple games that took 2 minutes to make can manage to be more fun than huge games – while opinion does differ, many of us can agree considering this is a forum based on a classic game remake.</p>
<p>You started going on about the “evolution of games” and how were past simple games. Which… didn’t make any sense to what I was asking, and I even apologized for not being clear enough.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="amazingcomedy">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/a/ed8c4c/40.png" class="avatar"> amazingcomedy:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>^This.<br>
Most games today are so simple, boring, and easy that it makes me wonder what happened to actually fun titles, titles like Mario 64, Ocarina of time, System Shock, Half-Life, etc. There’s no real soul in games anymore.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>^ This guy understands perfectly – he made mention of games that he thought were fun. Which makes it easier to analyse what was so fun about them.<br>
I guess the story threw people off, but I was just being truthful to what my thought process was. While it may seem like a list of his personal opinion, all those games I just so happen to love.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/reflection-of-modern-games/8768/27">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/reflection-of-modern-games/8768/27</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 19 May 2012 23:45:07 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8768-27</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/reflection-of-modern-games/8768.rss">Reflection of Modern Games</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Reflection of Modern Games</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Kairouseki]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I wasn’t saying you can’t have an opinion, it’s just you attacked me for addressing your opinion with how I felt on the matter, saying I wasn’t understanding what you were saying when I was. It seems you have no desire to argue your point and instead just attack those who don’t agree with it.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/reflection-of-modern-games/8768/26">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/reflection-of-modern-games/8768/26</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 19 May 2012 23:41:38 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8768-26</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/reflection-of-modern-games/8768.rss">Reflection of Modern Games</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Reflection of Modern Games</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[OrderOfDagon]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Kairouseki">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/k/57b2e6/40.png" class="avatar"> Kairouseki:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Music after the 80s sucks too amirite? Why can’t they make music anymore like the stuff I cherry pick from the past.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I respect your opinion. [COLOR=‘Black’]and the fact that you can’t read lol</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="danielsangeo">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/user_avatar/leakfree.org/danielsangeo/40/4347_2.png" class="avatar"> danielsangeo:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>“Fun” is a subjective term and some people would not find the older games (such as Atari or original Nintendo, ColecoVision, etc) as fun as newer more modern games (CoD, Half Life 2, Diablo 3, etc).  And vice versa.  And some people find some older games as fun as newer games.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Definitely; making a thread to see what others think has been done before. This whole mod was created off the subjective impulse of fun – and look what good has come of it? A great looking mod.</p>
<p>But fuck: Kairouseki is right! Opinions are bad! We can’t have them! Because game direction must be worshiped.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/reflection-of-modern-games/8768/25">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/reflection-of-modern-games/8768/25</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 19 May 2012 23:29:51 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8768-25</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/reflection-of-modern-games/8768.rss">Reflection of Modern Games</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Reflection of Modern Games</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Vitriol]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Older, simpler games are some of the most fun around. While I mostly play newer games these days, sometimes I crave for the older games. It is true that “they just don’t make em like they used to”. With a lot of games these days, there is something missing.</p>
<p>I now have a craving for Missile Command and Yars Revenge.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/reflection-of-modern-games/8768/24">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/reflection-of-modern-games/8768/24</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 19 May 2012 22:44:34 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8768-24</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/reflection-of-modern-games/8768.rss">Reflection of Modern Games</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Reflection of Modern Games</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Surplus]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Kairouseki">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/k/57b2e6/40.png" class="avatar"> Kairouseki:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Music after the 80s sucks too amirite? Why can’t they make music anymore like the stuff I cherry pick from the past.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Lol I love this comment.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/reflection-of-modern-games/8768/23">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/reflection-of-modern-games/8768/23</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 19 May 2012 22:34:26 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8768-23</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/reflection-of-modern-games/8768.rss">Reflection of Modern Games</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Reflection of Modern Games</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Kairouseki]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Music after the 80s sucks too amirite? Why can’t they make music anymore like the stuff I cherry pick from the past.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/reflection-of-modern-games/8768/22">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/reflection-of-modern-games/8768/22</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 19 May 2012 20:54:41 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8768-22</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/reflection-of-modern-games/8768.rss">Reflection of Modern Games</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Reflection of Modern Games</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[amazingcomedy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="OrderOfDagon">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/user_avatar/leakfree.org/orderofdagon/40/4963_2.png" class="avatar"> OrderOfDagon:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I feel as though games have left some ingredients in the past - ingredients like fun.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>^This.<br>
Most games today are so simple, boring, and easy that it makes me wonder what happened to actually fun titles, titles like Mario 64, Ocarina of time, System Shock, Half-Life, etc. There’s no real soul in games anymore.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/reflection-of-modern-games/8768/21">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/reflection-of-modern-games/8768/21</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 19 May 2012 20:41:44 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8768-21</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/reflection-of-modern-games/8768.rss">Reflection of Modern Games</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Reflection of Modern Games</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[OrderOfDagon]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>lol</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/reflection-of-modern-games/8768/20">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/reflection-of-modern-games/8768/20</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 19 May 2012 19:05:17 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8768-20</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/reflection-of-modern-games/8768.rss">Reflection of Modern Games</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Reflection of Modern Games</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[k3nny1550]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Kairouseki">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/k/57b2e6/40.png" class="avatar"> Kairouseki:</div>
<blockquote>
<p><a href="https://www.bestweekever.tv/bwe/images/2011/12/HEATH-LEDGER-OR-RICK-PERRY-09-1323702148.jpg" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">This thread.</a></p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I CANT QUIT YOU DRAGON :’(</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/reflection-of-modern-games/8768/19">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/reflection-of-modern-games/8768/19</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 19 May 2012 07:11:15 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8768-19</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/reflection-of-modern-games/8768.rss">Reflection of Modern Games</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Reflection of Modern Games</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[danielsangeo]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>“Fun” is a subjective term and some people would not find the older games (such as Atari or original Nintendo, ColecoVision, etc) as fun as newer more modern games (CoD, Half Life 2, Diablo 3, etc).  And vice versa.  And some people find some older games as fun as newer games.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/reflection-of-modern-games/8768/18">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/reflection-of-modern-games/8768/18</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 19 May 2012 07:02:04 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8768-18</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/reflection-of-modern-games/8768.rss">Reflection of Modern Games</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Reflection of Modern Games</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Surplus]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>You discovered that old games are fun.  Congratulations.  Welcome to what most people have know for 40 years.  They were games and still are, something doesn’t get labeled game and be successful without being entertaining.  Pokers like a century or two old and people still play that shit.</p>
<p>I think your statement about games being complicated / simple is more of personal one than an industry one.</p>
<p>Your choice between simple and complex games is dumb.  You don’t have to choose.  When I want a fun 4 player co-op game for the couch I can find one.  And when I want a deep story driven game I can find one.  Its a big industry and a lot is made in it.</p>
<p>Also the idea that games in the last 15 years haven’t been innovative is silly.  Games have been innovating massively.  There’s constantly game play mechanics and ideas breaking out that no one has seen before.  Thing is its becoming specialized so its less noticeable at a glance.  Which is more apparent.  The game that invents the tank game genre or the one that makes massive strides and improvements upon it.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/reflection-of-modern-games/8768/17">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/reflection-of-modern-games/8768/17</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 19 May 2012 06:01:47 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8768-17</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/reflection-of-modern-games/8768.rss">Reflection of Modern Games</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Reflection of Modern Games</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Kairouseki]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><a href="https://www.bestweekever.tv/bwe/images/2011/12/HEATH-LEDGER-OR-RICK-PERRY-09-1323702148.jpg" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">This thread.</a></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/reflection-of-modern-games/8768/16">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/reflection-of-modern-games/8768/16</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 19 May 2012 05:44:21 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8768-16</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/reflection-of-modern-games/8768.rss">Reflection of Modern Games</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Reflection of Modern Games</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[OrderOfDagon]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=9" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji only-emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/reflection-of-modern-games/8768/15">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/reflection-of-modern-games/8768/15</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 19 May 2012 05:40:17 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8768-15</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/reflection-of-modern-games/8768.rss">Reflection of Modern Games</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Reflection of Modern Games</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[k3nny1550]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>A pretentious one that’s played too many video games over the years but yes. Human.</p>
<p><em>makes Vulcan sign</em></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/reflection-of-modern-games/8768/14">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/reflection-of-modern-games/8768/14</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 19 May 2012 05:18:18 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8768-14</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/reflection-of-modern-games/8768.rss">Reflection of Modern Games</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Reflection of Modern Games</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[OrderOfDagon]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Oh look a human!</p>
<p>I come in peace.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/reflection-of-modern-games/8768/13">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/reflection-of-modern-games/8768/13</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 19 May 2012 05:08:07 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8768-13</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/reflection-of-modern-games/8768.rss">Reflection of Modern Games</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Reflection of Modern Games</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[k3nny1550]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I, too, enjoy playing my 22 year old Genesis console once in a while.</p>
<p>There’s some great games for it, too. Rocket Knight Adventures, Shinobi III, Sonic 2, Urban Strike. I agree in principle that graphics have become far too emphasized over quality gameplay. But there are well designed and fun games on just about any console worth mentioning. Phantasy Star II was a landmark RPG, but it plays like ass because it’s incredibly difficult to such a degree that a strategy guide had to be included <span class="bbcode-i">with the game.</span></p>
<p>Basically what people would probably infer about your story would be that you’re looking down on current gen games because they don’t have enough of a gameplay focus. Whether or not that was what you <span class="bbcode-i">meant</span> is more or less irrelevant. Combat sounds like a really cool game though, because it sounds like it’s got a lot of customization for how the game behaves.</p>
<p>The real problem with modern games is that sometimes there’s a “wrong way” to play a game. I go into Fire Emblem and I get my ass kicked by the RNG because I didn’t use the “right” units in earlier chapters. I’ll get stomped in Painkiller by the first major boss because I’m not using the “right” strategy.</p>
<p>There should not be a “wrong way” to play a game. Game design is based on the central conceit that the player is progressing through the game utilizing the interface according to their own choices. If there’s only one way to go through a level, or one strategy to use against a tough opponent, that negates the entire core function of the gameplay experience- interactivity.</p>
<p>We, as players, expect our inputs to mean something. We expect to be able to play a game, not press buttons and watch canned animations of a fight in a quick time sequence. We expect legitimate challenge out of our shooters, not endlessly dying over and over on “Whiskey Hotel” because we’re not following the specific path the game wants us to go.</p>
<p>I’m not saying linear games aren’t fun. There’s plenty of linear games that are lots of fun. Prince of Persia: The Sands of Time is highly linear, but it presents a well told story with relatable characters, has forgiving but brain-teasing movement puzzles, and speedy, intense combat sequences. Final Fantasy XIII has a combat system that can literally be boiled down to a button press to auto-combat, but it still requires strategy and the Paradigm Shift system allows the player to create a flexible battle strategy tailored to their characters’ strengths (that is, when the game takes off the training wheels about thirty hours in). Splinter Cell Chaos Theory has an excellent mix of linear and non-linear in the Bank level, where the player can spend as long as they like exploring a two story bank complex with attached gardens accomplishing objectives and avoiding guards with whatever methods they choose.</p>
<p>Games can be designed right and they can be designed wrong. Regardless of narrative, regardless of overall gameplay flow, from minute to minute; if the game is of a high quality, the player is going to be having fun. This applies to anything, from the Atari 2600 to the most advanced, Orphan heart powered multicore computers of the future.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/reflection-of-modern-games/8768/12">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/reflection-of-modern-games/8768/12</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 19 May 2012 05:03:09 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8768-12</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/reflection-of-modern-games/8768.rss">Reflection of Modern Games</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Reflection of Modern Games</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[OrderOfDagon]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Reese’s Puff Cerial!</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/reflection-of-modern-games/8768/11">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/reflection-of-modern-games/8768/11</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 19 May 2012 05:01:35 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8768-11</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/reflection-of-modern-games/8768.rss">Reflection of Modern Games</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Reflection of Modern Games</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[OrderOfDagon]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>It’s Reese’s for breakfast!</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/reflection-of-modern-games/8768/10">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/reflection-of-modern-games/8768/10</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 19 May 2012 04:59:04 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8768-10</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/reflection-of-modern-games/8768.rss">Reflection of Modern Games</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Reflection of Modern Games</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[deadlife101]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Derp</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/reflection-of-modern-games/8768/9">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/reflection-of-modern-games/8768/9</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 19 May 2012 04:04:26 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8768-9</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/reflection-of-modern-games/8768.rss">Reflection of Modern Games</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Reflection of Modern Games</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Kairouseki]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Whatever you say chap.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/reflection-of-modern-games/8768/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/reflection-of-modern-games/8768/8</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 19 May 2012 03:58:01 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8768-8</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/reflection-of-modern-games/8768.rss">Reflection of Modern Games</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
