<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Announcing: The Story of Crossfire</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/announcing-the-story-of-crossfire/14371</link>
    <description>Hey everyone!

Everyday, we get asked a singular question: “WHERE&#39;S XE-”- … No, not that one.“Where&#39;s Crossfire?” … Yea, that one. Until now, we&#39;ve just been saying “we&#39;re working on it!” or something to that effect. Today however, is different. We&#39;re now able to answer that question.

It&#39;s boring and painful (mostly boring) working on something that you can&#39;t talk about and everyone wants to know about it. Sorry guys, we aren&#39;t ready to talk about Xen yet, despite how boring/painful it is for us. Instead, we&#39;re going to be talking about Crossfire. Yep, we&#39;re going to be bringing you guys into the inner workings of what it&#39;s like to work on a multiplayer map for Black Mesa Multiplayer! Now, we&#39;re cheating a little. This isn&#39;t a start-from-scratch development cycle, we&#39;ve been tweaking the layout of Crossfire for a little while now so that it plays just as everyone remembers it back in the day.

We&#39;re going to make the process as simple and as understandable as possible. It&#39;s going to be quick! Let me lay out really quickly what we are planning to do with the rest of the development of Crossfire.

* We&#39;re going to show you guys what development versions of Crossfire look like. So you get to see it through all its different stages. I&#39;ve added shots of the unarted version of Crossfire below.
* We&#39;ll say why we do what we do. Why are we using this colour light? Why are the weapons placed the way they are? Why the heck is it taking so long!?! If there&#39;s something you don&#39;t necessarily think works, let us know.
* Anything you want to know? Ask! We&#39;ll take questions from you guys and have the MP team answer all the questions we can for you.
* Finally, we&#39;ll welcome you play the development and internal version of Crossfire, via the Black Mesa Public Beta and our Beta Servers. More info on that later.
We&#39;re totally excited to be able to start showing off what we&#39;ve been doing with Crossfire and being able to give you guys another window into the world of Black Mesa Multiplayer Development. Stay tuned to the normal channels for more information as it comes up.

[url=&#39;https://www.facebook.com/BlackMesaDevs&#39;]Facebook[/url] | [url=&#39;https://twitter.com/BlackMesaDevs&#39;]Twitter[/url] |[url=&#39;https://steamcommunity.com/groups/BlackMesa&#39;]Steam Group[/url]

[b]- The MP Team  :thumbup: [/b]

https://i.imgur.com/APGsxSh.png
https://i.imgur.com/kzAPjMO.png
https://i.imgur.com/v0zBWMH.png
https://i.imgur.com/dIsofDK.png</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 02 Sep 2015 01:29:39 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Developer Logs</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/announcing-the-story-of-crossfire/14371.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Announcing: The Story of Crossfire</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[MisterDigitalGuy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Sage J. Fox">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Sage J. Fox:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Not to mention it’s a tad ludicrous to assume it’s even possible for something exactly like HLDM to take place in BMDM. They’re gonna be different, there’s no way around that. And don’t know how you wouldn’t see that as okay.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>As Text mentioned in his gasworks dev blog, the HLDM maps were in much need of improvement. They had issues with flow and design, as well as being fairly bland. So I’d expect that BM crossfire to be very different from HL crossfire, albeit with good reason.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/announcing-the-story-of-crossfire/14371/27">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/announcing-the-story-of-crossfire/14371/27</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 02 Sep 2015 01:29:39 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14371-27</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/announcing-the-story-of-crossfire/14371.rss">Announcing: The Story of Crossfire</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Announcing: The Story of Crossfire</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Sage_J_Fox]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>There’s also the issue that, while taking community feedback in is of course important, it’s ultimately up solely to the devs what  their “goal” for BMDM is, a part of that being what they think its ideal player count is.</p>
<p>Not to mention it’s a tad ludicrous to assume it’s even possible for something exactly like HLDM to take place in BMDM. They’re gonna be different, there’s no way around that. And don’t know how you wouldn’t see that as okay.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/announcing-the-story-of-crossfire/14371/26">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/announcing-the-story-of-crossfire/14371/26</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 02 Sep 2015 00:16:59 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14371-26</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/announcing-the-story-of-crossfire/14371.rss">Announcing: The Story of Crossfire</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Announcing: The Story of Crossfire</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Slendgy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>While what you’re saying makes sense, It would be essentially twice the workload to create 2 very similar maps, especially if something that will certainly be done by the community is taking developer resources.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/announcing-the-story-of-crossfire/14371/25">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/announcing-the-story-of-crossfire/14371/25</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2015 21:51:33 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14371-25</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/announcing-the-story-of-crossfire/14371.rss">Announcing: The Story of Crossfire</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Announcing: The Story of Crossfire</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[fury]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote group-black-mesa-devs" data-username="TextFAMGUY1">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/user_avatar/leakfree.org/textfamguy1/40/4294_2.png" class="avatar"> TextFAMGUY1:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>We won’t do 2 versions of our own map, that doesn’t make sense. We have confidence in our design decisions and are always open for feedback and change!</p>
<p>However, we’re sure that the community will certainly make lots of interesting and awesome changes to what we do with it. I’m not sure if we’re planning on releasing MP vmfs or not (I believe we are, I’m not sure why it hasn’t happened yet) but I’m sure you’ll see lots of Crossfire variants on the workshops too. That’s the beauty of modding!</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Explain please…<br>
I think it’s normal to be confident about own work… at least it should be that way… otherwise it’d need more work  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=9" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"><br>
But yea… I think it would make sense to make 2 official versions of crossfire, because it’s a very popular map which was originally designed for duel (ofc it works in FFA, too) but it doesn’t work well in TDM (mostly because of wallgauss)… And in original crossfire there was no  secret room at all… Most online servers run a hacked version of the original map which allows players to enter the secret, so called “blue room”. I think the blue room is so popular because it enlarges the map further to support more players.<br>
But if you ask me, you should not design every map for 8 - 16 or more players… Bounce and Lambda Bunker for example were both originally designed for low playernumbers (3vs3 TDM works very good - it’s the best for HL Teamplay, because with few players it’s easier to communicate and share information with your team while having fast and action-packed gameplay)… BM maps are bigger and contain more items --&gt; It’s not good for small TDM like 3vs3. I’d say most current BM maps are currently best played in 5vs5 (maybe even more)… Personally I don’t enjoy to play such big matches on complicated maps.<br>
There should be big, small and medium sized maps in BMDM to allow all kind of matches… And it should be obvious to people what map is best suited for high or low playernumbers…<br>
I understand that people (noob players, who don’t understand the whole balance of the game) want to reach weapons quick to have more fun… But personally I think it’s is bad to design maps with Mc Donald’s mentality… Maps need depth in gameplay and a good learning curve to show off real quality. And it also adds depth to have dead ends and unimportant areas in maps for good players to use for their advantage. This kind of gameplay-design adds things to learn and motivates to practise and play the game more. Back to what I initially tried to say:<br>
Crossfire is extremely popular with low (Duel) and high playernumbers (16 or more player FFA) and could also be very fun in 3v3 (or maybe even slightly more) TDM, if there was a second version to support it better… In HLDM there was this extremely popular crossfire version called ag_crossfire (was also part of most league-mappools), which was bad for 1v1 (because of wallgaussable railings and overpowered secret rooms) but good for TDM, because it offered more space (blue room and gauss-secret), new crossbow-area at bunker-yard and simpler, redesigned bunker to make that area more useful. If you plan to make only one version, you should think about what your crossfire version should be… Should it stay a duel map (1v1) or should it be suited for Teamplay (I recommend to design it for 3vs3, because 3vs3 offers the best TDM experience on most maps imho… exceptions are boot_camp, stalkx and maybe gasworks). In my opinion the best way would be to have 2 versions. One for TDM and one for Duel, because both gamemodes play out differently and should get respected in their individual ways. But yea… Ofc there will be mods and it’s your decision what the official BM crossfire should be like.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/announcing-the-story-of-crossfire/14371/24">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/announcing-the-story-of-crossfire/14371/24</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2015 17:31:26 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14371-24</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/announcing-the-story-of-crossfire/14371.rss">Announcing: The Story of Crossfire</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Announcing: The Story of Crossfire</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Fr0z3n]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><em>Hopefully</em> the crossfire blog that I’d like to do will be going up this week. But there will definitely be something with Crossfire happening by Weds.</p>
<p>The stream this week will be a community showcase of 2 maps from the workshop, one very small, one very large. Both something to chat about.</p>
<p>Also, everything will happen by Weds (unless something happens to me), I have to travel the second half of the week.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/announcing-the-story-of-crossfire/14371/23">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/announcing-the-story-of-crossfire/14371/23</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2015 14:57:59 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14371-23</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/announcing-the-story-of-crossfire/14371.rss">Announcing: The Story of Crossfire</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Announcing: The Story of Crossfire</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[TextFAMGUY1]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>We won’t do 2 versions of our own map, that doesn’t make sense. We have confidence in our design decisions and are always open for feedback and change!</p>
<p>However, we’re sure that the community will certainly make lots of interesting and awesome changes to what we do with it. I’m not sure if we’re planning on releasing MP vmfs or not (I believe we are, I’m not sure why it hasn’t happened yet) but I’m sure you’ll see lots of Crossfire variants on the workshops too. That’s the beauty of modding!</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/announcing-the-story-of-crossfire/14371/22">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/announcing-the-story-of-crossfire/14371/22</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2015 14:26:08 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14371-22</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/announcing-the-story-of-crossfire/14371.rss">Announcing: The Story of Crossfire</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Announcing: The Story of Crossfire</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[fury]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I guess he will show some progress on upcoming BM dev twitch-stream… It’s sheduled for wednesday if I remember right… I thought a bit about what I would like to see in BM crossfire and I think there should be 2 versions. Version 1 should be just like the original Crossfire, but more detailed and maybe slightly different dimensions. Version 2 should be just like version 1, but more advanced… For example you could add new Areas behind MP5 house and RPG house… You could also make the RPG house cellar (known as “blue room”) accessible and add some believable layout to that area… I think I might just make an altered version of my dm_pro_crossfire… Crossfire version 2 could primaryly get designed for TDM, while version 1 would be designed for duel… Another idea I had was to add visuals to the airstrike. It would be cool to see jets flying in the 3d skybox right before the map gets nuked  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=9" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/announcing-the-story-of-crossfire/14371/21">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/announcing-the-story-of-crossfire/14371/21</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2015 13:07:32 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14371-21</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/announcing-the-story-of-crossfire/14371.rss">Announcing: The Story of Crossfire</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Announcing: The Story of Crossfire</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Artic_Xiongmao]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>So, it’s September. When is the next Story of Crossfire update coming?  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=9" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/announcing-the-story-of-crossfire/14371/20">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/announcing-the-story-of-crossfire/14371/20</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2015 10:15:57 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14371-20</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/announcing-the-story-of-crossfire/14371.rss">Announcing: The Story of Crossfire</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Announcing: The Story of Crossfire</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Fr0z3n]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Joe chief">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Joe chief:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Do you plan on creating cannons for the towers, or will they be replaced for weapons already ingame?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>We’re currently planning to use the .50Cal Machine guns</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/announcing-the-story-of-crossfire/14371/19">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/announcing-the-story-of-crossfire/14371/19</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 17 Aug 2015 14:26:46 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14371-19</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/announcing-the-story-of-crossfire/14371.rss">Announcing: The Story of Crossfire</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Announcing: The Story of Crossfire</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Admiral_Sakai]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>They are tiny, but I can see 50-cals in the towers in the bottom middle screenshot.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/announcing-the-story-of-crossfire/14371/18">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/announcing-the-story-of-crossfire/14371/18</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 17 Aug 2015 12:56:30 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14371-18</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/announcing-the-story-of-crossfire/14371.rss">Announcing: The Story of Crossfire</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Announcing: The Story of Crossfire</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Joe_chief]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Do you plan on creating cannons for the towers, or will they be replaced for weapons already ingame?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/announcing-the-story-of-crossfire/14371/17">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/announcing-the-story-of-crossfire/14371/17</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 17 Aug 2015 11:49:34 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14371-17</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/announcing-the-story-of-crossfire/14371.rss">Announcing: The Story of Crossfire</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Announcing: The Story of Crossfire</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Fr0z3n]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Narfin">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/n/46a35a/40.png" class="avatar"> Narfin:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Wait, I’m a little confused. Is this like the Story of Gasworks where you will be showing us all your progress up to the map’s current state, or are these screenshots current and we get to see Crossfire as you are developing it?</p>
<p>Either way I’m so excited for this! Crossfire is such an iconic and unique map (at the time, anyway). I do have a question: Are you planning to leave in the death button? I was bummed when the flood button was removed from Undertow :&lt;</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>These are screenshots of the current Crossfire, and you’ll be seeing it as we develop it.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/announcing-the-story-of-crossfire/14371/16">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/announcing-the-story-of-crossfire/14371/16</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 17 Aug 2015 11:11:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14371-16</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/announcing-the-story-of-crossfire/14371.rss">Announcing: The Story of Crossfire</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Announcing: The Story of Crossfire</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Narfin]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Wait, I’m a little confused. Is this like the Story of Gasworks where you will be showing us all your progress up to the map’s current state, or are these screenshots current and we get to see Crossfire as you are developing it?</p>
<p>Either way I’m so excited for this! Crossfire is such an iconic and unique map (at the time, anyway). I do have a question: Are you planning to leave in the death button? I was bummed when the flood button was removed from Undertow :&lt;</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/announcing-the-story-of-crossfire/14371/15">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/announcing-the-story-of-crossfire/14371/15</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 17 Aug 2015 02:39:55 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14371-15</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/announcing-the-story-of-crossfire/14371.rss">Announcing: The Story of Crossfire</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Announcing: The Story of Crossfire</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Dalek]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Will there be that secret room with the crossbow, batteries, and healthkits?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/announcing-the-story-of-crossfire/14371/14">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/announcing-the-story-of-crossfire/14371/14</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 17 Aug 2015 00:47:08 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14371-14</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/announcing-the-story-of-crossfire/14371.rss">Announcing: The Story of Crossfire</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Announcing: The Story of Crossfire</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Dmx6]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I just hope we will able to jump over the deathly Trigger like in HL1.  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=9" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/announcing-the-story-of-crossfire/14371/13">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/announcing-the-story-of-crossfire/14371/13</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 16 Aug 2015 21:20:54 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14371-13</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/announcing-the-story-of-crossfire/14371.rss">Announcing: The Story of Crossfire</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Announcing: The Story of Crossfire</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Fr0z3n]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Oh, I see, you kind of bounce off the lip and into the window.</p>
<p>Thats neat, I love those little things.</p>
<p>I will see what I can do.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/announcing-the-story-of-crossfire/14371/12">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/announcing-the-story-of-crossfire/14371/12</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 15 Aug 2015 17:13:14 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14371-12</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/announcing-the-story-of-crossfire/14371.rss">Announcing: The Story of Crossfire</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Announcing: The Story of Crossfire</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[fury]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><a href="https://youtu.be/j_Mo7prGfSI?t=23m53s" rel="nofollow noopener">youtu.be/j_Mo7prGfSI?t=23m53s</a><br>
Edit: 23:53<br>
you see i leave the room and gaussjump against the ramp below the window and get bounced into the uppder healthcharger batteries room.<br>
you can use the same kind of trick near the other LJ to jump up into MP5 house… (but i don’t have a video for that, sorry)<br>
It would also be cool if this jump would work in BM (later when you have new movement code):<br>
<a href="https://youtu.be/j_Mo7prGfSI?t=23m43s" rel="nofollow noopener">youtu.be/j_Mo7prGfSI?t=23m43s</a><br>
Edit: 21:43</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/announcing-the-story-of-crossfire/14371/11">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/announcing-the-story-of-crossfire/14371/11</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 15 Aug 2015 15:16:45 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14371-11</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/announcing-the-story-of-crossfire/14371.rss">Announcing: The Story of Crossfire</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Announcing: The Story of Crossfire</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Fr0z3n]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Could you provide a video of what you mean with that?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/announcing-the-story-of-crossfire/14371/10">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/announcing-the-story-of-crossfire/14371/10</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 15 Aug 2015 14:18:05 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14371-10</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/announcing-the-story-of-crossfire/14371.rss">Announcing: The Story of Crossfire</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Announcing: The Story of Crossfire</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[fury]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>you should readd the ramps below windows… they allow players to perform trickjumps… for example when you leave LJ Egon and gaussjump against the opposite window-ramp, you bounce into healthcharger batteries room. it’s a very useful and often used trick.<br>
edit: but yea… if these ramps won’t get added, people can still play my dm_pro_crossfire… it’s pretty much exact the same like in HLDM. I’d like to add some more dirt to the walls to make it look better… atm it looks way too clean… so if somebody knows a good overlay or decal texture that I could use to add dirt on walls I would be glad to know  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/wink.png?v=9" title=":wink:" class="emoji" alt=":wink:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/announcing-the-story-of-crossfire/14371/9">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/announcing-the-story-of-crossfire/14371/9</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 15 Aug 2015 12:32:26 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14371-9</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/announcing-the-story-of-crossfire/14371.rss">Announcing: The Story of Crossfire</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Announcing: The Story of Crossfire</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypt]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>It’s a start.</p>
<p>I definitely like that we’ll be seeing it go through most of development. I think that’ll help a lot in regards to feedback not necessarily being as drastic to implement as it would be on a more complete map.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/announcing-the-story-of-crossfire/14371/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/announcing-the-story-of-crossfire/14371/8</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 15 Aug 2015 04:39:05 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14371-8</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/announcing-the-story-of-crossfire/14371.rss">Announcing: The Story of Crossfire</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Announcing: The Story of Crossfire</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Slendgy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>The workshop one looks a bit more HL2 than Black Mesa.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/announcing-the-story-of-crossfire/14371/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/announcing-the-story-of-crossfire/14371/7</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 15 Aug 2015 02:26:36 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14371-7</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/announcing-the-story-of-crossfire/14371.rss">Announcing: The Story of Crossfire</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Announcing: The Story of Crossfire</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Admiral_Sakai]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I believe you may have been thinking of this: <a href="https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=438811384&amp;searchtext=" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=438811384&amp;searchtext=</a></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/announcing-the-story-of-crossfire/14371/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/announcing-the-story-of-crossfire/14371/6</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 14 Aug 2015 22:23:27 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14371-6</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/announcing-the-story-of-crossfire/14371.rss">Announcing: The Story of Crossfire</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Announcing: The Story of Crossfire</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[FlotsamX]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I haven’t been following Black Mesa that closely, but isn’t there already a BM Crossfire map? I remember playing one only about a month ago, with all the updated visuals of Black Mesa. Was that fanmade?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/announcing-the-story-of-crossfire/14371/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/announcing-the-story-of-crossfire/14371/5</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 14 Aug 2015 22:16:19 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14371-5</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/announcing-the-story-of-crossfire/14371.rss">Announcing: The Story of Crossfire</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Announcing: The Story of Crossfire</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Admiral_Sakai]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>All <span class="bbcode-i">right</span>, a new devblog!</p>
<p>That reminds me, I need to get myself in gear and work on that BMPD blog I promised people.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/announcing-the-story-of-crossfire/14371/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/announcing-the-story-of-crossfire/14371/4</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 14 Aug 2015 21:57:58 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14371-4</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/announcing-the-story-of-crossfire/14371.rss">Announcing: The Story of Crossfire</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Announcing: The Story of Crossfire</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Turret_Cube]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Yesh!!!1 More Boatz Plz</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/announcing-the-story-of-crossfire/14371/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/announcing-the-story-of-crossfire/14371/3</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 14 Aug 2015 20:53:20 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14371-3</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/announcing-the-story-of-crossfire/14371.rss">Announcing: The Story of Crossfire</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
