<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>DM_Undertow pipe bug + 2 others</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/dm-undertow-pipe-bug-2-others/13824</link>
    <description>Map: DM_Undertow

Getpos: setang 22.373985 -90.065651 0.000000
setpos -100.526596 -1057.720459 -562.735107;

When in an online server, it would seem that the bend of the waterflow in the pipe here constrains the player in place for a few seconds instead of quickly spitting them out - Whereas in a local game the player is smoothly ejected from the pipe going down the water flow. Possibly related to netcode rather than the map itself.

In addition, I noticed that after a few deaths, occasionally the viewmodels for all guns will become invisible until the end of the match, with the only sign of appearing being when the Revolver&#39;s ironsights are used. No solid data on this beyond all incidents of it so far occuring on Undertow.

Lastly, it would seem that Shadowplay does not work with the Steam version of Black Mesa - Not sure if this is a bug on GeForce Experience&#39;s end or Black Mesa&#39;s.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 06 May 2015 03:18:14 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>In-game Issues</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/dm-undertow-pipe-bug-2-others/13824.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>DM_Undertow pipe bug + 2 others</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[ValkyrurS7]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Map: DM_Undertow</p>
<p>Getpos: setang 22.373985 -90.065651 0.000000<br>
setpos -100.526596 -1057.720459 -562.735107;</p>
<p>When in an online server, it would seem that the bend of the waterflow in the pipe here constrains the player in place for a few seconds instead of quickly spitting them out - Whereas in a local game the player is smoothly ejected from the pipe going down the water flow. Possibly related to netcode rather than the map itself.</p>
<p>In addition, I noticed that after a few deaths, occasionally the viewmodels for all guns will become invisible until the end of the match, with the only sign of appearing being when the Revolver’s ironsights are used. No solid data on this beyond all incidents of it so far occuring on Undertow.</p>
<p>Lastly, it would seem that Shadowplay does not work with the Steam version of Black Mesa - Not sure if this is a bug on GeForce Experience’s end or Black Mesa’s.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/dm-undertow-pipe-bug-2-others/13824/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/dm-undertow-pipe-bug-2-others/13824/1</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 06 May 2015 03:18:14 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13824-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/dm-undertow-pipe-bug-2-others/13824.rss">DM_Undertow pipe bug + 2 others</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
