<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Least Favourite Chapter?</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/least-favourite-chapter/11083</link>
    <description>![](upload://ocwd1KXTKgu45N8H9zFA9eTtoTv.png)

A section of the game just not to your liking? Tell us what your least favourite chapter was and why.

Mine would be Residue Processing.

Conveyor belt mazes are still plentiful, and in the larger portions of the factory there are few ladders to use for backtracking after miscalculating a jump. Whoever was in charge of these levels probably aimed to stay true to the original, which they did very well, but some of these parts of could have benefit from a little reinventing.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 30 Sep 2012 00:48:10 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>The Cafeteria</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/least-favourite-chapter/11083.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Least Favourite Chapter?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Comrade_Tiki]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="xalener">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/x/cc9497/40.png" class="avatar"> xalener:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>My least favorite missions in the original HL ended up being my favorite in BM. So, yeah. That’s pretty cool.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Completely agreed. I used to hate On A Rail with a passion. Now I’ll look forward to it on any BM replays.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/least-favourite-chapter/11083/47">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/least-favourite-chapter/11083/47</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 30 Sep 2012 00:48:10 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11083-47</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/least-favourite-chapter/11083.rss">Least Favourite Chapter?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Least Favourite Chapter?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Twilightwolf4]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>they need to remove some crates and boxes from the tripmine trap in surface Tension</p>
<p>I feel like I have no movement options</p>
<p>actually, most of the levels were fine, but cluttered with unnecessary debris and boxes, crates, etc that, for me, seemed out of place</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/least-favourite-chapter/11083/46">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/least-favourite-chapter/11083/46</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 29 Sep 2012 23:41:07 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11083-46</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/least-favourite-chapter/11083.rss">Least Favourite Chapter?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Least Favourite Chapter?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[xalener]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Surface tension. Every little quirk left over from the combine AI showed up in the Hgrunts and reared their ugly heads.</p>
<p>My least favorite missions in the original HL ended up being my favorite in BM. So, yeah. That’s pretty cool.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/least-favourite-chapter/11083/45">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/least-favourite-chapter/11083/45</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 29 Sep 2012 20:52:35 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11083-45</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/least-favourite-chapter/11083.rss">Least Favourite Chapter?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Least Favourite Chapter?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Paz_Ortega_Andrade]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I liked all the chapters more or less, and I can’t really say that there were some chapters that I didn’t like at all. Each of them had something interesting that made me like them.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/least-favourite-chapter/11083/44">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/least-favourite-chapter/11083/44</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 29 Sep 2012 20:48:04 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11083-44</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/least-favourite-chapter/11083.rss">Least Favourite Chapter?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Least Favourite Chapter?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Comrade_Tiki]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I was kinda disappointed not to see any bullsquids in the resonance-cascade teleports…  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/frowning.png?v=9" title=":frowning:" class="emoji" alt=":frowning:"></p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="MaxTheLimit">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/m/0ea827/40.png" class="avatar"> MaxTheLimit:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Is there a youtube vid of this somewhere? The touchscreen works flawlessly for me. I want to see how it looks for someone who is seeing a problem with it.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>My framerate was atrocious enough in that section as-is. It was very poorly optimized. Normally I am able to get through such slideshows by facing toward the wall, but that section of the game forces you to stand in the middle of a complex arena.</p>
<p>I don’t think running FRAPS with the flickering targeting-cursor and slideshow garg-shaking tower would be wise. Plus the level design there sucked-- I ran straight for the far tower and waited as I watched the garg started shaking the first tower. Like wtf?</p>
<p>And when it came to operating the interactive screen with its flickering cursor, I tried clicking several times but it had no effect, and I was spamming the Use key with no effect, and that section of the game sucked vortigaunt ass. I tried clicking where I wanted the target to be with no effect, and tried clicking the fire button with no effect, and tried hitting spacebar with no effect (as the fire button was displayed like a space bar).</p>
<p>Give me a god-damn coordinate entry system, with a fire button which I don’t need to click on a dozen times, and I’ll have that garg for dessert. It’s from shit like that why I don’t have a smartphone.</p>
<p>…</p>
<p>But let me talk about parts I liked.</p>
<p>I loved that track-lowering section of On A Rail. I abandoned the train to explore on foot, and ended up finding the control room through its back-door. The multiple stages required for advancing were pleasantly hinted at by the sign in the control room. That section of OAR felt nonlinear but not large enough to get lost in.</p>
<p>I loved entering Questionable Ethics to find the swarm of houndeyes asleep. I had lost track of where I was in the previous chapter, so entering QE was a warm and sudden surprise. Exploring QE was fun, with the various rooms… snark-cannon… xen observation…<br>
but I never got the opportunity to lure human grunts into a tesla-containment trap. And once I gassed the headcrabs, in the xen observation area, I was unable to enter the room. I thought for sure the lockdown effect would be temporary, but it never seemed to expire. Fortunately I was not in need of its health|armor chargers, so it was only a small loss.</p>
<p>I loved the huge tangle  of machinery in Residue Processing. I had to manage my ammo very carefully in there; I work well under pressure, so that was fun. And unlocking all the doors to previous rooms?.. made me think about playing BM co-op. The mod has co-op potential.</p>
<p>And the last sentry guns I found, I was able to kidnap. I carried them along, down the big truck-elevator (after clearing out the alien fodder ahead), until I reached the second set of assassins. It was epic having two sentries on my side when dealing with those fast ladies… I only wish the guns didn’t run out of ammo so quickly.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/least-favourite-chapter/11083/43">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/least-favourite-chapter/11083/43</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 29 Sep 2012 19:47:23 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11083-43</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/least-favourite-chapter/11083.rss">Least Favourite Chapter?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Least Favourite Chapter?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Spamds]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>A bit off topic, but Lamda felt short and thus not very pleasant chapter. when I first gazed upon Lambda labs, after turning on the pumps… I went for the giant machine with circling platforms. After going through several teleports with almost every guess right, I found myself in last stage a bit quicker than I would’ve liked. I remember going through all the levels of Lambda in HL1. As for most annoying, Residue Processing was the one.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/least-favourite-chapter/11083/42">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/least-favourite-chapter/11083/42</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 24 Sep 2012 10:35:05 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11083-42</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/least-favourite-chapter/11083.rss">Least Favourite Chapter?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Least Favourite Chapter?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[MrFob]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>IMO, residue processing is one of the chapters where BM shows the biggest improvement over HL. Why? Because in HL, you were navigating through one grey room after another. Everything just had brown and grey textures with horrible resolution and in between that and the murky water, when I did it the first time in HL (and even when I repeated it), I had no idea where I was going. In BM, it captures the feel and the level architecture but there are more individual visual clues to distinguish the different areas and rooms and dagers are much more apparent.</p>
<p>As for Lambda core, the same thing is the case IMO. I had no problem with the elevators, etc. it took me a while to figure it all out as well but it was pure fun all the way. Besides, the coolent water looks amazing  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=9" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"> . As for the pool in the middle, I was really glad it was there because when I first entered the level, and I got rushed by what felt like about 20 Houndeyes, I got one to charge up right next to the explosive barrels on the upper floor and then jumped over the railing into the pool, escaping the explosion and killing about 10 of them in one stroke. Brilliant moment.</p>
<p>The morter screen: Is the flickering a bug? I thought it was supposed to be some sort of transmission error, static or something. While I agree it’s pretty bad to handle (especially with the garg shaking things up), I thought it was meant to do that.</p>
<p>I don’t really have a least favorite level, I really had a blast all the way through. while I was sad about some of the cuts, what was still there ist still awesome.</p>
<p>My greatest moment of dissapointment though: The scientist in the power section of Blast Pit no longer sits on top of the generator (“this is my hiding spot”) and then gets the shits when Gordon turns the thing on. I always loved that guy. BM makes up for it though with his further comments (“I had to ditch the others”) and the remarks of the second scientist at the beginning of that section who waits for his “friend”  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=9" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"> .</p>
<p>EDIT: <span class="mention">@Bunnykicker</span>: I think you are right. Somehow I remembered the original HL to be much more challanging in that section. Weren’t there quite a few grunts around in the pump sections originally? Maybe I am misremembering here but yea, to me it felt easier as well.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/least-favourite-chapter/11083/41">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/least-favourite-chapter/11083/41</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 24 Sep 2012 08:17:43 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11083-41</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/least-favourite-chapter/11083.rss">Least Favourite Chapter?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Least Favourite Chapter?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Dr_Maxwell]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Definitely Lambda Core.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/least-favourite-chapter/11083/40">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/least-favourite-chapter/11083/40</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 24 Sep 2012 08:11:37 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11083-40</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/least-favourite-chapter/11083.rss">Least Favourite Chapter?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Least Favourite Chapter?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[TheBunnyKicker]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I didn’t think lambda core was that confusing… Took me maybe an extra 30 minutes to figure out where to go in some places but you guys act like its pumpkin head 2.</p>
<p>Really it wasn’t that bad and it kind of felt rewarding to figure it out with little to no help.</p>
<p>That being said my least favorite chapter is still lambda core cus i felt the action kind of hit a screeching halt. There was maybe one room in the whole lab that made me actually have to try. The guy that says “its a zoo in there” before you get in made me think there would be a lot of Xen monsters but there really wasn’t.</p>
<p>Maybe its just me idk</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/least-favourite-chapter/11083/39">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/least-favourite-chapter/11083/39</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 24 Sep 2012 08:02:17 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11083-39</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/least-favourite-chapter/11083.rss">Least Favourite Chapter?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Least Favourite Chapter?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[RicheyEdwards]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="MaxTheLimit">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/m/0ea827/40.png" class="avatar"> MaxTheLimit:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Is there a youtube vid of this somewhere? The touchscreen works flawlessly for me. I want to see how it looks for someone who is seeing a problem with it.</p>
<p>Also, I still don’t like residue processing. It’s better than it was. I still don’t like the jumping and navigation though.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=2xaVQuWe1uA&amp;feature=plcp#t=3m30s" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Here</a>. The aiming reticle constantly jumping around, bit of input lag when you actually click to aim it and the actual cross-hair flickering almost constantly. I mean, I didn’t have any <span class="bbcode-i">real</span> problems using it other than mis-clicking a few times because of the input lag, but still.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-i">Note: that’s not my video and the bloke in it didn’t have any serious problems using it either, but the screen itself looks very buggy for many people.</span></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/least-favourite-chapter/11083/38">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/least-favourite-chapter/11083/38</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 24 Sep 2012 07:54:03 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11083-38</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/least-favourite-chapter/11083.rss">Least Favourite Chapter?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Least Favourite Chapter?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[dky.tehkingd.u]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I actually didn’t find Residue Processing to be all that horrible. I actually like Black Mesa’s version more than the Half-Life version, even if they are both quite similar in many aspects.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/least-favourite-chapter/11083/37">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/least-favourite-chapter/11083/37</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 23 Sep 2012 22:58:32 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11083-37</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/least-favourite-chapter/11083.rss">Least Favourite Chapter?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Least Favourite Chapter?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[sourcegamer101]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I have no least favourite chapters, they’re all good.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/least-favourite-chapter/11083/36">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/least-favourite-chapter/11083/36</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 23 Sep 2012 22:36:41 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11083-36</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/least-favourite-chapter/11083.rss">Least Favourite Chapter?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Least Favourite Chapter?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[bullsquid]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Residue processing requires more subtle clues about how to navigate it and to reinforce the feeling of loneliness that you should have exploring it. I remember that after chamber 19 in Portal you have levels with similar ambience. It would be cool if the devs used that knowledge to improve the level.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/least-favourite-chapter/11083/35">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/least-favourite-chapter/11083/35</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 23 Sep 2012 22:33:42 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11083-35</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/least-favourite-chapter/11083.rss">Least Favourite Chapter?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Least Favourite Chapter?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Bjossi]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Apprehension for me. It is the same torture as the HL1 version, if not more, thanks to the fact I can’t see squat underwater where you fight the fishes or in the freezer (I have bad eyesight). I might update this later since I just started Residue Processing.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/least-favourite-chapter/11083/34">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/least-favourite-chapter/11083/34</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 23 Sep 2012 22:30:23 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11083-34</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/least-favourite-chapter/11083.rss">Least Favourite Chapter?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Least Favourite Chapter?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Lost_one]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I don’t see why people hate residue Processing that much. sure there’s not many enemies to kill there, but it’s supposed to weaken you at that point in the game, you go from being a scientist with weapons to a scientist in a suit. You’ve been caught, your weapons are gone, you need to figure out a way back up to the surface, to find yourself some weapons and get to the lamda complex. You’re supposed to feel weak, lost, and alone. Thats the point of it. The pacing is so slow for that chapter because you’re lost, much like in OAR where you’re supposed to be lost.</p>
<p>Thats my two cents anyways. I don’t really have a least favorite chapter myself. OAR could have been longer really, I wanted to feel lost like in a maze. would have put more validity to the security guard’s comment “When you find the rocket…IF you find the rocket, you need to get up to the control room and launch it yourself.” Meaning that there was a maze between you and the rocket.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/least-favourite-chapter/11083/33">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/least-favourite-chapter/11083/33</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 23 Sep 2012 22:18:01 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11083-33</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/least-favourite-chapter/11083.rss">Least Favourite Chapter?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Least Favourite Chapter?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Medkit]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>No least loved chapters for me. Love Black Mesa, and I love Half-Life.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/least-favourite-chapter/11083/32">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/least-favourite-chapter/11083/32</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 23 Sep 2012 21:46:26 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11083-32</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/least-favourite-chapter/11083.rss">Least Favourite Chapter?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Least Favourite Chapter?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Bloodshot]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I actually loved residue processing. I like dangerous environmental hazards and traps.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/least-favourite-chapter/11083/31">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/least-favourite-chapter/11083/31</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 23 Sep 2012 21:44:10 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11083-31</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/least-favourite-chapter/11083.rss">Least Favourite Chapter?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Least Favourite Chapter?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[your_evil_twin]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I’d like to compliment whoever it is that made Residue Processing. I think pretty much everyone will agree that it was the weakest chapter in Half-Life, but the Black Mesa version was far less irritating. Sure, it’s a change of pace compared to rest of the game, but it’s now some reasonable puzzle gameplay rather than something you just want to noclip through.</p>
<p>I had no trouble with the Lambda Core coolant sections. Thought they looked fantastic and I enjoyed exploring and figuring out where to go. Going the “wrong” way would tend to lead to ammo or health or suit energy or something so no complaints there. Though I think it would have been good if there was more indication that activating the pumps unlocks an Auxillary Tank room; I stumbled upon it by accident and I can imagine other people instead thinking they need to jump into the coolant in the first area. (The pool of coolant in the first area serves no purpose, it has ladders to get out if you fall in but there’s nothing to find down there.)</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="MaxTheLimit">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/m/0ea827/40.png" class="avatar"> MaxTheLimit:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Is there a youtube vid of this somewhere? The touchscreen works flawlessly for me. I want to see how it looks for someone who is seeing a problem with it.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>For me its not that the screen itself was flickering, rather the targeting cursor that would flicker, a rapid flicker where it is invisible for longer than it is visible. I found that I had to furiously go CLICKCLICKCLICKCLICKCLICK where I wanted it to bomb for it actually register my click.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/least-favourite-chapter/11083/30">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/least-favourite-chapter/11083/30</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 23 Sep 2012 21:34:41 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11083-30</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/least-favourite-chapter/11083.rss">Least Favourite Chapter?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Least Favourite Chapter?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[bullsquid]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="dky.tehkingd.u">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/user_avatar/leakfree.org/dky.tehkingd.u/40/4377_2.png" class="avatar"> dky.tehkingd.u:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>No, the problem is that the elevators only become useful on your second or third playthrough when you actually already know the solution. The first time through, when you decide to take the elevator to explore, only to be sent back to the beginning, you really begin to hate it. Especially since EVERY elevator does that. And then you attempt to figure out why certain doors are locked, only to flip a switch that seemed to have zero relevance to the solution which magically unlocks the doors. And then you go through those doors only to find that you basically backtracked again.</p>
<p>In a backtracking game like Half-Life, if you’re going to backtrack, you should either make the backtracking route ONLY available once you’ve finished your task (eg, We’ve Got Hostiles), OR, make the backtracking route the exact same as the original route you took (eg, Blast Pit).</p>
<p>Based on that, the only useful and non-annoying elevators were the ones in the coolant pool, because they start off at the endpoint so you don’t ever think to explore using it.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I agree it should be better implemented, but if you take your time to observe you can actually use the elevator to your favor on the first walkthrough. I used them to have advantage in the battles against the vortigaunts. I wish they were more evident, though…</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/least-favourite-chapter/11083/29">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/least-favourite-chapter/11083/29</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 23 Sep 2012 20:51:52 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11083-29</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/least-favourite-chapter/11083.rss">Least Favourite Chapter?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Least Favourite Chapter?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Gunsofglory]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Surface Tension, just cause I hated it in Half life, liked it more in Black Mesa but still kinda was meh about it. I just like being inside Black Mesa rather than outside it. (Really liked the jets and stuff in the background though)</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/least-favourite-chapter/11083/28">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/least-favourite-chapter/11083/28</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 23 Sep 2012 20:46:47 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11083-28</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/least-favourite-chapter/11083.rss">Least Favourite Chapter?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Least Favourite Chapter?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Aiden_Pearce]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Residue Processing by far.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/least-favourite-chapter/11083/27">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/least-favourite-chapter/11083/27</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 23 Sep 2012 20:41:30 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11083-27</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/least-favourite-chapter/11083.rss">Least Favourite Chapter?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Least Favourite Chapter?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[lolschi]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Surface Tension for obvious reasons. Many things were cut.</p>
<p>What’s there is great, except for the helicopter battle. It took me some time to figure out that there is a box with infinite rockets. I think it’s the only ammo box in the entire game. To introduce such a mechanic during a tough bossfight is not a good idea. Plus there is no room to maneuver. The heli kills almost instantly and I don’t like the attack pattern. The battle felt a bit dull, almost like work. Wait 10 seconds, peak around corner, shoot, take cover. Repeat 10 times (on Hard). Sounds like a modern fps. <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/open_mouth.png?v=9" title=":open_mouth:" class="emoji" alt=":open_mouth:"><br>
The tank battles are much better.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/least-favourite-chapter/11083/26">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/least-favourite-chapter/11083/26</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 23 Sep 2012 20:29:21 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11083-26</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/least-favourite-chapter/11083.rss">Least Favourite Chapter?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Least Favourite Chapter?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[dky.tehkingd.u]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Yeah the portals in Lambda Core were really well done. That was the good section of that chapter.  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=9" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/least-favourite-chapter/11083/25">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/least-favourite-chapter/11083/25</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 23 Sep 2012 20:09:37 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11083-25</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/least-favourite-chapter/11083.rss">Least Favourite Chapter?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Least Favourite Chapter?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Mr-President]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I loved the Lambda Core chapter. Yeah, I got lost in it, but I loved it. It brought me back to when I used to wander around for hours in HL 1. And the portals… I explored every entrance from portal 01 to 09, just because of how awesome they looked.</p>
<p>The only two chapters that dissapointed me were On a Rail and Surface Tension, simply because a lot of portions from them were cut and I was expecting to relive a lot of the stuff that I did in HL1, but they were just… gone.</p>
<p>I sincerely hope that when Xen comes out, the developers would also finish the missing portions from On a Rail and Surface Tension.</p>
<p>In any case, the game was fantastic. Would play again. Can’t wait for Deathmatch. I used to play a lot of HL 1 DM back in the day.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/least-favourite-chapter/11083/24">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/least-favourite-chapter/11083/24</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 23 Sep 2012 20:05:50 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11083-24</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/least-favourite-chapter/11083.rss">Least Favourite Chapter?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Least Favourite Chapter?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[dky.tehkingd.u]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>No, the problem is that the elevators only become useful on your second or third playthrough when you actually already know the solution. The first time through, when you decide to take the elevator to explore, only to be sent back to the beginning, you really begin to hate it. Especially since EVERY elevator does that. And then you attempt to figure out why certain doors are locked, only to flip a switch that seemed to have zero relevance to the solution which magically unlocks the doors. And then you go through those doors only to find that you basically backtracked again.</p>
<p>In a backtracking game like Half-Life, if you’re going to backtrack, you should either make the backtracking route ONLY available once you’ve finished your task (eg, We’ve Got Hostiles), OR, make the backtracking route the exact same as the original route you took (eg, Blast Pit).</p>
<p>Based on that, the only useful and non-annoying elevators were the ones in the coolant pool, because they start off at the endpoint so you don’t ever think to explore using it.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/least-favourite-chapter/11083/23">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/least-favourite-chapter/11083/23</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 23 Sep 2012 20:04:44 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11083-23</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/least-favourite-chapter/11083.rss">Least Favourite Chapter?</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
