<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Dead Space for PC, Is it Worth getting?</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/dead-space-for-pc-is-it-worth-getting/1191</link>
    <description>Well, I&#39;m Looking into buying Dead Space for PC, But today, I went through Metascore reviews and there seems to be a problem with the mouse controls. Is it Really worth the $61.00 AU bucks?</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 17 Aug 2009 04:34:43 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Technology and Gaming</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/dead-space-for-pc-is-it-worth-getting/1191.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Dead Space for PC, Is it Worth getting?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Deathmonkey7]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I’ve played through it and beat it.<br>
It is definitely worth a buy.  Especially if you like survival horror games.</p>
<p>However, after you install it and before you play it, I recommend downloading a hack to remove the internet activation.</p>
<p>Also, if the game runs fine, then VSync will be alright.  It changes the timing of the refresh so that you don’t get funky lines across your screen when the game is in action.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/dead-space-for-pc-is-it-worth-getting/1191/18">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/dead-space-for-pc-is-it-worth-getting/1191/18</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 17 Aug 2009 04:34:43 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-1191-18</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/dead-space-for-pc-is-it-worth-getting/1191.rss">Dead Space for PC, Is it Worth getting?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Dead Space for PC, Is it Worth getting?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Comrade_Tiki]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I’d have been able to <span class="bbcode-i">play</span> it if I just went ahead and did that, so I’m starting to consider it.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/dead-space-for-pc-is-it-worth-getting/1191/17">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/dead-space-for-pc-is-it-worth-getting/1191/17</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 17 Aug 2009 03:45:58 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-1191-17</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/dead-space-for-pc-is-it-worth-getting/1191.rss">Dead Space for PC, Is it Worth getting?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Dead Space for PC, Is it Worth getting?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[intooblivion]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Just download it illegally.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/dead-space-for-pc-is-it-worth-getting/1191/16">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/dead-space-for-pc-is-it-worth-getting/1191/16</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 16 Aug 2009 21:28:37 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-1191-16</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/dead-space-for-pc-is-it-worth-getting/1191.rss">Dead Space for PC, Is it Worth getting?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Dead Space for PC, Is it Worth getting?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Neon_Impulse]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I liked it and it’s quite scary at times, but Dead space’s atmosphere is more like bioshock or SS2. It’s creepy, not really scary.</p>
<p>Plus there are a few funny little glitches that you can make with the monsters, I’ve always enjoyed that.</p>
<p>But since the thread seems to be finished and you’re probably going to get it, I guess this was a rather unnecessary post.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/dead-space-for-pc-is-it-worth-getting/1191/15">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/dead-space-for-pc-is-it-worth-getting/1191/15</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 16 Aug 2009 21:26:44 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-1191-15</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/dead-space-for-pc-is-it-worth-getting/1191.rss">Dead Space for PC, Is it Worth getting?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Dead Space for PC, Is it Worth getting?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Garcian_Smith]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Yes. It’s very good.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/dead-space-for-pc-is-it-worth-getting/1191/14">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/dead-space-for-pc-is-it-worth-getting/1191/14</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 16 Aug 2009 17:53:50 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-1191-14</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/dead-space-for-pc-is-it-worth-getting/1191.rss">Dead Space for PC, Is it Worth getting?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Dead Space for PC, Is it Worth getting?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Deimos]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I didn’t enjoy it at all to be honest, I couldn’t even finish it before I uninstalled it.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/dead-space-for-pc-is-it-worth-getting/1191/13">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/dead-space-for-pc-is-it-worth-getting/1191/13</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 16 Aug 2009 11:56:36 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-1191-13</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/dead-space-for-pc-is-it-worth-getting/1191.rss">Dead Space for PC, Is it Worth getting?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Dead Space for PC, Is it Worth getting?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Duck]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>What fuck no, Resident evil was a First in it’s times, Like 1,2 and 3, How could you say something like that about it. :grr:</p>
<p>/thread</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/dead-space-for-pc-is-it-worth-getting/1191/12">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/dead-space-for-pc-is-it-worth-getting/1191/12</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 16 Aug 2009 02:22:59 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-1191-12</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/dead-space-for-pc-is-it-worth-getting/1191.rss">Dead Space for PC, Is it Worth getting?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Dead Space for PC, Is it Worth getting?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Ramirezoid]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Fuck resident evil.</p>
<p>I got Dead Space used new on the 360 for about thirty USD a few months ago. The problem with the 360 version (and most console shooters) is that it’s hard as dicks to actually aim, especially at the asteroid parts.</p>
<p>Get the PC version if you don’t have an Xbox/ do not wantget weird addons and achievements.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/dead-space-for-pc-is-it-worth-getting/1191/11">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/dead-space-for-pc-is-it-worth-getting/1191/11</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 16 Aug 2009 00:37:06 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-1191-11</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/dead-space-for-pc-is-it-worth-getting/1191.rss">Dead Space for PC, Is it Worth getting?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Dead Space for PC, Is it Worth getting?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Duck]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>well, resident evil is my favorite series (except 5 (WHERE ARE THE ZOMBIES??!!))<br>
so Dead space shouldn’t have a problem with me</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/dead-space-for-pc-is-it-worth-getting/1191/10">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/dead-space-for-pc-is-it-worth-getting/1191/10</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 15 Aug 2009 23:54:57 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-1191-10</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/dead-space-for-pc-is-it-worth-getting/1191.rss">Dead Space for PC, Is it Worth getting?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Dead Space for PC, Is it Worth getting?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[a-dot]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>All i have to say to this thread is that dead space is just resident evil. BUT IN SPACE :awesome:</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/dead-space-for-pc-is-it-worth-getting/1191/9">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/dead-space-for-pc-is-it-worth-getting/1191/9</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 15 Aug 2009 23:39:34 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-1191-9</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/dead-space-for-pc-is-it-worth-getting/1191.rss">Dead Space for PC, Is it Worth getting?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Dead Space for PC, Is it Worth getting?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Comrade_Tiki]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Spooks">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/s/f08c70/40.png" class="avatar"> Spooks:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>The game has three difficulties and an additional fourth one after you beat it once.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Thank you, that’s some good advice that will come in handy! Lots of explanation with nothing that would spoil, that’s often hard to do.</p>
<p>My habit, if there are more than two settings, is to always play a game at its second-most-difficult setting. So with a fourth difficulty setting unlockable, I expect to start playing through on Hard.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/dead-space-for-pc-is-it-worth-getting/1191/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/dead-space-for-pc-is-it-worth-getting/1191/8</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 15 Aug 2009 23:10:59 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-1191-8</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/dead-space-for-pc-is-it-worth-getting/1191.rss">Dead Space for PC, Is it Worth getting?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Dead Space for PC, Is it Worth getting?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Spooks]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>The thing is the same as, say, Silent Hill. You finish it once, then you can start replaying the game from your final save on an increased difficulty but with unlockable items to encourage and enhance re-playability. It’s the same with Dead Space, but if you start a new game with your end-game save, or go to the next “round” as they are dubbed in-game, you’ll have all your weapons and equipment you had on your first playthrough from the start, and the monsters should be somewhat harder. However, you cannot change the difficulty once you’ve done that, you can finish the game on Normal, and then if you start again on Round 2 it will still have somewhat harder monsters, but you cannot start the game on Hard or Impossible with all your weapons and the unlockable suit. It’s kind of lame, but oh well, more replays are always good.</p>
<p>And to say something more about the mouse issues, I was happy (?) to get a bug using the Steam overlay/alt+tabbing that allowed me to see the Windows cursor displayed over the game. It really shows how the looking around is set, the in-game mouse has a, how to say, much smaller “Field of View” than the regular Windows pointer. In the menus, whether the Windows cursor moved by 10 pixels, the in-game cursor moved by 25 pixels. And on the contrary, in-game, I had to drag the Windows cursor to the screen edges for some time before the camera started turning around, it’s intentionally slower. (I’ve read some more whiny comments on Dead Space controls on the web while writing this post, I feel like I’m the only guy who actually had no gripes whatsoever with them. God, people are such crybabies.)</p>
<p>On that note I forgot to mention, I haven’t encountered a single crash or game-breaking bug with the game while playing it normally (the cursor one wasn’t from the game itself, just the overlay). I think it even had a confirmation dialog when you hit alt+f4. Now <span class="bbcode-i">THAT</span> you don’t see every day in PC ga<em>cough</em>ports<em>cough</em>mes.</p>
<p>Oh, and another tip for anyone wanting to play Dead Space - turn the brightness down, to the minimum if possible. And turn the volume up too.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/dead-space-for-pc-is-it-worth-getting/1191/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/dead-space-for-pc-is-it-worth-getting/1191/7</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 15 Aug 2009 16:12:15 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-1191-7</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/dead-space-for-pc-is-it-worth-getting/1191.rss">Dead Space for PC, Is it Worth getting?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Dead Space for PC, Is it Worth getting?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Duck]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Thanks, I guess I will be getting dead space, and thanks for the very descriptive reply spooks, you have given a allot of good and helpful information about that game and all reasons that I should get It no matter what anyone says, Yeah, I think starting On hard will be more achieving like you stated, but whats this whole “Round 1 / 2” thing the game is based with Rounds? that’s sounds allot different for a horror game, Or maybe this one just kicks all other horror games up the ass. Either way, I’m  certainly Convinced in Buying Dead space now.</p>
<p>Now, the Mouse. VSync you all say? well, What the hell is that anyways, And why would they have it in the game if it ruins the mouse movement? “(or like spooks said, Did they <span class="bbcode-i">want</span> it to be like that?” anyways, Should I wait till price Drops, that could be ages, Besides I’d Love to have the game now! :awesome:</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/dead-space-for-pc-is-it-worth-getting/1191/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/dead-space-for-pc-is-it-worth-getting/1191/6</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 15 Aug 2009 14:38:47 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-1191-6</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/dead-space-for-pc-is-it-worth-getting/1191.rss">Dead Space for PC, Is it Worth getting?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Dead Space for PC, Is it Worth getting?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Lopez]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I got Dead Space on PC and it was great, I preferred it with a 360 controller however. Make sure you don’t put VSYNC on because it goes all weird.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/dead-space-for-pc-is-it-worth-getting/1191/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/dead-space-for-pc-is-it-worth-getting/1191/5</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 15 Aug 2009 12:28:59 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-1191-5</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/dead-space-for-pc-is-it-worth-getting/1191.rss">Dead Space for PC, Is it Worth getting?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Dead Space for PC, Is it Worth getting?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Spooks]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>(this post may contain an abundance of bracketed text, commas, <span class="bbcode-i">formatted</span> <span class="bbcode-b">text</span> and raging at people failing and blaming the game for it)<br>
[/SIZE]<br>
<span class="bbcode-i">Short answer:</span> Yes.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-i">Long answer:</span> You may wait for a price drop, seeing as Australia and video games have a <span class="bbcode-i">special</span> connection when it comes to censoring and pricing.</p>
<p>Also, concerning the fact that there has been an uproar because of laggy mouse input - I can see where these people are coming from, if you play a lot of twitch games the mouse controls will ultimately feel choppy and unresponsive. But let me tell you something: The Internet is full of retards. If they call that bad controls I would be <span class="bbcode-i">disgusted</span> to play this game on a console. Smoother aiming movement? <span class="bbcode-b">THIS IS A SURVIVAL HORROR GAME FOR FUCKS SAKE</span>. Sometimes I cannot believe gamers today have become so spoiled. It’s all like complaining that you couldn’t aim well in Silent Hill. <span class="bbcode-b">WELL TAHTS TEH POINT. HURR.</span> :mono: I’ve even read people complain about the game not pausing when you open the inventory, “Oooh, but that necromorph still keeps attacking me! Can’t pop in the Statis pack!”. First of all, it was a fundamental design decision, second of all, it goes to show how much people <span class="bbcode-b">suck</span>. If you know how to play you’ll pretty much never have to carry a fucking Statis pack around because your Statis charge will never deplete, there’s no need to use it on monsters unless you’re brain-dead or completely outflanked, plus there’s rechargers everywhere, in fact you’ll be pretty much overflowing with ammo and credits (money) in the end of the game, Normal difficulty.</p>
<p>The mouse controls are <span class="bbcode-b">fine</span>, I have to admit that there’s some technical difficulties (disabling v-sync as Hamst3r mentioned or increasing/decreasing the maximum pre-rendered frames in your nVidia control panel, in case you have a nVidia card, seems to sovle those) and there’s one part that <span class="bbcode-b">may</span> get hard for you because of the somewhat sluggy aiming (I’m talking about the asteroids, yes they may be hard, but if I did it, you don’t have any fucking right to whine. You heard me, faggots.) but ultimately, if you weren’t dropped on your head as a baby, you will be able to play this game with a kb/m setup just <span class="bbcode-b">fine</span>.</p>
<p>Moving on to replay value, it depends on personal preference. Dead Space is no Oblivion, it’s average length is around 8 - 12 hours, but it’s one of the most re-playable games for me, right up there next to Half-Life 2. It’s something I will <span class="bbcode-b">not</span> uninstall for a long time and will eventually come back to every now and then. The game has a good story with a nice couple of obligatory twists, suffice it to say that it’s a horror fan’s dream come true. Now I’m definitely not big at horror movies, but Dead Space, from what I’ve heard, has Even Horizon, Alien, The Thing, (none of which I’ve actually watched/remember now) all nicely mashed in one, and in video game format at that. It’s very light in the graphics department while managing to look awesome, it’s one of the few, if not the only, game past, say, 2007 that I can run on High settings and still get a decent FPS (I have an average machine), the only other game I can name being Episode 2. I don’t even have to mention sound.</p>
<p>The game has three difficulties and an additional fourth one after you beat it once. I would recommend anyone to either rush it on Easy and generally don’t pay attention, just so he/she may unlock Impossible difficulty. Yes, the game feels pretty much unchallenging on Normal as I mentioned before and it was a bit of a let down for me, fortunately I’ve been having a lot more fun on Impossible and the game actually started feeling rewarding. Still, if you do CARE about the story, don’t rush on Easy, but for Christ’s sake don’t play on Normal either, go with Hard. Oh, and Pro-Tip: The game allows you to continue your play on “Round 2” (and possibly Round 3, etc, etc, don’t know) with all your weapons and an unlockable suit, but <span class="bbcode-i">you can’t actually change the difficulty</span>. So just beat it once, forget about Round 2 and start on Impossible. When/If you finish it on Impossible, <span class="bbcode-i">then</span> you can go on Round 2, plus you’ll have actually <span class="bbcode-i">earned</span> that fucking suit.</p>
<p>As a conclusion, Dead Space is great, even more, it’s awesome and win. And if you fail at it, man the fuck up. <span class="bbcode-b">TRY. FUCKING. HARDER.</span></p>
<p>FUCK YES, LONG ANSWER!</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/dead-space-for-pc-is-it-worth-getting/1191/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/dead-space-for-pc-is-it-worth-getting/1191/4</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 15 Aug 2009 12:14:50 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-1191-4</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/dead-space-for-pc-is-it-worth-getting/1191.rss">Dead Space for PC, Is it Worth getting?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Dead Space for PC, Is it Worth getting?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Hamst3r]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Yes.</p>
<p>I enjoyed Dead Space a lot. It’s one of my favorite games of 2007.  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=9" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
<p>The mouse control issue is correctable by disabling v-sync.</p>
<p>As with any game that relies on atmosphere, a bit of isolation and surround sound speakers or headphones goes a long way. So do yourself a favor and play it properly; by yourself, with the lights off and the sound up.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/dead-space-for-pc-is-it-worth-getting/1191/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/dead-space-for-pc-is-it-worth-getting/1191/3</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 15 Aug 2009 10:38:51 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-1191-3</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/dead-space-for-pc-is-it-worth-getting/1191.rss">Dead Space for PC, Is it Worth getting?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Dead Space for PC, Is it Worth getting?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Comrade_Tiki]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I received the game as a Christmas gift from my ex’s little sister, but my desktop does not have internet access, so I have been unable to activate it. Whoever decided online authentification was necessary for a singleplayer game <span class="bbcode-u">should be <span class="bbcode-b">shot</span></span>.</p>
<p>So, for someone who <span class="bbcode-i">has</span> been able to activate it, will it still be worth playing in one year’s time?</p>
<p>(I’m surprised the price has not dropped from $61 AU.)</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/dead-space-for-pc-is-it-worth-getting/1191/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/dead-space-for-pc-is-it-worth-getting/1191/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 15 Aug 2009 09:20:26 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-1191-2</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/dead-space-for-pc-is-it-worth-getting/1191.rss">Dead Space for PC, Is it Worth getting?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Dead Space for PC, Is it Worth getting?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Duck]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Well, I’m Looking into buying Dead Space for PC, But today, I went through Metascore reviews and there seems to be a problem with the mouse controls. Is it Really worth the $61.00 AU bucks?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/dead-space-for-pc-is-it-worth-getting/1191/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/dead-space-for-pc-is-it-worth-getting/1191/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 15 Aug 2009 09:11:12 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-1191-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/dead-space-for-pc-is-it-worth-getting/1191.rss">Dead Space for PC, Is it Worth getting?</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
