<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Before/After Experiment!</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/before-after-experiment/9450</link>
    <description>Hi everybody!

I would like to propose a bit of an experiment.  Up until BM&#39;s release, post what you think you will like about the mod, dislike, your thoughts, etc.  When the mod comes out and you play it, edit your original post to include what you actually think of the mod.  It would be interesting to see the difference!

I will go first.
-------------------

I think that BM will have a sort of &quot;Valve quality&quot; polish.  I am expecting a few bugs here or there, but otherwise I think that BM will be the best HL2 mod to date, even outshining GMod.  I think that the level design will be top-notch, the models will look professional, etc.  I am, however worried about the quality of the voice acting and non-Valve made animations.

---------------------

EDIT: Just played up to the beginning of We&#39;ve got Hostiles and so far it has exceeded my expectations by miles!  All of my concerns about voice acting and non-Valve made animations are now gone.  My only complaint about the mod is a little picky - the video/gameplay option defaults are pretty bad.  My game was set to easy by default, and my video quality had all of the textures/effects set to low/medium, even though my shitty macbook(I used bootcamp) can handle max settings on almost everything.  Everything else, however, is on-par with Valve games, and is much better than any recent CoD game.  Definitely worth the 7-year wait!</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 16 Sep 2012 02:25:26 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>The Cafeteria</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/before-after-experiment/9450.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Before/After Experiment!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[ZindroVokun]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Malidictus">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/m/7bcc69/40.png" class="avatar"> Malidictus:</div>
<blockquote>
<ol>
<li>Black Mesa turned out to be a “reimagining” of Half-Life with a lot more humour (not something I appreciate))</li>
</ol>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I personally thought HL was silly to begin with, the first one at least. The barneys and scientists were bumbling idiots, and the rooms were utterly insane - I mean the crate room? They have a room where they hang crates for fun? BM kept it and tried to make it make a bit more sense (the crates look like they go places, still weird though).</p>
<p>The only real example of humour that didn’t seem realistic was probably the toilet paper joke. The guard banter seemed pretty much like how a security guy would act to a co-worker; and most of the dialogue post-disaster seemed much more serious, with the exception of a scientist or two.</p>
<p>I expected HL1 with graphical updates and re-voiced. I didn’t expect them to go ahead and make it for the most part even more fun and cinematic. This has been a really good mod. But, I didn’t follow it all the way (due to its long dev time) so I guess I never got over-hyped.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/before-after-experiment/9450/52">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/before-after-experiment/9450/52</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 16 Sep 2012 02:25:26 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9450-52</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/before-after-experiment/9450.rss">Before/After Experiment!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Before/After Experiment!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Malidictus]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I honestly expected basically “Half-Life with better graphics.” That’s my own fault for no being better informed and just guessing blindly. Beyond this, I expected Black Mesa to look good, play better but be plagued with bad voice acting. I also expected it to be complete.</p>
<p>What actually happened:</p>
<ol>
<li>
<p>Black Mesa turned out to be a “reimagining” of Half-Life with a lot more humour (not something I appreciate) and very different location layouts in places. I am not disappointed with anything that’s been done to the levels themselves, I just wish there were more of it  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=9" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:">  Specifically, more On a Rail, more Surface Tension, more Forget About Freeman, more Residue Processing. All of these feel like they were “streamlined” and had large chunks of them taken out in the process. Basically, I like it enough that I wish there were more  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=9" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Black Mesa does look good. VERY good, in fact. And the voice acting doesn’t suck. Quite on the contrary - with the exception of a single line, the voice acting is GREAT! Eli doesn’t sound much like himself but Cleiner is spot on, and all the other unnamed characters sound convincing and well-acted. I’m quite amazed at this. Black Mesa is the first non-commercial product I’ve seen come out with voice acting that doesn’t make me want to strangle the actors. You guys should be making money out of this.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>I found out that Xen wouldn’t be included pretty early on, and I found out that the tutoria wouldn’t exist. Xen, at least, we’ll eventually see, but I’m still sad to lose the tutorial. To me, Half-Life is the only game where the tutorial actually felt like part of the story. Ah, well, at least Xen, I’m sure, will be amazing, if the rest of Black Mesa is anything to go by. I just hope it doesn’t take another eight years  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=9" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
</li>
</ol>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/before-after-experiment/9450/51">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/before-after-experiment/9450/51</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 16 Sep 2012 01:03:57 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9450-51</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/before-after-experiment/9450.rss">Before/After Experiment!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Before/After Experiment!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[dky.tehkingd.u]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="dky.tehkingd.u">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/user_avatar/leakfree.org/dky.tehkingd.u/40/4377_2.png" class="avatar"> dky.tehkingd.u:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>On-Topic: I think Black Mesa will just play <span class="bbcode-i">well</span>. It looks very professional and I’m looking forward to playing because of that. I’m especially excited for the HECU battles. Ultimate HECU fan right here! B)</p>
<p>When mod releases and I get past the WGH chapter, I’ll repost here with my thoughts on the new HECU.  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=9" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Bumping this thread because I said I would.</p>
<p>The new HECU are great. Others might disagree. I’ve heard people say they’re too difficult. I’ve heard people say that the voice acting sucks.</p>
<p>But in MY opinion the HECU are really fun to fight. Many times I die to them and I’m not disappointed. Rather, I’m impressed. They, unlike enemies in many other games, are able to use their advantages to their advantage. They’re aggressive. They push. They flank when you don’t expect. They’re COMPETENT. If you die to them, then it’s always your own fault, and likewise when you win a battle against them, it’s always because you actually out-fight them rather than the AI being stupid (as HL1 grunts sometimes were). I’ve found myself having to re-do many battles with a different strategy each time, because the last time I used a bad strategy and got killed.</p>
<p>As for the voices, I’m okay with them. Honestly if it’s a choice between these and the ridiculous robot voices from HL1, I’d gladly choose the new ones. Although sometimes it’s kind of ridiculous when they say “Dooo iiit” over and over again in an almost seductive manner for absolutely no reason. :meh:</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/before-after-experiment/9450/50">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/before-after-experiment/9450/50</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 16 Sep 2012 00:11:29 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9450-50</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/before-after-experiment/9450.rss">Before/After Experiment!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Before/After Experiment!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[SniperNoSniping9]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I’m probably going to regret this later but…<br>
I’m not going to lie I’m slightly disappointed. I was so hyped up for this game…And I feel as though it fell a little short.<br>
The graphics are sexy as hell. I am overly impressed with the graphics.<br>
I just feel turned off. It’s like looking at a sexy women and then you’re like “Hi, I’m (Insert name here)” and shes like “LIEK OMG HAI! I’M SARAH AND I LIKE” and she just goes on and on and never shuts up and while you’re trying to look for a place to talk she just keeps slamming the door and keeps talking.</p>
<p>BM is sexy, but I feel like I’m fumbling around too much trying to find the next doorway and or exit hole to get to the next part and I feel its unnecessary. Maybe its because I’m used to HL1 in all its simpleness. It may also be because I’m really tired.<br>
The voice acting is nice. The guns, the sounds. The whole thing is awesome. I just got really bored trying to fumble around trying to open every door to get to the next part of the stage.</p>
<p>But I would like to say Thank you to the dev’s you guys worked real hard and did a great job.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/before-after-experiment/9450/49">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/before-after-experiment/9450/49</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 15 Sep 2012 01:17:35 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9450-49</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/before-after-experiment/9450.rss">Before/After Experiment!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Before/After Experiment!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[_amp_8706_lpha]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Absolutely amazing.<br>
Surpassed my expectations.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/before-after-experiment/9450/48">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/before-after-experiment/9450/48</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 15 Sep 2012 00:48:14 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9450-48</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/before-after-experiment/9450.rss">Before/After Experiment!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Before/After Experiment!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[beyond_ltd]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I’m worrying that my computer can not handle BM… Well, we will see.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/before-after-experiment/9450/47">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/before-after-experiment/9450/47</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 14 Sep 2012 20:19:30 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9450-47</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/before-after-experiment/9450.rss">Before/After Experiment!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Before/After Experiment!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[jesse1994]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=q5th225wgsk" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=q5th225wgsk</a></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/before-after-experiment/9450/46">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/before-after-experiment/9450/46</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 14 Sep 2012 14:16:28 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9450-46</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/before-after-experiment/9450.rss">Before/After Experiment!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Before/After Experiment!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Axmann8]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="King_Kaddo">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/k/bcef8e/40.png" class="avatar"> King_Kaddo:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>My only concern is the voice acting, especially the voice of gman. I hope there will be a miracle and <span class="bbcode-u"><span class="bbcode-b">the real voice actor of Gman will hear about Black Mesa and volunteer for the gman part in Xen</span></span>.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<blockquote>
<p>Implying that could ever happen</p>
</blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/before-after-experiment/9450/45">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/before-after-experiment/9450/45</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 14 Sep 2012 12:12:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9450-45</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/before-after-experiment/9450.rss">Before/After Experiment!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Before/After Experiment!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Gloric]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Crypt19">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Crypt19:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Good luck with that.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Good luck with what? i’m just guessing in the dark. My assumptions aren’t some sort of criteria I expect.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Crypt19">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Crypt19:</div>
<blockquote>
<p><a href="https://www.accursedfarms.com/black-mesa-mod/" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Nope.</a></p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I never said to switch over to it permanently. But judging from that he wouldn’t do it due to the disruptive nature anyhow. I still don’t see how it could be any worse than the narration changing to Piratese for 1 episode. But that’s just me.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/before-after-experiment/9450/44">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/before-after-experiment/9450/44</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 14 Sep 2012 11:21:13 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9450-44</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/before-after-experiment/9450.rss">Before/After Experiment!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Before/After Experiment!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[pinkribbonscars]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="omegalucas">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/o/ecae2f/40.png" class="avatar"> omegalucas:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I’m just a bit scared about some NPC voices and animations (mainly the talking animation). Other than that, I think the game will be great.  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/smiley.png?v=9" title=":smiley:" class="emoji" alt=":smiley:"></p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Judging by this: <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=xQ3vVlaHHPc&amp;feature=related" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=xQ3vVlaHHPc&amp;feature=related</a>, there’s absolutely nothing to worry about when it comes to the NPCs animations :3</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/before-after-experiment/9450/43">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/before-after-experiment/9450/43</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 14 Sep 2012 11:18:22 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9450-43</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/before-after-experiment/9450.rss">Before/After Experiment!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Before/After Experiment!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[polyphonyEX]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I predict a ‘Valvelike’ experience.</p>
<p>Take from that what you will but I predict a game so polished and fundamentally GOOD that it dwarfs any reservation that could be had at all.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/before-after-experiment/9450/42">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/before-after-experiment/9450/42</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 14 Sep 2012 10:54:18 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9450-42</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/before-after-experiment/9450.rss">Before/After Experiment!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Before/After Experiment!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[FrontLineAssembly]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>No complaints. Can’t wait to hear the awesome voice acting (especially Gman, but we won’t see him in this release) and see the awesome animations, models, textures, etc. I bet this will be the best HL2 mod till date.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/before-after-experiment/9450/41">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/before-after-experiment/9450/41</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 14 Sep 2012 10:20:43 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9450-41</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/before-after-experiment/9450.rss">Before/After Experiment!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Before/After Experiment!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[PlausibleSarge]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Crypt19">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Crypt19:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Another thing I have on my mind as of 30 seconds ago is whether or not the puzzles have been redesigned so heavily that HL veterans won’t know <span class="bbcode-i">exactly what to do</span>. I seriously welcome the physics-based puzzles I’ve heard about.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I personally wish for a mix of old and new puzzles, or a twist on some of the old puzzles, simply because, while solving new puzzles can be fun, solving some of the old puzzles in new environments has great nostalgia value and can be just as fun despite the easiness of the puzzle. I still enjoy the tripmine puzzle in Surface Tension despite the fact that I know it by heart</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/before-after-experiment/9450/40">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/before-after-experiment/9450/40</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 14 Sep 2012 10:15:09 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9450-40</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/before-after-experiment/9450.rss">Before/After Experiment!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Before/After Experiment!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypt]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Another thing I have on my mind as of 30 seconds ago is whether or not the puzzles have been redesigned so heavily that HL veterans won’t know <span class="bbcode-i">exactly what to do</span>. I seriously welcome the physics-based puzzles I’ve heard about.</p>
<p>Post Play Edit: Once again, devs delivered. New level designs came familiar but new puzzles.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/before-after-experiment/9450/39">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/before-after-experiment/9450/39</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 14 Sep 2012 09:25:18 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9450-39</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/before-after-experiment/9450.rss">Before/After Experiment!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Before/After Experiment!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Sentinelrv]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="pinkribbonscars">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/p/a88e57/40.png" class="avatar"> pinkribbonscars:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>My biggest worries are the Hecu Soldiers AI and their voice overs. The aggressiveness of them was my favorite part of Half Life, and I hope they managed to carry it over to BMS. Everything else looks incredible, Valve quality, even, so I’m not worried about the rest.  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=9" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I’m also concerned about the aggressiveness of the soldiers. That’s the biggest downfall in Half-Life 2 for me. The Combine were way too easy to fight, where the Half-Life 1 soldiers were very challenging.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/before-after-experiment/9450/38">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/before-after-experiment/9450/38</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 14 Sep 2012 09:23:23 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9450-38</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/before-after-experiment/9450.rss">Before/After Experiment!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Before/After Experiment!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[pinkribbonscars]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>My biggest worries are the Hecu Soldiers AI and their voice overs. The aggressiveness of them was my favorite part of Half Life, and I hope they managed to carry it over to BMS. Everything else looks incredible, Valve quality, even, so I’m not worried about the rest.  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=9" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/before-after-experiment/9450/37">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/before-after-experiment/9450/37</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 14 Sep 2012 09:02:17 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9450-37</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/before-after-experiment/9450.rss">Before/After Experiment!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Before/After Experiment!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Reaps]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I heard it a while back which previewed some of the Gman voice acting, i think the actor was asked to speak a line or two of dialogue and it was absolutely spot on.</p>
<p>I’m not worried about the game at all just sleep deprivation.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/before-after-experiment/9450/36">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/before-after-experiment/9450/36</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 14 Sep 2012 08:58:45 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9450-36</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/before-after-experiment/9450.rss">Before/After Experiment!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Before/After Experiment!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Sentinelrv]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Thanks, found it.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/before-after-experiment/9450/35">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/before-after-experiment/9450/35</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 14 Sep 2012 08:58:44 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9450-35</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/before-after-experiment/9450.rss">Before/After Experiment!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Before/After Experiment!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Greenender]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Search the friendly web:</p>
<ul>
<li>Black Mesa Steamcast</li>
<li>Black mesa voice actors interview</li>
</ul>
<p>You’ll find it easily  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=9" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/before-after-experiment/9450/34">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/before-after-experiment/9450/34</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 14 Sep 2012 08:47:56 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9450-34</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/before-after-experiment/9450.rss">Before/After Experiment!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Before/After Experiment!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Sentinelrv]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Greenender">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/g/f0a364/40.png" class="avatar"> Greenender:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Guys, what are you talking about, have you heard the interview with voice actors (done some months ago)?? The g-man guy sounded fantastic, just as good as the original guy (Mike).</p>
<p>So don’t worry, g-man voice will be perfect  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=9" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Can anybody link me to this interview?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/before-after-experiment/9450/33">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/before-after-experiment/9450/33</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 14 Sep 2012 08:23:22 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9450-33</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/before-after-experiment/9450.rss">Before/After Experiment!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Before/After Experiment!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Trivo]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>My concerns:<br>
1: The voice acting (because of the YT video).<br>
2: The difference might be so much that certain parts are unrecognisable.</p>
<p>Overall expectation is I’ll enjoy the mod 99.9% then go through the sequels for a Half-Life No-Life weekend.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/before-after-experiment/9450/32">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/before-after-experiment/9450/32</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 14 Sep 2012 08:17:09 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9450-32</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/before-after-experiment/9450.rss">Before/After Experiment!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Before/After Experiment!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Greenender]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Guys, what are you talking about, have you heard the interview with voice actors (done some months ago)?? The g-man guy sounded fantastic, just as good as the original guy (Mike).</p>
<p>So don’t worry, g-man voice will be perfect  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=9" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/before-after-experiment/9450/31">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/before-after-experiment/9450/31</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 14 Sep 2012 08:15:19 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9450-31</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/before-after-experiment/9450.rss">Before/After Experiment!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Before/After Experiment!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[omegalucas]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I’m just a bit scared about some NPC voices and animations (mainly the talking animation). Other than that, I think the game will be great.  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/smiley.png?v=9" title=":smiley:" class="emoji" alt=":smiley:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/before-after-experiment/9450/30">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/before-after-experiment/9450/30</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 14 Sep 2012 07:44:43 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9450-30</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/before-after-experiment/9450.rss">Before/After Experiment!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Before/After Experiment!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Spudz]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I think I’ll get a strong sense of nostalgia, coupled with a feeling of immersion.<br>
The only things I’m worried about are, as said before, non-Valve animations and maybe some of the voice acting, although I’m not too worried about the G-Man as he sounds fine in the trailer. Oh, and I hope it isn’t too short.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/before-after-experiment/9450/29">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/before-after-experiment/9450/29</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 14 Sep 2012 06:46:43 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9450-29</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/before-after-experiment/9450.rss">Before/After Experiment!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Before/After Experiment!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[fade]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I just want the levels to feel a little bit more realistic than they were in HL1 (for instance, i want office complex to feel more like an actual office)… Its obvious the limitations of the engine HL1 was build on was the main factor, but from what ive seen thus far a little bit more realism to the environments is exactly what we are getting…</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/before-after-experiment/9450/28">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/before-after-experiment/9450/28</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 14 Sep 2012 06:30:02 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9450-28</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/before-after-experiment/9450.rss">Before/After Experiment!</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
