<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Jump height problem (not what you think)</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/jump-height-problem-not-what-you-think/11539</link>
    <description>I&#39;m going to start out by saying jumping in Black Mesa is exactly what was intended. I know about crouch jumping, I think it&#39;s used too excessively in the game but that it&#39;s the devs&#39; call. This thread isn&#39;t about that.

The problem is, I&#39;m getting stuck with the same Black Mesa jump height in other source mods, and worse yet, Half Life 2 Episode 2. I&#39;m going to guess it affects the other Half-Life 2 games, Portal 1, and possibly Portal 2 and TF2 (I have not tested them yet). This is obviously a huge problem, and I&#39;m pretty sure that I can possibly fix this if I delete enough things, but I have a sinking suspicion I&#39;ll end up deleting most of my Steam folder if I approach things haphazardly, and that&#39;s a lot of downloading.

Does anyone know what went wrong, what I can do to fix it, or at the very least what files/folders I need to delete and redownload fresh? I&#39;ve deleted Black Mesa and Episode 2, and redownloaded Episode 2, but the problem persists.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 17 May 2014 10:40:56 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>In-game Issues (Mod)</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/jump-height-problem-not-what-you-think/11539.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Jump height problem (not what you think)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Redglyph]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Jump height is a little too low indeed, to the point you can never use it and are forced to jump-crouch all the time. For those who want to modify it, it’s in</p>
<p>\SteamApps\sourcemods\BMS\BlackMesa\cfg\skill.cfg</p>
<p>(there’s no space, it’s “skill”, a bug in these forums I presume)</p>
<p>Change the following values (might need fine-tuning):</p>
<p><code>bms_normal_jump_vertical_speed			"185"
bms_normal_jump_crouch_vertical_speed		"185"</code></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/jump-height-problem-not-what-you-think/11539/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/jump-height-problem-not-what-you-think/11539/6</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2014 10:40:56 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11539-6</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/jump-height-problem-not-what-you-think/11539.rss">Jump height problem (not what you think)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Jump height problem (not what you think)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Latooni]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="dky.tehkingd.u">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/user_avatar/leakfree.org/dky.tehkingd.u/40/4377_2.png" class="avatar"> dky.tehkingd.u:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Is it the jump <span class="bbcode-i">distance</span> being affected, or the jump <span class="bbcode-i">height</span>?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I am positive it was the jump height; I couldn’t jump onto crates in HL2 without crouch-jumping. I thiiiink it’s fixed, I can now jump onto crates without it (though just barely - I can’t remember if that’s how it always was) and I will try to play through a good portion of HL2 and the episodes later this week to see if I can get through the game like this.</p>
<p>I’m a bit wary of setting up Black Mesa again without a fix, though. Or even a possible fix. I might try it later, but I appreciate any input people have. (</p>
<p>Thank you for all your help in advance.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/jump-height-problem-not-what-you-think/11539/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/jump-height-problem-not-what-you-think/11539/5</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 10 Dec 2012 19:15:01 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11539-5</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/jump-height-problem-not-what-you-think/11539.rss">Jump height problem (not what you think)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Jump height problem (not what you think)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[dky.tehkingd.u]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>This doesn’t apply to TF2, but I know that the jump height is exactly the same between HL2 and Black Mesa, according to this page: <a href="https://developer.valvesoftware.com/wiki/Dimensions" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://developer.valvesoftware.com/wiki/Dimensions</a></p>
<p>The exact same values apply to Black Mesa, with the exception being the jump-distance value. I know because I tested it in Hammer.</p>
<p>Is it the jump <span class="bbcode-i">distance</span> being affected, or the jump <span class="bbcode-i">height</span>?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/jump-height-problem-not-what-you-think/11539/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/jump-height-problem-not-what-you-think/11539/4</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 10 Dec 2012 05:47:04 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11539-4</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/jump-height-problem-not-what-you-think/11539.rss">Jump height problem (not what you think)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Jump height problem (not what you think)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Latooni]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Keresh">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/k/85f322/40.png" class="avatar"> Keresh:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Try deleting source sdk 2007 base.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I tried doing that; nothing really changed. Maybe I didn’t do it right? If someone gives me a tip on how to do it properly it’d be appreciated.</p>
<p>I tried deleting all the steam folders connected to Source, and removed all the games. I am currently redownloading those games, but halflife 2 is only a 3GB download, making me think I didn’t manage to get rid of Source, and I’m pretty sure that means I still have the jump bug.</p>
<p>I either need a better way to get rid of Source and redownload it, or a way to fix the problem.</p>
<p>I’m sorry for the long wait before responding, but I’ve been too busy for games for a while. I’d really like to fix this now, though.</p>
<p>EDIT: it just occurred to me 3.6 gigs is actually possibly the file size on HL2, I mixed it up with TF2’s massive 10gb size. Will test when I can, but please answer my concerns anyway, if you can.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/jump-height-problem-not-what-you-think/11539/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/jump-height-problem-not-what-you-think/11539/3</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 10 Dec 2012 01:58:52 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11539-3</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/jump-height-problem-not-what-you-think/11539.rss">Jump height problem (not what you think)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Jump height problem (not what you think)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Keresh]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Try deleting source sdk 2007 base.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/jump-height-problem-not-what-you-think/11539/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/jump-height-problem-not-what-you-think/11539/2</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 22 Oct 2012 10:43:12 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11539-2</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/jump-height-problem-not-what-you-think/11539.rss">Jump height problem (not what you think)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Jump height problem (not what you think)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Latooni]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I’m going to start out by saying jumping in Black Mesa is exactly what was intended. I know about crouch jumping, I think it’s used too excessively in the game but that it’s the devs’ call. This thread isn’t about that.</p>
<p>The problem is, I’m getting stuck with the same Black Mesa jump height in other source mods, and worse yet, Half Life 2 Episode 2. I’m going to guess it affects the other Half-Life 2 games, Portal 1, and possibly Portal 2 and TF2 (I have not tested them yet). This is obviously a huge problem, and I’m pretty sure that I can possibly fix this if I delete enough things, but I have a sinking suspicion I’ll end up deleting most of my Steam folder if I approach things haphazardly, and that’s a lot of downloading.</p>
<p>Does anyone know what went wrong, what I can do to fix it, or at the very least what files/folders I need to delete and redownload fresh? I’ve deleted Black Mesa and Episode 2, and redownloaded Episode 2, but the problem persists.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/jump-height-problem-not-what-you-think/11539/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/jump-height-problem-not-what-you-think/11539/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 21 Oct 2012 21:52:14 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11539-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/jump-height-problem-not-what-you-think/11539.rss">Jump height problem (not what you think)</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
