<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>-tools mode not launching</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/tools-mode-not-launching/14159</link>
    <description>I was looking to browse the stock particles to add a few effects to a map I&#39;m working on, but after launching the game with the [i]-tools -nop4[/i] command from Hammer, none of the tools showed up at all. I figured this was a problem from launching via Hammer, and launched the game directly from Steam with the same command line prompts, with no results.
This is a very big issue, because it not only prevents community developers from browsing, editing, and creating new particles and commentary, but also prevents Crowbar Collective from doing the same - And with Xen and (presumably) some of the MP maps still under development, I figure that that&#39;s kind of an important feature to have.

This wouldn&#39;t be such an issue if PCF files were easily human-readable, or if there was an external tool for viewing their contents, but without the -tools flag doing anything ingame, there&#39;s currently no way to even see what particles are available.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 01 Jun 2015 19:27:19 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Source 1</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/tools-mode-not-launching/14159.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>-tools mode not launching</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[JeffMOD]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I was looking to browse the stock particles to add a few effects to a map I’m working on, but after launching the game with the <span class="bbcode-i">-tools -nop4</span> command from Hammer, none of the tools showed up at all. I figured this was a problem from launching via Hammer, and launched the game directly from Steam with the same command line prompts, with no results.<br>
This is a very big issue, because it not only prevents community developers from browsing, editing, and creating new particles and commentary, but also prevents Crowbar Collective from doing the same - And with Xen and (presumably) some of the MP maps still under development, I figure that that’s kind of an important feature to have.</p>
<p>This wouldn’t be such an issue if PCF files were easily human-readable, or if there was an external tool for viewing their contents, but without the -tools flag doing anything ingame, there’s currently no way to even see what particles are available.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/tools-mode-not-launching/14159/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/tools-mode-not-launching/14159/1</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jun 2015 19:27:19 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14159-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/tools-mode-not-launching/14159.rss">-tools mode not launching</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
