<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Black Mesa is now available on Steam as an early access title!</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/black-mesa-is-now-available-on-steam-as-an-early-access-title/13819</link>
    <description>Black Mesa is now available for purchase on Steam early access for $19.99. Please [url=&#39;https://store.steampowered.com/app/362890/&#39;]visit our store page[/url] to find out more!

[b][u]What&#39;s new in the steam release?[/size][/u][/b]
The Steam release of Black Mesa includes various fixes, upgrades, and new features compared to Black Mesa&#39;s mod release.
* [b]Heavily updated single player experience [/b]- The Black Mesa singleplayer experience has greatly improved from the mod release; new visuals, new voiceover, updated gameplay encounters, stability changes and more. [b]Xen is not a part of the Steam release of Black Mesa, but it will be included as a free update to the retail title when it is ready.[/b]
* [b]Black Mesa Multiplayer - [/b]Fight with or against your friends, in two game modes (deathmatch and team deathmatch) across six iconic maps from the Half-Life universe: Bounce, Gasworks, Lambdabunker, Stalkyard, Subtransit and Undertow.
* [b]Custom Modding Tools [/b]- Use the same tools the developers used to create your own mods, modes and maps for Black Mesa and Black Mesa Multiplayer.
* [b]Fully integrated Workshop[/b] - And then share your work on the fully integrated workshop!
* [b]Complete Steam Integration[/b] - Collect trading cards, backgrounds, emoticons, achievements, and everything else you would expect out of a Steam integrated game
[u][b]Why Early Access?[/b][/u][/size]
Making a game with the scope and scale of Black Mesa is a massive undertaking. Back in 2012 we made the decision to release what we had completed up to that point, and were blown away by the community’s response, feedback, and improvements to our work. We want to keep that relationship alive and well by using Early Access as a tool for allowing our community to participate in the final phase of Black Mesa’s development.

In addition, our ambitions go beyond the original Xen chapters found in Half-Life. We have a standard of quality that we have to achieve. Early Access allows us to commit resources to bring you the remaining chapters with the quality that you expect.

[u][b]How is the full version planned to differ from the Early Access version?[/b][/u][/size]
* The conclusion of the single player campaign, with the addition of the Xen chapters
* Final polish on the Earth-based chapters of the single player campaign
* More multiplayer maps, both remakes and new layouts
* More multiplayer gameplay modes
[b][u]What is the current state of the Early Access version?[/u][/size][/b]
Over 10 hours of single player campaign. Multiplayer deathmatch and team deathmatch with 6 completely re-imagined Half-Life 1 maps on the Source Engine.

[u][b]Will the game be priced differently during and after Early Access?[/b][/u][/size]
Black Mesa will be $19.99 USD during the Early Access phase. The game may go slightly higher once out of Early Access (or we may keep it at $19.99).

[u][b]How are you planning on involving the Community in your development process?[/b][/u][/size]
We intend to work closely with our community as we complete the final portions of Black Mesa. We started out as a modding team aiming to do true justice to a Half-Life: Source port, and we won’t forget our roots.

The Black Mesa game hub and forums will be the primary points of interaction with our users. Many team members regularly browse these areas to discuss ideas with the community, and to show progress on game development. Community feedback will be sorted into groups and taken into account as we develop.

We also support Steam Workshop, and will be watching and encouraging developments there.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 06 May 2015 00:36:56 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>News &amp; Developer Updates</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/black-mesa-is-now-available-on-steam-as-an-early-access-title/13819.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Black Mesa is now available on Steam as an early access title!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[TextFAMGUY1]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Black Mesa is now available for purchase on Steam early access for $19.99. Please <a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/362890/" data-bbcode="true">visit our store page</a> to find out more!</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b"><span class="bbcode-u">What’s new in the steam release?[/size]</span></span><br>
The Steam release of Black Mesa includes various fixes, upgrades, and new features compared to Black Mesa’s mod release.</p>
<ul>
<li>
<span class="bbcode-b">Heavily updated single player experience </span>- The Black Mesa singleplayer experience has greatly improved from the mod release; new visuals, new voiceover, updated gameplay encounters, stability changes and more. <span class="bbcode-b">Xen is not a part of the Steam release of Black Mesa, but it will be included as a free update to the retail title when it is ready.</span>
</li>
<li>
<span class="bbcode-b">Black Mesa Multiplayer - </span>Fight with or against your friends, in two game modes (deathmatch and team deathmatch) across six iconic maps from the Half-Life universe: Bounce, Gasworks, Lambdabunker, Stalkyard, Subtransit and Undertow.</li>
<li>
<span class="bbcode-b">Custom Modding Tools </span>- Use the same tools the developers used to create your own mods, modes and maps for Black Mesa and Black Mesa Multiplayer.</li>
<li>
<span class="bbcode-b">Fully integrated Workshop</span> - And then share your work on the fully integrated workshop!</li>
<li>
<span class="bbcode-b">Complete Steam Integration</span> - Collect trading cards, backgrounds, emoticons, achievements, and everything else you would expect out of a Steam integrated game<br>
<span class="bbcode-u"><span class="bbcode-b">Why Early Access?</span></span>[/size]<br>
Making a game with the scope and scale of Black Mesa is a massive undertaking. Back in 2012 we made the decision to release what we had completed up to that point, and were blown away by the community’s response, feedback, and improvements to our work. We want to keep that relationship alive and well by using Early Access as a tool for allowing our community to participate in the final phase of Black Mesa’s development.</li>
</ul>
<p>In addition, our ambitions go beyond the original Xen chapters found in Half-Life. We have a standard of quality that we have to achieve. Early Access allows us to commit resources to bring you the remaining chapters with the quality that you expect.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-u"><span class="bbcode-b">How is the full version planned to differ from the Early Access version?</span></span>[/size]</p>
<ul>
<li>The conclusion of the single player campaign, with the addition of the Xen chapters</li>
<li>Final polish on the Earth-based chapters of the single player campaign</li>
<li>More multiplayer maps, both remakes and new layouts</li>
<li>More multiplayer gameplay modes<br>
<span class="bbcode-b"><span class="bbcode-u">What is the current state of the Early Access version?</span>[/size]</span><br>
Over 10 hours of single player campaign. Multiplayer deathmatch and team deathmatch with 6 completely re-imagined Half-Life 1 maps on the Source Engine.</li>
</ul>
<p><span class="bbcode-u"><span class="bbcode-b">Will the game be priced differently during and after Early Access?</span></span>[/size]<br>
Black Mesa will be $19.99 USD during the Early Access phase. The game may go slightly higher once out of Early Access (or we may keep it at $19.99).</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-u"><span class="bbcode-b">How are you planning on involving the Community in your development process?</span></span>[/size]<br>
We intend to work closely with our community as we complete the final portions of Black Mesa. We started out as a modding team aiming to do true justice to a Half-Life: Source port, and we won’t forget our roots.</p>
<p>The Black Mesa game hub and forums will be the primary points of interaction with our users. Many team members regularly browse these areas to discuss ideas with the community, and to show progress on game development. Community feedback will be sorted into groups and taken into account as we develop.</p>
<p>We also support Steam Workshop, and will be watching and encouraging developments there.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/black-mesa-is-now-available-on-steam-as-an-early-access-title/13819/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/black-mesa-is-now-available-on-steam-as-an-early-access-title/13819/1</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 06 May 2015 00:36:56 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13819-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/black-mesa-is-now-available-on-steam-as-an-early-access-title/13819.rss">Black Mesa is now available on Steam as an early access title!</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
