<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>TF2 not connecting to servers</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/tf2-not-connecting-to-servers/5152</link>
    <description>I&#39;ve been having this problem off and on the past couple months where I&#39;ll start up TF2, and when I go to select a server, usually I can see some servers, like say I&#39;m looking at my favorites list, so there&#39;s maybe 6 servers. I double click on one that looks like it has people, and then I instantly get a &quot;server is not responding&quot; error, and this happens with ANY server I try. if I refresh the list, sometimes the servers just disappear, same thing with restarting the game and /or steam.

the weird part is, if I try enough, it fixes itself, but also, sometimes it lets me connect to a server (which has no people) and I disconnect from it, and then none of the other servers work!

I&#39;ve experienced this on two completely different networks, though as far as I can remember, only wirelessly (not by choice, it&#39;s just all I have right now). And when it does work, I never do anything differently, I just keep trying. but sometimes it just won&#39;t work and I come back hours later and suddenly everything is fine.

I&#39;ve restarted tf2/steam/computer, I&#39;ve turned on/off my wireless card, and like I said, multiple netwroks have given me this problem, but never experienced it before say June of this year.

Computer is HP pavillion dv6700 laptop, running Win7 Professional (64bit) since February, 4 gigs ram, basic stock wireless card (broadcom 802.11g).

what&#39;s going on? any info would be appreciated, thanks</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 18 Aug 2010 23:47:54 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Help and Support</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/tf2-not-connecting-to-servers/5152.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>TF2 not connecting to servers</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Altamont_Raven]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="russilker">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/r/bbce88/40.png" class="avatar"> russilker:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>i assume you’re using one computer for this. did you try disabling firewalls (including Windows firewall)?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>well it’s enabled, but I never change it (and it’s always been that way) so I don’t see how that can be the problem.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>If you have access to the router on a network, make sure the packet filtration isnt set to some extreme safety level. steam should work without forwarding any ports but high security settings do interfere at times</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>well i don’t really have that kind of access to this router right now (subletting this place for a few more weeks) so maybe once I get control of my internet I can actually figure the problem out, instead of relying on university cable</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/tf2-not-connecting-to-servers/5152/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/tf2-not-connecting-to-servers/5152/4</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 18 Aug 2010 23:47:54 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-5152-4</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/tf2-not-connecting-to-servers/5152.rss">TF2 not connecting to servers</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>TF2 not connecting to servers</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Fancy_Pants]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>This happens to me alllll the time. I cannot connect to a single server through tf2, only the steam server browser works. Have you tried that?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/tf2-not-connecting-to-servers/5152/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/tf2-not-connecting-to-servers/5152/3</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 17 Aug 2010 23:38:56 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-5152-3</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/tf2-not-connecting-to-servers/5152.rss">TF2 not connecting to servers</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>TF2 not connecting to servers</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[russilker]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>let’s get the obvious suggestions out of the way –</p>
<p>i assume you’re using one computer for this. did you try disabling firewalls (including Windows firewall)?<br>
If you have access to the router on a network, make sure the packet filtration isnt set to some extreme safety level. steam should work without forwarding any ports but high security settings do interfere at times</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/tf2-not-connecting-to-servers/5152/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/tf2-not-connecting-to-servers/5152/2</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 17 Aug 2010 23:00:08 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-5152-2</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/tf2-not-connecting-to-servers/5152.rss">TF2 not connecting to servers</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>TF2 not connecting to servers</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Altamont_Raven]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I’ve been having this problem off and on the past couple months where I’ll start up TF2, and when I go to select a server, usually I can see some servers, like say I’m looking at my favorites list, so there’s maybe 6 servers. I double click on one that looks like it has people, and then I instantly get a “server is not responding” error, and this happens with ANY server I try. if I refresh the list, sometimes the servers just disappear, same thing with restarting the game and /or steam.</p>
<p>the weird part is, if I try enough, it fixes itself, but also, sometimes it lets me connect to a server (which has no people) and I disconnect from it, and then none of the other servers work!</p>
<p>I’ve experienced this on two completely different networks, though as far as I can remember, only wirelessly (not by choice, it’s just all I have right now). And when it does work, I never do anything differently, I just keep trying. but sometimes it just won’t work and I come back hours later and suddenly everything is fine.</p>
<p>I’ve restarted tf2/steam/computer, I’ve turned on/off my wireless card, and like I said, multiple netwroks have given me this problem, but never experienced it before say June of this year.</p>
<p>Computer is HP pavillion dv6700 laptop, running Win7 Professional (64bit) since February, 4 gigs ram, basic stock wireless card (broadcom 802.11g).</p>
<p>what’s going on? any info would be appreciated, thanks</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/tf2-not-connecting-to-servers/5152/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/tf2-not-connecting-to-servers/5152/1</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 17 Aug 2010 22:48:49 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-5152-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/tf2-not-connecting-to-servers/5152.rss">TF2 not connecting to servers</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
