<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Aiming up and down in Blood and other Build Engine games</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/aiming-up-and-down-in-blood-and-other-build-engine-games/12361</link>
    <description>So I picked up Blood and there is a way to aim up and down using the keyboard, but I can&#39;t figure out how to map those to moving the mouse up and down. I know that it won&#39;t help with aiming or anything but I&#39;d still like to be able to do it. I assume there&#39;s shortcuts for &quot;mouse up&quot; and &quot;mouse down&quot; like there are shortcuts for the other keys to use in the config file but I don&#39;t know what they would be and Google doesn&#39;t bring much up.

Edit: Never mind, seems I wasn&#39;t searching for the right thing. In settings there a Digital Mouse Movement section where you can set normal keyboard actions to mouse movement.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 06 Jul 2013 05:44:58 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Help and Support</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/aiming-up-and-down-in-blood-and-other-build-engine-games/12361.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Aiming up and down in Blood and other Build Engine games</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Kairouseki]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>So I picked up Blood and there is a way to aim up and down using the keyboard, but I can’t figure out how to map those to moving the mouse up and down. I know that it won’t help with aiming or anything but I’d still like to be able to do it. I assume there’s shortcuts for “mouse up” and “mouse down” like there are shortcuts for the other keys to use in the config file but I don’t know what they would be and Google doesn’t bring much up.</p>
<p>Edit: Never mind, seems I wasn’t searching for the right thing. In settings there a Digital Mouse Movement section where you can set normal keyboard actions to mouse movement.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/aiming-up-and-down-in-blood-and-other-build-engine-games/12361/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/aiming-up-and-down-in-blood-and-other-build-engine-games/12361/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 06 Jul 2013 05:44:58 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12361-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/aiming-up-and-down-in-blood-and-other-build-engine-games/12361.rss">Aiming up and down in Blood and other Build Engine games</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
