<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Georgia (Not state :| )</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/georgia-not-state/8121</link>
    <description>so... since there is nothing to debate about black mesa people talk about not related to BM things more and I am one of them. So I am interested about what people know about my country and also want to introduce to others.

[align=center][img]https://www.flags.net/images/largeflags/GEOR0001.GIF[/img]

[img]https://www.medeatravel.ge/assets/images/gerb_georgia.jpg[/img][/align]

[INDENT] So Georgia is post soviet country. It&#39;s capitol is called Tbilisi. Most of you don&#39;t know much about this country but it has a very important role in history but I&#39;ll just state most common things here.  Georgia is Orthodox Christian country converted in 4th century. Georgia is also considered as motherland of wine, recent archaeological discoveries have shown that culture of wine making was already well-developed in 5th century B.C. since Georgia was always frontier of war against Muslim conquerors it had not much power do develop in science. also Georgia is one of 13(as I remember) countries with its own alphabet. Georgia was most strong in 12 century which was called gold era (or something like that). Georgia is also famous of it&#39;s hospitality, in most of villages people will invite you to their house  if they will see that you need it (don&#39;t hope on that in City but people are hospital there as well).
 Well as for todays state Country is in a pretty bad shape but this is matter of long debates.
 Also if you are interested you can check Georgian music.
I love this song it is about city Kutaisi:
[url=&#39;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ovcDAUQsiaI&#39;]Revaz Lagidze -Anathem to Kutaisi[/url]
[url=&#39;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ArCGNGYtqws&#39;]Erisioni - Shatilis Asulo(modern version of famous folk song)[/url]
[url=&#39;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=O88k8gIq39g&#39;]Karkuchit Chamoiyvanes(Folk Song)[/url]
[url=&#39;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=X0lq7c3aiXg&amp;feature=related&#39;]Shenma Survilma Damlia[/url]
[url=&#39;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Q7ZiUWfWibY&amp;feature=related&#39;]Tu ase turfa iyavi[/url]
 Here are Georgia folk dance videos as well, which I consider to be pretty awesome. you can check it yourself:
This will be translated as Riders Dance (most interesting part from 1:00)
[url=&#39;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=vX_q_svYVu8&amp;feature=related&#39;]Mxedruli[/url]
[url=&#39;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=nCU0YG3DFlM&amp;feature=related&#39;]Dance &quot;shejibri&quot;/&quot;A Competition&quot;[/url]
[url=&#39;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=2XJx-9uGG94&amp;feature=related&#39;]Dance &quot;shejibri&quot;/&quot;A Competition&quot;[/url]
[url=&#39;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=7ryifuAUg5c&amp;feature=related&#39;]Khanjluri[/url]
and finally war dance, my favorite. In this dance dancers are fighting with swords:
[url=&#39;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=7092m7wzfWw&amp;feature=related&#39;]Khevsuruli[/url]

hope this is interesting  to you and you will enjoy it  :slight_smile: [/INDENT]</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 29 Nov 2011 12:15:41 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Off Topic</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/georgia-not-state/8121.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Georgia (Not state :| )</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Assassin]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>the new one is better, old flag was being used only for 12 years.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/georgia-not-state/8121/68">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/georgia-not-state/8121/68</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 29 Nov 2011 12:15:41 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8121-68</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/georgia-not-state/8121.rss">Georgia (Not state :| )</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Georgia (Not state :| )</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[TheOneAndOnly]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Yeah, I think I saw that one once, but didn’t buy it because I didn’t know what it was for. Silly me. That one seems easier to sew, so I may give it a try  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=9" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/georgia-not-state/8121/67">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/georgia-not-state/8121/67</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 29 Nov 2011 12:06:30 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8121-67</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/georgia-not-state/8121.rss">Georgia (Not state :| )</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Georgia (Not state :| )</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Assassin]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><span alt="" class="broken-image" title="This image is broken"><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-unlink svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#unlink"></use></svg></span><br>
this is old georgian flag which was changed in 2003. maybe you have this?</p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>Yeah, why back up your arguments when you can have others do it for you. Well, not my problem.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>well i am not backing them up because I don’t want to argue not because I can’t.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/georgia-not-state/8121/66">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/georgia-not-state/8121/66</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 29 Nov 2011 12:03:51 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8121-66</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/georgia-not-state/8121.rss">Georgia (Not state :| )</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Georgia (Not state :| )</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Bolteh]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><img src="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/original/3X/b/a/ba4a1fd696e846500f8ced6185c470f82f81d135.jpeg" alt="" data-base62-sha1="qzZCsa80tCvD9jTVHuQb2eUGAtL" width="650" height="463"></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/georgia-not-state/8121/65">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/georgia-not-state/8121/65</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 29 Nov 2011 11:58:52 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8121-65</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/georgia-not-state/8121.rss">Georgia (Not state :| )</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Georgia (Not state :| )</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[TheOneAndOnly]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Yeah, why back up your arguments when you can have others do it for you. Well, not my problem.</p>
<p>I really like the Georgian flag, as it happens. Back at home I had a collection of miniature flags, but never got around to find one. I guess it is a bit of an unknown country  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/frowning.png?v=9" title=":frowning:" class="emoji" alt=":frowning:">  Wonder if I could sew one… It seems a bit difficult, though.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/georgia-not-state/8121/64">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/georgia-not-state/8121/64</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 29 Nov 2011 11:56:34 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8121-64</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/georgia-not-state/8121.rss">Georgia (Not state :| )</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Georgia (Not state :| )</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Assassin]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>yes I can but I started this topic to introduce Georgia to people not to argue about Russia. if someone wants to prove anything against what I say he/she should search for proof. I have enough proof in form of 300k refugees(or even more).</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/georgia-not-state/8121/63">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/georgia-not-state/8121/63</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 29 Nov 2011 11:51:31 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8121-63</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/georgia-not-state/8121.rss">Georgia (Not state :| )</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Georgia (Not state :| )</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[TheOneAndOnly]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Uh huh. Alrighty then. But how about, you know, numbers, surveys, pie charts, papers and the like? Opinions alone will most likely never be enough. It’s the internet, I’m sure you can dig up some hard facts to back up your claims.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/georgia-not-state/8121/62">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/georgia-not-state/8121/62</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 29 Nov 2011 11:44:55 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8121-62</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/georgia-not-state/8121.rss">Georgia (Not state :| )</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Georgia (Not state :| )</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Assassin]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>Also, Assassin, you are always quoting what other people has told you as proof of your arguments. Gotta think fo’ yourself, bro.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>my quotes wont be enough because it will be considered as my opinion.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/georgia-not-state/8121/61">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/georgia-not-state/8121/61</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 29 Nov 2011 11:43:07 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8121-61</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/georgia-not-state/8121.rss">Georgia (Not state :| )</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Georgia (Not state :| )</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[TheOneAndOnly]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Dr. Karamazov">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Dr. Karamazov:</div>
<blockquote>
<p><span class="mention">@Jokerine</span><br>
If she’s an old Russian it wouldn’t surprise me.  Stalin is still popular amongst the older generation in Russia.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Yup, there are plenty of Russians around here (my boyfriend’s mom is from Russia, even), so you are probably right. I may try to chat the old lady up and see why she has the picture there.</p>
<p>Also, Assassin, you are always quoting what other people has told you as proof of your arguments. Gotta think fo’ yourself, bro.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/georgia-not-state/8121/60">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/georgia-not-state/8121/60</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 29 Nov 2011 11:37:54 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8121-60</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/georgia-not-state/8121.rss">Georgia (Not state :| )</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Georgia (Not state :| )</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Dr_Karamazov]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><span class="mention">@Jokerine</span><br>
If she’s an old Russian it wouldn’t surprise me.  Stalin is still popular amongst the older generation in Russia.</p>
<p>I can fully understand why.  This was a man who changed the soviet union from a backwards agricultural nation into a world superpower rivaling the US.<br>
If it wasn’t for Stalin’s industrialization projects which caused the fastest industrial growth ever seen (before or since) then the soviets would never have been able to stand against the might of Germany.  They would have crumbled under the force of Hitler’s attacks and there would have been no eastern front.</p>
<p>Without an eastern front the majority of the German forces would have been concentrated on the western front.  Would the allies have been able to fight their way through that?  We were split between the Pacific and European theatres, so if Hitler could concentrate his forces in one spot I really don’t think we could have won.</p>
<p>Thus Germany would have won the war.  Being weakened by the pwnage in Europe, America would have faltered in Asia and gotten pwnd by the Japanese and we’d end up in the Philip K. Dick story “Man in the High Castle” where the Axis won the war.</p>
<p>So there you have it.  Stalin single handedly won the war and that’s why many Russians still love him.</p>
<p>edit:  yes, before anyone mentions it;  I know that millions of people died in the process of the industrial reforms.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/georgia-not-state/8121/59">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/georgia-not-state/8121/59</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 29 Nov 2011 11:32:07 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8121-59</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/georgia-not-state/8121.rss">Georgia (Not state :| )</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Georgia (Not state :| )</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Assassin]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>That first one is a pretty provocative lookin’ dish.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>there are many dishes like that :3 but I couldn’t find pics :S</p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>Mindless violent assholes are common in any country. It seems that your grandmother was just victim of one of those fuckers. Did the people who attacked her know she was Georgian or just attack her for no reason?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>they are everywhere but not common, I am interested when he was fighting neither police nor people did anything? in russia no one did. they attacked not HIS grandmother but HIM and yes because he was georgian. also in Russia beating citizens of post-soviet countries is pretty much common. they hate north caucasian nations chechens, daghstnians and ect. they beat everyone. No, I hate them not because they fought against Georgia, but because of their ideology. you know, my uncle was in russian army and he tells me (he also dislikes russians) for Russia it is important that everyone else were worse than they are. and it is exactly what is happening today. they are working to worsen situation in “enemy” countries, not to improve themselves. I see this clearly and my “hatred” is quite reasoned.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/georgia-not-state/8121/58">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/georgia-not-state/8121/58</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 29 Nov 2011 11:24:59 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8121-58</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/georgia-not-state/8121.rss">Georgia (Not state :| )</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Georgia (Not state :| )</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[TheOneAndOnly]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Unrelated, but you know, Karamazov, near here this old lady has a pretty old framed picture of Stalin hanging in her garden. I’m sure she was alive by the time he ruled, so she probably is a fan too  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=9" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:">  I’ll see if I can get a picture of the picture.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/georgia-not-state/8121/57">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/georgia-not-state/8121/57</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 29 Nov 2011 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8121-57</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/georgia-not-state/8121.rss">Georgia (Not state :| )</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Georgia (Not state :| )</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Dr_Karamazov]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Assassin">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/a/ccd318/40.png" class="avatar"> Assassin:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I have Russian friends as well.</p>
<p>well maybe 5 or more times? I’ll tell you how friendly are Russians. my friend was in Moscow few years ago to his Grandma.<br>
so he tells me:</p>
<ul>
<li>…we walk as bands, I found there Georgians and always sticked with them.</li>
<li>heh… you can’t walk alone?</li>
<li>we once went near the Kremlin,  my friends went to buy some food and I stayed out. in few minutes some guy went… … … and he hit me in face and his friend came as well and began beating me. if my friends didn’t come in time I would have been dead.</li>
<li>they beat you in front of Kremlin?! but isn’t there a police?</li>
<li>well there were but they didn’t cared much.</li>
</ul>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>This is my saying which I like to stand by-<br>
It doesn’t matter about the religion, nationality, colour, class or profession; there are always nice people and always fucking assholes.</p>
<p>You are painting a picture of Russians being mostly evil, but I just don’t agree with that.  I also know many stories of people getting beaten up in Russia.  But I can give you even more stories of people getting attack in England.</p>
<p>Many years ago I bumped into a guy I went to school with (we’ll call him Chris).  It was a Friday night and my friend and I were walking home.  Anyway, Chris comes over and asks how our night was, we tell him it was fine and ask him how he was.  He told us that it was an ok night so far but that he was going to finish it off by beating up some ‘muslims’.  He then went into the nearest Kebab shop and started beating the shit out of some Turks for absolutely not reason other than the fact that he found it funny.  He really did find the whole thing hilarious.</p>
<p>Another guy from my class attacked a guy in a bar and bit his nose off.  He did a few years in prison for that.</p>
<p>Mindless violent assholes are common in any country.  It seems that your grandmother was just victim of one of those fuckers.  Did the people who attacked her know she was Georgian or just attack her for no reason?</p>
<p>I understand that there’s a great amount of bad blood between Russia and Georgia and I can see why you would have such strong feelings against them.  Just try not to let it cloud your vision and make you hate them all.</p>
<p>Also, I wouldn’t put too much faith into Russian votes making much difference in the out come.<br>
Stalin once said-<br>
<span class="bbcode-b"><span class="bbcode-i">“It is enough that the people know there was an election. The people who cast the votes decide nothing. The people who count the votes decide everything.”</span></span></p>
<p>I have to say, he has some of the best quotes around.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/georgia-not-state/8121/56">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/georgia-not-state/8121/56</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 29 Nov 2011 00:47:35 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8121-56</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/georgia-not-state/8121.rss">Georgia (Not state :| )</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Georgia (Not state :| )</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Dr_Karamazov]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>No waaaay.</p>
<p>Svetlana Stalin died today.  Stalin’s remaining child passed away at the age of 85 from cancer.  Bummer.<br>
She was one of the last links to that world.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/georgia-not-state/8121/55">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/georgia-not-state/8121/55</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 29 Nov 2011 00:33:44 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8121-55</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/georgia-not-state/8121.rss">Georgia (Not state :| )</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Georgia (Not state :| )</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[TheHippo]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Assassin">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/a/ccd318/40.png" class="avatar"> Assassin:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Lobiani - bean pie.<br>
<span alt="" class="broken-image" title="This image is broken"><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-unlink svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#unlink"></use></svg></span></p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>That first one is a pretty provocative lookin’ dish.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/georgia-not-state/8121/54">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/georgia-not-state/8121/54</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 28 Nov 2011 20:33:36 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8121-54</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/georgia-not-state/8121.rss">Georgia (Not state :| )</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Georgia (Not state :| )</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[geekofalltrades]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Assassin">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/a/ccd318/40.png" class="avatar"> Assassin:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I have Russian friends as well.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>It’s just that he hates them.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/georgia-not-state/8121/53">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/georgia-not-state/8121/53</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 28 Nov 2011 19:16:24 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8121-53</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/georgia-not-state/8121.rss">Georgia (Not state :| )</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Georgia (Not state :| )</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Assassin]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>Some of my best friends are Russian.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I have Russian friends as well.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>The Russian government did these things, not the Russian people and as we are all aware the Russian people don’t have much control over who is in charge of their country.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>your Russian friends are minority, also let me disagree about your opinion that only government is responsible for actions of Russia. People choose that government, People choose putin for first 6 years, people choose gnomedvedev and people will choose putin for next 24 years(did I mention that from now votes in Russia are once in 6 years?) so they are as well responsible for the actions of their government.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>I didn’t like George Bush, but that doesn’t mean I would hate all Americans. The US is currently torturing people in Guantanamo Bay, but that doesn’t mean that the American people are barbaric murderous animals.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>sigh, you just are too liberal. Russia and US are completely different countries. America is a blend of many nations Russians are mostly blend of Mongols and Slavs.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>How many times have you left Georgia Assassin? How many times have you left your bubble of hatred and seen these places you claim to know so much about?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>well maybe 5 or more times? I’ll tell you how friendly are Russians. my friend was in Moscow few years ago to his Grandma.<br>
so he tells me:</p>
<ul>
<li>…we walk as bands, I found there Georgians and always sticked with them.</li>
<li>heh… you can’t walk alone?</li>
<li>we once went near the Kremlin,  my friends went to buy some food and I stayed out. in few minutes some guy went… … … and he hit me in face and his friend came as well and began beating me. if my friends didn’t come in time I would have been dead.</li>
<li>they beat you in front of Kremlin?! but isn’t there a police?</li>
<li>well there were but they didn’t cared much.<br>
here is you lovely and sweet Russia.</li>
</ul>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>His birth name was not Soso. This was a nickname he had as a child which was given to him by his mother, but it isn’t his real name.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>well, let me disagree. Soso is a variation of Iosif/Ioseb this is not a nickname that is a name. my grandpa is a hardcore communist and I often talk with him about Stalin. well you can call him whatever you want anyway.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/georgia-not-state/8121/52">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/georgia-not-state/8121/52</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 28 Nov 2011 16:31:43 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8121-52</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/georgia-not-state/8121.rss">Georgia (Not state :| )</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Georgia (Not state :| )</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Dr_Karamazov]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Assassin">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/a/ccd318/40.png" class="avatar"> Assassin:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>actually his real name is Soso Jughashvili - სოსო ჯუღაშვილი.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I feel kind of bad arguing with a Georgian about this, but no.<br>
His birth name was not Soso.  This was a nickname he had as a child which was given to him by his mother, but it isn’t his real name.</p>
<p>Not to sound like an asshole, but I have read pretty much every contemporary book on Stalin I have been able to get my  hands on.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-i">Young Stalin</span> by Simon Sebag-Montifore is an excellent book detailing the life of Stalin before he came to power; heavily detailing his childhood, life as a bank robber, life in exile and his time as a revolutionary.</p>
<p>I’m a bit of an nerd when it comes to Mr. Stalin.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/georgia-not-state/8121/51">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/georgia-not-state/8121/51</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 28 Nov 2011 12:21:49 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8121-51</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/georgia-not-state/8121.rss">Georgia (Not state :| )</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Georgia (Not state :| )</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[mankyman6]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Having problems Georgia?</p>
<p>100,000 American troops should cure that right up!</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/georgia-not-state/8121/50">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/georgia-not-state/8121/50</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 28 Nov 2011 10:31:29 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8121-50</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/georgia-not-state/8121.rss">Georgia (Not state :| )</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Georgia (Not state :| )</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Jethrosoup]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>As an American I hold it my sacred duty to be an asshole to foreigners.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/georgia-not-state/8121/49">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/georgia-not-state/8121/49</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 27 Nov 2011 17:33:33 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8121-49</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/georgia-not-state/8121.rss">Georgia (Not state :| )</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Georgia (Not state :| )</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Dr_Karamazov]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Some of my best friends are Russian.<br>
Infact, from my current circle of friends I have 6 Russians, 2 Ukrainians, 1 Pole, 1 Azerbaijanian and 2 Kazakhs.<br>
It’s tough only speaking English when surrounded by ex-soviets.</p>
<p>Anyway, I think I can safely say that none of my friends have murdered any Georgians.  None of them are animals.  None of them hate Georgia.  None of them are beating up Georgians.  None of them are deporting them on planes.</p>
<p>I think you just haven’t grown up.  The Russian <span class="bbcode-b">government</span> did these things, not the Russian people and as we are all aware the Russian people don’t have much control over who is in charge of their country.</p>
<p>I didn’t like George Bush, but that doesn’t mean I would hate all Americans.  The US is currently torturing people in Guantanamo Bay, but that doesn’t mean that the American people are barbaric murderous animals.  It just means that they have a government filled with assholes.  On the whole most Americans are pretty nice people.  The same goes for Russians.  I have spent roughly 4 months in Russia and a month in the Ukraine and I can happily say that appart from their officials (who are miserable fuckheads) and their corrupt police, the average Russian is really quite friendly and helpful.</p>
<p>How many times have you left Georgia Assassin?  How many times have you left your bubble of hatred and seen these places you claim to know so much about?</p>
<p>Assassin, you need to distinguish between the government of a country and its people.<br>
I am very tempted to throw large piles of abuse at you concerning your childish nature and inability to think logically and past your racist upbringing, but I wont.</p>
<p>Just try and think logically.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/georgia-not-state/8121/48">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/georgia-not-state/8121/48</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 27 Nov 2011 17:29:38 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8121-48</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/georgia-not-state/8121.rss">Georgia (Not state :| )</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Georgia (Not state :| )</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Assassin]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>exactly</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/georgia-not-state/8121/47">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/georgia-not-state/8121/47</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 27 Nov 2011 13:41:05 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8121-47</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/georgia-not-state/8121.rss">Georgia (Not state :| )</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Georgia (Not state :| )</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Bolteh]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Whatever you say, champ.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/georgia-not-state/8121/46">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/georgia-not-state/8121/46</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 27 Nov 2011 11:08:04 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8121-46</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/georgia-not-state/8121.rss">Georgia (Not state :| )</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Georgia (Not state :| )</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Assassin]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>prejudice (“all Russians are animals”)</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>for you maybe it is prejudice, for me it is reality and fact. if this will make for you easier I’ll change all to most.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>nationalism (“Georgia is the best country in the world with the best culture, best people… Everyone else is dirty and inferior”)</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I don’t say that Georgia is best, I’ll even say that is far from normal. I just stated what I love in my country. bad sides of my country are a lot as well, if you want you will find them yourself just don’t ask Russians.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>xenophobia (“LULZ MUSLIMS KIEL KIEL”)</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>again wrong, I said that Georgia fought against Muslims in past and I haven said that I hate them. in there are also a LOT OF Georgians who are Muslims, but still they are few.</p>
<p>so where is here fascism ?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/georgia-not-state/8121/45">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/georgia-not-state/8121/45</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 27 Nov 2011 11:00:04 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8121-45</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/georgia-not-state/8121.rss">Georgia (Not state :| )</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Georgia (Not state :| )</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Bolteh]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Nobody here is claiming that Russia is the epitome of peace, serenity and kindness, but that doesn’t change the fact that pretty much every post you have made (including the original post) is filled with prejudice (“all Russians are animals”), nationalism (“Georgia is the best country in the world with the best culture, best people… Everyone else is dirty and inferior”), xenophobia (“LULZ MUSLIMS KIEL KIEL”)… Or well yeah… You know… Fascism.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/georgia-not-state/8121/44">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/georgia-not-state/8121/44</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 27 Nov 2011 10:41:42 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8121-44</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/georgia-not-state/8121.rss">Georgia (Not state :| )</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
