<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>OaR - Loop Mod</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/oar-loop-mod/12153</link>
    <description>[b][u]Current Status: Finished: [url]https://www.dropbox.com/s/q8ik53e37wgefxt/LoopMod.zip[/url][/u][/b]

Now available on ModDB: [url]https://www.moddb.com/mods/black-mesa-on-a-rail-loop-mod[/url]

[u]Introduction[/u]

Howdy everyone!

I am working on a mod for Black Mesa called the “Loop Mod”. What this mod does is add some new sections of track to the very first map for On a Rail. 

At the very beginning of the original Half Life’s On a Rail chapter, the player was presented with some looped hallways to navigate as they tried to find their way around, eventually finding the crane controls and being able to move on to the next section. At the time though the layout for this idea was confusing and nonsensical at best, and as a result was left out entirely from the Black Mesa mod.

I intend to return to the spirit of this section (without replicating the needless complexity, and – in general – make it easier to follow and understand).

[u]Implementation[/u]

This mod will add new sections to the map bm_c2a2a.

![](upload://qph78jIvrsZx9evcun08CYz2vAK.png)

Integrated into what was already there, the player will first go up the right shaft past the houndeyes, then will turn right into this loop addition. While there, they will run into an office where they can switch the tracks back at the junction. They will then be able to ride through the junction and make their way to the electric pool puzzle.

[u]Media[/u]
![](upload://bIF2yBOTmrjGFegRdlDOlVTXUKK.png)
![](upload://4TU18Fid0jxaF4Gm1A6YX7azg6t.png)
![](upload://v3qMOHGfAlB5qmdF9z3aJqpELPU.png)
![](upload://98Z5aUpFtg9oc4UbOdF4TkIwhLB.png)
![](upload://rQO4mm4Oq8zZQGCeAfhoUT8ycHp.png)

[u]Other info[/u]

Background – I have some experience in mapping for Portal 2, having created a few levels over the past couple of years (most of which are unfinished and will probably not see the light of day). Therefore, I believe that I have the skills necessary to create these new sections while keeping with the style set by the devs in the original map.

Compatibility – As I am sure many of you know, there is currently another mod for On a Rail named Oar Uncut. If you haven’t checked it out already, do so. It’s an excellent mod. If you have installed his mod or are planning to install it, I will be providing support for the mod. At release, I will also release a version of the altered map that will link seamlessly to his maps.

Office? – This new addition is born out of the necessity for a new method of switching track. In the original Half-Life the player could switch the tram’s path by shooting at switches. While this works great from a gameplay standpoint, it makes absolutely no sense and would not hold up in Black Mesa’s world. This office is also used to justify traveling down through the loop (because otherwise it would be a pointless addition and then what would the purpose of making the mod be?).</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 08 Jun 2018 19:44:20 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Source 1</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/oar-loop-mod/12153.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>OaR - Loop Mod</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[RK1]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Admiral Sakai">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Admiral Sakai:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Have you considered using a tool like <a href="https://developer.valvesoftware.com/wiki/Propper" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Propper</a> to convert some of the expensive sections into static props?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Of course I did. As a matter of fact, during the alpha phase of the project, I had to use Propper not only on that electrical box in that side room there, but I also used it for the bridge at the electrical pool puzzle. Among other places.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/oar-loop-mod/12153/292">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/oar-loop-mod/12153/292</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Jun 2018 19:44:20 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12153-292</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/oar-loop-mod/12153.rss">OaR - Loop Mod</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>OaR - Loop Mod</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Admiral_Sakai]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Have you considered using a tool like <a href="https://developer.valvesoftware.com/wiki/Propper" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Propper</a> to convert some of the expensive sections into static props?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/oar-loop-mod/12153/291">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/oar-loop-mod/12153/291</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Jun 2018 15:45:30 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12153-291</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/oar-loop-mod/12153.rss">OaR - Loop Mod</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>OaR - Loop Mod</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[RK1]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Hey, everyone! Loop Mod has finally been updated into the newest engine.</p>
<p>I’m happy that I’ve been able to do this. The inability to compile in 2013 has haunted me for the longest time and I’ve just beaten it. To contextualize this, when I first tried porting Loop Mod into the source version of Black Mesa, I had 7000 brushsides more than what the compiler would allow. My task was to bring that number down. After using pretty much every trick I could think of, I was able to knock off about 3500 brushsides without having to actually change anything (as was my former design principle). I then hit a block and never thought I would be able to knock off another 3500 and thus get to a compilable state. The maps still worked in the 2007 compiler!</p>
<p>But I never thought I would be able to get it into 2013, and here I am!</p>
<p>It has, however, come at a cost. As I mentioned in my previous post, I stated that I was going to have to make some significant changes to existing areas. This included my own areas as well. But also as previously stated, I’ve avoided anything that should impact gameplay to any appreciable degree. These changes are as follows:</p>
<ul>
<li>Simplification of the health charger room to the left of the first elevator</li>
<li>Removal of stairs in the ramp room</li>
<li>Removal of lowground near the electrical box room (where two vorts are fought)</li>
<li>Simplification of the H room between the two tracks where a bullsquid is fought</li>
<li>Simplification of a lot of things at the electrical pool puzzle.</li>
<li>Deletion of some vents and pipes around the map.<br>
At present, I’m sitting on the cusp of where the map stops working; the difference between the map compiling and not compiling is, in fact, a single brush. I’m that close. So I can’t stress enough that I really didn’t have a choice in these matters but to get it into the state it is now.</li>
</ul>
<p>With any luck, however, the maps should play the exact same. Hopefully y’all will agree with me.</p>
<p>That said, I did want to talk about a major development that helped me loads.</p>
<p>You see, the way that Black Mesa handles tunnel curves is very expensive brush-wise. I would suspect that a large number of brushes and brushsides comes from how those were constructed. I would dare say it’s inefficient. They’re also quite modular in a way and, considering that the stock maps weren’t as full as this one, it was a non-problem</p>
<p>But what I attempted to do was rebuild the tunnel curves from scratch. To do this, I took a length of tunnel and rotated it around a center point (which would be the radius of curvature). I did this in 10 degree increments, giving me 8 portions of track within the curve (just like BM uses 8 portions of track in the curve) plus 2 more sections that lie on-grid. This works best when these two on-grid sections are connected right with surrounding sections of tunnel (especially if said sections are straight). The main difference, however, if that the wall cladding, the track edges, and the sloped parts of the ceilings, which are expensive in the old way, are done much more efficiently.</p>
<p>To illustrate this, a single piece of sloped ceiling is made of 2 brushes of 5 brushsides each, and there are two of these pieces; one on each side of the tunnel. The wall cladding is, similarly, made of 2 brushes of 5 brushsides each, and there are two of these pieces; one on each side of the tunnel. The track sides are made of three brushes with one being 6 brushsides and the other 2 being of 5 brushsides each, and there are two of these setups; one on each side of the tunnel. So, in total, that’s 2x4x2 + 2x5x2 + 2x5x2+2x1x6 = 72 brushsides. Multiply this by 8 curve segments and you get 576 brushsides per curve.</p>
<p>In contrast, with my method, the cladding is made of a single brush of 6 brushsides (and again there are two of these), the sloped ceiling is made of a single brush of 5 sides (are there are two of these), and the tracksides are made of a single brush made out of 6 sides (and, again, two of these). SO we get 1x6x2 + 1x5x2 + 1x4x2 = 30 brushsides. Multiply this b 8 curve segments and you get 240 brushsides per curve.</p>
<p>You can see how helpful this is in overcoming the brushsides issue. It turns out that I was able to employ the method on four curves in the map (and I briefly considered using it on a fifth). I think this actually saved the map, if I’m being honest. As an added bonus, however, the curves came out looking really nice.</p>
<p>So there we have it. The mod has been updated. Enjoy!</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/oar-loop-mod/12153/290">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/oar-loop-mod/12153/290</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Jun 2018 05:42:25 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12153-290</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/oar-loop-mod/12153.rss">OaR - Loop Mod</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>OaR - Loop Mod</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[RedEye9]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username=".RK">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 .RK:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>(This post is slightly companion to a post made in the WGH - Vent Mod thread. Post here: <a href="https://forums.blackmesasource.com/index.php/Thread/16839-WGH-Vent-Mod/?postID=649089#post649089" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">WGH - Vent Mod</a>)</p>
<p>Hello, everyone.</p>
<p>So I’m currently working on an update to Loop Mod. Specifically, I want to get the map into a state where I can compile it in the newest source engine. Currently versions of the mod use a map compiled under BM’s 2007 version. While I don’t readily know what kinds of issues (if any) this causes, I do figure that there is probably a drop in quality in the final map.</p>
<p>I am somewhat interested in having consistency, especially since I know, for a fact, that the 2013 version is much more rigorous in its compilation than the 2007 version and a Loop Mod compiled under it would probably be so much better.</p>
<p>However, actually realizing this will be difficult and has already forced me to compromise one of the main design principles that I had with the mod. I have time and time again shown pride in my ability to keep the stock areas of the map completely intact and I have stated my intention of keeping things that way.</p>
<p>Sadly, I have to face the truth that, in order to get this map working in the 2013 version, I don’t have a choice anymore. I’ve previously talked about how the map has gained several thousand brushsides on transitioning from 2007 to 2013, and this limit is not something I can simply circumvent. In the past, I have taken great strides to simplify geometry, use Propper for especially difficult polygons, and many many other tricks to get that number down, and it worked in 2007. But I am out of options.</p>
<p>As such, there will be some changes to stock areas. I will mainly be focusing on areas that are not frequented by players, things which should have little to no impact on the average playthrough. I’m trying to tread as lightly as I can, and I’m not sure how much more I’ll need to do before I can call it good. But bear with me.</p>
<p>I also wanted to let you all know that I am currently exploring options on making Loop Mod easier to work when other mods are present on the same machine (and vice versa for other mods). I can’t promise that anything will actually come of this but, since I’m making this post now, I figured that I would say something.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>It might be helpful to make similar posts on the mods respective workshop pages.<br>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/workshop/browse/?appid=362890&amp;searchtext=Loop+Mod&amp;childpublishedfileid=0&amp;browsesort=textsearch&amp;section=home" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://steamcommunity.com/workshop/browse/?appid=362890&amp;searchtext=Loop+Mod&amp;childpublishedfileid=0&amp;browsesort=textsearch§ion=home</a><br>
Then again you might wait until they are updated.</p>
<p>EDIT: You already are  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=9" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/oar-loop-mod/12153/289">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/oar-loop-mod/12153/289</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 05 Jun 2018 18:54:31 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12153-289</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/oar-loop-mod/12153.rss">OaR - Loop Mod</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>OaR - Loop Mod</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[RK1]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>(This post is slightly companion to a post made in the WGH - Vent Mod thread. Post here: <a href="https://forums.blackmesasource.com/index.php/Thread/16839-WGH-Vent-Mod/?postID=649089#post649089" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">WGH - Vent Mod</a>)</p>
<p>Hello, everyone.</p>
<p>So I’m currently working on an update to Loop Mod. Specifically, I want to get the map into a state where I can compile it in the newest source engine. Currently versions of the mod use a map compiled under BM’s 2007 version. While I don’t readily know what kinds of issues (if any) this causes, I do figure that there is probably a drop in quality in the final map.</p>
<p>I am somewhat interested in having consistency, especially since I know, for a fact, that the 2013 version is much more rigorous in its compilation than the 2007 version and a Loop Mod compiled under it would probably be so much better.</p>
<p>However, actually realizing this will be difficult and has already forced me to compromise one of the main design principles that I had with the mod. I have time and time again shown pride in my ability to keep the stock areas of the map completely intact and I have stated my intention of keeping things that way.</p>
<p>Sadly, I have to face the truth that, in order to get this map working in the 2013 version, I don’t have a choice anymore. I’ve previously talked about how the map has gained several thousand brushsides on transitioning from 2007 to 2013, and this limit is not something I can simply circumvent. In the past, I have taken great strides to simplify geometry, use Propper for especially difficult polygons, and many many other tricks to get that number down, and it worked in 2007. But I am out of options.</p>
<p>As such, there will be some changes to stock areas. I will mainly be focusing on areas that are not frequented by players, things which should have little to no impact on the average playthrough. I’m trying to tread as lightly as I can, and I’m not sure how much more I’ll need to do before I can call it good. But bear with me.</p>
<p>I also wanted to let you all know that I am currently exploring options on making Loop Mod easier to work when other mods are present on the same machine (and vice versa for other mods). I can’t promise that anything will actually come of this but, since I’m making this post now, I figured that I would say something.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/oar-loop-mod/12153/288">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/oar-loop-mod/12153/288</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 05 Jun 2018 17:52:05 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12153-288</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/oar-loop-mod/12153.rss">OaR - Loop Mod</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>OaR - Loop Mod</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[RK1]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Bumping this in order to share an update.</p>
<p>As you might have been aware, the mods have not been compatible with the team version as of late. The recent update to OARU brought it to my attention but chances are the stock version was broken even before that.</p>
<p>Nevertheless, I think I’ve fixed it.</p>
<p>The sad truth is, ever since the transition to Source 2013, I haven’t been able to compile the maps <span class="bbcode-i">at all</span>. I never said anything about it even when porting the mod over to the workshop (I mean, it worked decently enough, after all), but wasn’t sure what I was going to do. And to explain why, the sdk tools have a built-in brushsides limit (which I previously dealt with during Loop Mod’s development) of 65536. In SDK 2007, Loop Mod was just under this at ~65300 brushsides. In 2013 however, as I recently sat down and did some tricks to find out, Loop Mod was about 72000 brushsides.</p>
<p>Why the jump? Well, compilers in different engines probably cut the maps in different ways.</p>
<p>Either way, I knew about the broken maps for a week and the reason it took me this long to get the fix out was contending with that brushsides problem. I used every trick that I know in tackling this problem; marking some areas for Propper and making some small detailing changes that simplified geometry to boot, etc. I was able to cut about 3500 brushsides. Sadly, that was only half of what I needed to cut. Anything more than that would have probably required some fairly radical changes to map design, which wouldn’t happen.</p>
<p>So I bit the bullet and compiled the map under 2007’s SDK where I knew it would still compile. And, now, it’s uploaded on the workshop. With any luck, you shouldn’t be able to tell that it’s compiled any differently (in fact, if you’ve played the steam versions already and not noticed anything odd, then you’ve already seen what I mean).</p>
<p>I did some rudimentary testing on these newly compiled maps but I’m pretty sure that they work. Let me know if something is still catastrophically broken.</p>
<p>Phew! Now that this is out of the way, I can work on updating Vent Mod tomorrow, which should take <span class="bbcode-i">only</span> tomorrow. For now, cheers!</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/oar-loop-mod/12153/287">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/oar-loop-mod/12153/287</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 15 Jan 2017 07:55:36 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12153-287</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/oar-loop-mod/12153.rss">OaR - Loop Mod</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>OaR - Loop Mod</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[KyuuGryphon]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Kinda late, but yep, can confirm it’s working now! Thanks!</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/oar-loop-mod/12153/286">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/oar-loop-mod/12153/286</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 09 Feb 2016 18:46:35 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12153-286</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/oar-loop-mod/12153.rss">OaR - Loop Mod</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>OaR - Loop Mod</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[RK1]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Welp, turns out vpk didn’t get the exact files I wanted it to. But I can confirm that the level transition is working now.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/oar-loop-mod/12153/285">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/oar-loop-mod/12153/285</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 09 Feb 2016 07:09:10 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12153-285</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/oar-loop-mod/12153.rss">OaR - Loop Mod</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>OaR - Loop Mod</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[KyuuGryphon]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I’m not subscribed to the stock version of Loop Mod, no. I can’t recreate the missing textures issue now, but what I did to fix it was resubscribe to OaR Uncut itself - for some reason, it seems like the addon priority for Black Mesa is that <span class="bbcode-i">older</span> addons take priority over <span class="bbcode-i">newer</span> ones.</p>
<p>To reiterate:<br>
Subscribing to Loop Mod while <span class="bbcode-i">already</span> subscribed to OaRU - game uses OaRU’s version of bm_c2a2a, and there are some missing textures at first (the one that comes to mind is the office window on the angled wall)<br>
Subscribing to Loop Mod, <span class="bbcode-i">then</span> subscribing to OaRU - game uses Loop Mod’s version of bm_c2a2a, no missing textures appear, <span class="bbcode-b">but</span> the game returns an error that it “can’t find a connection” between c2a2a and c2a2a1. Using the map command to go directly to c2a2a1 and onward shows that the rest of the chapter is using the OaRU content.</p>
<p>I don’t know how or why, but I suspect the missing texture issue is fixed by subscribing to OaRU <span class="bbcode-i">after</span> Loop Mod - from there, it doesn’t seem to matter what “order” they’re in.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/oar-loop-mod/12153/284">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/oar-loop-mod/12153/284</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 07 Feb 2016 22:20:21 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12153-284</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/oar-loop-mod/12153.rss">OaR - Loop Mod</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>OaR - Loop Mod</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[RK1]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I’m not quite sure what’s going on. Everything works perfectly fine on my machine. Can anyone show me some pictures of what is going on (the missing textures, I mean)?</p>
<p>Just for clarification, did all of you <span class="bbcode-u">unsubscribe</span> from the stock version of Loop Mod? You should have only the OARU version of Loop Mod if you have both of them.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/oar-loop-mod/12153/283">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/oar-loop-mod/12153/283</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 07 Feb 2016 21:57:30 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12153-283</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/oar-loop-mod/12153.rss">OaR - Loop Mod</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>OaR - Loop Mod</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Anevist]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>You know how to fix OAR Loop Mod textures ?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/oar-loop-mod/12153/282">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/oar-loop-mod/12153/282</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 07 Feb 2016 10:46:50 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12153-282</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/oar-loop-mod/12153.rss">OaR - Loop Mod</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>OaR - Loop Mod</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[KyuuGryphon]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Someone commented on the Workshop that the OaRU version’s not working for them - I went to try it myself, and I’m getting the same issue.</p>
<p>The game is still using the “stock” (OaRU version, I guess?) version of the first map, and there are missing textures everywhere. I don’t suppose anyone knows if there’s some way to set addon priority to fix this?</p>
<p>EDIT: Wait, fixed it - resubscribing to OaRU made things work again. Never mind!</p>
<p>EDIT2: Or not… Finishing the first map kicks me back to the main menu because it can’t find a connection.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/oar-loop-mod/12153/281">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/oar-loop-mod/12153/281</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 07 Feb 2016 05:37:59 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12153-281</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/oar-loop-mod/12153.rss">OaR - Loop Mod</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>OaR - Loop Mod</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[RK1]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="KevinJRattman">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/k/53a042/40.png" class="avatar"> KevinJRattman:</div>
<blockquote>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username=".RK">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 .RK:</div>
<blockquote></blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I don’t think renaming map files would help. For example, current Loop Mod thinks the maps are in A - B - C order, while Uncut thinks A - B - C - D - E - F - G. So first when the map transist from A to B it’s fine, but next it would go from B to C (as in Uncut) and then D… which should be B, because Loop mod thinks so. So conflict would still occur. I could be wrong here tho.<br>
-snip</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I do assert that it would work, and would be as simple as using entspy, renaming the files, and rebuilding cubemaps. Wouldn’t take too long, but it’s not something I should demand for either.</p>
<p>So with that said: <span class="bbcode-b">The OARU Version of Loop Mod is now on the workshop.</span></p>
<p>You can find it here: <a href="https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=617825144" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=617825144</a></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/oar-loop-mod/12153/280">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/oar-loop-mod/12153/280</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 06 Feb 2016 22:04:14 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12153-280</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/oar-loop-mod/12153.rss">OaR - Loop Mod</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>OaR - Loop Mod</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Caligula]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username=".RK">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 .RK:</div>
<blockquote>
<ol>
<li>Make a separate workshop download for an OARU-compatible version of Loop Mod. I’m more loathe of this option because it can cause a bit of a hassle for people, but it would make the game playable for certain.</li>
</ol>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>This is the best solution for sure. Incompatibility between steam OaRU and Loop mod is basically what stopping me to try full On a Rail Experience on steam.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/oar-loop-mod/12153/279">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/oar-loop-mod/12153/279</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 28 Jan 2016 14:52:59 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12153-279</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/oar-loop-mod/12153.rss">OaR - Loop Mod</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>OaR - Loop Mod</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[KevinJRattman]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username=".RK">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 .RK:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Howdy all!</p>
<p>So as most of you probably know by now, On a Rail Uncut has appeared on the workshop, Hot damn is that exciting, because we’re one step closer to having the entirety of the original game remade. By my counts, there’s only one more major release left, and we all know which one that is, but that’s for another time!</p>
<p>I’m bumping this because of a development which, quite frankly, I foresaw a long while ago but never really had any idea on how to approach it.</p>
<p>I foresaw two things happening once both this and Uncut were on the workshop:</p>
<ol>
<li>Uncut would completely override Loop Mod and Loop Mod would straight up fail to appear during a campaign or</li>
<li>The level transitions would need some working around, much like the mod version did.</li>
</ol>
<p>Thankfully, number one is not an issue at all, which is a happy relief. At least, on my machine, it appears that way. The other, however, is still a potent issue that prevents both mods from co-existing. For those unaware, Source handles transitions through a sort-of handshake system; when you use trigger_changelevels like Black Mesa does, both maps must reference each other (so the A map must reference the B map, and vice versa). So currently, with both mods installed, you will encounter Loop Mod <span class="bbcode-i">first</span>. After riding the elevator to the top and reaching the turret trap, the current steam workshop of Loop Mod will then try to take you to the B map (which contains offices + rocket silo). HOWEVER, with Uncut installed, the B map links back to an A2 map instead of A, and since this violates Source rules, it’ll instead deposit you on the main menu.</p>
<p>Again, I’m unsure how to go about this. There exists a solution but it is completely out of my hands. So I am actively pursuing two alternatives:</p>
<ol>
<li>Find a way to detect if a map exists and if so, place two changelevels into the map and disable one of them depending on whether or not Uncut exists. I was going to learn vscripts for this but logic_scripts don’t exist in BM, so alternatives would be good.</li>
<li>Make a separate workshop download for an OARU-compatible version of Loop Mod. I’m more loathe of this option because it can cause a bit of a hassle for people, but it would make the game playable for certain.</li>
</ol>
<p>Ideas are appreciated!</p>
<p>That said, Chon, if you’re reading this, what are the prospects of throwing some renames over those maps so that, for example, A1 is B, A2 is C, and so on and so forth? That would put the issue (both issues above in fact!) to bed for good.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I don’t think renaming map files would help. For example, current Loop Mod thinks the maps are in A - B - C order, while Uncut thinks A - B - C - D - E - F - G. So first when the map transist from A to B it’s fine, but next it would go from B to C (as in Uncut) and then D… which should be B, because Loop mod thinks so. So conflict would still occur. I could be wrong here tho.</p>
<p>Beside, I extremely doubt if Chon would take his time and edit the mod he practically abandoned. I saw some bugs in the mod and people were reporting bugs in the thread too, but he’s not even replied to them.</p>
<p>So, the best and the most straight solution would be to just make a separate compatible version. I honestely don’t think it would be that hassle to people. Just be sure to mention if it’s compatible or not both in the title and in the description. Also, put links for both version in the description so that people can easily navigate from version to version.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/oar-loop-mod/12153/278">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/oar-loop-mod/12153/278</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jan 2016 05:23:05 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12153-278</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/oar-loop-mod/12153.rss">OaR - Loop Mod</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>OaR - Loop Mod</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[RK1]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Howdy all!</p>
<p>So as most of you probably know by now, On a Rail Uncut has appeared on the workshop, Hot damn is that exciting, because we’re one step closer to having the entirety of the original game remade. By my counts, there’s only one more major release left, and we all know which one that is, but that’s for another time!</p>
<p>I’m bumping this because of a development which, quite frankly, I foresaw a long while ago but never really had any idea on how to approach it.</p>
<p>I foresaw two things happening once both this and Uncut were on the workshop:</p>
<ol>
<li>Uncut would completely override Loop Mod and Loop Mod would straight up fail to appear during a campaign or</li>
<li>The level transitions would need some working around, much like the mod version did.</li>
</ol>
<p>Thankfully, number one is not an issue at all, which is a happy relief. At least, on my machine, it appears that way. The other, however, is still a potent issue that prevents both mods from co-existing. For those unaware, Source handles transitions through a sort-of handshake system; when you use trigger_changelevels like Black Mesa does, both maps must reference each other (so the A map must reference the B map, and vice versa). So currently, with both mods installed, you will encounter Loop Mod <span class="bbcode-i">first</span>. After riding the elevator to the top and reaching the turret trap, the current steam workshop of Loop Mod will then try to take you to the B map (which contains offices + rocket silo). HOWEVER, with Uncut installed, the B map links back to an A2 map instead of A, and since this violates Source rules, it’ll instead deposit you on the main menu.</p>
<p>Again, I’m unsure how to go about this. There exists a solution but it is completely out of my hands. So I am actively pursuing two alternatives:</p>
<ol>
<li>Find a way to detect if a map exists and if so, place two changelevels into the map and disable one of them depending on whether or not Uncut exists. I was going to learn vscripts for this but logic_scripts don’t exist in BM, so alternatives would be good.</li>
<li>Make a separate workshop download for an OARU-compatible version of Loop Mod. I’m more loathe of this option because it can cause a bit of a hassle for people, but it would make the game playable for certain.</li>
</ol>
<p>Ideas are appreciated!</p>
<p>That said, Chon, if you’re reading this, what are the prospects of throwing some renames over those maps so that, for example, A1 is B, A2 is C, and so on and so forth? That would put the issue (both issues above in fact!) to bed for good.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/oar-loop-mod/12153/277">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/oar-loop-mod/12153/277</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 25 Jan 2016 22:15:01 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12153-277</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/oar-loop-mod/12153.rss">OaR - Loop Mod</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>OaR - Loop Mod</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Mr_GameCrazy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>It would be great if the workshop version of On a Rail Uncut worked like that.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/oar-loop-mod/12153/276">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/oar-loop-mod/12153/276</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 May 2015 22:45:26 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12153-276</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/oar-loop-mod/12153.rss">OaR - Loop Mod</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>OaR - Loop Mod</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[RK1]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Ignore this post!</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/oar-loop-mod/12153/275">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/oar-loop-mod/12153/275</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 May 2015 22:41:28 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12153-275</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/oar-loop-mod/12153.rss">OaR - Loop Mod</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>OaR - Loop Mod</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[KyuuGryphon]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>To be honest, I’m not entirely sure on that. There’s a file called “addonlist.txt” in the root folder, and I <span class="bbcode-i">think</span> the priority is from top-to-bottom? I haven’t really experimented with it much, tbh.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/oar-loop-mod/12153/274">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/oar-loop-mod/12153/274</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 May 2015 22:27:03 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12153-274</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/oar-loop-mod/12153.rss">OaR - Loop Mod</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>OaR - Loop Mod</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Mr_GameCrazy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>How does L4D2 check which has a higher priority?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/oar-loop-mod/12153/273">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/oar-loop-mod/12153/273</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 May 2015 22:22:33 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12153-273</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/oar-loop-mod/12153.rss">OaR - Loop Mod</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>OaR - Loop Mod</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[KyuuGryphon]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I dunno if Black Mesa has it already, but for L4D2 at least, there’s a “load order” for VPKs. If any files conflict between them, whichever is higher priority is used.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/oar-loop-mod/12153/272">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/oar-loop-mod/12153/272</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 May 2015 22:20:38 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12153-272</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/oar-loop-mod/12153.rss">OaR - Loop Mod</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>OaR - Loop Mod</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Mr_GameCrazy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Pauolo">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/p/eada6e/40.png" class="avatar"> Pauolo:</div>
<blockquote>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Mr. GameCrazy">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Mr. GameCrazy:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I like both Loop Mod and On a Rail Uncut. I usually play through On a Rail with both mods. I think the way it will work for both mods to work properly with Steam Workshop is that they both have to be combined as one mod due to both mods using different versions of the first On a Rail map (RK’s Loop Mod map and the stock map modified to transition to Text’s A1 map).</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I think it would be easier to upload the mod twice: one version for Black Mesa only and the other compatible with OaR Uncut.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>It would, but my concern is that the A map in Text’s mod and the A map in RK’s mod could conflict with each other.</p>
<p>That’s why I think it would be great if both mods were combined into one workshop mod for anyone who wants to play both mods.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/oar-loop-mod/12153/271">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/oar-loop-mod/12153/271</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 May 2015 22:18:13 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12153-271</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/oar-loop-mod/12153.rss">OaR - Loop Mod</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>OaR - Loop Mod</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Pauolo]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Mr. GameCrazy">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Mr. GameCrazy:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I like both Loop Mod and On a Rail Uncut. I usually play through On a Rail with both mods. I think the way it will work for both mods to work properly with Steam Workshop is that they both have to be combined as one mod due to both mods using different versions of the first On a Rail map (RK’s Loop Mod map and the stock map modified to transition to Text’s A1 map).</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I think it would be easier to upload the mod twice: one version for Black Mesa only and the other compatible with OaR Uncut.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/oar-loop-mod/12153/270">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/oar-loop-mod/12153/270</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 May 2015 22:15:25 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12153-270</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/oar-loop-mod/12153.rss">OaR - Loop Mod</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>OaR - Loop Mod</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Mr_GameCrazy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I like both Loop Mod and On a Rail Uncut. I usually play through On a Rail with both mods. I think the way it will work for both mods to work properly with Steam Workshop is that they both have to be combined as one mod due to both mods using different versions of the first On a Rail map (RK’s Loop Mod map and the stock map modified to transition to Text’s A1 map).</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/oar-loop-mod/12153/269">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/oar-loop-mod/12153/269</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 May 2015 21:58:11 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12153-269</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/oar-loop-mod/12153.rss">OaR - Loop Mod</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>OaR - Loop Mod</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Pauolo]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="RageMaker">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/r/e274bd/40.png" class="avatar"> RageMaker:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Gotta say I’m liking this simple change, makes the map a bit more like a system rather than a 1-way rail. Next up should be OAR uncut when that is released on retail edition</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>This chapter sure looks good with both mods.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/oar-loop-mod/12153/268">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/oar-loop-mod/12153/268</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 May 2015 21:46:06 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12153-268</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/oar-loop-mod/12153.rss">OaR - Loop Mod</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
