<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Game cant start for second time</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/game-cant-start-for-second-time/14192</link>
    <description>Hi, first of all let me tell you that your registration, verification and authentication process, is terrible, but lets go to the point...

I buyed Black Mesa in Steam, and I played it, I stoped and closed the game using the exit function of the game, it told me to save my progress and I saved it, didnt rebooted the machine, and I thought I would be able to play again, executing 2 times a game isnt an advanced issue, but it seems that this game, exactly the bms.exe file, doesnt want to leave me, even closing the game, and the task manager cant close it as well, steam wont close with a game &quot;running&quot;, and wont execute it 2 times, so I will have to restart my system in order to play black mesa again, I use Windows 8.1 Pro 64, If you need any specification let me know it, thanks for reading.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 13 Jun 2015 11:42:02 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>In-game Issues</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/game-cant-start-for-second-time/14192.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Game cant start for second time</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[wrkq]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>If after closing the game you can see bms.exe still running in task manager, the game did not close correctly.</p>
<p>And if you cannot kill the process with Task Manager, then something is seriously screwed up.<br>
The only time when you can’t kill a process that you started yourself is when it is stuck in the Windows kernel.</p>
<p>Just to verify, as Win 8.x renamed things in very confusing way:<br>
You need to expand “more details” at bottom, then click Details at top, find bms.exe and use End Task button on this tab to try forcible killing process.<br>
The tab named “Processes” is actually showing you application windows, and the “End Task” button on that tab is a bit more “gentle”, asking the program to close.</p>
<p>But anyway, if “End Task” on the Details tab fails to kill the process, (does it “not say anything” on first try, and then gives you “access denied” error when you try again?), it’s stuck in kernel.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-u">Update your drivers</span> (especially GPU and the often overlooked audio).</p>
<p>If it’s not the drivers, your Windows installation is somehow corrupted/infected.</p>
<p>Good luck.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/game-cant-start-for-second-time/14192/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/game-cant-start-for-second-time/14192/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jun 2015 11:42:02 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14192-2</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/game-cant-start-for-second-time/14192.rss">Game cant start for second time</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Game cant start for second time</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Lancro]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Hi, first of all let me tell you that your registration, verification and authentication process, is terrible, but lets go to the point…</p>
<p>I buyed Black Mesa in Steam, and I played it, I stoped and closed the game using the exit function of the game, it told me to save my progress and I saved it, didnt rebooted the machine, and I thought I would be able to play again, executing 2 times a game isnt an advanced issue, but it seems that this game, exactly the bms.exe file, doesnt want to leave me, even closing the game, and the task manager cant close it as well, steam wont close with a game “running”, and wont execute it 2 times, so I will have to restart my system in order to play black mesa again, I use Windows 8.1 Pro 64, If you need any specification let me know it, thanks for reading.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/game-cant-start-for-second-time/14192/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/game-cant-start-for-second-time/14192/1</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jun 2015 19:42:44 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14192-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/game-cant-start-for-second-time/14192.rss">Game cant start for second time</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
