<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Black Mesa will not launch!!!</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/black-mesa-will-not-launch/11213</link>
    <description>So, I downloaded Black Mesa through Desura (I also have steam, so this will not be the problem), and it is on my laptop. I have Black Mesa on another laptop (that I also used Desura to download it) and it runs, but at a choppy frame rate because its video card &amp; proccesor is crap. However, on this laptop it should not have any problems because my graphics card is better, its not an extremely powerful graphics card, but when I launch the game its goes to a black screen, then it kicks me out! I&#39;ve tried several things like updating my graphics drivers, setting my launch properties to    -safe, and even installing Black Mesa and Source SDK Base 2007 again, but its still not working. I hate going to my other laptop to play the game because its performance is so unbearable, but if someone has any ideas to what is going on it would help, and I need something good. Because I&#39;ve read other threads and those answers aren&#39;t helping my problems.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 01 Oct 2012 08:49:34 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>In-game Issues (Mod)</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/black-mesa-will-not-launch/11213.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Black Mesa will not launch!!!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Leijonasisu]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Would you mind explaining what fixed it?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/black-mesa-will-not-launch/11213/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/black-mesa-will-not-launch/11213/3</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 Oct 2012 08:49:34 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11213-3</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/black-mesa-will-not-launch/11213.rss">Black Mesa will not launch!!!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Black Mesa will not launch!!!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[sonicnerd16]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I figured out my problem, so never mind!!! For any of you who may have had answers, thanks any ways!</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/black-mesa-will-not-launch/11213/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/black-mesa-will-not-launch/11213/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 30 Sep 2012 23:24:15 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11213-2</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/black-mesa-will-not-launch/11213.rss">Black Mesa will not launch!!!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Black Mesa will not launch!!!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[sonicnerd16]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>So, I downloaded Black Mesa through Desura (I also have steam, so this will not be the problem), and it is on my laptop. I have Black Mesa on another laptop (that I also used Desura to download it) and it runs, but at a choppy frame rate because its video card &amp; proccesor is crap. However, on this laptop it should not have any problems because my graphics card is better, its not an extremely powerful graphics card, but when I launch the game its goes to a black screen, then it kicks me out! I’ve tried several things like updating my graphics drivers, setting my launch properties to    -safe, and even installing Black Mesa and Source SDK Base 2007 again, but its still not working. I hate going to my other laptop to play the game because its performance is so unbearable, but if someone has any ideas to what is going on it would help, and I need something good. Because I’ve read other threads and those answers aren’t helping my problems.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/black-mesa-will-not-launch/11213/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/black-mesa-will-not-launch/11213/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 29 Sep 2012 22:56:48 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11213-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/black-mesa-will-not-launch/11213.rss">Black Mesa will not launch!!!</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
