<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Anyone for Philopitty? Navel-gazers welcome!</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/anyone-for-philopitty-navel-gazers-welcome/2006</link>
    <description>Since the [url=&#39;https://forums.blackmesasource.com/showthread.php?t=1965&#39;]&quot;French Don&#39;t Like Scientology&quot;[/url] thread became a little derailed, I thought it might be an idea to start a philosophical rant thread so that we didn&#39;t get told off for wanton thread hi-jackery!

Only rules are that we keep it civil and stop circular arguing after four or five ripostes with a &quot;let&#39;s agree to disagree&quot; and start something new.  :smiley: 

Starter topic for 10.... is there such a thing as luck, chance or probability (since that was where the topic hi-jacking really got going!)...
[quote=&quot;ijgs&quot;]
Soup, my dear fellow, I&#39;m going to have to correct you when you say:it should really be:1 in 10,000,000 chances occur at a rate of about 40,000 per second on this planet, if not more frequently (taking every living creature&#39;s procreation into account). &quot;Chance&quot; and &quot;luck&quot; are observed to have happened every day; people die, people are born, accidents are had and avoided and so on. What happens is:
1) &quot;event&quot; 
2) we respond
3) ????
4) profi... ahem... in hindsight, we consider the initial event to be &quot;lucky&quot; or &quot;unlucky&quot;, depending on how well we came out of it all.

Luck &amp; chance are mere human rationalisations of ongoing chaos, NOT influencing factors [i]on[/i] that chaos. Events either happen or do not happen, there really isn&#39;t any grey area (oh, and insurance is a massive con as a result!).
[/quote]

[quote=&quot;Soup&quot;]
You&#39;re misunderstanding me there, ijgs. Like I said, chance is just probability of an event: I didn&#39;t say luck, or fortune or any other personified influence was involved. 

I disagree that chance/probability is a feeble attempt at rationalising chaos: I think it rationalises it pretty damn well. It&#39;s a model we use to predict the likelihood of events in the chaos that is the universe, nothing more, nothing less. It can&#39;t be feeble or strong: like mathematics, it just [i]is[/i]. 

To be honest, I don&#39;t see what you were actually objecting to in my post.
[/quote]

[quote=&quot;Soviet&quot;]
The human model of luck/probability matches it, but not well. It simply substitutes millions of minute influences that we can&#39;t begin to calculate (or don&#39;t care enough to) with a simple mathematical expression to predict certain outcomes. While we may describe them as occurring by chance, we simply don&#39;t have the time, want to put in the effort, or simply can&#39;t with our current technology define when and where these events will occur.
[/quote]

[quote=&quot;Soup&quot;]
My point is that whatever happens, there&#39;s a probability for it. You have a probability for your racehorse to win. However, all of it&#39;s molecules could vibrate in the same direction, sending into the sky at 500m/s: this isn&#39;t accounted for because the chance is so minute.

The probability model works the majority of the time, and that&#39;s what it aims for. If we could define when and where events will occur, it wouldn&#39;t be probability.
[/quote]
Fire at will!  :smiley:</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 16 Dec 2009 01:54:54 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Off Topic</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/anyone-for-philopitty-navel-gazers-welcome/2006.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Anyone for Philopitty? Navel-gazers welcome!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[ijgs]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="baconeggs">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/b/43a26b/40.png" class="avatar"> baconeggs:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>If you’ve ever seen the film Soylent Green you’ll understand.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I have indeed and I do! The Harry Harrison book “Make Room! Make Room!” on which it’s based is a much better story though and doesn’t have Charlton Heston giving himself splinters and going “NOOOOOOOOOO” (again!!)  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/smiley.png?v=9" title=":smiley:" class="emoji" alt=":smiley:"></p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="SassyRobot">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 SassyRobot:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I’d take the money and I find it hard to believe anyone wouldn’t, frankly.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I’d take the money, but it’d have to be a <span class="bbcode-i">lot</span> closer to a billion. Everyone’s got a price and I’m suprisingly avaricious, in spite of myself!  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=9" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="GreyRaven">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/g/aeb1de/40.png" class="avatar"> GreyRaven:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Where then, do your interpretations come from?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>My interpretations are born out of my reactions to the effects of my choices; these interpretations are constantly re-evaluated as time goes by - sometimes resulting in my initial interpretation being totally inverted, but that’s the nature of the beast. Where possible, I take the long view on my life and my choices, accepting that views can change as I mature. This “choice” (and indeed, all of the choices I make) can only be relevant to me, as can my perception and interpretation of choice. I accept that this <span class="bbcode-i">might</span> be a cop out. However it’s 0120hrs and I’m not really in the mood for deep thought!  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/smiley.png?v=9" title=":smiley:" class="emoji" alt=":smiley:"></p>
<p>In the light of that, I’m going to paraphrase your quote a little, apologies!</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="GreyRaven">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/g/aeb1de/40.png" class="avatar"> GreyRaven:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Perhaps you are right […] but this does not exclude the necessity of choosing.  However unimportant it may be, it is not possible to not choose.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I believe that the only negative choice is the choice of inaction, “yes I will” or “no I will not” are both positive, active choices. I also didn’t say ANYTHING about choice not being necessary, only that your choices are yours alone and that each choice informs subsequent choices</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="GreyRaven">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/g/aeb1de/40.png" class="avatar"> GreyRaven:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>That said, even if every choice is emergent, decision making is not.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Semantics much? surely a decision is a choice by another name? If, as I suspect, this is true, the rest of your rebuttal is rendered somewhat less potent!  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/wink.png?v=9" title=":wink:" class="emoji" alt=":wink:"></p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="GreyRaven">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/g/aeb1de/40.png" class="avatar"> GreyRaven:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Our decisions are necessarily formed based on our continual reactions to our environment.  Cause and effect.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Which is pretty much what I said, only I used the word “choice” instead of “decision”…</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="GreyRaven">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/g/aeb1de/40.png" class="avatar"> GreyRaven:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Psychologically speaking, our reactions stem from a complex series of chemically induced electrical signals in the brain.  Learning is nothing more than chemical reactions which are by themselves governed by predictable physical laws.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Surely you mean physiologically, not psychologically? Psychologically speaking, our reactions stem from our experiential history, not from chemicals. Learning is the ingraining &amp; formation of neuron signal paths as a result of those chemical reactions, which may or may not be governed by predictable physical laws - it is conceivable that our brain has a significant quantum aspect, which (for the moment) renders such prediction uncertain. Anyhow, both of these are interesting, but irrelevant to my stance that predetermination doesn’t exist.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="GreyRaven">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/g/aeb1de/40.png" class="avatar"> GreyRaven:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>While predetermination typically assumes that the guiding hand of fate has ordered the course of our lives, the fundamental principle of causality is difficult to argue with given the ordered nature of the world we live in.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>If one takes an existentialist viewpoint though (and I tend in that direction), the universe is chaos and not a neatly ordered thing. Given sufficient chaos a pattern (and therefore order) can be inferred, whether or not it exists. My interpretation of that chaos (and the pattern that I appear to see in it) is purely that, my <span class="bbcode-i">interpretation</span>. The chaos still exists, but my experience of it informs my interpretation of it. Thus the universe doesn’t have to conform to a causal model. I’m stopping now as it’s 0150hrs and I have to go to SLEEEEEEP!  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/smiley.png?v=9" title=":smiley:" class="emoji" alt=":smiley:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/anyone-for-philopitty-navel-gazers-welcome/2006/45">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/anyone-for-philopitty-navel-gazers-welcome/2006/45</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 16 Dec 2009 01:54:54 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2006-45</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/anyone-for-philopitty-navel-gazers-welcome/2006.rss">Anyone for Philopitty? Navel-gazers welcome!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Anyone for Philopitty? Navel-gazers welcome!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Someonerandm]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Soup">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/s/977dab/40.png" class="avatar"> Soup:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>My point was that that guy was saying he’d spend <span class="bbcode-i">half</span> of the money he got from killing someone to help others.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I said I was messing around. My real answers two pages back.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/anyone-for-philopitty-navel-gazers-welcome/2006/44">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/anyone-for-philopitty-navel-gazers-welcome/2006/44</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 15 Dec 2009 15:44:34 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2006-44</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/anyone-for-philopitty-navel-gazers-welcome/2006.rss">Anyone for Philopitty? Navel-gazers welcome!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Anyone for Philopitty? Navel-gazers welcome!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[GreyRaven]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="ijgs">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/i/5fc32e/40.png" class="avatar"> ijgs:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Each choice made is the alpha and omega, there is no “origin choice” that led to where I am today because all choice emerges from our interpretation of our environment.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Where then, do your interpretations come from?</p>
<p>In an effort to avoid being Socratic I’ll simply say that my argument here is that ‘choice’, be it an illusion or otherwise, is in practice a conscious or unconscious ‘act’ of decision making.  As Pascal argued, you cannot ‘not choose’.  There are no non-choices or non-actions, for even if you choose inaction, you have still chosen.  This is meaningful here because you are suggesting that the act of choosing is less important than our interpretations of that choice’s outcomes.  Perhaps you are right, as those interpretations are what will influence our future decision making, rather than the act of choosing itself, but this does not exclude the necessity of choosing.  However unimportant it may be, it is not possible to not choose.</p>
<p>That said, even if every choice is emergent, decision making is not.  We are pattern recognition machines, we are construct formers, and we name things and define them in order to construct the illusion of a more recognizable ordered environment.  Our decisions are necessarily formed based on our continual reactions to our environment.  Cause and effect.  Psychologically speaking, our reactions stem from a complex series of chemically induced electrical signals in the brain.  Learning is nothing more than chemical reactions which are by themselves governed by predictable physical laws.</p>
<p>While predetermination typically assumes that the guiding hand of fate has ordered the course of our lives, the fundamental principle of causality is difficult to argue with given the ordered nature of the world we live in.  Consequently, if all decision are made based on your interpretation of past events, and all your interpretations are fundamentally nothing more than predictable chemical signals, then all your decisions are governed by the laws of physics.</p>
<p>Granted, it would be nice if things were more complicated than that, if our decisions were more than just physics.  But, even if they are, my point is that they are still rooted in the physical world, and are still governed by an ordered environment.  Even if we cannot know how or why, the reality is that without causality, we are left with nothing but chaos.  Without basing your choices on prior experience, without cause and effect, you would be just as likely to choose to fly as you would choose to cross the street.  There would be no reason or method to any choice.  But even then, by nature of simply being a human, your choices would still the result of complex chemical reactions.</p>
<p>As well, much effort has been made to study the formation of the brain, and it is entirely probable, if not definitely proven, that the brain is always in a state of change, and its changes are dependent upon both its environment and the genetic map encoded into an individuals DNA.  Thus, even its physical structure is, at any given moment, a result of past experience.  Cause and effect.</p>
<p>While you may argue that predetermination does not exist, and I would be inclined to agree considering what it implies, I would argue that you have not yet disproved Causality.</p>
<p>I rather enjoy this subject, but if you are all looking for a new one, I might have a suggestion that is a bit of a brain teaser.  A number of years ago, the academic community at large decided that “Time”, even as a human notion, was a fundamental aspect of our existence, just like space.  Consequently, they argued, Time itself exists in the same way space “exists” dimensionally.  They concluded that for anything which exists, it must exist at a given time.  So we have the first dimension, which is a point, the second, which is a series of points that form a line (and any number of lines can form a plane), the third, in which a series of planes stacked on top of each other create depth, and the fourth, which is ‘time’.</p>
<p>I have a rather reasonable argument which potentially disproves the notion that time can exist as a dimension, and should you all be interested in this topic I would like to hear your thoughts.</p>
<p>I’m more than happy to continue on the subject of Choice and Luck though, even if it seems we’ve left “Luck” to its own devices at this point.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/anyone-for-philopitty-navel-gazers-welcome/2006/43">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/anyone-for-philopitty-navel-gazers-welcome/2006/43</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 15 Dec 2009 14:15:36 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2006-43</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/anyone-for-philopitty-navel-gazers-welcome/2006.rss">Anyone for Philopitty? Navel-gazers welcome!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Anyone for Philopitty? Navel-gazers welcome!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Soup]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>My point was that that guy was saying he’d spend <span class="bbcode-i">half</span> of the money he got from killing someone to help others.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/anyone-for-philopitty-navel-gazers-welcome/2006/42">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/anyone-for-philopitty-navel-gazers-welcome/2006/42</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 15 Dec 2009 13:24:09 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2006-42</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/anyone-for-philopitty-navel-gazers-welcome/2006.rss">Anyone for Philopitty? Navel-gazers welcome!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Anyone for Philopitty? Navel-gazers welcome!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Brother_Shrike]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><span class="mention">@bacon</span> - I agree completely - if only we weren’t so damned close-minded…</p>
<p>also, soylent green is made of people.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/anyone-for-philopitty-navel-gazers-welcome/2006/41">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/anyone-for-philopitty-navel-gazers-welcome/2006/41</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 15 Dec 2009 01:52:49 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2006-41</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/anyone-for-philopitty-navel-gazers-welcome/2006.rss">Anyone for Philopitty? Navel-gazers welcome!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Anyone for Philopitty? Navel-gazers welcome!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[ijgs]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>[edit] nothing to see here, this isn’t the post you were looking for, move along (bloodyforumplayingupagainmuttercursegrumble)</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/anyone-for-philopitty-navel-gazers-welcome/2006/40">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/anyone-for-philopitty-navel-gazers-welcome/2006/40</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 15 Dec 2009 01:42:22 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2006-40</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/anyone-for-philopitty-navel-gazers-welcome/2006.rss">Anyone for Philopitty? Navel-gazers welcome!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Anyone for Philopitty? Navel-gazers welcome!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[baconeggs]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Euthanasia aye? My view is always that it is not murder. I’ll just lay down a few arguments.</p>
<ol>
<li>
<p>Technically murder is the forceful taking of someone’s life against their will. Euthansia is different in that the victim wishes to die and is asking for assistance in this endevour. Therefore it is not murder on logical grounds.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>It can be said that euthanasia encourages people to die because the assistant is doing nothing to prevent it. This is not true, the choice to die is entirely up to the victim. As this is their own life they must make their own decisions as to what to do with it. I think preventing suicide should only apply to minors, who don’t have the percieved responsibility to make desicions like that. However, once you’re 18 you should be free to do what you want.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Euthanasia is much better than stand-alone suicide as the chance for success is increased. People trying to kill themselves along can often stuff it up, leaving them severely injured and disabled but not dead, as well as hyper depressed. Personally I’d rather be dead.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Finally, euthanasia is actually a viable option in this day and age. Humans are extremely overpopulated and this planet isn’t big enough to support us. As bad as it may sound, letting people kill themselves may do a great deal of good in the long run. If you’ve ever seen the film Soylent Green you’ll understand.</p>
</li>
</ol>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/anyone-for-philopitty-navel-gazers-welcome/2006/39">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/anyone-for-philopitty-navel-gazers-welcome/2006/39</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 14 Dec 2009 23:40:36 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2006-39</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/anyone-for-philopitty-navel-gazers-welcome/2006.rss">Anyone for Philopitty? Navel-gazers welcome!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Anyone for Philopitty? Navel-gazers welcome!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[ijgs]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I’ll welcome any further personal opinions though! Given that that’s how people form their opinions, by sharing them and “seeing what fits”  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=9" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"> .</p>
<p>Hmmm, next up? Did we get to the bottom of the euthanasia is murder thing (or is that just too tired for words?! haha!)? Failing that, erm… I’m out of ideas right now, 'sbeen a hard day and not enough caffeine!! I’ll have a think, unless anyone else has some juicy suggestions!</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/anyone-for-philopitty-navel-gazers-welcome/2006/38">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/anyone-for-philopitty-navel-gazers-welcome/2006/38</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 14 Dec 2009 23:20:25 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2006-38</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/anyone-for-philopitty-navel-gazers-welcome/2006.rss">Anyone for Philopitty? Navel-gazers welcome!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Anyone for Philopitty? Navel-gazers welcome!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[baconeggs]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Well, that kind of closes that argument. What next gentlemen?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/anyone-for-philopitty-navel-gazers-welcome/2006/37">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/anyone-for-philopitty-navel-gazers-welcome/2006/37</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 14 Dec 2009 22:52:40 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2006-37</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/anyone-for-philopitty-navel-gazers-welcome/2006.rss">Anyone for Philopitty? Navel-gazers welcome!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Anyone for Philopitty? Navel-gazers welcome!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[ijgs]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Some nicely made points there, I’ll see if my debating skills hold up to them!!  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/smiley.png?v=9" title=":smiley:" class="emoji" alt=":smiley:"></p>
<p>Yes, I concede that all the choices that I have made up to this point in my life will strongly tend to inform and shape any future choices that I make. To that extent (and that extent alone, in my personal opinion - and when all’s said and done, this can only ever be personal opinion really, since we’re not able to step outside of the box and gain an objective viewpoint) “predetermination” exists. A better word for it though is “learning”! When bad choices are made, we learn to avoid making them again; equally when good choices are made, we will tend to try and apply that knowledge again in the future. Is “learning” the same as “predetermination”? Predetermination implicitly suggests a prior arrangement of the events &amp; choices of your life, rather than reactions <span class="bbcode-i">to</span> events &amp; choices <span class="bbcode-i">in</span> your life.</p>
<p>Whether the choices (and the events that they lead to) are good or bad is only really discovered after they have been made. Sure you can apply previous experience to your choices and try to model likely outcomes (something else humans are very good at), but until you’ve made the choice and have gone through with it you can’t be <span class="bbcode-i">sure</span> of the outcome - at least, I’ve never been truly sure of many of my choices (for sure, jumping off a building’s a bit of a no-brainer, 6’ walls hurt, 500’ buildings will likely do more than just hurt - but you get my drift!). Some of the “best” choices I’ve made have been the ones that really hurt at the time; it’s only with eagle-eye hindsight that I know that to be true though.</p>
<p>I would argue that choice is a one-way emergent function. You can’t see past the choice you’re about to make and once you’ve made the choice, you can’t know what the outcome would have been if you’ve chosen a different option. However the emergent outcome is deemed “good” or “bad” based on our interpretation <span class="bbcode-i">of</span> it; i.e. it causes a reaction. By this interpretation one <span class="bbcode-i">could</span> view the choices of our lives as the “cause” and our reactions to these choices as the “effect”.</p>
<p>In my personal opinion (and this is born out of my personal experience) it doesn’t matter too much <span class="bbcode-i">WHAT</span> you chose - aside, perhaps, from fatal outcomes - it’s how you <span class="bbcode-i">reacted <span class="bbcode-b">to</span></span> the outcome that matters. Ergo, choice is a perceived phenomenon, rather than an actual one and therefore doesn’t have any “real” existence (and if it does, it’s not in the way that we understand it). Equally, fate or predetermination don’t exist in this model, since the choice was an emergent origin that led to a personal reaction, the sequence was constrained to the choice &amp; outcome. Each choice made is the alpha and omega, there is no “origin choice” that led to where I am today because all choice emerges from our interpretation of our environment.</p>
<p>I will add a caveat to this though; choices <span class="bbcode-i">are</span> (or can be) societally <span class="bbcode-i">influenced</span> by family, race, gender and so on. For example, I’m trying extremely hard to be an enlightened father to my kids, but I have no doubt that I’m passing at least some of my prejudices &amp; conceptions on to them. These will inevitably have some bearing on the choices they make; all things being equal though, I am not predetermining my children’s lives since they always have the choice to take another path. Granted there are parents out there who are very dogmatic or enforcing of their opinion. Even this more rigid constraint of opinion can be (and is) broken out of though, by people who realise that they are in control of their reactions, not anyone else.</p>
<p>Of course, this is all just my opinion; it holds true for me (so far, anyhow) and that’s probably all that anyone can honestly say.  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=9" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/anyone-for-philopitty-navel-gazers-welcome/2006/36">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/anyone-for-philopitty-navel-gazers-welcome/2006/36</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 14 Dec 2009 22:37:46 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2006-36</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/anyone-for-philopitty-navel-gazers-welcome/2006.rss">Anyone for Philopitty? Navel-gazers welcome!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Anyone for Philopitty? Navel-gazers welcome!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[GreyRaven]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>A question for you ijgs, as you’ve piqued my interest with this discussion.</p>
<p>How do you reconcile the concept of “free will” with an orderly universe?</p>
<p>Your action-reaction argument is unfortunately very ‘chicken-and-the-egg’ by nature, and ultimately offers no evidence to refute either predetermination or causality.  It merely suggests that the first action is unknown.  But even then every subsequent reaction, or effect, becomes a first cause for another.  A Reaction – Reaction chain is as causal as any Action – Reaction chain, and in fact demonstrates that your responses stem for prior causes themselves.</p>
<p>You’ve assumed that the freedom to choose between one action or another somehow undermines cause and effect, but the reality is that any choice will ultimately be the accumulated effect of any number of prior causes.  Consequently, without arguing that our choices are completely free from prior influences, then predetermination must exist.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/anyone-for-philopitty-navel-gazers-welcome/2006/35">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/anyone-for-philopitty-navel-gazers-welcome/2006/35</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 13 Dec 2009 19:04:45 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2006-35</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/anyone-for-philopitty-navel-gazers-welcome/2006.rss">Anyone for Philopitty? Navel-gazers welcome!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Anyone for Philopitty? Navel-gazers welcome!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[ijgs]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>right up to the point where the cleave your head with an AXE!!!</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/anyone-for-philopitty-navel-gazers-welcome/2006/34">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/anyone-for-philopitty-navel-gazers-welcome/2006/34</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 12 Dec 2009 23:56:05 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2006-34</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/anyone-for-philopitty-navel-gazers-welcome/2006.rss">Anyone for Philopitty? Navel-gazers welcome!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Anyone for Philopitty? Navel-gazers welcome!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[baconeggs]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Soviet">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/s/ecd19e/40.png" class="avatar"> Soviet:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Of course, this conclusion with emotion relies on the idea that emotion is in fact unpredictable, which to this point in our history has been proven time and time again by history itself.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Nonsense, if you know the person emotion is very predicatable.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/anyone-for-philopitty-navel-gazers-welcome/2006/33">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/anyone-for-philopitty-navel-gazers-welcome/2006/33</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2009 01:58:51 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2006-33</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/anyone-for-philopitty-navel-gazers-welcome/2006.rss">Anyone for Philopitty? Navel-gazers welcome!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Anyone for Philopitty? Navel-gazers welcome!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[ijgs]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>so basically it all comes down to my suggestion that it’s all about reaction, not action…</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/anyone-for-philopitty-navel-gazers-welcome/2006/32">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/anyone-for-philopitty-navel-gazers-welcome/2006/32</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2009 01:03:13 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2006-32</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/anyone-for-philopitty-navel-gazers-welcome/2006.rss">Anyone for Philopitty? Navel-gazers welcome!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Anyone for Philopitty? Navel-gazers welcome!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Soviet]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Someonerandm">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/s/d78d45/40.png" class="avatar"> Someonerandm:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Hey just thought of a metaphor (right word? I don’t know. English never has been my strongest subject) for that. Consider a choice to be a mathematical problem. Yes there is only one it can be answered (don’t get into higher level math, okay?), but you still have to go through the steps to solve it. When you make a choice, there is only one way to proceed, but you have to think to work that way out.</p>
<p>EDIT: Forgot to add the meaning of this. Essentially, the fact that you have to work it out means that you don’t know what to do, which means that this situation is new, which means that life can still surprise you, which is all you really need to know, whether or not you are predestined. So, in effect, who cares? It doesn’t affect how you live your life.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>That is assuming math is exactly the same as life, which would be quite an assumption. Ignoring the obvious flaws in math, one simply has to look at the application of math to see that the metaphor falls apart. Science, the application of math, has become separated into two parts, Newtonian and Quantum. One is completely predictable and relies on the math system we know and love, the other is shrouded in mystery and completely unpredictable.  Of course, one could argue that with further understanding of Quantum Mechanics it will become as predictable as gravity or magnetism. Fair enough.</p>
<p>Beyond this though, to say there is only one way to approach a mathematical problem isn’t true. In most math one can approach the solving of problems from all different directions, not just one. It is only in the most elementary math that the path you have to follow is set.</p>
<p>Beyond the metaphor, to suggest that there is one end point which is always arrived at by a singular choice implies that every action we take is weighed equally in our minds. However, I know for a fact that oftentimes I don’t even think before I do something, and equally sometimes I over-think things greatly. This means that for every decision I make, whether it be conscious or unconscious, with thought or without, I am following a set, methodical method. To say that these thoughts are all meant to arrive at their conclusion, regardless of their length implies a greater power is at work, which in turn goes back to Someonerandm’s post. Furthermore, emotion is completely unpredictable as it doesn’t work off of any rationale. While your argument may work to a point with logic, it falls apart with emotion. Of course, this conclusion with emotion relies on the idea that emotion is in fact unpredictable, which to this point in our history has been proven time and time again by history itself.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/anyone-for-philopitty-navel-gazers-welcome/2006/31">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/anyone-for-philopitty-navel-gazers-welcome/2006/31</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2009 01:00:19 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2006-31</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/anyone-for-philopitty-navel-gazers-welcome/2006.rss">Anyone for Philopitty? Navel-gazers welcome!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Anyone for Philopitty? Navel-gazers welcome!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Someonerandm]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Hey just thought of a metaphor (right word? I don’t know. English never has been my strongest subject) for that. Consider a choice to be a mathematical problem. Yes there is only one it can be answered (don’t get into higher level math, okay?), but you still have to go through the steps to solve it. When you make a choice, there is only one way to proceed, but you have to think to work that way out.</p>
<p>EDIT: Forgot to add the meaning of this. Essentially, the fact that you have to work it out means that you don’t know what to do, which means that this situation is new, which means that life can still surprise you, which is all you really need to know, whether or not you are predestined. So, in effect, who cares? It doesn’t affect how you live your life.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/anyone-for-philopitty-navel-gazers-welcome/2006/30">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/anyone-for-philopitty-navel-gazers-welcome/2006/30</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2009 00:38:27 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2006-30</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/anyone-for-philopitty-navel-gazers-welcome/2006.rss">Anyone for Philopitty? Navel-gazers welcome!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Anyone for Philopitty? Navel-gazers welcome!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[ijgs]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>glad to be of service!  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/smiley.png?v=9" title=":smiley:" class="emoji" alt=":smiley:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/anyone-for-philopitty-navel-gazers-welcome/2006/29">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/anyone-for-philopitty-navel-gazers-welcome/2006/29</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 09 Dec 2009 23:10:19 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2006-29</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/anyone-for-philopitty-navel-gazers-welcome/2006.rss">Anyone for Philopitty? Navel-gazers welcome!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Anyone for Philopitty? Navel-gazers welcome!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[baconeggs]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Thank fuck for that, it drives me mad when I can’t think of an argument against to whole predermination thing.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/anyone-for-philopitty-navel-gazers-welcome/2006/28">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/anyone-for-philopitty-navel-gazers-welcome/2006/28</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 09 Dec 2009 22:37:01 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2006-28</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/anyone-for-philopitty-navel-gazers-welcome/2006.rss">Anyone for Philopitty? Navel-gazers welcome!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Anyone for Philopitty? Navel-gazers welcome!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[ijgs]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Firstly, there is a machine that enables other humans to predict your choices; it’s called an fMRI scan and it can be used to predict simple boolean choices up to six seconds before you’re <span class="bbcode-i">consciously</span> aware of your choice. Fortunately, MRI machines weigh several tonnes and fill a room, so they’re not really a viable choice for mass populace control!  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/wink.png?v=9" title=":wink:" class="emoji" alt=":wink:"></p>
<p>I personally take issue with the whole predetermination thing, but that’s because I don’t believe in fate even more than I don’t believe in luck! I’m sure that, given enough data, one could propose that everything led back to one foundation event… oh wait… isn’t that the basis for Original Sin?!.. or statistics?!  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/wink.png?v=9" title=":wink:" class="emoji" alt=":wink:"></p>
<p>Secondly, is choice actually a primary, or originating, motivation, or a reactionary one? i.e. if you killed my kids, my reaction would probably be to come after you with a spade. However I would doubtless recoil from the reality of bludgeoning you to death with a garden tool, so I would choose not to do such a thing. Is that a primary choice or a reaction? I would contend that there is no such thing as cause and effect, since this presumes a beginning and an end. Rather there are many ongoing reactions to events.</p>
<p>Someonerandm stated that we “don’t know our own reactions”. I would argue that only the most self-unaware, or psychotic, person is ignorant of their reactions. I am constantly aware of many of my reactions (though possibly not all of them, I grant you). Choice something that happens internally and defines your actual reaction to an event; to continue the example above, I may recoil at the horror of spade bludgeonery, but choose to ignore that and beat you to a bloody pulp. Alternatively, I may choose to let you find your own demise.</p>
<p>While an external agent may be able to detect the moment that the choice occurred before I am aware of it, that doesn’t stop it being my choice and mine alone. Even if I was made aware of my sub-conscious intent, I could still choose to ignore <span class="bbcode-i">that</span> choice…</p>
<p>Crap, I’m starting to sound like R.D. Laing in his book “Knots”… :fffuuu:</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/anyone-for-philopitty-navel-gazers-welcome/2006/27">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/anyone-for-philopitty-navel-gazers-welcome/2006/27</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 09 Dec 2009 22:20:09 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2006-27</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/anyone-for-philopitty-navel-gazers-welcome/2006.rss">Anyone for Philopitty? Navel-gazers welcome!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Anyone for Philopitty? Navel-gazers welcome!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Someonerandm]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>But since we don’t know our own reactions, we still have choice. When making a choice, you still have to think it through, measure your options, etc. If you truly had no free choice, then such preparations would be worthless as you would already have a predetermined choice. And yes, given the same circumstances you would make the same choice, but what does that mean? There is only one way history can proceed, so that is a given. But if we don’t know how that history will proceed we can still make choices.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/anyone-for-philopitty-navel-gazers-welcome/2006/26">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/anyone-for-philopitty-navel-gazers-welcome/2006/26</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 09 Dec 2009 14:10:25 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2006-26</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/anyone-for-philopitty-navel-gazers-welcome/2006.rss">Anyone for Philopitty? Navel-gazers welcome!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Anyone for Philopitty? Navel-gazers welcome!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[baconeggs]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Someonerandm">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/s/d78d45/40.png" class="avatar"> Someonerandm:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Second, at baconeggs, while it is true that it would be possible to predict every action ever taken in the universe, that doesn’t change the fact that you are still making a choice. If there was a machine that calculated all out fates, then we would not have truly free will, as it would be dictated and shaped by the machine, but since there is no such machine, we still have a freedom to choose.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Since your actions are shaped by the chemical reactions in your brain, they are by default predicatable and out of your hands. A machine that could calculate fates would simply act as a tool to guide us along a predetermined path. You say freedom to choose yet the reality is that you would have always made the same choice given the same input, and this input is predetermined and unchanging.</p>
<p>The idea is that everything you do is based upon something else, nothing is done completely independantly and therefore will is has limited freedom, if any.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/anyone-for-philopitty-navel-gazers-welcome/2006/25">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/anyone-for-philopitty-navel-gazers-welcome/2006/25</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 09 Dec 2009 06:08:28 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2006-25</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/anyone-for-philopitty-navel-gazers-welcome/2006.rss">Anyone for Philopitty? Navel-gazers welcome!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Anyone for Philopitty? Navel-gazers welcome!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Someonerandm]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>First of, ijgs, my point stands that any man has the ultimate potential to make much, much more than 1,000,000 pounds. So, using this reason, if I were to kill one random person in order to get 1,000,000 pounds, while it could be someone who would be worth sacrificing for the greater good, there is a small but key chance that that person will do great things, and ultimately save many more people than a measly million quid could ever save, and to me, that tiny risk is too great.</p>
<p>Second, at baconeggs, while it is true that it would be possible to predict every action ever taken in the universe, that doesn’t change the fact that you are still making a choice. If there was a machine that calculated all out fates, then we would not have truly free will, as it would be dictated and shaped by the machine, but since there is no such machine, we still have a freedom to choose.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/anyone-for-philopitty-navel-gazers-welcome/2006/24">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/anyone-for-philopitty-navel-gazers-welcome/2006/24</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 09 Dec 2009 04:08:50 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2006-24</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/anyone-for-philopitty-navel-gazers-welcome/2006.rss">Anyone for Philopitty? Navel-gazers welcome!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Anyone for Philopitty? Navel-gazers welcome!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[baconeggs]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="ijgs">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/i/5fc32e/40.png" class="avatar"> ijgs:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Of course it does, you are completely free to murder someone… and society is completely free to investigate that murder and take action. Laws are merely the codification of a consensus opinion; feel free to go break them, but also feel free to take the consequences!</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>But you assume that the choice to murder is one made by that person alone. Since theoretically any event can be predicted with the right amount of data, this means that anything that has or will happen is predetermined.</p>
<p>If someone chooses to murder based upon say, anger built up from a previous traumatic event, it stands to reason that their choice was predetermined by that event, which in itself can be predicted. If you trace back the origin of that traumatic experience you would find that it was caused by an equally predictable event.</p>
<p>The illusion of free will comes from our inability to trace back the causes of everything, but if it could be done you would find that everything that has ever happened is due to a single occurance at the beginning of time.</p>
<p>People don’t just choose to do things, they make decisions based upon previous predetermined experiences.</p>
<p>I personally don’t agree with this argument, but I have never found a sufficient rebuttal for it.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/anyone-for-philopitty-navel-gazers-welcome/2006/23">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/anyone-for-philopitty-navel-gazers-welcome/2006/23</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 09 Dec 2009 03:37:03 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2006-23</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/anyone-for-philopitty-navel-gazers-welcome/2006.rss">Anyone for Philopitty? Navel-gazers welcome!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Anyone for Philopitty? Navel-gazers welcome!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[ijgs]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Someonerandm">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/s/d78d45/40.png" class="avatar"> Someonerandm:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I think that any one mans potential is greater than the one million dollars and the lives that would save.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Oh, I don’t know, you could save most of the population of Burkina Faso (around 15 million) with a million quid, wouldn’t that be worth it??</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/anyone-for-philopitty-navel-gazers-welcome/2006/22">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/anyone-for-philopitty-navel-gazers-welcome/2006/22</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 09 Dec 2009 00:55:56 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2006-22</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/anyone-for-philopitty-navel-gazers-welcome/2006.rss">Anyone for Philopitty? Navel-gazers welcome!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Anyone for Philopitty? Navel-gazers welcome!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Someonerandm]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>It is limitlessssssssss.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/anyone-for-philopitty-navel-gazers-welcome/2006/21">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/anyone-for-philopitty-navel-gazers-welcome/2006/21</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 08 Dec 2009 22:22:25 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2006-21</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/anyone-for-philopitty-navel-gazers-welcome/2006.rss">Anyone for Philopitty? Navel-gazers welcome!</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
