<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Internet Modem...</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/internet-modem/7073</link>
    <description>Yesterday morning, Our internet wouldn&#39;t connect. Around 12nn the internet connected so I started playing my games. Then around 1 pm, 3 guys claiming to be from our internet service provider said that they were sorry for the downtime of the internet during the morning. They said that all the whole city lost internet connection from them and that they were sorry. 

After explaining some stuff... They offered my mother a modem that would make our internet boost up to 3 mbps. My mother said that they should show us first that the internet will really boost up to 3mbps. So they connected their modem and did some &quot;things&quot;... I&#39;m a newbie to computers so I don&#39;t know what they were doing. Well after those &quot;things&quot; They went to a speedtest site and showed us that our internet is at 3mbps. They then went to youtube and showed us that the videos load fast which is true. My mother paid them $20 for the modem. Before they left, one of the guys gave me a list of account names and passwords. He said that I should try to connect any of those accounts, if one doesn&#39;t work... try another account until one connects. We tested those accounts but only 3 connected. They said that maintenance is still not done and that the others should work fine after the maintenance. Of course I thought it was weird but I was so excited to do stuff with the internet, that I couldn&#39;t think clearly enough to figure out anything. 

The next day... none of the account connected. I connected our original account with their modem but the speed was only at 1 mbps. That&#39;s when I figured out that we got fooled and those accounts were from other people who pay for 3mbps. I told my family about it and said to just use our account. I thought Bullschit of course... we have contact numbers of those guys but I doubt they would come back.

I feel so stupid...:[

I&#39;ll contact our internet service provider about this and change our password.

Now... Is there ANYTHING ELSE I SHOULD KNOW? About other operations they might do. I want to avoid this kind of event from happening again.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 07 May 2011 22:26:54 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Help and Support</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/internet-modem/7073.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Internet Modem...</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[sersoft]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>enjoy my 5 year old adsl2 modem</p>
<p>just bought 3.5g of weed with the 20bux</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/internet-modem/7073/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/internet-modem/7073/7</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 07 May 2011 22:26:54 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7073-7</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/internet-modem/7073.rss">Internet Modem...</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Internet Modem...</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[russilker]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>25mbps upload/download FiOS ftw</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/internet-modem/7073/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/internet-modem/7073/6</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 07 May 2011 21:05:41 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7073-6</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/internet-modem/7073.rss">Internet Modem...</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Internet Modem...</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[pendulum]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Hazzmat">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/h/8dc957/40.png" class="avatar"> Hazzmat:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Well someone’s feeling proud of his epenis  :rolleyes:</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>yeah i just saw today that my speed has doubled! haha</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/internet-modem/7073/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/internet-modem/7073/5</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 07 May 2011 17:15:24 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7073-5</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/internet-modem/7073.rss">Internet Modem...</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Internet Modem...</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Hazzmat]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Well someone’s feeling proud of his epenis  :rolleyes:</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/internet-modem/7073/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/internet-modem/7073/4</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 07 May 2011 16:28:04 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7073-4</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/internet-modem/7073.rss">Internet Modem...</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Internet Modem...</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[pendulum]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>3 mbit … thats blazing fast !!</p>
<p>this is mine  <img src="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/original/2X/d/de2c8a11c773fd202cdce7064ee0a0189690974a.png" alt="" data-base62-sha1="vHrqg1cPQHw7b56Yr4vX4AFNus2" width="350" height="200"></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/internet-modem/7073/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/internet-modem/7073/3</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 07 May 2011 13:52:09 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7073-3</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/internet-modem/7073.rss">Internet Modem...</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Internet Modem...</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Hazzmat]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I’m so sorry but this just had to be done<br>
<span alt="" class="broken-image" title="This image is broken"><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-unlink svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#unlink"></use></svg></span></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/internet-modem/7073/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/internet-modem/7073/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 07 May 2011 13:06:07 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7073-2</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/internet-modem/7073.rss">Internet Modem...</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Internet Modem...</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[rx33gundam]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Yesterday morning, Our internet wouldn’t connect. Around 12nn the internet connected so I started playing my games. Then around 1 pm, 3 guys claiming to be from our internet service provider said that they were sorry for the downtime of the internet during the morning. They said that all the whole city lost internet connection from them and that they were sorry.</p>
<p>After explaining some stuff… They offered my mother a modem that would make our internet boost up to 3 mbps. My mother said that they should show us first that the internet will really boost up to 3mbps. So they connected their modem and did some “things”… I’m a newbie to computers so I don’t know what they were doing. Well after those “things” They went to a speedtest site and showed us that our internet is at 3mbps. They then went to youtube and showed us that the videos load fast which is true. My mother paid them $20 for the modem. Before they left, one of the guys gave me a list of account names and passwords. He said that I should try to connect any of those accounts, if one doesn’t work… try another account until one connects. We tested those accounts but only 3 connected. They said that maintenance is still not done and that the others should work fine after the maintenance. Of course I thought it was weird but I was so excited to do stuff with the internet, that I couldn’t think clearly enough to figure out anything.</p>
<p>The next day… none of the account connected. I connected our original account with their modem but the speed was only at 1 mbps. That’s when I figured out that we got fooled and those accounts were from other people who pay for 3mbps. I told my family about it and said to just use our account. I thought Bullschit of course… we have contact numbers of those guys but I doubt they would come back.</p>
<p>I feel so stupid…:[</p>
<p>I’ll contact our internet service provider about this and change our password.</p>
<p>Now… Is there ANYTHING ELSE I SHOULD KNOW? About other operations they might do. I want to avoid this kind of event from happening again.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/internet-modem/7073/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/internet-modem/7073/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 07 May 2011 10:26:41 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7073-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/internet-modem/7073.rss">Internet Modem...</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
