<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>FakeFactory Ceases Work On Cinematic Mod</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/fakefactory-ceases-work-on-cinematic-mod/13560</link>
    <description>After almost 10 years, FakeFactory releases the final version of his Cinematic Mod for HL2, CM 2013 Final, and ends  further development on it.

He may return to the project, once the Source 2 engine is finally released.


[url=&#39;https://cinematicmod.com/forum/viewtopic.php?f=26&amp;t=3956&#39;]https://cinematicmod.com/forum/viewtopic.php?f=26&amp;t=3956[/url]</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2015 10:46:22 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Half-Life Series</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/fakefactory-ceases-work-on-cinematic-mod/13560.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>FakeFactory Ceases Work On Cinematic Mod</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Dadster]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="(rot)(fodder">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 (rot)(fodder:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>DADSTER YOU BEAUTIFUL PERSON</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Couldn’t stand the thought of you running round and tossin’ ur cookies every 500 yards, or so   8|   &lt;X   &lt;X   :cursing:   .   .   .   travel  - - -&gt;.   8|   &lt;X   :cursing:   (repeat)   .   .   .   .   .</p>
<p>Glad I could help !</p>
<p>Since you’re playing CM2013, this “MASSIVE Props HD Overhaul” mod may deepen your experience. Purdy props are better than fugly ones.</p>
<p><a href="https://hl2.gamebanana.com/skins/136418" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://hl2.gamebanana.com/skins/136418</a><br>
.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/fakefactory-ceases-work-on-cinematic-mod/13560/32">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/fakefactory-ceases-work-on-cinematic-mod/13560/32</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2015 10:46:22 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13560-32</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/fakefactory-ceases-work-on-cinematic-mod/13560.rss">FakeFactory Ceases Work On Cinematic Mod</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>FakeFactory Ceases Work On Cinematic Mod</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[_rot_fodder]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Dadster">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/d/e495f1/40.png" class="avatar"> Dadster:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>@ (rot)(fodder</p>
<p>Here’s a mod that removes the pornographic graffiti from the game   -   <a href="https://hl2.gamebanana.com/skins/137168" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://hl2.gamebanana.com/skins/137168</a></p>
<hr>
<p>FakeFactory has released a patch for his CM2013 Final mod. It’s been updated to v1.01     -   <a href="https://cinematicmod.com/forum/viewtopic.php?f=26&amp;t=3956" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://cinematicmod.com/forum/viewtopic.php?f=26&amp;t=3956</a></p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>DADSTER YOU BEAUTIFUL PERSON</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/fakefactory-ceases-work-on-cinematic-mod/13560/31">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/fakefactory-ceases-work-on-cinematic-mod/13560/31</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2015 07:15:50 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13560-31</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/fakefactory-ceases-work-on-cinematic-mod/13560.rss">FakeFactory Ceases Work On Cinematic Mod</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>FakeFactory Ceases Work On Cinematic Mod</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Malidictus]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Yup. Unchecked Head Bob and Weapon Recoil. If it made a difference, I couldn’t feel it. Incidentally, I disable Head Bob AND View Sway in Black Mesa entirely. I couldn’t play for very long with either enabled.</p>
<p><em>edit</em><br>
And what I wasn’t expecting was that the Cinematic Mod actually breaks a lot of the scripted sequences in Half-Life 2. The instance where Lamarr is supposed to jump into the teleporter and much things up sees the Headcrab just standing and doing nothing. That part of Route Kanal where you shoot a mounted gun until an APC shows up and shoots rockets at you also doesn’t work. The APC shows up and… Does nothing. I simply gave up in the part where you’re swimming in water and a cop throws flaming barrels at you from above. The barrels blow open a grate for you to pass through, but it’s too high off the water and I never did find a way to get up there. That, and disabling the Cinematic Mod weapons causes the pistol reload animation to bug and distort.</p>
<p>The idea is solid and it does make the Half-Life maps look a lot prettier, but it ends up making the game look uglier because things which worked in the original game don’t in the mod. The models, for example. The “original Valve models” are not the original Valve models. They have been touched up with different textures and, in the process, lost most of their facial animations. I remember Barney as an animate, sarcastic guy with a corked eyebrow. The Barney I ran into spoke with a blank face and dead eyes, almost like the models used to back in the old Half-Life when they didn’t HAVE facial animation.</p>
<p>It could be I mucked up something in my install folder, but I ran into too many technical issues to be able to appreciate the frankly very pretty maps.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/fakefactory-ceases-work-on-cinematic-mod/13560/30">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/fakefactory-ceases-work-on-cinematic-mod/13560/30</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2015 00:55:31 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13560-30</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/fakefactory-ceases-work-on-cinematic-mod/13560.rss">FakeFactory Ceases Work On Cinematic Mod</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>FakeFactory Ceases Work On Cinematic Mod</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Dadster]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Malidictus">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/m/7bcc69/40.png" class="avatar"> Malidictus:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>. . . . .  The mod has a built-in VERY heavy head bob that none of the mod-specific options seem to disable. It makes me instantly seasick, meaning I either never sprint (impossible, since it’s required in a few places) or else grab a barf bag.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Just to be sure, did you uncheck the head bob option in the Configurator Tool?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/fakefactory-ceases-work-on-cinematic-mod/13560/29">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/fakefactory-ceases-work-on-cinematic-mod/13560/29</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2015 21:16:41 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13560-29</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/fakefactory-ceases-work-on-cinematic-mod/13560.rss">FakeFactory Ceases Work On Cinematic Mod</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>FakeFactory Ceases Work On Cinematic Mod</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Malidictus]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Yes, it seems like it so far. There are a couple of things I can’t find out how to tweak, however, and no - I don’t mean the obscene graffiti.  The mod has a built-in VERY heavy head bob that none of the mod-specific options seem to disable. It makes me instantly seasick, meaning I either never sprint (impossible, since it’s required in a few places) or else grab a barf bag. Personal issue, but there it is. The other is an odd oversight. You can customise the models for civilians and Combine soldiers, but this doesn’t reflect on the game’s zombies at all - they still use the CM-specific character model bases. I would have expected that zombies would be inexorably tied to the models they’re based on, so customising one would automatically customise the other.</p>
<p>At this point, my experimentation with the Cinematic Mod weapons has more or less come to a permanent end. Combine Machinegun aside, they look pretty good but the animations just don’t work very well. All the weapons seem to have an odd delay between hitting the “Fire” button and when the weapon actually animates the sound and muzzle flash, almost as if Gordon is a little slow to respond. This is odd, because they still hit as if they fired instantly, making the whole experience feel a bit awkward. But again - that’s optional so I can’t really hold it against the mod. I was just hoping for a weapon mod for Half-Life, though, akin to llpon’s reanimations and weapon models for Black Mesa. I never realised how much I mised the separate pistol slide release on reload until I didn’t have it any more.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/fakefactory-ceases-work-on-cinematic-mod/13560/28">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/fakefactory-ceases-work-on-cinematic-mod/13560/28</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2015 15:01:20 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13560-28</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/fakefactory-ceases-work-on-cinematic-mod/13560.rss">FakeFactory Ceases Work On Cinematic Mod</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>FakeFactory Ceases Work On Cinematic Mod</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Dotard]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Hence the mod is good, while using the “lite/light” version.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/fakefactory-ceases-work-on-cinematic-mod/13560/27">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/fakefactory-ceases-work-on-cinematic-mod/13560/27</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2015 13:50:54 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13560-27</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/fakefactory-ceases-work-on-cinematic-mod/13560.rss">FakeFactory Ceases Work On Cinematic Mod</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>FakeFactory Ceases Work On Cinematic Mod</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Malidictus]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Frankly, I can see why FakeFactory gets a bad rap around these parts. A lot of the changes in the Cinematic Mod have nothing to do with Half-Life whatsoever. Father Henry (whom the mod refers to as “Monk” despite being a priest O_o) is given a black trenchcoat with sunglasses. Considering all of Ravenholm takes place at night, that’s twice as hilarious. The rest of the character models don’t fare much better, usually changing people into completely different people, with frankly badly-done model work. So far no surprises.</p>
<p>The guns were another big disappointment. As you might have seen elsewhere, I was really excited about getting higher-rez, better-animated guns than what Half-Life 2 has to offer, but the swaps aren’t very good. A lot of stuff is mostly the same but up-textured, like the Crowbar, Gravity Gun and Crossbow. Those are actually pretty good and highly detailed while retaining their beat-up old look. The automatic weapons, however, are swapped for contemporary-looking guns, which is frankly VERY out-of-place for a sci-fi setting like this, especially when you turn the Combine Machinegun into what looks like a large M16-looking rifle. The animations are really off, as well, though I suspect/hope that’s just issues with my installation. The basic pistol has a distinct delay between when the hammer strikes and when the gun actually fires. What this means is it basically doesn’t recoil or play a muzzle flash if you shoot it fast enough. I know llpon’s weapon animations are a divisive topic here, but after playing with them in Black Mesa, the Cinematic Mod weapons feel outright amateurish.</p>
<p>The map improvements look pretty cool, though. Yes, they change the feel of the game more than slightly, but that’s to be expected and it’s not always a bad change. City 17 was originally inspired by various Bulgarian cities, most notably the capital. Being that I’m from Bulgaria, all of City 17 felt very familiar to me, as it looks pretty spot-on to the real world, minus the actual street layout, obviously. The Cinematic Mod changes that quite a bit, but I couldn’t tell you which direction it pulls the environment in since it’s not as instantly recognisable to me. In either case, it’s a welcome bit of additional detail over Half-Life’s decade-old maps designed for far lower-end PCs and an inferior version of Source.</p>
<p>Once I actually get the Cinematic Mod working properly (Avast keeps blocking a specific file from the installer with a “suspected” worm, Avast being what it is), I might end up stripping the mod of everything sans the maps. If anything, it’s worth a shot, because what I tested so far is pretty cool.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/fakefactory-ceases-work-on-cinematic-mod/13560/26">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/fakefactory-ceases-work-on-cinematic-mod/13560/26</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2015 12:00:45 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13560-26</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/fakefactory-ceases-work-on-cinematic-mod/13560.rss">FakeFactory Ceases Work On Cinematic Mod</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>FakeFactory Ceases Work On Cinematic Mod</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Malidictus]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Well, so far so good. The thing is pretty customisable. Getting rid of all the extra character models was pretty easy, but the thing crashes like crazy. I’d be interested in dropping a few first impressions if I can get it to work.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/fakefactory-ceases-work-on-cinematic-mod/13560/25">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/fakefactory-ceases-work-on-cinematic-mod/13560/25</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2015 20:16:26 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13560-25</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/fakefactory-ceases-work-on-cinematic-mod/13560.rss">FakeFactory Ceases Work On Cinematic Mod</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>FakeFactory Ceases Work On Cinematic Mod</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Kenley]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Yeah, all of the crap is optional.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/fakefactory-ceases-work-on-cinematic-mod/13560/24">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/fakefactory-ceases-work-on-cinematic-mod/13560/24</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2015 17:10:31 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13560-24</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/fakefactory-ceases-work-on-cinematic-mod/13560.rss">FakeFactory Ceases Work On Cinematic Mod</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>FakeFactory Ceases Work On Cinematic Mod</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Malidictus]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>So I had a look at the Cinematic Mod screenshots, and I’m of two minds about it.</p>
<p>On the one hand, the environments do look vastly improved. Let’s face it - Half-Life 2 is an old, dated game by this point. It looks its age. Sprucing it up is a good thing, even if not all the improvements seem very notable. On the other hand… MY GOD the character models are utterly dreadful! What the hell happened there? It’s like something out of Y3DF! I mean, if you’re going to model your character design after 3D porn, at least pick a decent artist to copy, like Umemaro or Chimera. Don’t be the guy who does BAXS. WOW that is just BAD! Not only are the character models themselves butt ugly, but they’re also thematically completely inappropriate for the rest of the game, and shockingly so. Yikes!</p>
<p>If all of that crap is optional, I might give the mod a shot, just to see Half-Life from another perspective. Wonder if this guy’s done anything to Ravenholm… On the one hand, that place REALLY needs a touch-up, as I’ve mentioned elsewhere. On the other hand, FakeFactory’s idea of a “cool” is pretty much the antithesis of what Ravenholm is, so this has the potential to go hilariously bad… I think I might play with the porn graffiti on, though, just to see what they are. As you can tell by my previous paragraph, I’m not exactly prudish, but it’s entirely possible they clash with the rest of the game’s style too much. Even if they would fit the king of graffiti I see on walls and buildings around these parts.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/fakefactory-ceases-work-on-cinematic-mod/13560/23">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/fakefactory-ceases-work-on-cinematic-mod/13560/23</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2015 14:44:19 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13560-23</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/fakefactory-ceases-work-on-cinematic-mod/13560.rss">FakeFactory Ceases Work On Cinematic Mod</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>FakeFactory Ceases Work On Cinematic Mod</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Dadster]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>@ (rot)(fodder</p>
<p>Here’s a mod that removes the pornographic graffiti from the game   -   <a href="https://hl2.gamebanana.com/skins/137168" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://hl2.gamebanana.com/skins/137168</a></p>
<hr>
<p>FakeFactory has released a patch for his CM2013 Final mod. It’s been updated to v1.01     -   <a href="https://cinematicmod.com/forum/viewtopic.php?f=26&amp;t=3956" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://cinematicmod.com/forum/viewtopic.php?f=26&amp;t=3956</a></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/fakefactory-ceases-work-on-cinematic-mod/13560/22">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/fakefactory-ceases-work-on-cinematic-mod/13560/22</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2015 09:47:05 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13560-22</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/fakefactory-ceases-work-on-cinematic-mod/13560.rss">FakeFactory Ceases Work On Cinematic Mod</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>FakeFactory Ceases Work On Cinematic Mod</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypt]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="M-Man">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 M-Man:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>What’s sad is that it lasted for 10 years.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/fakefactory-ceases-work-on-cinematic-mod/13560/21">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/fakefactory-ceases-work-on-cinematic-mod/13560/21</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 13 Dec 2014 02:54:43 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13560-21</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/fakefactory-ceases-work-on-cinematic-mod/13560.rss">FakeFactory Ceases Work On Cinematic Mod</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>FakeFactory Ceases Work On Cinematic Mod</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[coldroll]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="M-Man">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 M-Man:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>It’s the young modder’s “might as well throw THIS in there” mentality. What’s sad is that it lasted for 10 years.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I don’t think he’s that young I remember reading about the fake factory mod seven years ago on his website and I’m pretty sure he said he was forty something at the time so who knows he might be fifty something now.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/fakefactory-ceases-work-on-cinematic-mod/13560/20">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/fakefactory-ceases-work-on-cinematic-mod/13560/20</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2014 21:45:36 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13560-20</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/fakefactory-ceases-work-on-cinematic-mod/13560.rss">FakeFactory Ceases Work On Cinematic Mod</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>FakeFactory Ceases Work On Cinematic Mod</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[M-Man]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>It’s the young modder’s “might as well throw THIS in there” mentality. What’s sad is that it lasted for 10 years.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/fakefactory-ceases-work-on-cinematic-mod/13560/19">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/fakefactory-ceases-work-on-cinematic-mod/13560/19</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2014 19:21:52 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13560-19</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/fakefactory-ceases-work-on-cinematic-mod/13560.rss">FakeFactory Ceases Work On Cinematic Mod</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>FakeFactory Ceases Work On Cinematic Mod</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[coldroll]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="(rot)(fodder">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 (rot)(fodder:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>The thing about it that irks me is that the lack of thought put into the mod is <span class="bbcode-b"><span class="bbcode-i">astounding</span></span>. Often the placement of things and just the things themselves don’t make any sense. It’s like Uwe Boll ate some transformers dvds, the batman soundtrack and a playboy magazine then opened up hammer and just had bowel movements all over everything.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>That’s the cinematic mod in a nutshell.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/fakefactory-ceases-work-on-cinematic-mod/13560/18">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/fakefactory-ceases-work-on-cinematic-mod/13560/18</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2014 22:50:26 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13560-18</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/fakefactory-ceases-work-on-cinematic-mod/13560.rss">FakeFactory Ceases Work On Cinematic Mod</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>FakeFactory Ceases Work On Cinematic Mod</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Dotard]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>The models and soundtrack are completely optional, turn those off and you’ve got HL2 as you know it with much better textures and effects.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/fakefactory-ceases-work-on-cinematic-mod/13560/17">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/fakefactory-ceases-work-on-cinematic-mod/13560/17</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2014 13:09:04 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13560-17</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/fakefactory-ceases-work-on-cinematic-mod/13560.rss">FakeFactory Ceases Work On Cinematic Mod</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>FakeFactory Ceases Work On Cinematic Mod</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[InquisitorLampshade]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I just looked into this mod and WTF? In some cases they did good work improving the terrain but everything else seems moronic. Alyx looks like a porn star, Barnie looks like somebody else entirely, and I’m sure it only gets worse from there.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/fakefactory-ceases-work-on-cinematic-mod/13560/16">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/fakefactory-ceases-work-on-cinematic-mod/13560/16</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2014 08:27:22 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13560-16</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/fakefactory-ceases-work-on-cinematic-mod/13560.rss">FakeFactory Ceases Work On Cinematic Mod</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>FakeFactory Ceases Work On Cinematic Mod</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[GilCMassey]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>That was a wonderful image  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/smiley.png?v=9" title=":smiley:" class="emoji" alt=":smiley:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/fakefactory-ceases-work-on-cinematic-mod/13560/15">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/fakefactory-ceases-work-on-cinematic-mod/13560/15</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2014 07:13:17 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13560-15</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/fakefactory-ceases-work-on-cinematic-mod/13560.rss">FakeFactory Ceases Work On Cinematic Mod</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>FakeFactory Ceases Work On Cinematic Mod</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[_rot_fodder]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>The thing about it that irks me is that the lack of thought put into the mod is <span class="bbcode-b"><span class="bbcode-i">astounding</span></span>. Often the placement of things and just the things themselves don’t make any sense. It’s like Uwe Boll ate some transformers dvds, the batman soundtrack and a playboy magazine then opened up hammer and just had bowel movements all over everything.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/fakefactory-ceases-work-on-cinematic-mod/13560/14">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/fakefactory-ceases-work-on-cinematic-mod/13560/14</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2014 01:35:11 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13560-14</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/fakefactory-ceases-work-on-cinematic-mod/13560.rss">FakeFactory Ceases Work On Cinematic Mod</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>FakeFactory Ceases Work On Cinematic Mod</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Orpheon]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Some of the stuff was pretty cool but there were a number of things I disliked. For instance, the new character models. Half looked like aliens trying to imitate humans based on anime characters, the others looked alright but nothing like their original counterparts. Barney got changed from a normal looking, slightly overweight security guard to some square-jawed action hero type. And Alyx was changed from a regular, practical, no-nonsense action woman into some borderline porn model. Second was the music, which was all taken from well-known movie soundtracks and such, and every time I hear the music I’m like, “Wait…what? Where do I know this from?” Third was the odd foliage. CM made the foliage much more lush, which is alright, although it makes things a bit less dreary, which is kind of the point, and some of the trees look downright weird and bloated. And then there is apparently the porn graffiti, which I didn’t even notice.</p>
<p>Anyway I know some of this is optional and can be turned off, and some of this may have been changed since I last tried it, but the point is that FakeFactory’s mod has always reflected his specific ideals for Half-Life 2, and that of course divided fans of the game. Some appreciated his changes, some didn’t. I think the reason that people here are so vehement about the mod is because they appreciated Valve’s original vision, and would have been happy to have a simple graphical update or even a BM-style remake, but not one that differs so greatly from the original, like CM’s does.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/fakefactory-ceases-work-on-cinematic-mod/13560/13">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/fakefactory-ceases-work-on-cinematic-mod/13560/13</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2014 00:06:30 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13560-13</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/fakefactory-ceases-work-on-cinematic-mod/13560.rss">FakeFactory Ceases Work On Cinematic Mod</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>FakeFactory Ceases Work On Cinematic Mod</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[_rot_fodder]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="FERGUS">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/f/bbce88/40.png" class="avatar"> FERGUS:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>You know, it is named <span class="bbcode-b">Cinematic</span> mod. The whole purpose is to transform it into something that looks [COLOR=‘Red’]like the shallowest of Hollywood productions made with massive budgets and tiny, underdeveloped brains.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>EDIT: Did anyone ever get around to deleting all of the ridiculous porn graffiti, literally every twenty feet? I suspended my disbelief with half foot thick titanium cables but that shit was just too ridiculous, even for fakefactory.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/fakefactory-ceases-work-on-cinematic-mod/13560/12">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/fakefactory-ceases-work-on-cinematic-mod/13560/12</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2014 21:08:17 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13560-12</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/fakefactory-ceases-work-on-cinematic-mod/13560.rss">FakeFactory Ceases Work On Cinematic Mod</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>FakeFactory Ceases Work On Cinematic Mod</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[JohnWorfin]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I’ve never played it but It does look quite polished. I heard he wanted to code for BMS but he was de-nied</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/fakefactory-ceases-work-on-cinematic-mod/13560/11">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/fakefactory-ceases-work-on-cinematic-mod/13560/11</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2014 19:18:10 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13560-11</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/fakefactory-ceases-work-on-cinematic-mod/13560.rss">FakeFactory Ceases Work On Cinematic Mod</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>FakeFactory Ceases Work On Cinematic Mod</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[FERGUS]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>You know, it is named <span class="bbcode-b">Cinematic</span> mod. The whole purpose is to transform it into something that looks like a Hollywood production.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/fakefactory-ceases-work-on-cinematic-mod/13560/10">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/fakefactory-ceases-work-on-cinematic-mod/13560/10</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2014 16:21:44 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13560-10</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/fakefactory-ceases-work-on-cinematic-mod/13560.rss">FakeFactory Ceases Work On Cinematic Mod</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>FakeFactory Ceases Work On Cinematic Mod</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Maxey]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Dadster">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/d/e495f1/40.png" class="avatar"> Dadster:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Not so much, from what he was able to squeeze out of and accomplish using the antiquated Source 1 engine. Review the changelogs during the course of the Cinematic Mod’s development.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>If only that was complemented with a proper aesthetical sensibility instead of completely changing the mood of the game with out of place models and music.</p>
<p>Sure, you can argue that’s optional but come on, that’s nothing but the actual intention of the author.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/fakefactory-ceases-work-on-cinematic-mod/13560/9">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/fakefactory-ceases-work-on-cinematic-mod/13560/9</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2014 08:44:34 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13560-9</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/fakefactory-ceases-work-on-cinematic-mod/13560.rss">FakeFactory Ceases Work On Cinematic Mod</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>FakeFactory Ceases Work On Cinematic Mod</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Dadster]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="jessiestorm88">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/j/f19dbf/40.png" class="avatar"> jessiestorm88:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I’ll have to try this one out I don’t think I ever got around to it. Also what was the name of that other HL2 overhaul? I thought there was supposed to be a final version of it coming out sometime soon as well.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I had a link to the mod’s forum, but I just discovered they’ve gone into hiding, for some reason?</p>
<p><a href="https://facepunch.com/showthread.php?t=1263005&amp;page=83" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://facepunch.com/showthread.php?t=1263005&amp;page=83</a></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/fakefactory-ceases-work-on-cinematic-mod/13560/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/fakefactory-ceases-work-on-cinematic-mod/13560/8</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2014 07:25:36 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13560-8</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/fakefactory-ceases-work-on-cinematic-mod/13560.rss">FakeFactory Ceases Work On Cinematic Mod</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
