<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>missing sound during Tau Cannon introduction scene</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/missing-sound-during-tau-cannon-introduction-scene/14167</link>
    <description>After searching the forums, I do not see that anyone else has reported this yet (apologies if I missed it though or if you&#39;re already aware of it).  During the introduction of the Tau Cannon in Questionable Ethics -- the scene where Freeman hears the unlucky guard and the scientist talking through the wall, then the guard accidentally overcharges the gun causing their demise - it seems the charge-up sound of the Tau Cannon is missing during this conversation.  It was present in the 2012 free mod version, but it&#39;s no longer in the retail version.   I&#39;m not sure if this is an accident or it was an intentional choice in order to overhear the dialogue better, but I&#39;m assuming for now it&#39;s a glitch.

Here are two youtube links  I found for comparison.  At first I thought maybe it was only me, that my sound file had been corrupted or something, but since it&#39;s also missing in this youtube user&#39;s playthrough, I guess that means the sound file was lost in the update.

2015 retail version:   [youtu.be/-RPhaQnno3A?t=684](https://youtu.be/-RPhaQnno3A?t=684)

2012 mod version:  [youtu.be/qE5o7vgnH4I?t=432](https://youtu.be/qE5o7vgnH4I?t=432)


edit:  If the youtube time index links I posted don&#39;t work,  go to 11:24 for the first vid and 7:12 for the second</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 03 Jun 2015 00:49:20 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>In-game Issues</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/missing-sound-during-tau-cannon-introduction-scene/14167.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>missing sound during Tau Cannon introduction scene</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Vortexyz]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>After searching the forums, I do not see that anyone else has reported this yet (apologies if I missed it though or if you’re already aware of it).  During the introduction of the Tau Cannon in Questionable Ethics – the scene where Freeman hears the unlucky guard and the scientist talking through the wall, then the guard accidentally overcharges the gun causing their demise - it seems the charge-up sound of the Tau Cannon is missing during this conversation.  It was present in the 2012 free mod version, but it’s no longer in the retail version.   I’m not sure if this is an accident or it was an intentional choice in order to overhear the dialogue better, but I’m assuming for now it’s a glitch.</p>
<p>Here are two youtube links  I found for comparison.  At first I thought maybe it was only me, that my sound file had been corrupted or something, but since it’s also missing in this youtube user’s playthrough, I guess that means the sound file was lost in the update.</p>
<p>2015 retail version:   <a href="https://youtu.be/-RPhaQnno3A?t=684" rel="nofollow noopener">youtu.be/-RPhaQnno3A?t=684</a></p>
<p>2012 mod version:  <a href="https://youtu.be/qE5o7vgnH4I?t=432" rel="nofollow noopener">youtu.be/qE5o7vgnH4I?t=432</a></p>
<p>edit:  If the youtube time index links I posted don’t work,  go to 11:24 for the first vid and 7:12 for the second</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/missing-sound-during-tau-cannon-introduction-scene/14167/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/missing-sound-during-tau-cannon-introduction-scene/14167/1</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jun 2015 00:49:20 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14167-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/missing-sound-during-tau-cannon-introduction-scene/14167.rss">missing sound during Tau Cannon introduction scene</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
