<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>low fps - nvidia - adaptive vsync</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/low-fps-nvidia-adaptive-vsync/9825</link>
    <description>don&#39;t know about ati owners, but for nvidia users i&#39;ve found disabling adaptive vsync has resolved low fps problems (which i have enabled by default in global settings).

add *\source sdk base 2007\hl2.exe to your games list and disable it.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 15 Sep 2012 21:04:25 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>In-game Issues (Mod)</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/low-fps-nvidia-adaptive-vsync/9825.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>low fps - nvidia - adaptive vsync</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[lexa2]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Could you elaborate a bit more on the hardware and software configuration of your PC? What game settings had you been using when been getting lags? Had you had vsync turned on? If yes - was it turned on in-game or forced on using nVIDIA CP and/or some other third-party tools? Had you been using DXoverrider to force triple buffered vsync in BMS? What were lags - which you believe had been caused by the adaptive vsync - like to? Was it a gradual FPS drop below your vsync frequency (60Hz usually which means “graduate drop below 60 FPS”) or had you been having “instant drop” to 30/20FPS? I fyou don’t know how to measure FPS in Source games: use third-party tools like FRAPS or DXtory or open up the in-game console and type in:</p>
<p><code>
disconnect
cl_showfps 2
sv_cheats 1
+showbudget</code></p>
<p>And then load up the save and head on to a place where you had been experiencing some lags. Take a screenshot there and post it here so devs could try to reproduce this problem on their rigs.</p>
<p>I’m a bit surprised really that you claim that adaptive vsync causes lags in BMS - it really shouldn’t as adaptive vsync technology should do quite the opposite remedying the problem with 60-30-60 vsync-related FPS stutters by turning off vsync (at expense of visuals - you would get tearing artefacts in return) whatsoever as soon as FPS drops below 60.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/low-fps-nvidia-adaptive-vsync/9825/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/low-fps-nvidia-adaptive-vsync/9825/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 15 Sep 2012 21:04:25 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9825-2</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/low-fps-nvidia-adaptive-vsync/9825.rss">low fps - nvidia - adaptive vsync</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>low fps - nvidia - adaptive vsync</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[TwoToes]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>don’t know about ati owners, but for nvidia users i’ve found disabling adaptive vsync has resolved low fps problems (which i have enabled by default in global settings).</p>
<p>add *\source sdk base 2007\hl2.exe to your games list and disable it.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/low-fps-nvidia-adaptive-vsync/9825/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/low-fps-nvidia-adaptive-vsync/9825/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 15 Sep 2012 11:39:52 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9825-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/low-fps-nvidia-adaptive-vsync/9825.rss">low fps - nvidia - adaptive vsync</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
