<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Addition to the HECU Humvee</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/addition-to-the-hecu-humvee/6647</link>
    <description>Hey there everypeople. I&#39;ve been working with source for a long time, and this mod will be alot of fun when it&#39;s done.

Here&#39;s what I&#39;ve been thinking: When Black Mesa is released, there&#39;s bound to be alot of people who&#39;d want to make their own custom maps for Black Mesa, what with all the fresh new hardware that it has to offer. Being one of those people, I figured I&#39;d suggest something about the Humvee as a prerequisite.

Although it might be used as a static prop in the campaign, It has potential to be more than that. If the developers haven&#39;t anything against it, any modeller could rig driveable vehicles out of the HMMVW, HEMMT, or M35 to be used in custom campaigns. The HMMVW has the most potential out of all of them because the turret could be rigged to be aimable. Through a couple of extra entities in hammer, you essentially have an HECU fast attack vehicle/light transport, which would diversify the use of armor in potential missions.

What would add to the diversity though (my suggestion to the developers) is to add a mounted 50 calibur gun as a body group to the humvee, similar to the TOW launcher. It&#39;s kind of strange how there isn&#39;t a version of that to begin with(at least not that I am aware of), but it would make the black mesa humvee the whole package. You&#39;d have 50 cal humvees for alien infantry, and TOW humvees for the big and gruesome behemoths.

If you think about it, the humvee could be used as an actual entity in the campaign. It could replace some mounted 50 cals or TOW missiles to add diversity, and would probably add a challenge if the humvee was capable of moving around as well. It doesn&#39;t make it look useless the way I see it. I&#39;ll leave that up to the developers, but I still think adding a 50 cal body group is a good idea. Hopefully someone is willing to agree.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2011 05:13:25 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Suggestion Box</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/addition-to-the-hecu-humvee/6647.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Addition to the HECU Humvee</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Barnacle_Jim]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Inb4 <span alt="" class="broken-image" title="This image is broken"><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-unlink svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#unlink"></use></svg></span></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/addition-to-the-hecu-humvee/6647/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/addition-to-the-hecu-humvee/6647/3</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2011 05:13:25 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-6647-3</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/addition-to-the-hecu-humvee/6647.rss">Addition to the HECU Humvee</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Addition to the HECU Humvee</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Dr_Strangelove]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><a href="https://forums.blackmesasource.com/showthread.php?t=22" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://forums.blackmesasource.com/showthread.php?t=22</a></p>
<p>Also no.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/addition-to-the-hecu-humvee/6647/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/addition-to-the-hecu-humvee/6647/2</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2011 01:26:43 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-6647-2</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/addition-to-the-hecu-humvee/6647.rss">Addition to the HECU Humvee</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Addition to the HECU Humvee</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Dark_Signal]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Hey there everypeople. I’ve been working with source for a long time, and this mod will be alot of fun when it’s done.</p>
<p>Here’s what I’ve been thinking: When Black Mesa is released, there’s bound to be alot of people who’d want to make their own custom maps for Black Mesa, what with all the fresh new hardware that it has to offer. Being one of those people, I figured I’d suggest something about the Humvee as a prerequisite.</p>
<p>Although it might be used as a static prop in the campaign, It has potential to be more than that. If the developers haven’t anything against it, any modeller could rig driveable vehicles out of the HMMVW, HEMMT, or M35 to be used in custom campaigns. The HMMVW has the most potential out of all of them because the turret could be rigged to be aimable. Through a couple of extra entities in hammer, you essentially have an HECU fast attack vehicle/light transport, which would diversify the use of armor in potential missions.</p>
<p>What would add to the diversity though (my suggestion to the developers) is to add a mounted 50 calibur gun as a body group to the humvee, similar to the TOW launcher. It’s kind of strange how there isn’t a version of that to begin with(at least not that I am aware of), but it would make the black mesa humvee the whole package. You’d have 50 cal humvees for alien infantry, and TOW humvees for the big and gruesome behemoths.</p>
<p>If you think about it, the humvee could be used as an actual entity in the campaign. It could replace some mounted 50 cals or TOW missiles to add diversity, and would probably add a challenge if the humvee was capable of moving around as well. It doesn’t make it look useless the way I see it. I’ll leave that up to the developers, but I still think adding a 50 cal body group is a good idea. Hopefully someone is willing to agree.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/addition-to-the-hecu-humvee/6647/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/addition-to-the-hecu-humvee/6647/1</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2011 01:20:12 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-6647-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/addition-to-the-hecu-humvee/6647.rss">Addition to the HECU Humvee</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
