<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Two glitches in the warehouse full of mines [Fixed]</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/two-glitches-in-the-warehouse-full-of-mines-fixed/10655</link>
    <description>When i played through the part where there is a lot of trip mines everywhere and you have to avoid them I found two glitches:

1: I&#39;m able to pick up the alien gun off of the dead body just by going close to the back fenced of the elevator. I assume you&#39;re not supposed to be able to grab the gun until you go all the way around and manage to get into the lift.

It&#39;s not a huge problem since there&#39;s no enemies to shoot, just thought it was rather unrealistic.

2: Originally playing through this part I managed to get all the way around avoiding the mines and got right up to the lift (On the same level as it, not on the raised platform). Standing in front of the lift with three mine sensor beams running across I thought I had to jump though the gap in the beams. Trying this I set one off and blew up, but since I actually got into the lift area the game auto saved as I was blowing up.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 18 Sep 2012 00:00:14 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>In-game Issues (Mod)</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/two-glitches-in-the-warehouse-full-of-mines-fixed/10655.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Two glitches in the warehouse full of mines [Fixed]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[G-ManLambda]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>When i played through the part where there is a lot of trip mines everywhere and you have to avoid them I found two glitches:</p>
<p>1: I’m able to pick up the alien gun off of the dead body just by going close to the back fenced of the elevator. I assume you’re not supposed to be able to grab the gun until you go all the way around and manage to get into the lift.</p>
<p>It’s not a huge problem since there’s no enemies to shoot, just thought it was rather unrealistic.</p>
<p>2: Originally playing through this part I managed to get all the way around avoiding the mines and got right up to the lift (On the same level as it, not on the raised platform). Standing in front of the lift with three mine sensor beams running across I thought I had to jump though the gap in the beams. Trying this I set one off and blew up, but since I actually got into the lift area the game auto saved as I was blowing up.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/two-glitches-in-the-warehouse-full-of-mines-fixed/10655/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/two-glitches-in-the-warehouse-full-of-mines-fixed/10655/1</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 18 Sep 2012 00:00:14 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-10655-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/two-glitches-in-the-warehouse-full-of-mines-fixed/10655.rss">Two glitches in the warehouse full of mines [Fixed]</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
