<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Security guard CQC bug</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/security-guard-cqc-bug/12302</link>
    <description>Just thought I should mention it, in case no one else has... There&#39;s a rather serious bug with the Black Mesa security guards. They&#39;re completely incapable of defending themselves if whatever they&#39;re fighting is sufficiently close to them. This applies to both hostile NPCs and the player (if the player provokes them into attacking). 

Basically, if whatever they&#39;re attempting to fight is close enough, the security guards will stop shooting and stand there with their weapons aimed indefinitely. If a zombie corners one, they&#39;ll just stand there and let the zombie continuously swipe at them. If you&#39;re the kind of player that likes screwing with Black Mesa personnel, you can simply run up to security guards to prevent them from being able to fight you. I don&#39;t know if it&#39;d be better to let them shoot at point-blank range or add some kind of melee system like the HECU marines have, but something should really be done about that...  :stuck_out_tongue:</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 14 May 2013 08:04:33 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>In-game Issues (Mod)</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/security-guard-cqc-bug/12302.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Security guard CQC bug</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Mr_Someguy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Medkit">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/m/57b2e6/40.png" class="avatar"> Medkit:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Personally I also find the guards too tolerant, it takes me a moderate deal to make them attack me.<br>
For me the most serious bug, or problem, is the security guard in OAR, armed with a shotgun, hiding behind a crate. He nearly doesn’t shoot at the marines at all, while the marines take him down in a few seconds. He is useless.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Yeah, this is a weird bug he has sometimes. He does shoot, but he’s not effective. Either he’ll wait roughly an entire second before shooting, or he’ll turn tail and hopelessly try to run away. Either way, he’s always dead within a 3 seconds or less. He also does very poor damage, he takes about 3-6 shots to kill a Marine. SMG Marines are often able to spray him down before he even shoots once.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/security-guard-cqc-bug/12302/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/security-guard-cqc-bug/12302/6</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2013 08:04:33 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12302-6</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/security-guard-cqc-bug/12302.rss">Security guard CQC bug</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Security guard CQC bug</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Medkit]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Personally I also find the guards too tolerant, it takes me a moderate deal to make them attack me.<br>
For me the most serious bug, or problem, is the security guard in OAR, armed with a shotgun, hiding behind a crate. He nearly doesn’t shoot at the marines at all, while the marines take him down in aa few seconds. He is useless.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/security-guard-cqc-bug/12302/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/security-guard-cqc-bug/12302/5</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2013 23:21:36 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12302-5</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/security-guard-cqc-bug/12302.rss">Security guard CQC bug</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Security guard CQC bug</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[imadoofus]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=PyGz5Hnh96I&amp;list=PL0p4ieQlUKg2y4smeENi5NutQ9W57myaM&amp;index=2" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=PyGz5Hnh96I&amp;list=PL0p4ieQlUKg2y4smeENi5NutQ9W57myaM&amp;index=2</a></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/security-guard-cqc-bug/12302/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/security-guard-cqc-bug/12302/4</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2013 17:38:12 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12302-4</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/security-guard-cqc-bug/12302.rss">Security guard CQC bug</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Security guard CQC bug</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[te47]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Yeah, I first noticed this bug during the pre-crowbar guard escort sequence. Many times, that guard ended up being cornered by a zombie and became defenseless as a result. Every time that happens, I get a Glock before I get the crowbar, which just seems so wrong…</p>
<p>It’s also a big issue if you like provoking security guards into attacking you. I do that for fun occasionally because I love games that are realistic enough to allow for friendly fire, but I load a save afterwards because I tend to take games seriously. But once you learn that cornering a guard and standing right in front of him makes him shut down, that becomes your default strategy (if damage avoidance is a concern). Which totally kills it.  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=9" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/security-guard-cqc-bug/12302/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/security-guard-cqc-bug/12302/3</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 11 May 2013 03:15:29 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12302-3</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/security-guard-cqc-bug/12302.rss">Security guard CQC bug</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Security guard CQC bug</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Mr_Someguy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I’ve noticed this as well, but it never seemed to be a huge issue since 90% of the time the guard just moved away and started shooting again. It can be problematic if he gets cornered though. It would be cool if instead they used Alyx’s CQB zombie kills, since they are supposed to be well trained. Would also make the ‘escort guard’ at the beginning more fun.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/security-guard-cqc-bug/12302/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/security-guard-cqc-bug/12302/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 11 May 2013 01:52:17 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12302-2</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/security-guard-cqc-bug/12302.rss">Security guard CQC bug</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Security guard CQC bug</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[te47]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Just thought I should mention it, in case no one else has… There’s a rather serious bug with the Black Mesa security guards. They’re completely incapable of defending themselves if whatever they’re fighting is sufficiently close to them. This applies to both hostile NPCs and the player (if the player provokes them into attacking).</p>
<p>Basically, if whatever they’re attempting to fight is close enough, the security guards will stop shooting and stand there with their weapons aimed indefinitely. If a zombie corners one, they’ll just stand there and let the zombie continuously swipe at them. If you’re the kind of player that likes screwing with Black Mesa personnel, you can simply run up to security guards to prevent them from being able to fight you. I don’t know if it’d be better to let them shoot at point-blank range or add some kind of melee system like the HECU marines have, but something should really be done about that…  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=9" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/security-guard-cqc-bug/12302/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/security-guard-cqc-bug/12302/1</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2013 17:32:47 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12302-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/security-guard-cqc-bug/12302.rss">Security guard CQC bug</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
