<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Long time fan, first &quot;fixes&quot; post</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/long-time-fan-first-fixes-post/13859</link>
    <description>Hello forum,

I am a long time fan of this project and have been playing Half-Life since the release back in 1998. Mainly, I played HLDM religiously for about 4 years straight along with Quake 3 (I still play both on and off).  Fast paced first person shooters that are movement and aim driven have always been a passion of mine.

Enough about the formalities. I am here to talk about a few &quot;fixes&quot; for  multiplayer BM. The following are foundings that I believe will make MP as close to the original as possible, while holding true to the fast paced long jumping shotgun to the face roots.

-Satchel takes too long to explode after release. It should be able to explode in mid air.
-RPG should start off with laser sight
-Faster zoom with x-bow.
-Be able to change zoom fov, not just zoom sensitivity
-No cool down for long jump. Long jumping is an integral part HLDM tau jumping and overall fluid control. It slows down the game tempo too much by having a cool down.
-Slow down health and armor regeneration on wall kits.  Maybe not to original speed, but it can be slowed a tad.
-Decrease amount of hand grenades to 3 or 4, not freaking 10! I do not enjoy spam for breakfast.
-Widen/increase hit box for tau/357/crossbow? They all seem to go through enemy while strafing.
-No tau spread on walls or corner shots? I thought it could be OP in original, but not to have any spread completely changes the game in my opinion.
- Tau cannon takes too long to start it&#39;s first charged shot. Should be quicker to charge and shoot.
- Tau charging sound is too loud when fully charged. Can&#39;t hear anything, but the weapon.
-Fast weapon switch &amp; zoom switch between weapons. The game pace seems very slowed down. Been a while since I played original, but it certainly has a delay which hinders game intensity.
-RPG is sometimes auto reloaded after switching weapons.
-Faster placement of trip mines. Also trip mines should be able to be placed at a slightly further distance.
-Trip mines hit box seems messed up from different angles. Shooting it with xbow (should be most accurate weapon) from the side may or may not explode it.
-Xbow recoil cooldown takes to long to be centered. Always seem to be aiming high on second shot. Reload time seems very long as well.
- Sound goes dim when getting hit by anything - even a crowbar?
-Machine gun has no recoil - too accure from far length.

I thought $20 was a fair price to charge for a game that has been without funding for years. All these stupid kids on the forum are just trolling. Keep up the great work &amp; I hope my input can be of use. I will update this post as I discover more &quot;fixes&quot;.

-FuNke  &lt;3</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 07 May 2015 04:01:21 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>The Cafeteria</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/long-time-fan-first-fixes-post/13859.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Long time fan, first &quot;fixes&quot; post</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[FuNkeG]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Hello forum,</p>
<p>I am a long time fan of this project and have been playing Half-Life since the release back in 1998. Mainly, I played HLDM religiously for about 4 years straight along with Quake 3 (I still play both on and off).  Fast paced first person shooters that are movement and aim driven have always been a passion of mine.</p>
<p>Enough about the formalities. I am here to talk about a few “fixes” for  multiplayer BM. The following are foundings that I believe will make MP as close to the original as possible, while holding true to the fast paced long jumping shotgun to the face roots.</p>
<p>-Satchel takes too long to explode after release. It should be able to explode in mid air.<br>
-RPG should start off with laser sight<br>
-Faster zoom with x-bow.<br>
-Be able to change zoom fov, not just zoom sensitivity<br>
-No cool down for long jump. Long jumping is an integral part HLDM tau jumping and overall fluid control. It slows down the game tempo too much by having a cool down.<br>
-Slow down health and armor regeneration on wall kits.  Maybe not to original speed, but it can be slowed a tad.<br>
-Decrease amount of hand grenades to 3 or 4, not freaking 10! I do not enjoy spam for breakfast.<br>
-Widen/increase hit box for tau/357/crossbow? They all seem to go through enemy while strafing.<br>
-No tau spread on walls or corner shots? I thought it could be OP in original, but not to have any spread completely changes the game in my opinion.</p>
<ul>
<li>Tau cannon takes too long to start it’s first charged shot. Should be quicker to charge and shoot.</li>
<li>Tau charging sound is too loud when fully charged. Can’t hear anything, but the weapon.<br>
-Fast weapon switch &amp; zoom switch between weapons. The game pace seems very slowed down. Been a while since I played original, but it certainly has a delay which hinders game intensity.<br>
-RPG is sometimes auto reloaded after switching weapons.<br>
-Faster placement of trip mines. Also trip mines should be able to be placed at a slightly further distance.<br>
-Trip mines hit box seems messed up from different angles. Shooting it with xbow (should be most accurate weapon) from the side may or may not explode it.<br>
-Xbow recoil cooldown takes to long to be centered. Always seem to be aiming high on second shot. Reload time seems very long as well.</li>
<li>Sound goes dim when getting hit by anything - even a crowbar?<br>
-Machine gun has no recoil - too accure from far length.</li>
</ul>
<p>I thought $20 was a fair price to charge for a game that has been without funding for years. All these stupid kids on the forum are just trolling. Keep up the great work &amp; I hope my input can be of use. I will update this post as I discover more “fixes”.</p>
<p>-FuNke  &lt;3</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/long-time-fan-first-fixes-post/13859/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/long-time-fan-first-fixes-post/13859/1</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 07 May 2015 04:01:21 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13859-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/long-time-fan-first-fixes-post/13859.rss">Long time fan, first &quot;fixes&quot; post</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
