<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>More Difficulties.</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/more-difficulties/14475</link>
    <description>First off i hope i am posting this in the correct area if not please move it. Dear Developers before you release the final part of the game could you please add 2 more difficulties to the game for us that are not faint of heart.

Difficulties: 
[b]Very Hard[/b]: 2x more damage to Freeman and Enemies than Hard difficulty.
[b]Unforeseen Consequences[/b]: 2x more damage to Freeman and Enemies than Very Hard difficulty.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 24 Nov 2015 07:18:25 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>The Cafeteria</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/more-difficulties/14475.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>More Difficulties.</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Rainman89]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Sounds good to me.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/more-difficulties/14475/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/more-difficulties/14475/3</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 24 Nov 2015 07:18:25 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14475-3</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/more-difficulties/14475.rss">More Difficulties.</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>More Difficulties.</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[darkone]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>thoughs are not really difficulties, just changing values isn’t really changing dificulties.</p>
<p>If anything I would suggest adding a survival mode. (likely a bad idea but all ideas can be tweeked)</p>
<p>[spoiler]concept</p>
<p>survival of the fittest, enemies die faster but so do you a full charged suit only protects against 5 or 6 rounds and a grenade will always be your death, that said it is the same with the enemies with your average alien going down in one or two shots of a pistol and hecu soldiers going down in 3 or 4 shots.</p>
<p>features<br>
weapon limit:  you are limited to 5 weapons that said you can drop weapons at any time and pick up guns off the ground, sometimes this is quicker then reloading.<br>
less ammo and health: ammo spawns are halved in amounts not only that but all sources except infinite catches and charger have lower ammo and health</p>
<p>your suit is your life: keep it charge as with out a charge you are only 2 or 3 shots form death.</p>
<p>AI tweeks</p>
<p>h-grunts<br>
changes:</p>
<ul>
<li>limited ammo 2-10 mags (unlikely to use all of) have glock/revolver side arms.</li>
<li>will throw grenades more often but are limited to 2. not all soldiers have them, soldiers with them have them on the model shot to detonate.</li>
</ul>
<p>new: heavy grunts (see new: means idea of mine highly unlikely to ever happen)<br>
info: human soldiers armed with a m249 saw, they can unload death at anything, but only carry 200 rounds of ammo, after which they swap to their glocks.<br>
note: the saw can be used but can not be reloaded like the m60 in l4d. the quicker you kill them the more ammo you can get.</p>
<p>guards<br>
changes</p>
<ul>
<li>more accurate, but more likely to spawn with less then full health.</li>
<li>in later levels may have mp5’s or crossbows, though are limited in ammo for them having 1 or 2 mags. (will use grenade launcher on mp5’s)</li>
<li>use grenades from time to time, rarely and generally only have one if they have them.</li>
</ul>
<p>vortagaunts<br>
changes</p>
<ul>
<li>can revive other vorts by shocking them, so gib the vorts unless you want something dead to come back.</li>
</ul>
<p>headcrab<br>
changes</p>
<ul>
<li>can try to turn Gordon into a zombie</li>
</ul>
<p>zombies<br>
changes<br>
*headcrab may detach from a wounded and try and turn gordon into a zombie<br>
*guard zombies may pull a grenade like zombine’s.<br>
*guard zombies may drop a mag or two from a glock or revolver.</p>
<p>A-grunts<br>
changes<br>
*snark grenades, may throw a snark nest which will walk around for a few seconds then explode showering the area in acid and 1-3 live snarks.<br>
*charge, may charge the player when low health knocking everything out of the way be it friend or enemy.</p>
<p>new: A-grunt heavy<br>
info: an A-grunt with almost tank like armor and two hive hands, is almost immune to any none explosive damage, would only be seen in surface tension and xen.</p>
<p>bullsquid<br>
changes<br>
*grapple attack: will try and grab the player preventing them from running before tail whipping them knocking them down.</p>
<p>hound eyes<br>
changes<br>
*directed shock wave, rarely a hound eye may start charging its attack out of the range of the player only to seen a directed pulse at the player, this does more damage but also hurts the hound eye.<br>
[/spoiler]</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/more-difficulties/14475/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/more-difficulties/14475/2</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 24 Nov 2015 04:13:14 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14475-2</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/more-difficulties/14475.rss">More Difficulties.</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>More Difficulties.</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Rainman89]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>First off i hope i am posting this in the correct area if not please move it. Dear Developers before you release the final part of the game could you please add 2 more difficulties to the game for us that are not faint of heart.</p>
<p>Difficulties:<br>
<span class="bbcode-b">Very Hard</span>: 2x more damage to Freeman and Enemies than Hard difficulty.<br>
<span class="bbcode-b">Unforeseen Consequences</span>: 2x more damage to Freeman and Enemies than Very Hard difficulty.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/more-difficulties/14475/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/more-difficulties/14475/1</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Nov 2015 22:09:18 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14475-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/more-difficulties/14475.rss">More Difficulties.</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
