<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Opinions over the HECU</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/opinions-over-the-hecu/12522</link>
    <description>I think the HECU are such meaningful characters of the game that they deserved their own thread, for people to express their thoughts over their gameplay and character. 
So I’ll start by expressing some thoughts and ideas I had over them myself. (Watch out for the wall of text)

[b]The non-human developer’s idea[/b]

The developers “apparently” wanted the grunts to seem quite inhuman for people not to feel sympathy over them, but this is quite an odd statement, as when you hear the soldier’s  speeches, they do seem human (even though they may be a bit cartoony), especially how they respond to the player’s actions.  And them feeling more human shouldn’t really be the main reason for players to feel sympathy towards the grunts, if that’s what the team really wants to achieve, it’s their character, but I’ll discuss their character later. However I do wish to point out that their idle speeches should be improved, I mean they have ONLY 4 idle speeches in which 2 are the famous lines “Do iiit” (Do what?) and “I’m tired of playing games” (Is this supposed to make them sound badass? Like “Bring the fight” kind of thing, I never got this one) , this 2 lines along the “Agh he got me” should be considered to be removed. They should also use their “mission” speeches more often, since they are rarely heard. In fact, I think they could have predetermined idle speeches, for certain parts of the game, eg. In parts were you are constantly battling them, maybe after taking down a squad, you could hear: “We lost contact with zulu, moving in to investigate” while they head to your direction, or maybe in some others as you approach them hear: “Deliah 3 is not responding, should we investigate?  *HQ: Negative Romeo you’re to hold your position* Roger HQ, Squad hold positions!”  This could also show professionalism in a little way, since people complain about them not feeling very professional.

Now gameplay wise, yes they seem very inhuman due to their reaction and aim, but we already know that, and the devs are probably doing their best to fix this. But aside from that I thought that their Ai could also see a great improvement if they also reacted to other things than the player.  For example: When barrels or any other explosive material blows up near them but does not kill them, they could tumble from the blast and get back up from the ground to continue fighting; or you could see them sometimes patrolling areas, not just waiting for the player; also after battling aliens and some surviving, they should regroup, this one could be applied to the scene in the second map of default on a rail, when after killing the vorts, they just go idle in the positions they were during the fight, instead they could regroup in the middle of the zone if they haven’t seen freeman and if their squad leader is still alive, you could see him head in first, and use his “regroup” animation while the rest of the soldiers head to him. Aside from that maybe they should give them also more idle animations, some to be maybe in predetermined parts of the game and some others to be ramdom. I have made some possible candidates in SFM (Forgive me for not being the best quality as my SFM was constantly crashing and limiting my improvements):

Idle 1: Which is the Deafault by Black mesa     
Idle 2: (for the hl fans  :wink:  )To be random along idle 1 (yes I know, he’s holding it with the wrong hand)
![](upload://p7HWIDL3R63EUo80njCkhpXGEor.jpeg)

Idle 3: (Sitting down) maybe in certain parts were the HECU is keeping a look out and may be tired from battle (possibly in on a rail since its nighttime) or where they control an area which they believe to be of low risk (Maybe around QE and the beginning of ST, I could totally see them like this in c2a5b and C2a5d)
Idle 4: (Resting mp5 in arm) to be random too (Yes, wrong hand again)
![](upload://6tJR2wxZJmpTMb7EtCDmKRbbaEV.jpeg)

Idle 5: (Fatigued) To be seen in places where the HECU has battled aliens, near their corpses, could also be seen along 3
Idle 6: (Resting) To be like 3, I think at some points of the game hatless soldiers could be seen too, to imply they were not expecting an attack
![](upload://t8rGwRUsXiYKOvNn8pww6KMAuTp.jpeg)

[b]The HECU’s character[/b]
(My post has already been huge, I don’t know if this should have a thread on its own, as its almost as big as the first one)

Now many people conflict towards the Dev’s decision over the HECU’s character decision and I can see where they’re coming from. In half life, the HECU’s character was not really touched that much aside from them seeming to be professional and that they were there to kill you.  However this did bring a sense of moral ambiguity as the player would imagine them being just or unjust mainly due to game progression.  In current black mesa this is no longer there because their characters have been touched more than in the original half-life, which is not a bad thing, especially by the fact that they no longer feel like robots and feel more human (irony for the dev’s original idea uh?).  But sadly this sense of moral ambiguity is gone because the player gets to hear more informal speeches from them, and they feel overall like plain assholes, now let me explain my reasoning behind this: At the beginning its ok that they feel like that with the “no one’s fought back” speech, and that the player then questions himself with the  “I didn’t sign up for this shit” speech and QE, but then the “rape” speech reminds you that they’re assholes again, this one’s the killer as it takes away the Questionable from “Questionable ethics”.  But I think this can be corrected by adding more speeches at certain parts of the game, I’ve thought of 2 scenes that could maybe do the trick:

1) 2 HECU’s  talking during QE (could probably be added around the beginning or be the 2 that are walking the hallway before the Agrunts)

[COLOR=&#39;DarkGreen&#39;]You know, when I first heard the objectives I thought HQ had gone insane, but now that I see all this...

[COLOR=&#39;Lime&#39;]Yeah, these guys were playing with fire and got what they deserved.

[COLOR=&#39;DarkGreen&#39;]I guess I can see why the aliens are so pissed, well if they can think anyways

(amused)[COLOR=&#39;lime&#39;] Yeah sure, try talking to frankensquid.

2) 3 HECU’s discuss over freeman, 2 which are taking a break (For this one I think the best spot for it to happen is if the player takes the first pipe exit at the right of the first tank battle, at C2a5d, I think even idle 3 and 6 could be used for this 2 soldiers at the scene)

[COLOR=&#39;Cyan&#39;]What are you two doing? This is no time for breaks; uglies can strike at any moment 

[COLOR=&#39;Lime&#39;]Relax, just look around, there’s no way anything is getting past us

[COLOR=&#39;Green&#39;]Yeah! Any alien that comes this way will get his ass royally boned

[COLOR=&#39;Cyan&#39;]It’s not the aliens I’m worried about, is this freeman guy

[COLOR=&#39;Lime&#39;]You really believe in this freeman crap, I mean one guy doing all this by himself...

[COLOR=&#39;Green&#39;]Yeah HQ must be confusing BMRF resistance with him, I mean didn’t some guys capture him already?

[COLOR=&#39;Cyan&#39;]Don’t think so, I heard radio chatter about him reappearing again and taking down Sierra and Quebec. Hell I heard he took down a helo!

[COLOR=&#39;Lime&#39;]Ok that’s just ridiculous

[COLOR=&#39;Cyan&#39;]How are you sure? I heard an explosion not so long ago, like a crash, what if that’s the helo? What if he is here? 

[COLOR=&#39;Lime&#39;]There are explosions everywhere! I’m surprised this place hasn’t blown up already!

[COLOR=&#39;Green&#39;]He is not coming here don’t worry

(When freeman is already partly out of the pipe)
*All three turn around and look at you* Huh?  IT’S FREEEMAN! 
 
I also think maybe hearing more lines from HQ, as it was in the missile launch scene, would also be a nice feature, to remind the player that the soldiers are taking orders, and are not just gunning people down for fun, also this could show some professionalism as well. I also thought about a possible last speech if the HQ voice was included: 

*There’s a dead hecu next to the door’s switch leading to the Lambda complex, just behind the sentrys, as the player approaches static is heard from his helmet* This  is HQ, the operation is over, the last birds have already lift off, if you have evacuated, congratulations, if you haven’t, your sacrifice shall be honored… HQ out.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2013 23:39:03 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>The Cafeteria</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/opinions-over-the-hecu/12522.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Opinions over the HECU</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[OrderOfDagon]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Every HECU model should be reskinned with Jesus. It would only improve the game, honestly.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/opinions-over-the-hecu/12522/49">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/opinions-over-the-hecu/12522/49</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2013 23:39:03 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12522-49</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/opinions-over-the-hecu/12522.rss">Opinions over the HECU</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Opinions over the HECU</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[raw_bean]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Let he who wants to lose his motherfucking kneecaps cast the first stone, bitches.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/opinions-over-the-hecu/12522/48">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/opinions-over-the-hecu/12522/48</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2013 22:34:58 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12522-48</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/opinions-over-the-hecu/12522.rss">Opinions over the HECU</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Opinions over the HECU</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[danielsangeo]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><img src="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/original/3X/6/4/649b8e504d075b06db997386da5102efd28ef756.jpeg" alt="" data-base62-sha1="em11us1O6AqaAL2MB6gszcfE0qq" width="467" height="238"></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/opinions-over-the-hecu/12522/47">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/opinions-over-the-hecu/12522/47</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2013 19:30:59 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12522-47</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/opinions-over-the-hecu/12522.rss">Opinions over the HECU</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Opinions over the HECU</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[raw_bean]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="OrderOfDagon">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/user_avatar/leakfree.org/orderofdagon/40/4963_2.png" class="avatar"> OrderOfDagon:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>My opinion of the HECU: They must have the <span class="bbcode-b">training of christ</span> because they seem to be able to snapshot me in the face from over 15 meters away without even flinching – even on easy mode.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>It’s true folks, Jesus Christ was a headshot master.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/opinions-over-the-hecu/12522/46">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/opinions-over-the-hecu/12522/46</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2013 17:31:02 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12522-46</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/opinions-over-the-hecu/12522.rss">Opinions over the HECU</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Opinions over the HECU</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[OrderOfDagon]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><span class="bbcode-b">My opinion of the HECU</span>: They must have the training of christ because they seem to be able to snapshot me in the face from over 15 meters away without even flinching – even on easy mode.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">About the backpacks, and a bit more:</span> Should definitely bring them back, because they look a bit unassuming without them. I always thought the huge-ass testosterone-pumped elite military force was way fucking intimidating; it felt like a play on your concept of yourself, as if you thought you were this one-man army up until the point when they came in, and they made you rethink just how equipped and tough you were by being fucking manly as all hell. It kinds reminded me of the bad-guys from The Rock movie with Nick Cage and Sean Connery… Anyways, I also enjoyed their very specific AI in the original Half-Life, as it provided a much needed change of pace in combat – something that the game heavily relies on to keep it interesting as the whole game is just a shooting spree. That change of pace is something that seems a bit out-of-touch in Black Mesa, where they just seem to be a bit robotic, much like the Combine. It just seemed that everyone was doing something different in the original Half-life. For instance, most soldiers on contact would run to cover, others would flush you out in a direction you weren’t facing, and the rest would be lopping grenades at my nearest cover while screaming scary things in their walkie-talkies making me anxious. All of which the big backpacks full of special who-knows-what gave them an interesting appearance when compared to COD-style basic looking gear.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">And NemesisVSJill:</span> I love your post. Too many people ignore the atmosphere that their characters give off, and it’s always important to me. I can’t possibly care about engineers and medics when they wouldn’t feel right to begin with… cool name by the way.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/opinions-over-the-hecu/12522/45">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/opinions-over-the-hecu/12522/45</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2013 11:21:07 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12522-45</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/opinions-over-the-hecu/12522.rss">Opinions over the HECU</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Opinions over the HECU</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[ysrael214]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>The engineers may appear in the QE ambush and Lambda Core. That ambush wasn’t in Half-Life and it didn’t break the canon much.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/opinions-over-the-hecu/12522/44">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/opinions-over-the-hecu/12522/44</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2013 10:06:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12522-44</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/opinions-over-the-hecu/12522.rss">Opinions over the HECU</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Opinions over the HECU</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Dominus_Tempus]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="bur">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/b/87869e/40.png" class="avatar"> bur:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Yeah, it’s not like shit like this “breaks the canon” or anything</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Seriously though, there is not a single reason why something realistic like that could not be implemented. Saying that it shouldn’t be put in the game just because it wasn’t in the original is flawed logic.</p>
<p>Honestly, I think a large part of the appeal of Black Mesa is the fact that the team was enhancing the original with many things that weren’t there before.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/opinions-over-the-hecu/12522/43">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/opinions-over-the-hecu/12522/43</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2013 16:19:20 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12522-43</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/opinions-over-the-hecu/12522.rss">Opinions over the HECU</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Opinions over the HECU</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Han_Shot_First]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>They do have specific voice acting. The Young Human Grunt Voices are the voices for the medics. They really do need to fix the regular HECU voice acting though… and the AI… They look cool though, so I guess that is a plus. Maybe add a little bit of variance like the joint ops mod? I play with the joint ops mod, and it looks much better.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/opinions-over-the-hecu/12522/42">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/opinions-over-the-hecu/12522/42</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2013 12:42:34 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12522-42</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/opinions-over-the-hecu/12522.rss">Opinions over the HECU</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Opinions over the HECU</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[skyace65]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Joe chief">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Joe chief:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Well the medics are in the game, and I think that was a good decission by the devs, as for the engineers, I imagine they didn’t really find somewhere to fit them in.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>okay I just noticed the medics after looking specifically for them. they need some more obvious markings to show they are medics.</p>
<p>if they could do that and add in all the other variants(and fix voice acting) than it would be fantastic</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/opinions-over-the-hecu/12522/41">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/opinions-over-the-hecu/12522/41</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2013 02:24:38 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12522-41</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/opinions-over-the-hecu/12522.rss">Opinions over the HECU</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Opinions over the HECU</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[bur]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Yeah, it’s not like shit like this “breaks the canon” or anything</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/opinions-over-the-hecu/12522/40">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/opinions-over-the-hecu/12522/40</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2013 14:24:06 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12522-40</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/opinions-over-the-hecu/12522.rss">Opinions over the HECU</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Opinions over the HECU</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Swaggless]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="JeffMOD">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/user_avatar/leakfree.org/jeffmod/40/4333_2.png" class="avatar"> JeffMOD:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Okay, but when did that happen in Half-Life?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>No where… but this is Black Mesa, not Half-Life…</p>
<p>Not that they SHOULD put it in, however, the fact that it wasn’t in Half-Life shouldn’t stop them from implementing it, should they find it creates fun gameplay that can be integrated well into the existing game.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/opinions-over-the-hecu/12522/39">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/opinions-over-the-hecu/12522/39</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2013 13:33:21 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12522-39</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/opinions-over-the-hecu/12522.rss">Opinions over the HECU</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Opinions over the HECU</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[JeffMOD]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Okay, but when did that happen in Half-Life?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/opinions-over-the-hecu/12522/38">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/opinions-over-the-hecu/12522/38</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2013 11:32:20 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12522-38</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/opinions-over-the-hecu/12522.rss">Opinions over the HECU</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Opinions over the HECU</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Dr_Maxwell]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>They can blowtorch doors away, allowing for Combine-style entrances.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/opinions-over-the-hecu/12522/37">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/opinions-over-the-hecu/12522/37</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2013 00:13:47 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12522-37</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/opinions-over-the-hecu/12522.rss">Opinions over the HECU</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Opinions over the HECU</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Joe_chief]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Well the medics are in the game, and I think that was a good decission by the devs, as for the engineers, I imagine they didn’t really find somewhere to fit them in.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/opinions-over-the-hecu/12522/36">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/opinions-over-the-hecu/12522/36</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2013 19:20:13 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12522-36</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/opinions-over-the-hecu/12522.rss">Opinions over the HECU</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Opinions over the HECU</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[skyace65]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I’ll never understand the devs with trying to make you not feel sympathy for them. the original didn’t have any problems so why change it now? and valve licensed an entire expansion pack to show you the soldier point of view and how they had it just as bad</p>
<p>more dialogue would be great but I’d also prefer the current lines redone with the VAs not told to sound ridiculous.</p>
<p>actually one thing i really would like is to bring in some of the different character models Opposing force added like medics and engineers(i think there were a few more) just to give them some visual variety</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/opinions-over-the-hecu/12522/35">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/opinions-over-the-hecu/12522/35</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 23 Nov 2013 19:38:33 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12522-35</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/opinions-over-the-hecu/12522.rss">Opinions over the HECU</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Opinions over the HECU</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Nemesisvsjill]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Ok, here’s my interpretation of the HECU in Half-Life, then Black Mesa.</p>
<p><a href="https://images3.wikia.nocookie.net/__cb20090802164207/half-life/en/images/a/a8/HECU_orig_models.jpg" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://images3.wikia.nocookie.net/__cb20090802164207/half-life/en/images/a/a8/HECU_orig_models.jpg</a><br>
Confident badasses, war veterans who can fight in extreme situations such as Black Mesa, and still kick the alien’s ass at first. Tough and competent guys who don’t talk much, shoot and throw a lot of grenades. But in the end, still humans. Some of them would be reluctant to shooting scientist (but would do so anyway because that’s their orders), while some others would take pleasure from doing it. They look extremely cool, you could just figure out each model’s personnality just by looking at it (like, that beret wearing guy who looks like a damn sadist, or that balaclava one who might be the silent type…). They are extremely strong and charismatic, and their speeches sound nice too (for instance, when a soldier gets hit, he would sometime shout “IS THAT ALL YOU GOT ?”, or “YOU GOT NOTHING !”.<br>
In a nutshell, hardcore professionals.</p>
<p><a href="https://www.majhost.com/gallery/sgtpieman/BMWIP/bm_c2a5d0006.jpg" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://www.majhost.com/gallery/sgtpieman/BMWIP/bm_c2a5d0006.jpg</a><br>
Gross incompetents who should be lucky to have a job. Young sadist douchebags and one-liner-shouting David-Hayter impersonnators, who do evil stuff for no good reason. They all look and sound completely random. They are not war veterans, they are not badasses, and they are certainly not good enough to survive the very hostile environment of Black Mesa. They don’t look particularly good (like those who aren’t wearing any gloves at all. The options should be either fingerless gloves or full gloves. No gloves ? Meh)</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/opinions-over-the-hecu/12522/34">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/opinions-over-the-hecu/12522/34</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2013 18:31:22 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12522-34</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/opinions-over-the-hecu/12522.rss">Opinions over the HECU</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Opinions over the HECU</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Zeroniz0]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="urcousinvinnie5">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/u/b9bd4f/40.png" class="avatar"> urcousinvinnie5:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>just like the HECU skins I say the backpacks should be put on at random. Some models without them and some with them. just like the gas masks, helmets, and the chest packs</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Good idea.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/opinions-over-the-hecu/12522/33">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/opinions-over-the-hecu/12522/33</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2013 08:23:44 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12522-33</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/opinions-over-the-hecu/12522.rss">Opinions over the HECU</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Opinions over the HECU</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[urcousinvinnie5]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>just like the HECU skins I say the backpacks should be put on at random. Some models without them and some with them. just like the gas masks, helmets, and the chest packs</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/opinions-over-the-hecu/12522/32">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/opinions-over-the-hecu/12522/32</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2013 04:30:51 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12522-32</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/opinions-over-the-hecu/12522.rss">Opinions over the HECU</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Opinions over the HECU</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypt]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>^<br>
I’m sure as soon as the BM source code is released someone will at least attempt to do so.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/opinions-over-the-hecu/12522/31">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/opinions-over-the-hecu/12522/31</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 20 Oct 2013 15:48:01 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12522-31</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/opinions-over-the-hecu/12522.rss">Opinions over the HECU</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Opinions over the HECU</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[bur]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>no they haven’t, he’s talking about an opposing force mod for black mesa, not something like tripmine’s stuff</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/opinions-over-the-hecu/12522/30">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/opinions-over-the-hecu/12522/30</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 20 Oct 2013 15:27:35 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12522-30</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/opinions-over-the-hecu/12522.rss">Opinions over the HECU</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Opinions over the HECU</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Gordon_Fishman]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Swaggless">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/s/a698b9/40.png" class="avatar"> Swaggless:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Yeah, backpacks would be good. During my playthough of Op4 recently, I was noticing how the HECU had backpacks, and the Black Ops did not. It gave them different silhouettes, and made it easier to tell who was who. This would come in handy if someone were to make Black Mesa: Opposing Force.</p>
<p>But it’s also good for that classic feel.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Um, hate to break this to you buddy, bust someone has been…for a long time…</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/opinions-over-the-hecu/12522/29">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/opinions-over-the-hecu/12522/29</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 20 Oct 2013 00:52:09 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12522-29</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/opinions-over-the-hecu/12522.rss">Opinions over the HECU</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Opinions over the HECU</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[subatomic]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I’m almost finished playing the original Half-Life, and the truth is I don’t like the HECU voices in Black Mesa: Source <span class="bbcode-b">or</span> Half-Life. The BMS HECU is over-the-top in a bad way, but at least they sound like humans - albeit comically evil humans. The Half-Life HECU voices sound like robots. Every. Line. Is. Made. Of. Separate. Words. It works okay in the original game because I’m adjusted to the various limitations given the game’s age, but when I tried OldDirtyBastard’s <a href="https://forums.blackmesasource.com/showthread.php?t=14675" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">HECU Radio chatter swap</a> for BMS, the clipped speech stuck out like a sore thumb. It’s only a genuine improvement with the scripted sequences. (The dialogue swap directly following Apprehension is a huge step in the right direction.)</p>
<p>Like others, I have to wonder why the HECU in BMS are a bunch of David Hayter-impersonating jerks. I’ve read that the dev team didn’t want us to sympathize with them, but I’m not sure I get that explanation. It doesn’t matter to me if they sound like normal guys, they’re trying to kill me. I’m not going to hesitate shooting them if they’re shooting me.</p>
<p>What I have to wonder is if the decision isn’t more about not disrespecting actual soldiers. “Support Our Troops” has become a 21st century mantra, and I think this culture of ultimate respect and admiration for the men and women fighting in the armed forces has influenced the decision to portray the HECU as comically evil. The idea is that our brothers and fathers and friends wouldn’t do what the HECU is doing, they’d never participate in the slaughter of civilian scientists, especially on their own soil. The recent spate of public shootings I think also has played into it. In American culture, it’s one thing to watch/play an American character killing German or Japanese soldiers in WWII, or Chechen terrorists in 2012, it’s another to have Americans killing Americans. That’s just not done, right? Thus, the decision to make the HECU over-the-top comic villains who couldn’t possibly be normal average Joes. No disrespect, because these are not human beings, they’re monsters in camo.</p>
<p>If that’s the true reason, it’s one I can understand. That being said, maybe we <span class="bbcode-i">should</span> sympathize with the HECU, maybe I should question the morality of what I’m doing and who I’m working for. We’ve unleashed an apocalypse through sheer hubris. We’re mad scientists blowing up the world because we can. A more human HECU is not going to stop me from eliminating immediate threats to my life, but it will leave me with a deeper, more complex set of emotions at the end of a run and I like that.</p>
<p>edit: sorry if I’m way off base here. It’s only the really good stuff that gets me thinking like this, so it’s a testament to the game’s brilliance!</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/opinions-over-the-hecu/12522/28">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/opinions-over-the-hecu/12522/28</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2013 18:07:20 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12522-28</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/opinions-over-the-hecu/12522.rss">Opinions over the HECU</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Opinions over the HECU</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[RHYS4190]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Swaggless">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/s/a698b9/40.png" class="avatar"> Swaggless:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I like the idea of extra idles, and having the soldiers patrol. I was playing Op4 today, and was noticing how my squad would patrol around and check areas around me, and thought that it’d be neat to see HECU in BM do the same. I like the idea of more HECU dialogue, but not TOO much. Maybe 1 or 2 new scenes, tops. The only problem with the speeches you have written out is that they seem a bit long. Most dialogues that don’t contain gameplay/objective information are much shorter. I DO think some more idle dialogue amongst soldiers is CERTAINLY in order. (See “Doo iit”). A statement &amp; response system would be nice. Like the scientists and HL2 rebels. Re-do some of the lines to make them more human, and I think that’s all I’ll need to make the grunts more… relate-able. They’re humans just thrown into this situation just like the BMRF personal. Granted, they are more prepared, but they are are also still people.</p>
<p>Long story short: More idle animations, patrolling soldiers, new voices, more idle dialogue, and maybe 1 or 2 new short dialogues, please!</p>
<p>Oh, and hand gestures, like the Combine.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>well I did not get that in hl2 they say the vorgiuns where actually slave’s I mean interloper really to me when I was 10 looked more like a mining complex.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/opinions-over-the-hecu/12522/27">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/opinions-over-the-hecu/12522/27</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2013 01:01:36 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12522-27</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/opinions-over-the-hecu/12522.rss">Opinions over the HECU</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Opinions over the HECU</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[BendyBread]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Han_Shot_First">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/h/f04885/40.png" class="avatar"> Han_Shot_First:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I don’t want a “dumber AI”, I want a better designed one. I want an AI that makes me plan out my attack, and makes me think about where I should go. An AI that makes me cover my flanks, and doesn’t make me feel to comfortable just camping in one spot. The current AI doesn’t make me do any of those things. It needs to be fixed.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Prime example being the big fight in QE. Unless you’ve played it before or go through it 45 times to practice, you’re pretty much sniping from the stairs and then eventually doing cleaning up.</p>
<p>I had absolutely no fun with that except for the bad ass music.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/opinions-over-the-hecu/12522/26">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/opinions-over-the-hecu/12522/26</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 08 Sep 2013 10:12:45 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12522-26</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/opinions-over-the-hecu/12522.rss">Opinions over the HECU</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Opinions over the HECU</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Han_Shot_First]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I don’t want a “dumber AI”, I want a better designed one. I want an AI that makes me plan out my attack, and makes me think about where I should go. An AI that makes me cover my flanks, and doesn’t make me feel to comfortable just camping in one spot. The current AI doesn’t make me do any of those things. It needs to be fixed.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/opinions-over-the-hecu/12522/25">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/opinions-over-the-hecu/12522/25</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 07 Sep 2013 07:30:41 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12522-25</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/opinions-over-the-hecu/12522.rss">Opinions over the HECU</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
