<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>a few thoughts</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/a-few-thoughts/9840</link>
    <description>So I want to post a few thoughts about my experience with BM .

First of all, great job devs!
It&#39;s a really stunning game, all the waiting really was worth it.

Well, while the overall game is awesome there are a few minor annoyances:
1. Ladders: they are somewhat terrible. Either you&#39;re glued to them or you don&#39;t get on them(sometimes while falling etc).
Also the movement on there is not optimal at all.
Sometimes I climbed up and then wanted to get down again and pressed &quot;s&quot; instead of &quot;w&quot; but I still climbed up for some reason(and died a few times because of that).

2. The Heli and Tank in Surface Tension at the cliff: This damn heli eats up 8 rockets and a armored tank just needs 3? something with the balancing seems to be a bit off there.

3. Jumping: the normal jumping height is not in anyway useful, maybe for jumping over cans but nothing else. I don&#39;t remember that HL had this awkward jumping.

4. random crashes/crashes while map loads with activated flashlight.

5. The Crowbar swing animation: it looks very stiff, you would expect a full swing in the air instead it&#39;s stopping rather abruptly.

6. Crawling animation: the pelvis looks rather flat and it looks kinda awkward... well but this is really a very minor issue. 
![](upload://2jll6wax7QcLOwlugWJpx05eaWM.jpeg)

7. Assassin model: The assassins lower and upper body don&#39;t seem to be connected correctly:
![](upload://5IAuDLrzHBBtr7YTR3BLxLVNDmH.jpeg)
![](upload://6IOcsInoGUvp6pOKBSSnnTcdLgt.jpeg)


That&#39;s it so far, if I find anything else I&#39;ll post again in this thread.

Thanks for this awesome mod!</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 23 Nov 2012 14:25:33 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>The Cafeteria</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/a-few-thoughts/9840.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>a few thoughts</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Flatline]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="BendyBread">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/user_avatar/leakfree.org/bendybread/40/4457_2.png" class="avatar"> BendyBread:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>You’re on the BM forums. Most people here are HL1 elitists/“veterans”. Have an opinion on something that doesn’t match the hivemind? Get the shit abused out of you by the crazies.</p>
<p>It’s really quite unfortunate because you can’t have proper discussions and chat about things when everyone either acts like a 12 year old throwing a tantrum, just blatantly hates you, or has an overall superiority complex about them. It’s even worse when the mods aren’t much different at times.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Please don’t tar people with one brush. I think we’ve got a pretty decent community going here since the post-launch reboot. And if you have a problem with one of the moderators, feel free to send us a PM.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/a-few-thoughts/9840/30">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/a-few-thoughts/9840/30</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 23 Nov 2012 14:25:33 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9840-30</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/a-few-thoughts/9840.rss">a few thoughts</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>a few thoughts</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[noonem]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Lost one">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Lost one:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Did you really play the original half life or are you just saying you did? Because from what you said, you sound more like you enjoy call of duty than what the half life series has to offer.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Holy fuck, I must’ve offended you so much for you to bust out “I BET THIS GUY LIKES CALL OF DUTY.” First off, I’m talking about Black Mesa and how the level design in a few places felt confusing to me and didn’t make much sense when comparing to Half Life.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Lost one">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Lost one:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>First off, Crouch jumping has been in the half life series since the first half life. When you get to Xen, you’ll find just how much you have to rely on ctrl+space for long jumping. So getting the crouch jumping down now is a necessity anyways.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Jesus. It’s like you didn’t even read what I said. Jump crouching is annoying in Black Mesa. It’s wasn’t annoying in Half-Life. It feels fluid in HL and HL2. But here it’s frustrating and just takes a while longer to get used to.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Lost one">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Lost one:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Second, there’s nothing wrong with Residue Processing. I was able to clear that chapter with relatively few problems. Nothing a little Exploration can’t solve. The idea with the game isn’t how fast you can complete it. It’s how well you do, the more you explore the more likely you’re going to survive the next encounter.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>There’s not much to explore. It’s the remade level design isn’t that good. Stop taking this so seriously, I still enjoyed the mod. What, am I like not able to dislike things you like or something?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/a-few-thoughts/9840/29">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/a-few-thoughts/9840/29</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 19 Sep 2012 15:24:18 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9840-29</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/a-few-thoughts/9840.rss">a few thoughts</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>a few thoughts</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Pudding]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Tinker">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/t/e47774/40.png" class="avatar"> Tinker:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Also, i found one more “hole” in this game. I don’t think i was supposed to go that way.  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/frowning.png?v=9" title=":frowning:" class="emoji" alt=":frowning:"><br>
<a href="https://youtu.be/9xa4DdHRJi4" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://youtu.be/9xa4DdHRJi4</a></p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>lol nice job finding that glitch  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/smiley.png?v=9" title=":smiley:" class="emoji" alt=":smiley:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/a-few-thoughts/9840/28">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/a-few-thoughts/9840/28</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 16 Sep 2012 21:00:04 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9840-28</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/a-few-thoughts/9840.rss">a few thoughts</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>a few thoughts</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Dotard]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Tinker">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/t/e47774/40.png" class="avatar"> Tinker:</div>
<blockquote>
<p><a href="https://youtu.be/9xa4DdHRJi4" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://youtu.be/9xa4DdHRJi4</a></p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>that’s because you aren’t supposed to follow Gman, the scripted scene didn’t occur  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/smiley.png?v=9" title=":smiley:" class="emoji" alt=":smiley:">  only later with the hound already dead, lol</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/a-few-thoughts/9840/27">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/a-few-thoughts/9840/27</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 16 Sep 2012 18:22:34 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9840-27</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/a-few-thoughts/9840.rss">a few thoughts</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>a few thoughts</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Tinker]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I got my guard at the beginning dead to get his gun so i could save a scientist from two headcrabs some rooms later. Sadly, i couldnt save him. The entire scene was scripted and both headcrabs weren’t real.  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/frowning.png?v=9" title=":frowning:" class="emoji" alt=":frowning:"></p>
<p>The game is awesome, although there are a couple of things i was dissapointed with.</p>
<p>Why did devs cut of the game that big segment of Surface Tension chapter before Garg?</p>
<p>Is it just me or this game realy is too shiny? Most of it’s surfaces look like they have been oiled. I tried to reduce this effect but i only found commands to completely disable specular maps. Is there any way to slightly reduse specular lighting without disabling it?</p>
<hr>
<p>Also, i found one more “hole” in this game. I don’t think i was supposed to go that way.  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/frowning.png?v=9" title=":frowning:" class="emoji" alt=":frowning:"><br>
<a href="https://youtu.be/9xa4DdHRJi4" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://youtu.be/9xa4DdHRJi4</a></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/a-few-thoughts/9840/26">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/a-few-thoughts/9840/26</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 16 Sep 2012 18:04:06 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9840-26</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/a-few-thoughts/9840.rss">a few thoughts</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>a few thoughts</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Lost_one]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="noonem">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/n/d9b06d/40.png" class="avatar"> noonem:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Everything was fine, I was enjoying the mod and praising it, and then I got to Residue Processing. And I don’t know if someone else designed these maps, or what but they are god damn frustrating. Even more so than they are in Half-Life.</p>
<p>There’s the room where the pipe explodes, that was also confusing because it really doesn’t look like you’d be able to jump over that fence, because let’s be honest, the jumping isn’t that great in this mod. Like the op said, regular jumping is useless. You have to push ctrl to jump over EVERYTHING. It’s made me realise how much I fucking hate jumping in first person shooters.<br>
And then there’s the worst offence. What happens after it. That rotating-radiation jumpy thingy. When I first looked at, I didn’t even realise that it was that. Plus, there’s no indication that you’re supposed to jump on it, it literally looks like you’ll fall in as soon as you do.<br>
I don’t even want to talk about what happened next. I got to the part with the poopy sewage water, and I spent 20 minutes in that shit, with no idea where I was going, what I was doing, when those frustrating minutes were over and I found myself near the dead security guard. I had no idea what I had done to get there. No fucking clue. In Half-Life, sure some parts got frustrating, you still understood what you had to do, where you had to go. In Black Mesa, at least in Residue Processing, I’m able fucking finish the map and still have no idea what I did. The next parts were okay, but I still had a bad taste in my mouth after all of that shit.</p>
<p>That was a really disappointing chapter, and I don’t dislike the mod. Hell, I’ve even liked a chapter here and there even more than the original. Unforeseen Consequences was  amazing.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Did you really play the original half life or are you just saying you did? Because from what you said, you sound more like you enjoy call of duty than what the half life series has to offer.</p>
<p>First off, Crouch jumping has been in the half life series since the first half life. When you get to Xen, you’ll find just how much you have to rely on ctrl+space for long jumping. So getting the crouch jumping down now is a necessity anyways.</p>
<p>Second, there’s nothing wrong with Residue Processing. I was able to clear that chapter with relatively few problems. Nothing a little Exploration can’t solve. The idea with the game isn’t how fast you can complete it. It’s how well you do, the more you explore the more likely you’re going to survive the next encounter.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/a-few-thoughts/9840/25">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/a-few-thoughts/9840/25</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 16 Sep 2012 16:45:05 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9840-25</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/a-few-thoughts/9840.rss">a few thoughts</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>a few thoughts</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[ZindroVokun]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I didn’t know the guard could die, the zombies beat on mine for about a minute and he stayed up, so I assumed he was a tutorial guard, there to teach players the value of having guards follow you by making you rely on him?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/a-few-thoughts/9840/24">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/a-few-thoughts/9840/24</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 16 Sep 2012 16:25:41 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9840-24</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/a-few-thoughts/9840.rss">a few thoughts</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>a few thoughts</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[robot_deodorant]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I think I found a crowbar holding a door shut. It was my first weapon also…</p>
<p>The ladders did seem touchy, but after a while I got used to them. Jumping was biggest annoyance. Trying not to set off those trip mines… ahhh… I think I spent over an hour in that one room alone.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/a-few-thoughts/9840/23">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/a-few-thoughts/9840/23</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 16 Sep 2012 16:04:11 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9840-23</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/a-few-thoughts/9840.rss">a few thoughts</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>a few thoughts</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[PlausibleSarge]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="FERGUS">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/f/bbce88/40.png" class="avatar"> FERGUS:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>My first weapon was the crowbar because my guard didn’t die.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>This</p>
<p>I still think either the guard should be later or the crowbar earlier though. there is just something iconic about crowbar first.</p>
<p>That being said, HL2 Episode 1 and 2 didn’t start with the crowbar, and they play fine</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/a-few-thoughts/9840/22">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/a-few-thoughts/9840/22</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 16 Sep 2012 15:54:03 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9840-22</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/a-few-thoughts/9840.rss">a few thoughts</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>a few thoughts</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[FERGUS]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>My first weapon was the crowbar because my guard didn’t die.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/a-few-thoughts/9840/21">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/a-few-thoughts/9840/21</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 16 Sep 2012 15:45:08 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9840-21</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/a-few-thoughts/9840.rss">a few thoughts</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>a few thoughts</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[pfannkuchen_gesicht]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>oh btw, the first “weapon” of gordon was a bit disappointing and also not very true to the HL series.<br>
Why not the crowbar?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/a-few-thoughts/9840/20">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/a-few-thoughts/9840/20</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 16 Sep 2012 14:12:38 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9840-20</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/a-few-thoughts/9840.rss">a few thoughts</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>a few thoughts</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Frogacuda]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="pfannkuchen_gesicht">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/p/ee7513/40.png" class="avatar"> pfannkuchen_gesicht:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Jumping: the normal jumping height is not in anyway useful, maybe for jumping over cans but nothing else. I don’t remember that HL had this awkward jumping.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>The jump height and the height at which you can automatically walk up something (like a step) appear to be roughly the same. I haven’t found one object in the game that you can jump on that you can’t just walk up. I don’t mind that the crouch jump is still a core mechanic, but it’s pretty silly to make the jump literally useless on its own.</p>
<p>I just went in the skill.cfg and upped the jumping height, and it doesn’t seem to break any puzzles, so all is right with the world. I hope they tweak this in future official releases, it seems like a common complaint.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/a-few-thoughts/9840/19">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/a-few-thoughts/9840/19</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 15 Sep 2012 23:05:50 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9840-19</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/a-few-thoughts/9840.rss">a few thoughts</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>a few thoughts</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypt]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I only had difficulty Surface Tension and figuring out how to activate the pump/coolant system for the second tank, and that was more me overlooking small details.</p>
<p>The jumping <span class="bbcode-i">was</span> very low, though, seemingly like they had crouch jumping over everything in mind. But that level design, oh my god was that amazing.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/a-few-thoughts/9840/18">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/a-few-thoughts/9840/18</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 15 Sep 2012 21:22:27 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9840-18</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/a-few-thoughts/9840.rss">a few thoughts</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>a few thoughts</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Dotard]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Source Engine’s underwater “visibility” made it kinda worse ^_ not to mention the annoying “drowning shader”</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/a-few-thoughts/9840/17">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/a-few-thoughts/9840/17</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 15 Sep 2012 21:14:56 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9840-17</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/a-few-thoughts/9840.rss">a few thoughts</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>a few thoughts</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[FrontLineAssembly]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Yeah, that’s what i thought too but i didn’t find Residue Processing to last so long compared to the other chapters. Apprehension was really annoying though, but it was like that in the original too, dammit underwater exploring with the cargo truck (whatever that green vehicle was) in the way making me think that you aren’t supposed to go that way.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/a-few-thoughts/9840/16">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/a-few-thoughts/9840/16</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 15 Sep 2012 20:42:23 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9840-16</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/a-few-thoughts/9840.rss">a few thoughts</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>a few thoughts</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Dotard]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Thanks, it’s even more confusing than in the original (no offense to the developers) ironic, because according to the wiki, the initial version was redesigned for being confusing “_”</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/a-few-thoughts/9840/15">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/a-few-thoughts/9840/15</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 15 Sep 2012 20:34:47 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9840-15</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/a-few-thoughts/9840.rss">a few thoughts</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>a few thoughts</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Pudding]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Dotard, go to the beginning room before you meet the dead cop, look for a open shaft in the vent  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/wink.png?v=9" title=":wink:" class="emoji" alt=":wink:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/a-few-thoughts/9840/14">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/a-few-thoughts/9840/14</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 15 Sep 2012 20:22:33 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9840-14</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/a-few-thoughts/9840.rss">a few thoughts</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>a few thoughts</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Dotard]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I agree with the guy above, I’m stuck at Residue Processing as well, more precisely at the start… went downstairs and both doors are locked, dunno where to go… the glass upstairs can’t be broken</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/a-few-thoughts/9840/13">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/a-few-thoughts/9840/13</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 15 Sep 2012 20:20:29 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9840-13</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/a-few-thoughts/9840.rss">a few thoughts</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>a few thoughts</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[FrontLineAssembly]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Music was good, but it was SO loud.</p>
<p>I couldn’t hear what the black guy told me after i had the H.E.V suit on, i didn’t change it though, but i wish i did. After finishing the game i will try again and lower the music volume, because 100% music volume gives me ear bleeding.</p>
<p>I also felt like it was misplaced, some music plays either too early or too late (and it doesn’t fade away, which ruins the scene), like for instance the moment before you have to burn the tentacles, it plays all of a sudden with no special context in it, feels anti-climatic.</p>
<p>The music is good and good quality but the music setup (placement and volume) IS HORRIBLE. Please do fix.</p>
<p>Also, it seems some sounds are missing as they don’t seem to load in console (it says failed to load sound, probably missing from disk/repisitory), some other files gives errors as well.</p>
<p>Now for the serious bugs: Random crashes both middle-loading and after, the VERTEX (entity) OVERLOAD crash if you go to some specific area, i had this in Lambda Core where you fight the F_assasin’s for the last time. Some textures looked horrible and glitched out. If you look at the water from The Dam in Surface Tension from above it looks scattered and horrible, i had this somewhere else too. Do note that i save this BEFORE i pressed the overflood button, is water supposed to be there before you press it? Might be a graphical effect/bug.</p>
<p>Sorry for the weired spell, grammar, and formating as i am just typing this down fast before i go to bed.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/a-few-thoughts/9840/12">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/a-few-thoughts/9840/12</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 15 Sep 2012 20:19:35 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9840-12</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/a-few-thoughts/9840.rss">a few thoughts</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>a few thoughts</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Alx]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Never had any trouble with any ladders myself. E key + up and down, felt perfect to me.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/a-few-thoughts/9840/11">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/a-few-thoughts/9840/11</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 15 Sep 2012 19:03:12 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9840-11</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/a-few-thoughts/9840.rss">a few thoughts</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>a few thoughts</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[XeXe]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="pfannkuchen_gesicht">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/p/ee7513/40.png" class="avatar"> pfannkuchen_gesicht:</div>
<blockquote>
<ol>
<li>Ladders: they are somewhat terrible. Either you’re glued to them or you don’t get on them(sometimes while falling etc)</li>
</ol>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>oh yes, those ladders… they will appear in my nightmares :fffuuu:</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/a-few-thoughts/9840/10">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/a-few-thoughts/9840/10</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 15 Sep 2012 17:22:05 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9840-10</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/a-few-thoughts/9840.rss">a few thoughts</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>a few thoughts</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[pfannkuchen_gesicht]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>found something strange:<br>
The assassins lower and upper body don’t seem to be connected correctly:<br>
<div class="lightbox-wrapper"><a class="lightbox" href="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/original/3X/2/8/2815302a77e2e2dc45b3b949bbbf12f61fc34e03.jpeg" data-download-href="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/2815302a77e2e2dc45b3b949bbbf12f61fc34e03" title=""><img src="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/optimized/3X/2/8/2815302a77e2e2dc45b3b949bbbf12f61fc34e03_2_690x388.jpeg" alt="" data-base62-sha1="5IAuDLrzHBBtr7YTR3BLxLVNDmH" width="690" height="388" srcset="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/optimized/3X/2/8/2815302a77e2e2dc45b3b949bbbf12f61fc34e03_2_690x388.jpeg, https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/optimized/3X/2/8/2815302a77e2e2dc45b3b949bbbf12f61fc34e03_2_1035x582.jpeg 1.5x, https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/optimized/3X/2/8/2815302a77e2e2dc45b3b949bbbf12f61fc34e03_2_1380x776.jpeg 2x" data-small-upload="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/optimized/3X/2/8/2815302a77e2e2dc45b3b949bbbf12f61fc34e03_2_10x10.png"><div class="meta"><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-far-image svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#far-image"></use></svg><span class="filename"></span><span class="informations">1920×1080 167 KB</span><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-discourse-expand svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#discourse-expand"></use></svg></div></a></div><br>
<div class="lightbox-wrapper"><a class="lightbox" href="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/original/3X/2/f/2f1dc27d0e73afa1ee5d7e28f9e5caa893511a71.jpeg" data-download-href="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/2f1dc27d0e73afa1ee5d7e28f9e5caa893511a71" title=""><img src="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/optimized/3X/2/f/2f1dc27d0e73afa1ee5d7e28f9e5caa893511a71_2_690x388.jpeg" alt="" data-base62-sha1="6IOcsInoGUvp6pOKBSSnnTcdLgt" width="690" height="388" srcset="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/optimized/3X/2/f/2f1dc27d0e73afa1ee5d7e28f9e5caa893511a71_2_690x388.jpeg, https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/optimized/3X/2/f/2f1dc27d0e73afa1ee5d7e28f9e5caa893511a71_2_1035x582.jpeg 1.5x, https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/optimized/3X/2/f/2f1dc27d0e73afa1ee5d7e28f9e5caa893511a71_2_1380x776.jpeg 2x" data-small-upload="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/optimized/3X/2/f/2f1dc27d0e73afa1ee5d7e28f9e5caa893511a71_2_10x10.png"><div class="meta"><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-far-image svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#far-image"></use></svg><span class="filename"></span><span class="informations">1920×1080 234 KB</span><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-discourse-expand svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#discourse-expand"></use></svg></div></a></div></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/a-few-thoughts/9840/9">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/a-few-thoughts/9840/9</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 15 Sep 2012 17:13:58 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9840-9</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/a-few-thoughts/9840.rss">a few thoughts</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>a few thoughts</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Lost]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I’ve only completed the first two chapters but it is great so far. First death by ladder!</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/a-few-thoughts/9840/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/a-few-thoughts/9840/8</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 15 Sep 2012 16:14:46 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9840-8</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/a-few-thoughts/9840.rss">a few thoughts</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>a few thoughts</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[noonem]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Everything was fine, I was enjoying the mod and praising it, and then I got to Residue Processing. And I don’t know if someone else designed these maps, or what but they are god damn frustrating. Even more so than they are in Half-Life.</p>
<p>There’s the room where the pipe explodes, that was also confusing because it really doesn’t look like you’d be able to jump over that fence, because let’s be honest, the jumping isn’t that great in this mod. Like the op said, regular jumping is useless. You have to push ctrl to jump over EVERYTHING. It’s made me realise how much I fucking hate jumping in first person shooters.<br>
And then there’s the worst offence. What happens after it. That rotating-radiation jumpy thingy. When I first looked at, I didn’t even realise that it was that. Plus, there’s no indication that you’re supposed to jump on it, it literally looks like you’ll fall in as soon as you do.<br>
I don’t even want to talk about what happened next. I got to the part with the poopy sewage water, and I spent 20 minutes in that shit, with no idea where I was going, what I was doing, when those frustrating minutes were over and I found myself near the dead security guard. I had no idea what I had done to get there. No fucking clue. In Half-Life, sure some parts got frustrating, you still understood what you had to do, where you had to go. In Black Mesa, at least in Residue Processing, I’m able fucking finish the map and still have no idea what I did. The next parts were okay, but I still had a bad taste in my mouth after all of that shit.</p>
<p>That was a really disappointing chapter, and I don’t dislike the mod. Hell, I’ve even liked a chapter here and there even more than the original. Unforeseen Consequences was  amazing.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/a-few-thoughts/9840/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/a-few-thoughts/9840/7</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 15 Sep 2012 15:42:49 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9840-7</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/a-few-thoughts/9840.rss">a few thoughts</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>a few thoughts</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[yrr]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Well, if Pfannkuchen_gesicht has already made a thread for “a few thoughts”, I’m going to share mine too  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=9" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:">  . First of all: A tremendous Mod, jaw-dropping on the run. I am not done yet, playing on hard (The HECU is friggin tough, unlike the dumb Combine) but I am enjoying it. Only thing that bugs me are the annotations, or hints like “Press CTRL + Space to duck-jump” etc. These should really bigger, maybe even another font, color and orientation on the screen. I missed them easily and while I have no Problems since I know HL, it could be difficult for Newbies. For instance, I knew you can zoom with your HEV, but there was no Hint that would have shown the player he can zoom. Well, maybe I missed it. I hope you get my point. Second thing is the balancing of the weapons.The .357 is a powerful ally in the original HL, it is really powerful in Black Mesa, too, but the balancing isn’t my type. In HL it was a one shot - one kill weapon, whereas in BM it’s more of a hit-and-miss weapon. The Shotgun… I already said that I’M playing on hard, so less damage and tougher enemies are common, but 4(!) shotgun bursts and a zombie still isn’t dead (unless you shoot in the headcrab) ? Really ? I know you can control the damage via convars, but it shouldn’t be meant to balance the game by yourself.<br>
So, my 2 Cents… beware, Edits may follow  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=9" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:">  Back to duty:freeman:</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/a-few-thoughts/9840/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/a-few-thoughts/9840/6</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 15 Sep 2012 14:53:15 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9840-6</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/a-few-thoughts/9840.rss">a few thoughts</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
