<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>GTA IV and EFLC problems.</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/gta-iv-and-eflc-problems/7623</link>
    <description>Hi, I&#39;ve been having this problem with gta IV and EFLC ever since I bought it for I believe $20 on steam. As soon as it was finished updating I tried to start it up. Now this is where the problem starts. The rockstar social club thing pops up at random and if it does when I try to start it up there is a 40% chance it will work for gta iv but a 0% chance with EFLC. If it doesn&#39;t work for gta iv it just has a black screen and after a few seconds it will give me this &quot;gta iv is not responding&quot; shit. Same with EFLC. I have tried defragmenting the game, and trying to configure the game files, and still no luck. If anyone can help that would be awesome. 

PS I know it is not a system problem because I have proper graphics and direct x installed, it might just be a game problem.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 05 Aug 2011 05:40:21 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Help and Support</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/gta-iv-and-eflc-problems/7623.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>GTA IV and EFLC problems.</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Disturbulator]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Something similar happened to mine (still <span class="bbcode-i">is</span> happening).</p>
<p>But.</p>
<p>When you sign in and the screen goes black.<br>
Nothing will happen.</p>
<p>SO I wait for ~2-3 minutes and it kickstarts and works flawlessly.<br>
Although, I would still like it more if I didn’t have to wait so long for the initial startup.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/gta-iv-and-eflc-problems/7623/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/gta-iv-and-eflc-problems/7623/2</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 05 Aug 2011 05:40:21 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7623-2</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/gta-iv-and-eflc-problems/7623.rss">GTA IV and EFLC problems.</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>GTA IV and EFLC problems.</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Ragnatas]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Hi, I’ve been having this problem with gta IV and EFLC ever since I bought it for I believe $20 on steam. As soon as it was finished updating I tried to start it up. Now this is where the problem starts. The rockstar social club thing pops up at random and if it does when I try to start it up there is a 40% chance it will work for gta iv but a 0% chance with EFLC. If it doesn’t work for gta iv it just has a black screen and after a few seconds it will give me this “gta iv is not responding” shit. Same with EFLC. I have tried defragmenting the game, and trying to configure the game files, and still no luck. If anyone can help that would be awesome.</p>
<p>PS I know it is not a system problem because I have proper graphics and direct x installed, it might just be a game problem.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/gta-iv-and-eflc-problems/7623/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/gta-iv-and-eflc-problems/7623/1</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 05 Aug 2011 00:23:36 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7623-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/gta-iv-and-eflc-problems/7623.rss">GTA IV and EFLC problems.</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
