<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Second-Hand Halflife 2 Problem</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/second-hand-halflife-2-problem/755</link>
    <description>Okay guys (and girls, of course - hi girls! *waving*),

I have been a serious dumbass and bought Half-Life 2 and the Episode Pack on amazon.com. Second hand, so it has been in use before. You can already imagine what my problem is, but I will articulate it anyway:

The product code is already in use, and I have not yet been able to contact the original owner of this copy. On the steam website I came across this:
[quote]
If you recently purchased a new retail game which requires activation on Steam and are encountering a &quot;Duplicate CD Key&quot; error message, you must contact Valve to have the CD Key moved to your account. Please contact us through our online support system as outlined here:

Contacting VALVe Billing and Support

You must have a copy of your valid purchase receipt from within the last 90 days to have the CD Key moved to your account.

Note:
We do not accept receipts from online auction websites or used software vendors. If you do not provide a valid purchase receipt, Valve will not be able to transfer the CD Key.

We do not reset CD Keys which have been disabled for violations of the Steam Subscriber Agreement and/or End User License Agreement or banned by VAC for cheating infractions. 
[/quote]
I imagine that amazon.com, in this case, is exactly what they would call a &quot;used software vendor&quot;, is it not? I did not know about this when purchasing it, and now I am feeling seriously pissed. I have probably given my money to some asshole who keeps playing this game over steam, knowing that I cannot do shit with his copy. And yes, I AM feeling dumb like hell for not having known better in the first place, so please spare me with comments on that! If there is anybody else here having experienced similar problems and coming up with a possible solution (no illegal stuff, please!), I would be very grateful. 

Before I buy this game a second time for an even larger prize in the next pc-and-video-market, I wanna know if there is anything I can do to make my LEGALLY purchased copies of HL2 and the Episodes actually work on my computer.

Many thanks in advance to all who will answer my question seriously.

DansonDelta40</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 06 Jul 2009 17:25:18 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Half-Life Series</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/second-hand-halflife-2-problem/755.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Second-Hand Halflife 2 Problem</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[ppp]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Perhaps, though I would have said that was implied.  If you offer ‘half life 2’ you are surely offering to sell ‘the game’ not a useless disk with ‘half life 2’ written on it.  This must have happened before so I would have thought Amazon would be familiar with the issue and have a policy on it one way or the other.  I’d count it as ‘product was incomplete/faulty’ because it was missing a vital part - an unused serial number.  Of course if I remember rightly you are obliged to wait an age first to give the vendor a chance to fix the issue.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/second-hand-halflife-2-problem/755/26">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/second-hand-halflife-2-problem/755/26</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jul 2009 17:25:18 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-755-26</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/second-hand-halflife-2-problem/755.rss">Second-Hand Halflife 2 Problem</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Second-Hand Halflife 2 Problem</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Imonfire]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I think he’d have to prove that the seller did not said it was a registered Steam copy.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/second-hand-halflife-2-problem/755/25">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/second-hand-halflife-2-problem/755/25</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jul 2009 03:43:10 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-755-25</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/second-hand-halflife-2-problem/755.rss">Second-Hand Halflife 2 Problem</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Second-Hand Halflife 2 Problem</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[ppp]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Surely you can complain to Amazon and get a refund from them?  They do provide some kind of guarantee with their marketplace sales I thought.  They just insist you ‘try to sort it out with the vendor first’.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/second-hand-halflife-2-problem/755/24">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/second-hand-halflife-2-problem/755/24</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jul 2009 02:37:18 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-755-24</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/second-hand-halflife-2-problem/755.rss">Second-Hand Halflife 2 Problem</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Second-Hand Halflife 2 Problem</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[DansonDelta40]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>And everyone lived happily ever after. At least until we find the guy that sold it to you and break his legs.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>No problem. He sent his copy directly from his home, apparently. The address and everything is on the package. Maybe I will go there by car in a few days and talk with him about the matter. Yes, TALK with him. I am a DIPLOMATIC guy. I am living in Germany, and here, every time a lunatic youth runs amok and kills his fellow students and teachers, it’s always the games that are blamed. Never the question comes up whether his parents might have done something wrong, or if his social background might suggest some causes thar might have led to the incident. Or from where he had the gun in the first place - it’s not like you can go gun shopping like in the N.A.U. Now right after having purchased a copy of half-life 2 I ain’t gonna go hurting anybody, because it’s my fellow gamers who will be punished for it.</p>
<p>If he proves a real asshole, I can still break his limbs, tie him to a chair and cut his skin off while teaching him lessons about honesty.<br>
:pirate:</p>
<p>Just kiddn’:ninja:</p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>If you hadn’t bought it again, I could’ve easily gifted you a copy through STEAM, both HL2 and EP1 seeing as I own 4 copies of HL2 and at least 2 copies of EP1.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Whow… um… thanks - I guess. Why the hell didn’t you say that earlier? You wouldn’t also have a copy of CS Source to spare, would ya? That’s the only thing not included in my orange box that I am missng. <em>really cute smile</em></p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>I would have knocked on my neighbors door</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>My neighbours to the right are a big bunch of gipsies. If I had gone knocking down their door the whole family would have gone knocking down ME before I could have asked anything. My other neighbours are an old married couple. They don’t even have a computer, let alone know how to operate one. And they surely wouldn’t give a shit about me being punked by some asshole from the internet. Hell, I would grow gray hair while trying to explain the whole situation to them. In the meantime, Half-Life 3 and 4 would be completed. And Black Mesa Source would already be legendary.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/second-hand-halflife-2-problem/755/23">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/second-hand-halflife-2-problem/755/23</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jul 2009 20:01:49 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-755-23</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/second-hand-halflife-2-problem/755.rss">Second-Hand Halflife 2 Problem</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Second-Hand Halflife 2 Problem</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Samapico]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="DansonDelta40">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/d/bbce88/40.png" class="avatar"> DansonDelta40:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>(at least she could use a little training in three-dimensional-orientation).</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>hahaha</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/second-hand-halflife-2-problem/755/22">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/second-hand-halflife-2-problem/755/22</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jul 2009 19:29:03 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-755-22</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/second-hand-halflife-2-problem/755.rss">Second-Hand Halflife 2 Problem</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Second-Hand Halflife 2 Problem</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[CatzEyes93]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Personally… I would have knocked on my neighbors door and asked him to purchase the game and then gift it to you.  I think that would have been another option for those that dont have a credit card.</p>
<p>It would involve the neighbor having to set up an account and all… but it was another option.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/second-hand-halflife-2-problem/755/21">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/second-hand-halflife-2-problem/755/21</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jul 2009 15:18:34 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-755-21</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/second-hand-halflife-2-problem/755.rss">Second-Hand Halflife 2 Problem</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Second-Hand Halflife 2 Problem</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Lord_Grievous]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>If you hadn’t bought it again, I could’ve easily gifted you a copy through STEAM, both HL2 and EP1 seeing as I own 4 copies of HL2 and at least 2 copies of EP1.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/second-hand-halflife-2-problem/755/20">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/second-hand-halflife-2-problem/755/20</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jul 2009 13:43:03 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-755-20</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/second-hand-halflife-2-problem/755.rss">Second-Hand Halflife 2 Problem</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Second-Hand Halflife 2 Problem</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Wasabi]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>And everyone lived happily ever after. At least until we find the guy that sold it to you and break his legs.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/second-hand-halflife-2-problem/755/19">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/second-hand-halflife-2-problem/755/19</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jul 2009 01:54:19 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-755-19</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/second-hand-halflife-2-problem/755.rss">Second-Hand Halflife 2 Problem</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Second-Hand Halflife 2 Problem</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[DansonDelta40]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I actually tried to contact valve, but have not gotten any reply so far. I expected nothing more - their disclaimer on the steam website (quoted by me in the first posting of this thread) explicitly says that used software is not supported. And I unknowingly (meaning unaware of the consequences) bought Half-Life 2 and the Episode Pack from a third person on <a href="http://amazon.com" rel="nofollow noopener">amazon.com</a>, not from a market or store.</p>
<p>That’s why I decided to just buy it again, and this time the proper way. I didn’t want to have to wait for hours in front of my computer while I would be downloading it, and couldn’t imagne buying it again over the internet (which had been my major mistake in the first place), so I took a stroll around in the nearest city and luckily found one budget copy of the orange box in a large electronics and entertainment market.</p>
<p>I am actually quite something over eighteen, but have never yet had to use Paypal, and didn’t want to start now just because of one game. Although I must admit that now, after I have played a few chapters and also had a sneak peak at “Portal”, I think it was worth all the stress. Maybe “Portal” will even be something my girlfriend might have fun with (at least she could use a little training in three-dimensional-orientation).</p>
<p>So that’s it from me now. I have solved my problem and am content now with what I have. I hope all questions have been answered.</p>
<p>Thank all of you who actually tried to help - to those who only made unnecessary remarks or attempted to make fun of me I cannot say anything adequate.</p>
<p>Thread can be closed on my account.</p>
<p>See ya! DansonDelta40</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/second-hand-halflife-2-problem/755/18">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/second-hand-halflife-2-problem/755/18</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jul 2009 01:50:05 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-755-18</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/second-hand-halflife-2-problem/755.rss">Second-Hand Halflife 2 Problem</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Second-Hand Halflife 2 Problem</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Level]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Nintyuk">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/user_avatar/leakfree.org/nintyuk/40/4570_2.png" class="avatar"> Nintyuk:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Taken from Pay-Pal’s User Agreement<a href="https://www.paypal.com/uk/cgi-bin/webscr?cmd=xpt/UserAgreement/ua/EUUA-outside#eligibility-policy" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Here</a></p>
<p>So technically you have breached this agreement,  im not going to say any thing but when it comes to  money i always follow the rules.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I doubt it’d be the first EULA you’ve broken. Paypal doesn’t care as long as you don’t send your money to a scam and expect to get it back, then they’ll whip out the 18 years old thing.</p>
<p>Go to the bank and ask for all the details they ask for. They’ll help you out no problem.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/second-hand-halflife-2-problem/755/17">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/second-hand-halflife-2-problem/755/17</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 04 Jul 2009 23:10:46 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-755-17</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/second-hand-halflife-2-problem/755.rss">Second-Hand Halflife 2 Problem</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Second-Hand Halflife 2 Problem</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Brother_Shrike]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="shredhead">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/s/c89c15/40.png" class="avatar"> shredhead:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Soo…why didn’t you just contact Valve and get them to move the CD key to your Steam account?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>It’s already on his steam account. There is no non-steam version of the orange box.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/second-hand-halflife-2-problem/755/16">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/second-hand-halflife-2-problem/755/16</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 04 Jul 2009 22:44:10 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-755-16</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/second-hand-halflife-2-problem/755.rss">Second-Hand Halflife 2 Problem</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Second-Hand Halflife 2 Problem</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Lolipopman]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Maxaxle">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/m/58956e/40.png" class="avatar"> Maxaxle:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>RE: The Orange Box: $80 or $100 worth of games for $30 or $40? WORTH IT.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Lol, i bought The orange box for, what i think, is 25$ (250kr)</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/second-hand-halflife-2-problem/755/15">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/second-hand-halflife-2-problem/755/15</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 04 Jul 2009 20:26:05 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-755-15</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/second-hand-halflife-2-problem/755.rss">Second-Hand Halflife 2 Problem</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Second-Hand Halflife 2 Problem</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Nintyuk]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Imonfire">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/i/e47c2d/40.png" class="avatar"> Imonfire:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>No you don’t. I’m not 18 and I have a Paypal account.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Taken from Pay-Pal’s User Agreement<a href="https://www.paypal.com/uk/cgi-bin/webscr?cmd=xpt/UserAgreement/ua/EUUA-outside#eligibility-policy" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Here</a></p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<ol start="2">
<li>
<p>Eligibility and Types of Accounts</p>
<ol>
<li>
</li></ol>
<p>2.1 Eligibility. To be eligible for our Services, you must be at <span class="bbcode-b">least 18 years old</span> and a resident of one of the countries listed on the PayPal Worldwide page.</p>
</li>
</ol>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>So technically you have breached this agreement,  im not going to say any thing but when it comes to  money i always follow the rules.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/second-hand-halflife-2-problem/755/14">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/second-hand-halflife-2-problem/755/14</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 04 Jul 2009 20:15:19 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-755-14</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/second-hand-halflife-2-problem/755.rss">Second-Hand Halflife 2 Problem</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Second-Hand Halflife 2 Problem</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Maxaxle]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="shredhead">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/s/c89c15/40.png" class="avatar"> shredhead:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Soo…why didn’t you just contact Valve and get them to move the CD key to your Steam account?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>They don’t support secondhand game buyers. Keeps them in buisness.</p>
<p>RE: The Orange Box: $80 or $100 worth of games for $30 or $40? WORTH IT.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/second-hand-halflife-2-problem/755/13">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/second-hand-halflife-2-problem/755/13</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 04 Jul 2009 18:56:28 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-755-13</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/second-hand-halflife-2-problem/755.rss">Second-Hand Halflife 2 Problem</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Second-Hand Halflife 2 Problem</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[shredhead]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="DansonDelta40">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/d/bbce88/40.png" class="avatar"> DansonDelta40:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I have just scoured the area for any stores likely to have it for sale and found a budget version of the orange box in the “classics”-category at a local entertainment electronics market. No neat box, no booklet, just two disks and a reference card. But it is the original content of the orange box, and I am installing it at the moment. Cost me another 20 euros, which really hurts, cause I am unemployed at the moment, but then again - there has not been much to be happy about in my life recently, except having a nice game to play every now and then. So I had to buy the game two times and plug my unprotected gaming computer to the internet, just to make it work. I seriously hope this game is damn good! :pirate:</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Soo…why didn’t you just contact Valve and get them to move the CD key to your Steam account?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/second-hand-halflife-2-problem/755/12">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/second-hand-halflife-2-problem/755/12</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 04 Jul 2009 17:55:38 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-755-12</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/second-hand-halflife-2-problem/755.rss">Second-Hand Halflife 2 Problem</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Second-Hand Halflife 2 Problem</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Imonfire]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Nintyuk">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/user_avatar/leakfree.org/nintyuk/40/4570_2.png" class="avatar"> Nintyuk:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>But you need to be over 18 to get a PayPal account, and that might be a problem.  If he’s 17 (or under) like me that can be very frustrating.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>No you don’t. I’m not 18 and I have a Paypal account.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/second-hand-halflife-2-problem/755/11">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/second-hand-halflife-2-problem/755/11</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 04 Jul 2009 17:28:32 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-755-11</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/second-hand-halflife-2-problem/755.rss">Second-Hand Halflife 2 Problem</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Second-Hand Halflife 2 Problem</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Hazzmat]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>You won’t be disappointed.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/second-hand-halflife-2-problem/755/10">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/second-hand-halflife-2-problem/755/10</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 04 Jul 2009 17:10:23 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-755-10</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/second-hand-halflife-2-problem/755.rss">Second-Hand Halflife 2 Problem</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Second-Hand Halflife 2 Problem</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[DansonDelta40]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I have just scoured the area for any stores likely to have it for sale and found a budget version of the orange box in the “classics”-category at a local entertainment electronics market. No neat box, no booklet, just two disks and a reference card. But it is the original content of the orange box, and I am installing it at the moment. Cost me another 20 euros, which really hurts, cause I am unemployed at the moment, but then again - there has not been much to be happy about in my life recently, except having a nice game to play every now and then. So I had to buy the game two times and plug my unprotected gaming computer to the internet, just to make it work. I seriously hope this game is damn good! :pirate:</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/second-hand-halflife-2-problem/755/9">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/second-hand-halflife-2-problem/755/9</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 04 Jul 2009 16:02:15 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-755-9</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/second-hand-halflife-2-problem/755.rss">Second-Hand Halflife 2 Problem</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Second-Hand Halflife 2 Problem</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[JeffMOD]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Buy it retail. There are lots of stores where you can buy HL2 and the episodes, or get the orange box, you get all three plus TF2 and Portal.<br>
Plus with retail you get a neat box to look at and a manual to read while you wait for the download to finish. Or you used to get a manual, HL2 just has a reference card.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/second-hand-halflife-2-problem/755/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/second-hand-halflife-2-problem/755/8</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 04 Jul 2009 14:21:55 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-755-8</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/second-hand-halflife-2-problem/755.rss">Second-Hand Halflife 2 Problem</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Second-Hand Halflife 2 Problem</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Savant]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Medevilae">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/m/aca169/40.png" class="avatar"> Medevilae:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Is the content of the game on the CD? If so there has to be someway to get it off other than Steam.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p><strong>cough</strong> illegal<strong>cough</strong></p>
<p>Actually, on the other hand, it really isn’t because he/she did give money for the game, so it makes it… well… a bit more… legal? :fffuuu:</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/second-hand-halflife-2-problem/755/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/second-hand-halflife-2-problem/755/7</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 04 Jul 2009 13:56:23 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-755-7</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/second-hand-halflife-2-problem/755.rss">Second-Hand Halflife 2 Problem</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Second-Hand Halflife 2 Problem</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Medevilae]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Is the content of the game on the CD? If so there has to be someway to get it off other than Steam.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/second-hand-halflife-2-problem/755/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/second-hand-halflife-2-problem/755/6</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 04 Jul 2009 13:37:30 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-755-6</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/second-hand-halflife-2-problem/755.rss">Second-Hand Halflife 2 Problem</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Second-Hand Halflife 2 Problem</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Nintyuk]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Raminator">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/r/6bbea6/40.png" class="avatar"> Raminator:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>You don’t need a credit card to buy games on Steam, they also accept PayPal.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>But you need to be over 18 to get a PayPal account, and that might be a problem.  If he’s 17 (or under) like me that can be very frustrating.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/second-hand-halflife-2-problem/755/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/second-hand-halflife-2-problem/755/5</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 04 Jul 2009 13:00:54 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-755-5</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/second-hand-halflife-2-problem/755.rss">Second-Hand Halflife 2 Problem</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Second-Hand Halflife 2 Problem</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[DansonDelta40]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>So you are basically saying that I won’t be able to play this game ever? I have already installed steam and (desperate as I am) tried to contact valve. No reaction so far. They say in their disclaimer that people with used software will not be supported, so I can guess what my chances are. Not one single store in my range has this game. If I buy it on Amazon, I cannot play it, and on steam I cannot buy it because I have no credit card.</p>
<p>I am starting to hate this game… and what is even worse: I won’t be able to play Black Mesa: Source when it is finished!</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/second-hand-halflife-2-problem/755/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/second-hand-halflife-2-problem/755/4</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 04 Jul 2009 12:35:55 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-755-4</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/second-hand-halflife-2-problem/755.rss">Second-Hand Halflife 2 Problem</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Second-Hand Halflife 2 Problem</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Wasabi]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I’m afraid, short of contacting Valve, there’s nothing you can do.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/second-hand-halflife-2-problem/755/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/second-hand-halflife-2-problem/755/3</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 04 Jul 2009 10:51:55 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-755-3</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/second-hand-halflife-2-problem/755.rss">Second-Hand Halflife 2 Problem</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Second-Hand Halflife 2 Problem</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Eric_Fong]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Just don’t buy second-hand stuff game from internet.</p>
<p>Buy game from steam is better. <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=9" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/second-hand-halflife-2-problem/755/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/second-hand-halflife-2-problem/755/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 04 Jul 2009 09:49:44 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-755-2</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/second-hand-halflife-2-problem/755.rss">Second-Hand Halflife 2 Problem</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
