<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Reloading Weapons Meta</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/reloading-weapons-meta/14373</link>
    <description>After playing the game for some time, I noticed a small but extremely annoying thing about reloading. I&#39;m the kind of person who likes to switch weapons immediately after reloading for more firepower. However, I keep finding myself switching weapons too early and end up canceling the reload for the previous weapon I had, despite seeing the new mag go into the gun. This small problem can have pretty bad consequences if in the wrong situation, which is why I would like it if the reload timings were adjusted where as soon as the magazine is put in the weapon, it is reloaded, rather than the gun being reloaded after the entire reload animation finishes. Valve made this change in CS:GO, and it makes reloading extremely convenient and faster when switching from secondary to primary or vice versa, because there is clear feedback for you to be allowed to switch weapons again. The weapons severely affected by uneven reload timings are the Spas12, Glock, Magnum, and Crossbow.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 20 Aug 2015 17:44:24 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>The Cafeteria</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/reloading-weapons-meta/14373.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Reloading Weapons Meta</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Sage_J_Fox]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Question is then, would they redo/retime the reload animations so the “mag in” on the new one is where the end of the sequence is on the old one? Otherwise everything would actually be reloading faster (as only a part of the animation’s time is the time taken for the reload to complete, versus the whole time for the animation to play).</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/reloading-weapons-meta/14373/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/reloading-weapons-meta/14373/7</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 20 Aug 2015 17:44:24 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14373-7</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/reloading-weapons-meta/14373.rss">Reloading Weapons Meta</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Reloading Weapons Meta</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Dragunov2]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>But a good one!</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/reloading-weapons-meta/14373/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/reloading-weapons-meta/14373/6</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 20 Aug 2015 16:26:49 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14373-6</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/reloading-weapons-meta/14373.rss">Reloading Weapons Meta</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Reloading Weapons Meta</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[TextFAMGUY1]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>We can certainly look into this at some point though it’s not high priority. It is something which has always bugged me, too.</p>
<p>I would personally love it if the reload was broken into various “stages” that the game remembers. So for example, if you start to reload and he takes the mag out, and then you switch weapons, when you bring the gun back out, the mag is still out and you can’t fire it. It then plays the rest of the reload animation, where you only have to load a new mag in. I guess this would make reload cancelling impossible which might annoy some people, but personally I’ve always found it silly that games don’t do this already to be honest - it can’t be THAT hard. I guess it significantly increases the number of reload animations required, but I dunno, I’ve never liked the way games handle reloading anyway.</p>
<p>Rant aside, that’s all just my personal opinion. We won’t be doing that for BMS, was just musing out loud. The issue which is the title of the topic, I can bring it up with the programmers/animators, though, see if we can get anywhere.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/reloading-weapons-meta/14373/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/reloading-weapons-meta/14373/5</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 20 Aug 2015 16:20:53 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14373-5</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/reloading-weapons-meta/14373.rss">Reloading Weapons Meta</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Reloading Weapons Meta</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Igoreso]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I agree, it’d be nice addition, especially after getting accustomed to this feature in CS:GO.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Sage J. Fox">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Sage J. Fox:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I think that’s done with the 3015 (EVENT_WEAPON_RELOAD) animation event in the reload sequence</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>It is possible to use that but it’s not this way by default. For example, in HL2 sources it relies on the length of whole reloading animation. I believe the same happens in BM.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/reloading-weapons-meta/14373/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/reloading-weapons-meta/14373/4</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 20 Aug 2015 15:09:30 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14373-4</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/reloading-weapons-meta/14373.rss">Reloading Weapons Meta</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Reloading Weapons Meta</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[fury]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>agree with sourcegamer…</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/reloading-weapons-meta/14373/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/reloading-weapons-meta/14373/3</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 18 Aug 2015 11:03:09 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14373-3</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/reloading-weapons-meta/14373.rss">Reloading Weapons Meta</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Reloading Weapons Meta</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Sage_J_Fox]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I think that’s done with the 3015 (EVENT_WEAPON_RELOAD) animation event in the reload sequence. Not 100% positive, but if it is, should be possible to fix yourself, provided the weapon animations decompile correctly.</p>
<p>For singleplayer/multiplayer you host only, of course.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/reloading-weapons-meta/14373/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/reloading-weapons-meta/14373/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 16 Aug 2015 22:51:27 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14373-2</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/reloading-weapons-meta/14373.rss">Reloading Weapons Meta</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Reloading Weapons Meta</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[sourcegamer101]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>After playing the game for some time, I noticed a small but extremely annoying thing about reloading. I’m the kind of person who likes to switch weapons immediately after reloading for more firepower. However, I keep finding myself switching weapons too early and end up canceling the reload for the previous weapon I had, despite seeing the new mag go into the gun. This small problem can have pretty bad consequences if in the wrong situation, which is why I would like it if the reload timings were adjusted where as soon as the magazine is put in the weapon, it is reloaded, rather than the gun being reloaded after the entire reload animation finishes. Valve made this change in CS:GO, and it makes reloading extremely convenient and faster when switching from secondary to primary or vice versa, because there is clear feedback for you to be allowed to switch weapons again. The weapons severely affected by uneven reload timings are the Spas12, Glock, Magnum, and Crossbow.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/reloading-weapons-meta/14373/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/reloading-weapons-meta/14373/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 16 Aug 2015 22:38:49 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14373-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/reloading-weapons-meta/14373.rss">Reloading Weapons Meta</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
