<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Great Ideas and Poor to None Execution</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/great-ideas-and-poor-to-none-execution/359</link>
    <description>Hello, My name isn&#39;t important, but my message is.


I&#39;m sure some of you have had an amazing ideas, I mean amazing, imaginations going wild ideas, but as with everything, reality is a cold viaginaless bitch with a shitie asshole instead.

I&#39;d like to talk about, share your stories and unfinished works.

Myself I write stuff, I never get pass two pages most days, I&#39;ve ever only written two things above 50 A4 pages long.


here is some of my failed works.

[b][u][align=center]Intatius Zal, Commander:[/align][/u][/b]
[quote]
There is a void of darkness that fills the area, a voice creeps from the shadows and speaks of a storm, but this isn’t a normal storm, it is the storm of life being cast aside for the benefit of powerful groups bent of control, this is the voice of reason and all hope.

The Voice: It cold, the fields are covered in blood and a terror masses its hunger for victory in the skies, these are dark days for the race of man, and these are dark days for earth. 

The Voice: But there is light among the great darkness, sadly the light is another form of evil, but a war must be won with another kind evil to save the race of man, it is so sad that victory will cost the galaxy to much pain in the end, because man will bring an end to all life in the coming days, but I’ll tell the story of how man will became a giant of the stars. 

The Voice: I will tell you a story of hope that turn on the stars above, this is the story of how man became the greatest empire of them all. It all begins on the fall of the Xer’kinal empire grip of earth.

The dark void began to shine with life and the darkness began to fade from its shadowy depths. 

The Voice: it begins here…

When the darkness faded away it gave way to a wonderful grand hall, the walls where bright white, clearly it was a marble finish, the grand hall was very long with an office in the back, the middle of the floor was a grand red carpet with a lighter red on the edges of the carpet, the walls where covered with paintings, in the office was a man in white uniform, there was two guards beside the man in white, clearly to protect the white uniformed man from possible danger, but from what? 

Behind the white uniformed man was a very large painting of a man in a grey suit, this was Intatius Zal, the greatest leader of the remanding human race.

There is a man walking towards the back of the grand hall, his foot steps echo the hall, such an echo could be heard, the man didn’t take to long getting towards the white uniformed man, the man walked up 4  steps to reach the white uniformed man and then man spoke to the white uniformed man.

Lt. Pike: Intatius Zal, Commander.
Commander Hans: Yeah, yeah. Intatius Zal, Lt. Pike. What be the news from the front?

Commander Hans spoke with a German accent while Pike spoke with an accent like an English man.

Lt. Pike: the Americas fell within two hours and the country Ireland was worse hit; Commander Hans.

Commander Hans: How so, Lt. Pike?

Lt. Pike: the surface was scored; recon ships confirmed this, commander.

Commander Hans: Dear lord, if Ireland was hit like this, what of England?

Lt. Pike: 20% of England was caught in the attack, commander.

Commander Hans: When can we expect another attack like this Lt. Pike?

Lt. Pike: Intel doesn’t have a clue, commander.

Commander Hans: this is grim news indeed, Lt. Pike. 

The voice of the story teller spoke once again and the grand hall began to fade into darkness.

The Voice: Earth was about to deal a blow to the Xer’kinal once and for all, but the cost would be too great on human life. The humans massed the greatest feet of ships in they’re history, for years they built ship under the surface of the planet, using the technology taken from the Xer’kinal to built hope for the race of man, they waited for the right moment to strike and that moment came soon enough. The things I’ve learned from the race of man is never doubt they’re ability to fight, even if the technology is less advanced than your own. 
[/quote]
[b][u][align=center]Ah Shit…[/align][/u][/b]
[quote]
Episode One: It had to happen to me…

The scene fades in on a street; there is an empty street in front of the cut scene camera, cars on fire, dead bodies’ lying to root on the street, the sky was black as night, the lamp posts where flickering, there was the sounds of screaming in the background as if someone was being attacked, there was sounds of guns going off, they sounded near by, the camera zooms in on the scene of the street, the camera stops and looks on a dead body. 

Hero: This is me

A voice clips starts to play…

Hero: not to long ago this was a quite street, and then all this started, we thought we could take care of this mess, but we we’re wrong…

The scene starts to fade out…

Hero: It had to happen to me…

The game moves onto another map.

The scene fades on to office; our hero is talking to his friend, “Max Well Gunner” writing comes up on screen “24 hours earlier”, hero and gunner are talking about the wave of crimes hitting the city of “New Derry”. Reports are coming that “Biotech” a lead in the city of work, power for the city, and controls almost every part of the city, but there a few that hold back, fight the power that steps on them in New Derry. But times are changing, as seen in latest crimes, what Biotech wants many of it’s people to believe is that they’re make things better for the people, better living for all, always a job for them, but this is cover story for what’s really happening, they’re make more people unemployed than hiring people of the city. But report’s of a new drug has hit the streets and the source’s say that Biotech is behind this new drug dub “BioGen”. The police force believe that Biogen is another way for Biotech to make more money, there are also reports of missing people, these are the people that biotech make unemployed, the reports coming say that a Biotech van pulls up and takes them away, but the people who have come to say this have disappeared them self’s, most surprising that these people once worked for biotech. But it’s up to “Mike B. Hero” &amp; “Maxwell Gunner” to find out what going on with the people of New Derry and stop this once and for all.

Gunner: Hey Mike, what are we going to do about this?

Hero: I don’t know, but we must find out where these people are being taken.

Gunner: Yeah that’s all well and good but how are we supposed to find one?

Hero: I may have a plan….

Gunner: Any chance of filling me on this plan? 

Hero: well I was thinking that these people used to work at biotech for a long time, but where fired due to over employment…

Gunner: yeah I know this Mike; I am working on the same case as you, duh…

Hero: will you let me get to the point!

Gunner: ok ok… 

Hero: Well if we get Tony to hack their system again…

Gunner: he did it before?

Hero: Yes back in the early days of Biotech, he said he left a backdoor for him self if he ever needed something from Biotech’s data banks.

Gunner: That’s good; we may need him to hack their data base more than once if the way things are going with these reports are going we may need him more than often.

Hero: Well he can’t get access to the whole database; more or less he’s a high ranking office manager, which isn’t much in the way of Biotech employment for system access Max.

Gunner: oh I see.

Hero: So we’ll ask Tony to help us out, for this, plant a fake Ex-worker file in their database, put the file in the next list for “pick up” and see what happens.

The scene fades out.

Now the player should be able
[/quote]
[b][u][align=center]No Regret…[/align][/u][/b]
[quote]
++Prologue++

The world screams with the madness of crime, the echoes of the past rise, and the body of a fallen hero lies in a dark room, with a body bag covering his broken body, the room is empty but for the bed trolley holding the body bag above it. The fallen hero speaks his last words through his dying mind.

Jake Mc Johnson: I did my duty, I served to the best of my ability, and what did I get for my problems, paper work, and the red tape. I could have taken down every scum bag if I hadn’t followed the book, fact that it didn’t do me any good for me in the end. So here I am, dead, you can only guess what transpired, but then you make up a fantastic story of how I lived, pff… I barely made minimal wage, no, I did something stupid, I betrayed my own kind, my duty, but then again, I have no regret…

**Intro credits**

The is no light, but there is only darkness

Jake Mc Johnson: It began on a dark night, a routine patrol, I won’t bore you with all the details, there merely human ones.

The sound of a car can be heard slowly fading in.

Jake Mc Johnson: My partner Lousy was a quiet man, rarely spoke to me, but only if needed somebody to help, most people would stop to listen to hear a single word; he had that karma around him; a rare man indeed. 

The world begins to fade into dimly lighted car 
[/quote]
Remember, feel free to post your unfinished work.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 20 May 2009 20:38:38 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Off Topic</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/great-ideas-and-poor-to-none-execution/359.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Great Ideas and Poor to None Execution</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Ramirezoid]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Here’s a bunch of shit.</p>
<p><div class="lightbox-wrapper"><a class="lightbox" href="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/original/2X/e/e37ff88f1d5607c740f90fd5b27e7d10114e5ac6.jpeg" data-download-href="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/e37ff88f1d5607c740f90fd5b27e7d10114e5ac6" title=""><img src="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/original/2X/e/e37ff88f1d5607c740f90fd5b27e7d10114e5ac6.jpeg" alt="" data-base62-sha1="wsyyRiDvnUWTpHS1j28vO8mLLxA" width="529" height="500" data-small-upload="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/optimized/2X/e/e37ff88f1d5607c740f90fd5b27e7d10114e5ac6_2_10x10.png"><div class="meta"><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-far-image svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#far-image"></use></svg><span class="filename"></span><span class="informations">800×756 52.1 KB</span><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-discourse-expand svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#discourse-expand"></use></svg></div></a></div></p>
<p>^FreemanBG fortunately was kind enough to steal and color this a slap it on deviantART.</p>
<p>The LEGO Gordon is sitting in my room somewhere rotting.</p>
<p><div class="lightbox-wrapper"><a class="lightbox" href="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/original/2X/4/4f52d724c50c22537d10c37972bfea60ed1ecb77.jpeg" data-download-href="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/4f52d724c50c22537d10c37972bfea60ed1ecb77" title=""><img src="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/original/2X/4/4f52d724c50c22537d10c37972bfea60ed1ecb77.jpeg" alt="" data-base62-sha1="bjJcHGNyeHDAEa7O6OXl2mh4KDt" width="568" height="500" data-small-upload="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/optimized/2X/4/4f52d724c50c22537d10c37972bfea60ed1ecb77_2_10x10.png"><div class="meta"><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-far-image svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#far-image"></use></svg><span class="filename"></span><span class="informations">800×703 55.2 KB</span><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-discourse-expand svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#discourse-expand"></use></svg></div></a></div></p>
<p>Don’t fuck with carrot enthusiasts. Don’t even think about eating them without utensils and good table manners.</p>
<p><div class="lightbox-wrapper"><a class="lightbox" href="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/original/2X/0/0827283b1fa0f23ed511da742b9573e631499f47.png" data-download-href="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/0827283b1fa0f23ed511da742b9573e631499f47" title=""><img src="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/optimized/2X/0/0827283b1fa0f23ed511da742b9573e631499f47_2_662x500.png" alt="" data-base62-sha1="1a7IeYWrimPP6bm1RT30RiY0MrZ" width="662" height="500" srcset="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/optimized/2X/0/0827283b1fa0f23ed511da742b9573e631499f47_2_662x500.png, https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/original/2X/0/0827283b1fa0f23ed511da742b9573e631499f47.png 1.5x, https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/original/2X/0/0827283b1fa0f23ed511da742b9573e631499f47.png 2x" data-small-upload="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/optimized/2X/0/0827283b1fa0f23ed511da742b9573e631499f47_2_10x10.png"><div class="meta"><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-far-image svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#far-image"></use></svg><span class="filename"></span><span class="informations">799×603 572 KB</span><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-discourse-expand svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#discourse-expand"></use></svg></div></a></div></p>
<p>An incredibly hard to read ref sheet for a character of mine. It’s kind of enormous.</p>
<p><a href="https://www.fpsbanana.com/wips/28552" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">My Half-Life 2 Zombies which I might finish later.</a></p>
<p><div class="lightbox-wrapper"><a class="lightbox" href="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/original/2X/9/92b31557b4a0989c64095aca92efc9585ebbe4c1.png" data-download-href="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/92b31557b4a0989c64095aca92efc9585ebbe4c1" title=""><img src="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/optimized/2X/9/92b31557b4a0989c64095aca92efc9585ebbe4c1_2_666x500.png" alt="" data-base62-sha1="kVLouvXyQuMaOiNJmEqStUpJywh" width="666" height="500" srcset="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/optimized/2X/9/92b31557b4a0989c64095aca92efc9585ebbe4c1_2_666x500.png, https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/original/2X/9/92b31557b4a0989c64095aca92efc9585ebbe4c1.png 1.5x, https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/original/2X/9/92b31557b4a0989c64095aca92efc9585ebbe4c1.png 2x" data-small-upload="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/optimized/2X/9/92b31557b4a0989c64095aca92efc9585ebbe4c1_2_10x10.png"><div class="meta"><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-far-image svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#far-image"></use></svg><span class="filename"></span><span class="informations">800×600 1.1 MB</span><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-discourse-expand svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#discourse-expand"></use></svg></div></a></div></p>
<p>Headcrab Stormtrooper zombie.  I’m rebuilding the crab part so you can wear it regular and see out of it (it’s made of wire, tape, stuffing, and a t-shirt) I have since removed the M1 helemt this was built around, so he’s floppy, too.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/great-ideas-and-poor-to-none-execution/359/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/great-ideas-and-poor-to-none-execution/359/3</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 20 May 2009 20:38:38 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-359-3</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/great-ideas-and-poor-to-none-execution/359.rss">Great Ideas and Poor to None Execution</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Great Ideas and Poor to None Execution</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[mattemuse]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Why did you have to make a new thread for this? You could have just posted it in your show off thread…</p>
<p>lol nah, I’m just joshing ya, man… I have the same problem. Easy to start something, tough as hell to finish it.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/great-ideas-and-poor-to-none-execution/359/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/great-ideas-and-poor-to-none-execution/359/2</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 20 May 2009 18:59:35 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-359-2</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/great-ideas-and-poor-to-none-execution/359.rss">Great Ideas and Poor to None Execution</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Great Ideas and Poor to None Execution</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Grand_General_Hot]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Hello, My name isn’t important, but my message is.</p>
<p>I’m sure some of you have had an amazing ideas, I mean amazing, imaginations going wild ideas, but as with everything, reality is a cold viaginaless bitch with a shitie asshole instead.</p>
<p>I’d like to talk about, share your stories and unfinished works.</p>
<p>Myself I write stuff, I never get pass two pages most days, I’ve ever only written two things above 50 A4 pages long.</p>
<p>here is some of my failed works.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b"><span class="bbcode-u">[align=center]Intatius Zal, Commander:[/align]</span></span></p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>There is a void of darkness that fills the area, a voice creeps from the shadows and speaks of a storm, but this isn’t a normal storm, it is the storm of life being cast aside for the benefit of powerful groups bent of control, this is the voice of reason and all hope.</p>
<p>The Voice: It cold, the fields are covered in blood and a terror masses its hunger for victory in the skies, these are dark days for the race of man, and these are dark days for earth.</p>
<p>The Voice: But there is light among the great darkness, sadly the light is another form of evil, but a war must be won with another kind evil to save the race of man, it is so sad that victory will cost the galaxy to much pain in the end, because man will bring an end to all life in the coming days, but I’ll tell the story of how man will became a giant of the stars.</p>
<p>The Voice: I will tell you a story of hope that turn on the stars above, this is the story of how man became the greatest empire of them all. It all begins on the fall of the Xer’kinal empire grip of earth.</p>
<p>The dark void began to shine with life and the darkness began to fade from its shadowy depths.</p>
<p>The Voice: it begins here…</p>
<p>When the darkness faded away it gave way to a wonderful grand hall, the walls where bright white, clearly it was a marble finish, the grand hall was very long with an office in the back, the middle of the floor was a grand red carpet with a lighter red on the edges of the carpet, the walls where covered with paintings, in the office was a man in white uniform, there was two guards beside the man in white, clearly to protect the white uniformed man from possible danger, but from what?</p>
<p>Behind the white uniformed man was a very large painting of a man in a grey suit, this was Intatius Zal, the greatest leader of the remanding human race.</p>
<p>There is a man walking towards the back of the grand hall, his foot steps echo the hall, such an echo could be heard, the man didn’t take to long getting towards the white uniformed man, the man walked up 4  steps to reach the white uniformed man and then man spoke to the white uniformed man.</p>
<p>Lt. Pike: Intatius Zal, Commander.<br>
Commander Hans: Yeah, yeah. Intatius Zal, Lt. Pike. What be the news from the front?</p>
<p>Commander Hans spoke with a German accent while Pike spoke with an accent like an English man.</p>
<p>Lt. Pike: the Americas fell within two hours and the country Ireland was worse hit; Commander Hans.</p>
<p>Commander Hans: How so, Lt. Pike?</p>
<p>Lt. Pike: the surface was scored; recon ships confirmed this, commander.</p>
<p>Commander Hans: Dear lord, if Ireland was hit like this, what of England?</p>
<p>Lt. Pike: 20% of England was caught in the attack, commander.</p>
<p>Commander Hans: When can we expect another attack like this Lt. Pike?</p>
<p>Lt. Pike: Intel doesn’t have a clue, commander.</p>
<p>Commander Hans: this is grim news indeed, Lt. Pike.</p>
<p>The voice of the story teller spoke once again and the grand hall began to fade into darkness.</p>
<p>The Voice: Earth was about to deal a blow to the Xer’kinal once and for all, but the cost would be too great on human life. The humans massed the greatest feet of ships in they’re history, for years they built ship under the surface of the planet, using the technology taken from the Xer’kinal to built hope for the race of man, they waited for the right moment to strike and that moment came soon enough. The things I’ve learned from the race of man is never doubt they’re ability to fight, even if the technology is less advanced than your own.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p><span class="bbcode-b"><span class="bbcode-u">[align=center]Ah Shit…[/align]</span></span></p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>Episode One: It had to happen to me…</p>
<p>The scene fades in on a street; there is an empty street in front of the cut scene camera, cars on fire, dead bodies’ lying to root on the street, the sky was black as night, the lamp posts where flickering, there was the sounds of screaming in the background as if someone was being attacked, there was sounds of guns going off, they sounded near by, the camera zooms in on the scene of the street, the camera stops and looks on a dead body.</p>
<p>Hero: This is me</p>
<p>A voice clips starts to play…</p>
<p>Hero: not to long ago this was a quite street, and then all this started, we thought we could take care of this mess, but we we’re wrong…</p>
<p>The scene starts to fade out…</p>
<p>Hero: It had to happen to me…</p>
<p>The game moves onto another map.</p>
<p>The scene fades on to office; our hero is talking to his friend, “Max Well Gunner” writing comes up on screen “24 hours earlier”, hero and gunner are talking about the wave of crimes hitting the city of “New Derry”. Reports are coming that “Biotech” a lead in the city of work, power for the city, and controls almost every part of the city, but there a few that hold back, fight the power that steps on them in New Derry. But times are changing, as seen in latest crimes, what Biotech wants many of it’s people to believe is that they’re make things better for the people, better living for all, always a job for them, but this is cover story for what’s really happening, they’re make more people unemployed than hiring people of the city. But report’s of a new drug has hit the streets and the source’s say that Biotech is behind this new drug dub “BioGen”. The police force believe that Biogen is another way for Biotech to make more money, there are also reports of missing people, these are the people that biotech make unemployed, the reports coming say that a Biotech van pulls up and takes them away, but the people who have come to say this have disappeared them self’s, most surprising that these people once worked for biotech. But it’s up to “Mike B. Hero” &amp; “Maxwell Gunner” to find out what going on with the people of New Derry and stop this once and for all.</p>
<p>Gunner: Hey Mike, what are we going to do about this?</p>
<p>Hero: I don’t know, but we must find out where these people are being taken.</p>
<p>Gunner: Yeah that’s all well and good but how are we supposed to find one?</p>
<p>Hero: I may have a plan….</p>
<p>Gunner: Any chance of filling me on this plan?</p>
<p>Hero: well I was thinking that these people used to work at biotech for a long time, but where fired due to over employment…</p>
<p>Gunner: yeah I know this Mike; I am working on the same case as you, duh…</p>
<p>Hero: will you let me get to the point!</p>
<p>Gunner: ok ok…</p>
<p>Hero: Well if we get Tony to hack their system again…</p>
<p>Gunner: he did it before?</p>
<p>Hero: Yes back in the early days of Biotech, he said he left a backdoor for him self if he ever needed something from Biotech’s data banks.</p>
<p>Gunner: That’s good; we may need him to hack their data base more than once if the way things are going with these reports are going we may need him more than often.</p>
<p>Hero: Well he can’t get access to the whole database; more or less he’s a high ranking office manager, which isn’t much in the way of Biotech employment for system access Max.</p>
<p>Gunner: oh I see.</p>
<p>Hero: So we’ll ask Tony to help us out, for this, plant a fake Ex-worker file in their database, put the file in the next list for “pick up” and see what happens.</p>
<p>The scene fades out.</p>
<p>Now the player should be able</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p><span class="bbcode-b"><span class="bbcode-u">[align=center]No Regret…[/align]</span></span></p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>++Prologue++</p>
<p>The world screams with the madness of crime, the echoes of the past rise, and the body of a fallen hero lies in a dark room, with a body bag covering his broken body, the room is empty but for the bed trolley holding the body bag above it. The fallen hero speaks his last words through his dying mind.</p>
<p>Jake Mc Johnson: I did my duty, I served to the best of my ability, and what did I get for my problems, paper work, and the red tape. I could have taken down every scum bag if I hadn’t followed the book, fact that it didn’t do me any good for me in the end. So here I am, dead, you can only guess what transpired, but then you make up a fantastic story of how I lived, pff… I barely made minimal wage, no, I did something stupid, I betrayed my own kind, my duty, but then again, I have no regret…</p>
<p><strong>Intro credits</strong></p>
<p>The is no light, but there is only darkness</p>
<p>Jake Mc Johnson: It began on a dark night, a routine patrol, I won’t bore you with all the details, there merely human ones.</p>
<p>The sound of a car can be heard slowly fading in.</p>
<p>Jake Mc Johnson: My partner Lousy was a quiet man, rarely spoke to me, but only if needed somebody to help, most people would stop to listen to hear a single word; he had that karma around him; a rare man indeed.</p>
<p>The world begins to fade into dimly lighted car</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Remember, feel free to post your unfinished work.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/great-ideas-and-poor-to-none-execution/359/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/great-ideas-and-poor-to-none-execution/359/1</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 20 May 2009 18:51:45 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-359-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/great-ideas-and-poor-to-none-execution/359.rss">Great Ideas and Poor to None Execution</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
