<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Questions to game_round_win &amp; mp_round_time Entities</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/questions-to-game-round-win-mp-round-time-entities/15305</link>
    <description>Hello fellas,
i am trying  to create some kind of an Assault for the Mutiplayer, but i am stuck with some open questions, i hope the Devs can help me here.

1). I can add with the [b]mp_round_time[/b] Entity time to the Timer with the Input [i]AddRoundTime[/i] but it seems the [i]Round Time[/i] property is not working. Could it be the server overwrites this value with the Server values? Or does the Entity need somehow be activated? I havnt found an Input for this.
is there a way to create an output when the round time is over? I want to make the Marines win when the Scientists Team have failed to fulfill their task in the given time.


2). Next problem i have is with the [b]game_round_win[/b] Entity, the [i]RoundWin[/i] Input works fine but i activated the keyvalues [i]Force map rese[/i]t &amp; [i]Switch teams on map win?[/i],  both seems not to work. After the Scientists won the round the Server changes to the next level, no matter what Value is set to [i]Force map reset[/i].

3). n the Crossfire Update you had this change: &quot;Can	now lock teams for competitive play&quot; how does it work? Is it possible to activate it in a map?

4). And the last question for this post is: How can i add several items to the Team Spawnpoints? I tried to seperate the items with commas but it dont seems to work.


If anyone is interested in the .vmf file, i uploaded it here for research: [url=&#39;https://www.wikiupload.com/6BB96J7G5PEZUD1&#39;]Klick me![/url]</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2017 10:59:07 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Source 1</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/questions-to-game-round-win-mp-round-time-entities/15305.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Questions to game_round_win &amp; mp_round_time Entities</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Dmx6]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Hello fellas,<br>
i am trying  to create some kind of an Assault for the Mutiplayer, but i am stuck with some open questions, i hope the Devs can help me here.</p>
<p>1). I can add with the <span class="bbcode-b">mp_round_time</span> Entity time to the Timer with the Input <span class="bbcode-i">AddRoundTime</span> but it seems the <span class="bbcode-i">Round Time</span> property is not working. Could it be the server overwrites this value with the Server values? Or does the Entity need somehow be activated? I havnt found an Input for this.<br>
is there a way to create an output when the round time is over? I want to make the Marines win when the Scientists Team have failed to fulfill their task in the given time.</p>
<p>2). Next problem i have is with the <span class="bbcode-b">game_round_win</span> Entity, the <span class="bbcode-i">RoundWin</span> Input works fine but i activated the keyvalues <span class="bbcode-i">Force map rese</span>t &amp; <span class="bbcode-i">Switch teams on map win?</span>,  both seems not to work. After the Scientists won the round the Server changes to the next level, no matter what Value is set to <span class="bbcode-i">Force map reset</span>.</p>
<p>3). n the Crossfire Update you had this change: “Can	now lock teams for competitive play” how does it work? Is it possible to activate it in a map?</p>
<p>4). And the last question for this post is: How can i add several items to the Team Spawnpoints? I tried to seperate the items with commas but it dont seems to work.</p>
<p>If anyone is interested in the .vmf file, i uploaded it here for research: <a href="https://www.wikiupload.com/6BB96J7G5PEZUD1" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Klick me!</a></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/questions-to-game-round-win-mp-round-time-entities/15305/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/questions-to-game-round-win-mp-round-time-entities/15305/1</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2017 10:59:07 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-15305-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/questions-to-game-round-win-mp-round-time-entities/15305.rss">Questions to game_round_win &amp; mp_round_time Entities</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
