<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Obesity</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/obesity/2521</link>
    <description>Our modern lifestyles have lead to a massive increase in Obesity, in [url=&#39;https://www.independent.co.uk/life-style/health-and-families/health-news/massive-increase-in-obesity-means-onethird-of-children-are-overweight-475136.html&#39;]England one third of the children[/url], and one in four adults are overweight, and [url=&#39;https://www.cdc.gov/obesity/data/trends.html&#39;]in America the problem is much the same if not worse[/url]. Obesity causes massive problem for our national health services, spending millions in buying new equipment and ambulances to cater for them. But is this increase in Obesity in your opinion, an illness or people just being lazy? And how do you feel about those who are obese?

It is a fact that many people are born not being able to digest as much as others without it showing very quickly, but is this for some an excuse? People also eat because they are depressed, depression is very much a sickness, and so that constitutes illness. There are those however that sit around all day, playing games on computers, eating fast food and junk, generally being lazy, that then pile on the pounds, do they deserve our sympathies? And do they make up the majority of the obese and if so, why should our governments fork out millions to look after them? Yes it is basic human rights, but does this not push out those who generally need help more for less selfish reasons?

On the other side of the argument, is it so wrong to be overweight? Should you not be proud of who you are and what you look like? Does it matter what you eat, or that you lack much exercise, just as long as you are enjoying doing what you are doing? Should the press and people be more considerate or more accepting of you regardless of your size? And if you are obese or have suffered from obesity what would you say made you that way and do you find that you are frequently discriminated against because of your size, is that right in your opinion or wrong?

Is the increase in Obesity an illness or laziness?</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 22 Aug 2011 03:03:02 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Off Topic</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/obesity/2521.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Obesity</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Fancy_Pants]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>tl;motherfucking dr dude you can be healthy and fat, christ</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/obesity/2521/133">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/obesity/2521/133</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 22 Aug 2011 03:03:02 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2521-133</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/obesity/2521.rss">Obesity</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Obesity</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Jeannotvb]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Fancy Pants">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Fancy Pants:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>well ok nobody ever said that but i guess<br>
and no i am aware of the difference between being overweight and obese but i am saying an obese person can be just as if not more healthy than someone of average weight so i dont see the point of the debate</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>When you refer to an obese person being healthy, do you mean that he does not have any deficiencies in minerals and vitamins? Because even if that’s the case, obesity brings lots of risk factors with it that one cannot overlook. That being said, I guess it’s somewhat possible for obese people to be healthier than average weight people but unfortunately most obese people aren’t like that. In fact, most obese people are severely deficient in many vitamins and minerals because the junk food they eat contains nothing of value.</p>
<p>Also note, the danger of obesity depends for a large portion on where the fat is located. The danger spots would be places like the chest where most of the important organs are located. For females the fat is often stored around the hips, this is actually less dangerous and these people have a smaller chance of heart disease as opposed to men who usually have fat deposits around the important organs.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="bur">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/b/87869e/40.png" class="avatar"> bur:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>jeannotvb is thinking of the obesity severe enough to be damaging to your health, fancy pants is thinking of obesity as simply being overweight, but not necessarily that severely<br>
i think</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>People who are overweight have just slightly more weight then is recommended by health agencies, people who are obese have a LOT more weight than is recommended. I agree it’s not a perfect system though, body builders for example could be classified as obese which is ridiculous. There’s more problems but I cba to mention them, I guess it’s best to determine the body fat percentage.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/obesity/2521/132">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/obesity/2521/132</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 22 Aug 2011 01:27:35 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2521-132</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/obesity/2521.rss">Obesity</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Obesity</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[geekofalltrades]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Christfuck, that’s the dumbest thing I’ve ever heard.  Obesity is not a disease.  It’s an irresponsible life decision.  It’s no more a disease than getting plugs or lip implants.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/obesity/2521/131">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/obesity/2521/131</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 21 Aug 2011 23:32:15 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2521-131</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/obesity/2521.rss">Obesity</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Obesity</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[TheHippo]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>obesity is a classified as a disease. a <span class="bbcode-i">disease</span>. you can’t be healthy when you’re sick.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/obesity/2521/130">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/obesity/2521/130</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 21 Aug 2011 22:10:22 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2521-130</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/obesity/2521.rss">Obesity</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Obesity</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Medevilae]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Weight classifications are touchy, because BMI sucks. They should be based on BFI instead.</p>
<p>EDIT: Eh, kind of just paraphrased what Fancy said but yeah.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/obesity/2521/129">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/obesity/2521/129</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 21 Aug 2011 19:29:31 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2521-129</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/obesity/2521.rss">Obesity</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Obesity</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Fancy_Pants]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Jeannotvb">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/j/90ced4/40.png" class="avatar"> Jeannotvb:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>True, though I wouldn’t go as far as stating obesity is healthy.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>well ok nobody ever said that but i guess<br>
and no i am aware of the difference between being overweight and obese but i am saying an obese person can be just as if not more healthy than someone of average weight so i dont see the point of the debate</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/obesity/2521/128">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/obesity/2521/128</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 21 Aug 2011 18:43:15 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2521-128</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/obesity/2521.rss">Obesity</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Obesity</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[danielsangeo]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>There is obese and then there is “morbidly obese”.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/obesity/2521/127">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/obesity/2521/127</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 21 Aug 2011 14:10:38 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2521-127</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/obesity/2521.rss">Obesity</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Obesity</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[bur]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>what all this is about, really, is what you see as “obesity”</p>
<p>jeannotvb is thinking of the obesity severe enough to be damaging to your health, fancy pants is thinking of obesity as simply being overweight, but not necessarily that severely</p>
<p>i think</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/obesity/2521/126">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/obesity/2521/126</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 21 Aug 2011 13:59:02 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2521-126</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/obesity/2521.rss">Obesity</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Obesity</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Jeannotvb]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Fancy Pants">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Fancy Pants:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>no jk u can be healthy and obese just like u can be unhealthy and average weight</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>True, though I wouldn’t go as far as stating obesity is healthy.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/obesity/2521/125">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/obesity/2521/125</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 21 Aug 2011 10:52:29 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2521-125</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/obesity/2521.rss">Obesity</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Obesity</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[danielsangeo]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Because fatty fat fatters are fucking fat fatties.</p>
<p>Or somethin’.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/obesity/2521/124">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/obesity/2521/124</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 21 Aug 2011 06:15:18 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2521-124</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/obesity/2521.rss">Obesity</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Obesity</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Fancy_Pants]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>FUCK FATTIES!!<br>
no jk u can be healthy and obese just like u can be unhealthy and average weight<br>
let people be fat if they want<br>
for real bros how is this a debate</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/obesity/2521/123">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/obesity/2521/123</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 21 Aug 2011 06:12:33 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2521-123</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/obesity/2521.rss">Obesity</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Obesity</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Jeannotvb]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="KenCastle">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/k/d78d45/40.png" class="avatar"> KenCastle:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>No, I wouldn’t. You’re quite assumptive over someone you don’t know shit about.  You ever been to Subway? Hey, maybe <span class="bbcode-i">you</span> get a large order of fries and a large burger but lots of people don’t and get just as much enjoyment out of a little kiddy burger and a medium sized water and a salad. Some people do have very high metabolisms. For instance, my mother can eat cookie dough [high colorie] and actually lose weight. Sure, that’s not the norm for everyone but it’s dumb to just go around assuming. She had to actually go to different grocery stores because everyone thought she was feeding an army and it was just food for her and she was embarrassed.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>True, I don’t know shit about you, but I do know shit about food.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="KenCastle">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/k/d78d45/40.png" class="avatar"> KenCastle:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>You ever been to Subway?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>No.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="KenCastle">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/k/d78d45/40.png" class="avatar"> KenCastle:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Hey, maybe <span class="bbcode-i">you</span> get a large order of fries and a large burger but lots of people don’t and get just as much enjoyment out of a little kiddy burger and a medium sized water and a salad.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>That doesn’t change the fact that fast food diets are insanely calorie dense and nutrient deficient. Even if you ate a ‘kiddy burger’ and salad three times a day I’d find it hard to believe you can stay as <span class="bbcode-i">thin as a pencil</span>.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="KenCastle">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/k/d78d45/40.png" class="avatar"> KenCastle:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Some people do have very high metabolisms.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Does that mean they burn an extra 1000 calories a day? Of course not. Metabolism is not an excuse for obesity.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="KenCastle">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/k/d78d45/40.png" class="avatar"> KenCastle:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>For instance, my mother can eat cookie dough [high colorie] and actually lose weight. Sure, that’s not the norm for everyone but it’s dumb to just go around assuming.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>You can’t contribute overweight/obesity to a single food item, it’s a combination of lack of exercise and consuming too much calories. A lot of foods these days are so calorie dense however that even exercise might not be enough.</p>
<ul>
<li>
</li></ul>
<p>Anyway, obesity and the diseases that come with it are a major issue in western nations. 1 in 3 is now overweight or obese, many have diabetes type 2 and we have record deaths of heart disease, stroke and cancer (they are in fact the top 3 causes of death). This was not always so, so clearly you can’t blame this on genetics nor metabolism. You can take the healthiest people in the world and put them on a western diet, they WILL get health issues, regardless of their genetics. China is the perfect example of this.</p>
<ul>
<li>
</li></ul>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Guzzi">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/g/f9ae1b/40.png" class="avatar"> Guzzi:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I’ve been reading a book that talks about the chemical reactions in a persons brain when that person falls victim to addiction. Sugar and carbohydrates are noted as being as addictive as heroin, cigarettes, alcohol (and the list can go on) to the right kind of person i.e. obese people.</p>
<p>I would say (The book also states this) people who are obese are no different than an alcoholic or heroin user(Or even someone addicted to video games, my own opinion for VG’s). If there is one thing this book taught me is that an addiction is a addiction. The chemicals Serotonin and Dopamine are involved with alcohol, carbs/sugars, heroin, cocain, PCP, LSD, and minute levels of Serotonin and Dopamine are present even for marijuana smokers. (Although ALL mammals have something called Cannabinoids aka THC receptors in the brain who’s soul purpose is for THC. The main component in weed that gets someone high. Fun little fact there. Chew it up.)</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>It’s true, that’s why food companies love to use high-fructose corn syrup, table sugar, salt, MSG and other sweeteners to make the eating experience as pleasant as possible to make sure the consumer buys the product again and possibly in larger quantities. We evolved to chase those tasty experiences so we could find the right foods in nature, modern technology however has made it possible to concentrate them which (as you explained) causes many problems like addiction.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/obesity/2521/122">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/obesity/2521/122</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 20 Aug 2011 20:05:50 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2521-122</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/obesity/2521.rss">Obesity</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Obesity</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Guzzi]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I would assume that, since everyone on this planet eats food, one would think everyone would like to be educated on what foods are healthy and ultimately just how to eat a balanced diet.</p>
<pre><code>THAT is what the thread is currently about.
</code></pre>
<p>I’ve been reading a book that talks about the chemical reactions in a persons brain when that person falls victim to addiction. Sugar and carbohydrates are noted as being as addictive as heroin, cigarettes, alcohol (and the list can go on) to the right kind of person i.e. obese people.</p>
<p>I would say (The book also states this) people who are obese are no different than an alcoholic or heroin user(Or even someone addicted to video games, my own opinion for VG’s). If there is one thing this book taught me is that an addiction is a addiction. The chemicals Serotonin and Dopamine are involved with alcohol, carbs/sugars, heroin, cocain, PCP, LSD, and minute levels of Serotonin and Dopamine are present even for marijuana smokers. (Although ALL mammals have something called Cannabinoids aka THC receptors in the brain who’s soul purpose is for THC. The main component in weed that gets someone high. Fun little fact there. Chew it up.)</p>
<p>For anyone who is interested in the book you might be able to find it at your Library.<br>
It’s called “The Chemical Carousel: What Science Tells Us About Beating Addiction” It’s a very very good read for anyone willing to stimulate their brain cells reading instead playing a video game. That’s right! You’re all guilty!</p>
<p>THAT is what the thread title implies this thread is about.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/obesity/2521/121">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/obesity/2521/121</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 20 Aug 2011 17:23:06 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2521-121</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/obesity/2521.rss">Obesity</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Obesity</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[KenCastle]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Jeannotvb">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/j/90ced4/40.png" class="avatar"> Jeannotvb:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>The genetics argument is mostly bullshit, it’s the typical excuse among overweight people. They simply eat too much of the wrong food. They often don’t recognize how bad their diet is, even foods they think are healthy are often the complete opposite.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>True but genetics are often a part of it. I’m not making excuses for the people. Lots of people genuinely are more apt to get fat but they still choose to stuff their faces. Not everyone’s frame is the same, nor is their fat distribution or their metabolism. Give a Big Mac to one person and they gain weight and give it someone else and they might not. Some people require more calories to survive and some people require far less. I’m in the category that’d require more. If I were trapped in a survival situation where food was of short supply I have no doubt I’d be one of the first to starve to death.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>You’re overreacting, if you ate fast food meals all the time (3+ times a day) then you would be overweight within a matter of months.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>No, I wouldn’t. You’re quite assumptive over someone you don’t know shit about. It depends on what kinds of fast food you eat, not all of it is super unhealthy. Some people actually look online at the calories, serving size, etc. and make good informed decisions. You ever been to Subway? Hey, maybe <span class="bbcode-i">you</span> get a large order of fries and a large burger but lots of people don’t and get just as much enjoyment out of a little kiddy burger and a medium sized water and a salad. Some people do have very high metabolisms. For instance, my mother can eat cookie dough [high colorie] and actually lose weight. Sure, that’s not the norm for everyone but it’s dumb to just go around assuming. She had to actually go to different grocery stores because everyone thought she was feeding an army and it was just food for her and she was embarrassed.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/obesity/2521/120">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/obesity/2521/120</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 20 Aug 2011 14:42:36 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2521-120</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/obesity/2521.rss">Obesity</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Obesity</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[calhoun_freeman]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I’m fat, and I’m not proud. Imma exercise. After I play some games.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/obesity/2521/119">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/obesity/2521/119</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 20 Aug 2011 10:23:55 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2521-119</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/obesity/2521.rss">Obesity</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Obesity</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Jeannotvb]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>The genetics argument is mostly bullshit, it’s the typical excuse among overweight people. They simply eat too much of the wrong food. They often don’t recognize how bad their diet is, even foods they think are healthy are often the complete opposite.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="KenCastle">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/k/d78d45/40.png" class="avatar"> KenCastle:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I’m as thin as a pencil [figuratively speaking] and I eat junk food ALL THE TIME.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>You’re overreacting, if you ate fast food meals all the time (3+ times a day) then you would be overweight within a matter of months.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/obesity/2521/118">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/obesity/2521/118</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 20 Aug 2011 10:10:44 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2521-118</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/obesity/2521.rss">Obesity</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Obesity</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[KenCastle]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Not to gloat or anything but I’m as thin as a pencil [figuratively speaking] and I eat junk food ALL THE TIME. I get offended when people assume I must puke everything up or I’m on some super strong medicine, cause I don’t do those things. I do exercise though when I’m not busy owning stupid people on TF2 but I often go weeks without.</p>
<p>I’d say it’s 50% genetics and 50% lifestyle cause I’ve seen people eat extremely healthy and still be huge but most overweight folks don’t do that.</p>
<p>Simply put, if you get lost in the skin folds of your significant other while making love than he/she is overweight  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/smiley.png?v=9" title=":smiley:" class="emoji" alt=":smiley:">  I can’t tell you how many times I’ve seen that in porn videos lol. The person is squirming around with a facial expression like, “Help meee!”</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/obesity/2521/117">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/obesity/2521/117</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 20 Aug 2011 09:53:05 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2521-117</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/obesity/2521.rss">Obesity</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Obesity</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[mankyman6]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Jokerine">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Jokerine:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Great insight there.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Indeed</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/obesity/2521/116">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/obesity/2521/116</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2011 02:13:52 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2521-116</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/obesity/2521.rss">Obesity</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Obesity</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[TheOneAndOnly]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Great insight there.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/obesity/2521/115">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/obesity/2521/115</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2011 02:08:44 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2521-115</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/obesity/2521.rss">Obesity</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Obesity</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[mankyman6]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I blame cupcakes <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=9" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/obesity/2521/114">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/obesity/2521/114</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2011 02:07:36 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2521-114</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/obesity/2521.rss">Obesity</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Obesity</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[CatzEyes93]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I bet they can survive longer being pinned in a car after an accident puts them out of sight.</p>
<p>&lt;_&lt;</p>
<blockquote>
<p>_&gt;</p>
</blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/obesity/2521/113">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/obesity/2521/113</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 21 May 2010 14:54:50 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2521-113</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/obesity/2521.rss">Obesity</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Obesity</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[bur]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Yesterday on the news: overweight people have a higher chance of surviving intensive care, because they can get energy from their fat, or something.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/obesity/2521/112">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/obesity/2521/112</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 21 May 2010 14:42:11 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2521-112</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/obesity/2521.rss">Obesity</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Obesity</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[DeleteThis]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>ha Crysis Nanosuit arm<br>
If people are so concerned about obesity maybe they shouldn’t feed their kids super-fatty foods like morons, same thing with T.V. No, they dodge personal responsibility so much that they immediately blame everyone around them. It just sickens me that’s all. Ah well fashion trends come and go, but ignorance will always stay</p>
<p>If you’re 5 foot 9 inches and between 140-145 pounds is that overweight?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/obesity/2521/111">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/obesity/2521/111</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 21 May 2010 05:34:41 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2521-111</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/obesity/2521.rss">Obesity</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Obesity</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[sersoft]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><div class="lightbox-wrapper"><a class="lightbox" href="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/original/2X/f/ff9c18e065b18bff8af6de498322c6964a66a7b4.png" data-download-href="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/ff9c18e065b18bff8af6de498322c6964a66a7b4" title=""><img src="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/optimized/2X/f/ff9c18e065b18bff8af6de498322c6964a66a7b4_2_690x462.png" alt="" data-base62-sha1="AtebSzO0R6C4E4pciA1THeelPhi" width="690" height="462" srcset="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/optimized/2X/f/ff9c18e065b18bff8af6de498322c6964a66a7b4_2_690x462.png, https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/original/2X/f/ff9c18e065b18bff8af6de498322c6964a66a7b4.png 1.5x, https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/original/2X/f/ff9c18e065b18bff8af6de498322c6964a66a7b4.png 2x" data-small-upload="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/optimized/2X/f/ff9c18e065b18bff8af6de498322c6964a66a7b4_2_10x10.png"><div class="meta"><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-far-image svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#far-image"></use></svg><span class="filename"></span><span class="informations">900×603 612 KB</span><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-discourse-expand svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#discourse-expand"></use></svg></div></a></div></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/obesity/2521/110">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/obesity/2521/110</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 19 May 2010 01:19:39 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2521-110</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/obesity/2521.rss">Obesity</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Obesity</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Imonfire]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><span alt="" class="broken-image" title="This image is broken"><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-unlink svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#unlink"></use></svg></span></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/obesity/2521/109">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/obesity/2521/109</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 18 May 2010 23:59:29 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2521-109</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/obesity/2521.rss">Obesity</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
