<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Steam Trading Cards</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/steam-trading-cards/12379</link>
    <description>Can&#39;t seem to find a thread up yet, so here it goes. What are all your opinions?

I personally find it a little uncomfortable. I dislike the idea of a video game client trying to turn my behavior outside of video games into a video game. Especially the fact that there&#39;s rewards for simply buying a game. It all just kinda rubs me wrong. I&#39;m not going too bitch much about it because in the end it&#39;s not a feature that in any way degrades my steam experience. It&#39;s just a bit of an uncomfortable territory in my opinion, like the M$ thing about achievements for watching videos and shit.

However I do find it intensely annoying that steam features I may want to actually use such as profile customization are dependent on this scheme that I don&#39;t feel like getting too involved in.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2013 08:41:38 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Technology and Gaming</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/steam-trading-cards/12379.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Steam Trading Cards</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Jack_Freeman]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>So far they’ve proven useful. I gathered a lot of cards and sold them so I could pay for a cheap DLC.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/steam-trading-cards/12379/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/steam-trading-cards/12379/6</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2013 08:41:38 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12379-6</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/steam-trading-cards/12379.rss">Steam Trading Cards</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Steam Trading Cards</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Kairouseki]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I hope I can sell whatever cards I do get. I don’t see much use in leveling up with most of the useless stuff you get for doing so.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/steam-trading-cards/12379/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/steam-trading-cards/12379/5</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2013 04:31:30 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12379-5</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/steam-trading-cards/12379.rss">Steam Trading Cards</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Steam Trading Cards</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[GilCMassey]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Hell, I got 20 and I only talk to like 7. And as for the topic:</p>
<p>I don’t quite know how I feel yet. It seems like an ok idea, but the OP has a point with the M$ thing.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/steam-trading-cards/12379/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/steam-trading-cards/12379/4</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2013 04:22:53 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12379-4</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/steam-trading-cards/12379.rss">Steam Trading Cards</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Steam Trading Cards</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[FERGUS]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="geekofalltrades">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/g/c2a13f/40.png" class="avatar"> geekofalltrades:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Extra friends list slots?  Really?  It sounds like our friends list will be capped at 300, then go up by 5 slots every time you level.  Not that I’ll ever likely approach 300 friends, but why is that considered a reward?  Why aren’t friends lists just unlimited to start with?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I always wondered which kind of person you are if you manage to get so many friends on steam. Are you just adding people because they where performing well in a game you played?</p>
<p>It’s like facebook. I have people in my friend list that for some reason have over 2000 facebook friends. Why? I have 119 and I can honestly say that I haven’t had any contact with atleast 90 of them in years, I could remove them without feeling any loss.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/steam-trading-cards/12379/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/steam-trading-cards/12379/3</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2013 04:19:55 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12379-3</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/steam-trading-cards/12379.rss">Steam Trading Cards</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Steam Trading Cards</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[geekofalltrades]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I like the cards themselves because they’re marketable (or at least the summer sale ones are), so I can throw them on the market for a rebate on whatever game I’ve just bought or have been playing.</p>
<p>On the other hand, a lot of the rewards being offered for crafting them are either gimmicky bullshit or stuff we should get anyway.  I mean, crafting game badges from trading cards now earns you XP towards your Steam level, and…</p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>Leveling up earns you non-tradable items like profile showcases, extra friends list slots, and more.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Extra friends list slots?  Really?  It sounds like our friends list will be capped at 300, then go up by 5 slots every time you level.  Not that I’ll ever likely approach 300 friends, but why is that considered a reward?  Why aren’t friends lists just unlimited to start with?  You can also get tradable, marketable emoticons, which…</p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>…can be used anywhere on Steam where you can type, like chat, discussions, and profiles.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Again, that’s not a reward.  That’s trivial bullshit.  Why wouldn’t you just add emoticons to your chat client and let everyone use them?</p>
<p>I’ll continue to put the cards up on the market to fatten my Steam wallet a bit, and I won’t really miss these extra “features” they’re bundled with.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/steam-trading-cards/12379/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/steam-trading-cards/12379/2</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2013 22:53:29 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12379-2</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/steam-trading-cards/12379.rss">Steam Trading Cards</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Steam Trading Cards</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[garrthbarrttinn]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Can’t seem to find a thread up yet, so here it goes. What are all your opinions?</p>
<p>I personally find it a little uncomfortable. I dislike the idea of a video game client trying to turn my behavior outside of video games into a video game. Especially the fact that there’s rewards for simply buying a game. It all just kinda rubs me wrong. I’m not going too bitch much about it because in the end it’s not a feature that in any way degrades my steam experience. It’s just a bit of an uncomfortable territory in my opinion, like the M$ thing about achievements for watching videos and shit.</p>
<p>However I do find it intensely annoying that steam features I may want to actually use such as profile customization are dependent on this scheme that I don’t feel like getting too involved in.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/steam-trading-cards/12379/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/steam-trading-cards/12379/1</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2013 22:32:57 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12379-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/steam-trading-cards/12379.rss">Steam Trading Cards</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
