<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>1 hour in Anomalous materials</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/1-hour-in-anomalous-materials/9778</link>
    <description>Game is great.
There was so much nostalgia during that tram ride and at the same time it was new and improved.

As a person that has passed more time in pre-resonance cascade black mesa than all the time spent in any real life libraries (be them school, college or public), I just had to inspect every inch of Sector C. :freeman:
I think I may have missed something, so I will be coming back to it with cheats and noclip after my playthrough.

The dialogue, the voices they all seem so alive. Even the fact (bug?) that people that talk to you avoid direct eye contact (head towards you, eyes looking over your shoulder) just add to the feel of being in a lab full of nerds  :smiley: 

That guy in the locker room that enumerates the new features of your new H.E.V. compared to his one in the old days. All nice touches.


I guess it is bad manners to bitch about things in my second post in my new forum registration, but I just have to take this out of my chest:

1) [u]No H.E.V. voice output when you put it on.[/u] Startup music is ok, but I really miss that half a minute of computer voice telling you what has been activated.

2) [u]Only 1 teleportation during the resonance cascade[/u]. When I heard the voice com in the tram to talk about sport events and semifinals I screamed &quot;That is not cannon!!!&quot;, but that was nothing compared to the lack of teleporting hiccups that made the original experience that much more intense.
I know - Xen not finished. Still there is a difference between not finishing a sequence of several levels with many unseen enemies and not having several shots of the landscape.
Also if you ever reach to release Xen and you decide to redo this part so that you actually add some of it don&#39;t forget to allow the player to look around. Static camera = breaks immersion ; Free camera while you are trapped in an unknown world for unknown duration until next teleporter jump = many heartbeats skipped.

3) [u]Many new props, but many remain static[/u]. I guess now is a good time to explain where that 1 hour was spent before I actually entered the test chamber. I decided to move all the chairs in the labs with me in the test chamber and then maybe get them all the way to Lambda complex  :smiley: 
I got up to 6 chairs, I was flinging them around, got several &quot;cease and desist or some shit&quot; come backs  :smiley: , but I was disappointed that there were chairs that weren&#39;t made in moveable props. I love the new details added, but adding overhead cabinets and not making them interactive just makes me sad.  :frowning: 


Anyway those were the things I wanted to share with you. I expect to play the rest of the game on a single breath without wasting time so much so I probably won&#39;t have anything to complain about after that. I decided I might as well bitch about this now  :slight_smile:</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 15 Sep 2012 18:22:01 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>The Cafeteria</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/1-hour-in-anomalous-materials/9778.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>1 hour in Anomalous materials</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[TrantaLocked]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Lol he is just trying to see the bright side of things.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/1-hour-in-anomalous-materials/9778/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/1-hour-in-anomalous-materials/9778/6</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 15 Sep 2012 18:22:01 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9778-6</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/1-hour-in-anomalous-materials/9778.rss">1 hour in Anomalous materials</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>1 hour in Anomalous materials</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[itzkin]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="trenmost">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/t/a88e4f/40.png" class="avatar"> trenmost:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>if you mean the Black Mesa Hazard Course decathlon, that was in the original too. you just didnt pay attention in HL1  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=9" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Oh my! I just watched a video about it on youtube.<br>
I never understood that part of the speech until now.<br>
I guess my English has improved :freeman:</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="TrantaLocked">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/t/7feea3/40.png" class="avatar"> TrantaLocked:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>There was no guy in the locker room who talked about the H.E.V. for me.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>There is only one guy in the locker room (talking about ties when you enter). Pass by him with HEV and he will give you some sentences.</p>
<p>I disagree that you’d feel fed up with it, as it is the feedback of an apparatus that is meant to keep you alive. I’d be interested in hearing its start up log every time mind you.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/1-hour-in-anomalous-materials/9778/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/1-hour-in-anomalous-materials/9778/5</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 15 Sep 2012 11:29:59 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9778-5</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/1-hour-in-anomalous-materials/9778.rss">1 hour in Anomalous materials</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>1 hour in Anomalous materials</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[uk_sniper]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Personally i was glad there was no 45 seconds of HEV waffle. if you had to wear that suit everyday for work, you’d want to puncture your own ear drums hearing that crap day in day out.</p>
<p>I spent lots of time investigating with the use key, annoying scientists and generally dicking around. I was actually quite concerned how far you had to go before you got your crowbar, I went back because I thought I must have missed it.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/1-hour-in-anomalous-materials/9778/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/1-hour-in-anomalous-materials/9778/4</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 15 Sep 2012 09:39:08 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9778-4</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/1-hour-in-anomalous-materials/9778.rss">1 hour in Anomalous materials</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>1 hour in Anomalous materials</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[trenmost]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>if you mean the Black Mesa Hazard Course decathlon, that was in the original too. you just didnt pay attention in HL1  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=9" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
<p>i also missed the hev voice in the beginning, and also some sounds could be improved (like houndeye’s, teleportation sounds, vortigaunts sounds, and i missed the siren after the resonance cascade, and some more)</p>
<p>but that is the only thing i can think of for future improvements.</p>
<p>mod is really awesome  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=9" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/1-hour-in-anomalous-materials/9778/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/1-hour-in-anomalous-materials/9778/3</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 15 Sep 2012 09:04:15 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9778-3</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/1-hour-in-anomalous-materials/9778.rss">1 hour in Anomalous materials</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>1 hour in Anomalous materials</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[TrantaLocked]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>There was no guy in the locker room who talked about the H.E.V. for me.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/1-hour-in-anomalous-materials/9778/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/1-hour-in-anomalous-materials/9778/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 15 Sep 2012 08:55:34 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9778-2</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/1-hour-in-anomalous-materials/9778.rss">1 hour in Anomalous materials</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>1 hour in Anomalous materials</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[itzkin]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Game is great.<br>
There was so much nostalgia during that tram ride and at the same time it was new and improved.</p>
<p>As a person that has passed more time in pre-resonance cascade black mesa than all the time spent in any real life libraries (be them school, college or public), I just had to inspect every inch of Sector C. :freeman:<br>
I think I may have missed something, so I will be coming back to it with cheats and noclip after my playthrough.</p>
<p>The dialogue, the voices they all seem so alive. Even the fact (bug?) that people that talk to you avoid direct eye contact (head towards you, eyes looking over your shoulder) just add to the feel of being in a lab full of nerds  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/smiley.png?v=9" title=":smiley:" class="emoji" alt=":smiley:"></p>
<p>That guy in the locker room that enumerates the new features of your new H.E.V. compared to his one in the old days. All nice touches.</p>
<p>I guess it is bad manners to bitch about things in my second post in my new forum registration, but I just have to take this out of my chest:</p>
<ol>
<li>
<p><span class="bbcode-u">No H.E.V. voice output when you put it on.</span> Startup music is ok, but I really miss that half a minute of computer voice telling you what has been activated.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p><span class="bbcode-u">Only 1 teleportation during the resonance cascade</span>. When I heard the voice com in the tram to talk about sport events and semifinals I screamed “That is not cannon!!!”, but that was nothing compared to the lack of teleporting hiccups that made the original experience that much more intense.<br>
I know - Xen not finished. Still there is a difference between not finishing a sequence of several levels with many unseen enemies and not having several shots of the landscape.<br>
Also if you ever reach to release Xen and you decide to redo this part so that you actually add some of it don’t forget to allow the player to look around. Static camera = breaks immersion ; Free camera while you are trapped in an unknown world for unknown duration until next teleporter jump = many heartbeats skipped.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p><span class="bbcode-u">Many new props, but many remain static</span>. I guess now is a good time to explain where that 1 hour was spent before I actually entered the test chamber. I decided to move all the chairs in the labs with me in the test chamber and then maybe get them all the way to Lambda complex  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/smiley.png?v=9" title=":smiley:" class="emoji" alt=":smiley:"><br>
I got up to 6 chairs, I was flinging them around, got several “cease and desist or some shit” come backs  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/smiley.png?v=9" title=":smiley:" class="emoji" alt=":smiley:"> , but I was disappointed that there were chairs that weren’t made in moveable props. I love the new details added, but adding overhead cabinets and not making them interactive just makes me sad.  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/frowning.png?v=9" title=":frowning:" class="emoji" alt=":frowning:"></p>
</li>
</ol>
<p>Anyway those were the things I wanted to share with you. I expect to play the rest of the game on a single breath without wasting time so much so I probably won’t have anything to complain about after that. I decided I might as well bitch about this now  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=9" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/1-hour-in-anomalous-materials/9778/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/1-hour-in-anomalous-materials/9778/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 15 Sep 2012 08:23:09 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9778-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/1-hour-in-anomalous-materials/9778.rss">1 hour in Anomalous materials</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
