<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Zoning issue exiting Blast Pit</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/zoning-issue-exiting-blast-pit/10559</link>
    <description>Down the ladder, there is a level load, a continuity error, and an evil autosave. 

When I first climbed down the ladder, on zone I was dropped off the ladder, fell to the bottom and died. Also the second time I zoned in, I noticed the entire ladder is caged after the zoning (presumably to prevent the drop, but didn&#39;t work) but not before. 

My suggestion to fix it would be to add a circular walkway around the tube, where the level load is. Either as you get near it, touch it, or flip the switch I&#39;m about to mention, the load will be triggered. This will prevent falling to your death. 

The ladder would continue down as it does, but there would be a retractable trapdoor above the ladder, preventing progress. On the walkway, next to the ladder there could be a button to retract it. On the other side of the walkway around the mid-tunnel point could be a door, to tie it in with being a maintenance station at mid-level of the tunnel. 

This would mean that the loading wouldn&#39;t take place on the ladder, and you wouldn&#39;t be dropped to your doom. Also give more reason for there to be a ladder down there.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 17 Sep 2012 14:48:34 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>In-game Issues (Mod)</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/zoning-issue-exiting-blast-pit/10559.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Zoning issue exiting Blast Pit</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[neura]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Down the ladder, there is a level load, a continuity error, and an evil autosave.</p>
<p>When I first climbed down the ladder, on zone I was dropped off the ladder, fell to the bottom and died. Also the second time I zoned in, I noticed the entire ladder is caged after the zoning (presumably to prevent the drop, but didn’t work) but not before.</p>
<p>My suggestion to fix it would be to add a circular walkway around the tube, where the level load is. Either as you get near it, touch it, or flip the switch I’m about to mention, the load will be triggered. This will prevent falling to your death.</p>
<p>The ladder would continue down as it does, but there would be a retractable trapdoor above the ladder, preventing progress. On the walkway, next to the ladder there could be a button to retract it. On the other side of the walkway around the mid-tunnel point could be a door, to tie it in with being a maintenance station at mid-level of the tunnel.</p>
<p>This would mean that the loading wouldn’t take place on the ladder, and you wouldn’t be dropped to your doom. Also give more reason for there to be a ladder down there.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/zoning-issue-exiting-blast-pit/10559/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/zoning-issue-exiting-blast-pit/10559/1</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 17 Sep 2012 14:48:34 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-10559-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/zoning-issue-exiting-blast-pit/10559.rss">Zoning issue exiting Blast Pit</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
