<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Game crash</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/game-crash/10232</link>
    <description>Okay... I know I&#39;m going to sound like a complete moron... but I&#39;ll do my best to explain it as best as I can. 

I&#39;m in the area where you meet the first major big fish monsters that pulls that scientist off the rails and into the water. Headed up to see the other scientist watching overheard who directs you to the tranquillizer gun. 

Shot the fish with the tranquillizer gun, and attempted to then shoot it with pistol or SMG, the game crashes after firing a couple of shots into it. 

Thinking maybe I wasn&#39;t supposed to shoot him with my guns and leave him tranquillised, I left him there and went to talk to the other scientist - but he just harps on about nothing. 

Not sure what to do here... I can&#39;t get past this section without it crashing (assuming I am supposed to kill the fish after you&#39;ve tranquillised it).</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 16 Sep 2012 22:12:54 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>In-game Issues (Mod)</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/game-crash/10232.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Game crash</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Piano_Man]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Then what do you do after you’ve tranquillised it???</p>
<p>Where do you go?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/game-crash/10232/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/game-crash/10232/3</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 16 Sep 2012 22:12:54 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-10232-3</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/game-crash/10232.rss">Game crash</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Game crash</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[vktech]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>As far as I know, the crossbow kills it, so just let it be. Even if it is a tranquilizer, it wouldn’t wake up for at least an hour, irl.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/game-crash/10232/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/game-crash/10232/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 16 Sep 2012 14:16:11 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-10232-2</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/game-crash/10232.rss">Game crash</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Game crash</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Piano_Man]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Okay… I know I’m going to sound like a complete moron… but I’ll do my best to explain it as best as I can.</p>
<p>I’m in the area where you meet the first major big fish monsters that pulls that scientist off the rails and into the water. Headed up to see the other scientist watching overheard who directs you to the tranquillizer gun.</p>
<p>Shot the fish with the tranquillizer gun, and attempted to then shoot it with pistol or SMG, the game crashes after firing a couple of shots into it.</p>
<p>Thinking maybe I wasn’t supposed to shoot him with my guns and leave him tranquillised, I left him there and went to talk to the other scientist - but he just harps on about nothing.</p>
<p>Not sure what to do here… I can’t get past this section without it crashing (assuming I am supposed to kill the fish after you’ve tranquillised it).</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/game-crash/10232/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/game-crash/10232/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 16 Sep 2012 12:03:30 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-10232-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/game-crash/10232.rss">Game crash</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
