<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Scripting help</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/scripting-help/14117</link>
    <description>Hey,

I&#39;ve been playing around with CM 13 trying to edit it personally so that it is more like Half Life 2 and for the most part have it lore friendly (as much as it can be) in terms of non-visuals. I&#39;ve come up with a problem of getting the proper music playing when it should be ( I hated the whole cinematic soundtrack, listening to batman music while driving the airboat), like arriving at Eli&#39;s lab or watching the cops beat up the two citizens at the start of Route Kanal.

Nobody on their forums responds anymore, so no luck there. I was hoping if any of you could help me out? There were a couple sequences I got restored to where it should be playing (Ravenholm Intro, entering Kleiner&#39;s lab themes) by editing their respective script files, but for some reason there are levels and sequences which I can&#39;t find files that manage them.

For instance, I editing level_sounds_ravenholm.txt in the script folder and got that fixed, but I can&#39;t find one for say the canals that affects music, not to mention editing level_sounds_music.txt is worthless

Any insight for this guys?</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 23 May 2015 22:33:48 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Source 1</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/scripting-help/14117.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Scripting help</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[RageMaker]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Hey,</p>
<p>I’ve been playing around with CM 13 trying to edit it personally so that it is more like Half Life 2 and for the most part have it lore friendly (as much as it can be) in terms of non-visuals. I’ve come up with a problem of getting the proper music playing when it should be ( I hated the whole cinematic soundtrack, listening to batman music while driving the airboat), like arriving at Eli’s lab or watching the cops beat up the two citizens at the start of Route Kanal.</p>
<p>Nobody on their forums responds anymore, so no luck there. I was hoping if any of you could help me out? There were a couple sequences I got restored to where it should be playing (Ravenholm Intro, entering Kleiner’s lab themes) by editing their respective script files, but for some reason there are levels and sequences which I can’t find files that manage them.</p>
<p>For instance, I editing level_sounds_ravenholm.txt in the script folder and got that fixed, but I can’t find one for say the canals that affects music, not to mention editing level_sounds_music.txt is worthless</p>
<p>Any insight for this guys?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/scripting-help/14117/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/scripting-help/14117/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 23 May 2015 22:33:48 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14117-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/scripting-help/14117.rss">Scripting help</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
