<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>TFC map: Decant in progress</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/tfc-map-decant-in-progress/4050</link>
    <description>I&#39;ve cautiously commenced construction concerning Casbah-coloured corridors covering capture-the-flag qualities.

[b][COLOR=&#39;DimGray&#39;]Nah, just kidding. I know better than to alliterate an entire post.[/b]


[b]Decant[/b] is named in line with the following definition:
[quote=&quot;Wiktionary&quot;]
1. To pour off gently, as liquor, so as not to disturb the sediment; or to pour from one vessel into another; as, to decant wine.
[/quote]
It is named similarly to my previous map, Deluge (which is a great flood). The context of this new map, however, will be a drought. [COLOR=&#39;DimGray&#39;](If you want a backstory, let&#39;s say there wasn&#39;t enough water for everybody to get through the drought, so they decided to play a game of capture-the-flag to determine who gets all the water... and then in the context of this game they started killing oneother to get an advantage.)

The setting is a desert basin. There will be [i]four[/i] bases, with the cliff-encircled main yard crossed by a mutual trench-like structure, which is bottomed off by translucent toe-deep water to represent the shortage.

The sandy areas in this main yard, which are everything but the teams&#39; bases and the trenches, will deal a tiny amount of heat damage (to deter crossing through them, and promote using the trench conduit). I should add, this is a classist measure, because the pyro will be capable of crossing the sand untouched. (Although there&#39;s not really anything to gain by doing so, beside arriving unexpected. It just wouldn&#39;t make sense to hurt him with heat, so he gets to be immune.)


Scoring is anticipated +4 for capturing, -2 for getting captured, and +1 for somebody else capping/getting-captured. The three non-winning teams could cooperate against the winning team to lower their advantage (-2). Furthermore, if you get Blue&#39;s flag out of their base but you are killed and another team steals it, your team will still be rewarded some for the effort of screwing Blue over (+1).

The scoring renders it impossible to win if you do not capture. If the three enemy teams perform equally against oneanother, however, it is possible to draw them without capturing (so long as your defence is flawless).
This is because every other team would have:* Captured 1 (+4)
* Lost 1 (-2)
* Absorbed 1 (+1)

and gain a net of 3. You, meanwhile, would gain +1 for each of those 3 captures that took place. Your team would tie.


I have a plan for the resupply to reduce spam. Players will spawn with few or no grenades, and pick up from a row the kinds of grenades they may use. So, a team with balanced classes will be able to use more grenades. A team with all Soldiers, however, will have to share the available nail-grenades, as the MIRV supply goes unused. Get it?



I have taken the following worldcraft screenie to show as few specifics as possible, while still getting the idea across. Right now, it is meant to be acrid. More may be posted as more progress is made. Only upon completion will I try to make it seem beautiful.

[img]https://img52.imageshack.us/img52/3452/decant.gif[/img]

Questions, opinions, suggestions, or critique? I am open for comments. [COLOR=&#39;Black&#39;]And I&#39;m quite kind if you start with anything rather than stale insults. Indeed, I appreciate fresh hostility, with approaches I haven&#39;t seen before. It&#39;s only the boring insults that drive me to reply equally insultingly. Even [i]then[/i] I&#39;m trying to give you some pointers.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 23 May 2010 07:29:21 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Show Off</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/tfc-map-decant-in-progress/4050.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>TFC map: Decant in progress</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Comrade_Tiki]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Every once in a while I like to run around the entire level seeing how it feels… :retard: my computer can handle the horrendous r_speeds.</p>
<p>More practically, when deciding how to flesh out new areas, I can spectate around what whole brushes I have, so I know where I can expand without needing to resize and duplicate a lot of things.</p>
<p>It won’t really be <span class="bbcode-i">route</span>, per se, but it will be a place between the bases that other classes don’t want to cut through. [COLOR=‘DimGray’](It’s out in the open, so I’m not sure pyros would want to hang around there either…)</p>
<p>The class-specificity is partially inspired by another map. I remember it was one I liked, which had an M3-halftrack brushwork somewhere in it, and a water route for each team whose heating unit at one end could be turned on and off (to optionally boil non-pyros trying to pass through it). It was called <span class="bbcode-b">Gustavo10_Corps68</span></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/tfc-map-decant-in-progress/4050/9">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/tfc-map-decant-in-progress/4050/9</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 23 May 2010 07:29:21 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-4050-9</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/tfc-map-decant-in-progress/4050.rss">TFC map: Decant in progress</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>TFC map: Decant in progress</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Spycrabz]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>^ This</p>
<p>Also, digging the idea of a specific route for Pyro, maybe some other class-specific routes?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/tfc-map-decant-in-progress/4050/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/tfc-map-decant-in-progress/4050/8</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 23 May 2010 07:21:23 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-4050-8</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/tfc-map-decant-in-progress/4050.rss">TFC map: Decant in progress</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>TFC map: Decant in progress</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[_Gotta]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>instead of using the box… why not just use the cordon tool?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/tfc-map-decant-in-progress/4050/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/tfc-map-decant-in-progress/4050/7</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 23 May 2010 06:24:36 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-4050-7</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/tfc-map-decant-in-progress/4050.rss">TFC map: Decant in progress</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>TFC map: Decant in progress</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Comrade_Tiki]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Just a brief update, showing some external progress:</p>
<p><span alt="" class="broken-image" title="This image is broken"><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-unlink svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#unlink"></use></svg></span></p>
<p>[COLOR=‘DimGray’]ignore the gigantic brick box surrounding the level</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/tfc-map-decant-in-progress/4050/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/tfc-map-decant-in-progress/4050/6</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 23 May 2010 05:28:53 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-4050-6</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/tfc-map-decant-in-progress/4050.rss">TFC map: Decant in progress</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>TFC map: Decant in progress</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Comrade_Tiki]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>27 April 2063</p>
<p>Potable water runs low. The clouds show no sign of rain. In the three years since the desalinator rusted out, it’s never been this bad. There’s not enough left to hydrate the community until autumn.</p>
<p>The elders have suggested a game, as a means to decide which block must leave and search for shelter elsewhere. Only, there’s nowhere else to go.</p>
<p>The spirit of competition runs high. So does the spirit of cooperation among each team. In four days we’ll compete, and try to keep our flag in our block while removing somebody else’s.</p>
<p>30 April 2063</p>
<p>Gunfire erupted. It looks like the game is happening early. As somebody thought killing everybody else would make it easier to capture their flags, we’ve equipped ourselves in turn.</p>
<p>If I die to help us win, at least I know my children will have somewhere to live. If I kill to help us win, well at least that’s one less mouth to wet.</p>
<p>Time to act.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Preliminary map info. I’ll precede those logs with the gameplay technicals once it’s all working.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/tfc-map-decant-in-progress/4050/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/tfc-map-decant-in-progress/4050/5</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 07 May 2010 07:30:20 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-4050-5</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/tfc-map-decant-in-progress/4050.rss">TFC map: Decant in progress</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>TFC map: Decant in progress</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Comrade_Tiki]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Worldcraft’s still available for download <span class="bbcode-i">somewhere</span>, but I have to say I slipped there, I keep forgetting they changed the name to Hammer - - there’s really nothing wrong with Hammer 3.5, which is what I’m actually using. (Nothing wrong except the boring name, of course  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=9" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"> )</p>
<p>To answer your question though, <span class="bbcode-b">Worldcraft</span> was the name up until they became Hammer 3.4, and so, 3.3 is available from places like <a href="https://www.filefront.com/797536/Worldcraft-3.3/" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">this</a>. I just installed it and everything’s intact. If you want to go <span class="bbcode-i">way</span> back, see if your Half-Life CD has the Worldcraft hidden in your directories. My version has 2.1 on it…</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/tfc-map-decant-in-progress/4050/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/tfc-map-decant-in-progress/4050/4</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 06 May 2010 23:15:01 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-4050-4</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/tfc-map-decant-in-progress/4050.rss">TFC map: Decant in progress</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>TFC map: Decant in progress</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Doop]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>How do you downgrade to worldcraft? All the supposed “downloads” I found are just the current hammer even though I search for 3.0/3.5 (that is the correct version, right?)</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/tfc-map-decant-in-progress/4050/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/tfc-map-decant-in-progress/4050/3</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 06 May 2010 20:44:12 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-4050-3</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/tfc-map-decant-in-progress/4050.rss">TFC map: Decant in progress</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>TFC map: Decant in progress</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[JohnKiller118]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Needs to be more cartoony.</p>
<p>And more fun.</p>
<p>I’ll stick with Team Fortress 2!</p>
<p><span alt="" class="broken-image" title="This image is broken"><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-unlink svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#unlink"></use></svg></span></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/tfc-map-decant-in-progress/4050/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/tfc-map-decant-in-progress/4050/2</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 06 May 2010 19:17:25 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-4050-2</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/tfc-map-decant-in-progress/4050.rss">TFC map: Decant in progress</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>TFC map: Decant in progress</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Comrade_Tiki]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I’ve cautiously commenced construction concerning Casbah-coloured corridors covering capture-the-flag qualities.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">[COLOR=‘DimGray’]Nah, just kidding. I know better than to alliterate an entire post.</span></p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Decant</span> is named in line with the following definition:</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Wiktionary">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Wiktionary:</div>
<blockquote>
<ol>
<li>To pour off gently, as liquor, so as not to disturb the sediment; or to pour from one vessel into another; as, to decant wine.</li>
</ol>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>It is named similarly to my previous map, Deluge (which is a great flood). The context of this new map, however, will be a drought. [COLOR=‘DimGray’](If you want a backstory, let’s say there wasn’t enough water for everybody to get through the drought, so they decided to play a game of capture-the-flag to determine who gets all the water… and then in the context of this game they started killing oneother to get an advantage.)</p>
<p>The setting is a desert basin. There will be <span class="bbcode-i">four</span> bases, with the cliff-encircled main yard crossed by a mutual trench-like structure, which is bottomed off by translucent toe-deep water to represent the shortage.</p>
<p>The sandy areas in this main yard, which are everything but the teams’ bases and the trenches, will deal a tiny amount of heat damage (to deter crossing through them, and promote using the trench conduit). I should add, this is a classist measure, because the pyro will be capable of crossing the sand untouched. (Although there’s not really anything to gain by doing so, beside arriving unexpected. It just wouldn’t make sense to hurt him with heat, so he gets to be immune.)</p>
<p>Scoring is anticipated +4 for capturing, -2 for getting captured, and +1 for somebody else capping/getting-captured. The three non-winning teams could cooperate against the winning team to lower their advantage (-2). Furthermore, if you get Blue’s flag out of their base but you are killed and another team steals it, your team will still be rewarded some for the effort of screwing Blue over (+1).</p>
<p>The scoring renders it impossible to win if you do not capture. If the three enemy teams perform equally against oneanother, however, it is possible to draw them without capturing (so long as your defence is flawless).<br>
This is because every other team would have:* Captured 1 (+4)</p>
<ul>
<li>Lost 1 (-2)</li>
<li>Absorbed 1 (+1)</li>
</ul>
<p>and gain a net of 3. You, meanwhile, would gain +1 for each of those 3 captures that took place. Your team would tie.</p>
<p>I have a plan for the resupply to reduce spam. Players will spawn with few or no grenades, and pick up from a row the kinds of grenades they may use. So, a team with balanced classes will be able to use more grenades. A team with all Soldiers, however, will have to share the available nail-grenades, as the MIRV supply goes unused. Get it?</p>
<p>I have taken the following worldcraft screenie to show as few specifics as possible, while still getting the idea across. Right now, it is meant to be acrid. More may be posted as more progress is made. Only upon completion will I try to make it seem beautiful.</p>
<p><span alt="" class="broken-image" title="This image is broken"><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-unlink svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#unlink"></use></svg></span></p>
<p>Questions, opinions, suggestions, or critique? I am open for comments. [COLOR=‘Black’]And I’m quite kind if you start with anything rather than stale insults. Indeed, I appreciate fresh hostility, with approaches I haven’t seen before. It’s only the boring insults that drive me to reply equally insultingly. Even <span class="bbcode-i">then</span> I’m trying to give you some pointers.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/tfc-map-decant-in-progress/4050/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/tfc-map-decant-in-progress/4050/1</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 06 May 2010 10:58:36 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-4050-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/tfc-map-decant-in-progress/4050.rss">TFC map: Decant in progress</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
