<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>suggestions for BM</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/suggestions-for-bm/14046</link>
    <description>Ok just a random group of suggestions for black mesa retail.


First of the DAM fight, really needs some improvements, right now it feels lack luster especially the copter fight and the bridge collapse.


I actually have A suggestion for this, re add the big ass gun to the dam

[img]https://vignette4.wikia.nocookie.net/half-life/images/b/b2/HECU_dam_turret_brush.jpg/revision/latest?cb=20100303115421&amp;path-prefix=en[/img]

This thing well not this thing exactly, replace it with A fortified TOW on the back of on M1075, set up so it looks like the soldiers where unloading the TOW in order to place it on the fortified building on the far side. This might take some work to get it well placed, but here is the idea.

when the player opens the gate on the dam and makes it about half way across one of two soldiers will get on the TOW and blast the bridge to the control tower, while the other fires off a flare calling in the copter. At this point the player can either take out the soldiers on the TOW, dive into the water, or head back to the ware house and gauss gun the copter.

For the TOW, this would introduce the player to the HECU&#39;s heavy weapons, it would also allow an AT weapon that a smart player can take advantage of to blast the copter. as the TOW is on the back of an m1075 which is being unloaded it has a large amount of cover in the forms of crates making it a good possession for fighting the copter. (as fighting it in the warehouse is well difficult at best.



The reasoning for these ideas is the following.

1. makes the destruction of the bridge more understandable, as it is the path doesn&#39;t look unstable before it collapses.
2. introduces the player to the TOW in a more controlled situation, allowing a smart player to head over to the now empty TOW and learn about it, while yes it is still under hostile attack, it provides a point of interest.
3. allows for a better explanation of the bridge collapse then it just fell down.
4. a flare calling in the copter would make more sense then it just happening on the situation... either that or having a soldier say something like &quot;call the chopper we got freeman on the dam&quot; but the player would likely shoot the soldier before this is finished.


minor suggestion
1. if something like this is done give the soldiers using the TOW a minimalist load out, aka no helmet, just a vest, and glocks. As the soldiers are implied to have been unloading the m1075.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 17 May 2015 03:38:47 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>The Cafeteria</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/suggestions-for-bm/14046.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>suggestions for BM</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[darkone]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>So no opinions on this good or bad?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/suggestions-for-bm/14046/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/suggestions-for-bm/14046/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 17 May 2015 03:38:47 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14046-2</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/suggestions-for-bm/14046.rss">suggestions for BM</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>suggestions for BM</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[darkone]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Ok just a random group of suggestions for black mesa retail.</p>
<p>First of the DAM fight, really needs some improvements, right now it feels lack luster especially the copter fight and the bridge collapse.</p>
<p>I actually have A suggestion for this, re add the big ass gun to the dam</p>
<p><img src="https://vignette4.wikia.nocookie.net/half-life/images/b/b2/HECU_dam_turret_brush.jpg/revision/latest?cb=20100303115421&amp;path-prefix=en" alt="" width="617" height="418"></p>
<p>This thing well not this thing exactly, replace it with A fortified TOW on the back of on M1075, set up so it looks like the soldiers where unloading the TOW in order to place it on the fortified building on the far side. This might take some work to get it well placed, but here is the idea.</p>
<p>when the player opens the gate on the dam and makes it about half way across one of two soldiers will get on the TOW and blast the bridge to the control tower, while the other fires off a flare calling in the copter. At this point the player can either take out the soldiers on the TOW, dive into the water, or head back to the ware house and gauss gun the copter.</p>
<p>For the TOW, this would introduce the player to the HECU’s heavy weapons, it would also allow an AT weapon that a smart player can take advantage of to blast the copter. as the TOW is on the back of an m1075 which is being unloaded it has a large amount of cover in the forms of crates making it a good possession for fighting the copter. (as fighting it in the warehouse is well difficult at best.</p>
<p>The reasoning for these ideas is the following.</p>
<ol>
<li>makes the destruction of the bridge more understandable, as it is the path doesn’t look unstable before it collapses.</li>
<li>introduces the player to the TOW in a more controlled situation, allowing a smart player to head over to the now empty TOW and learn about it, while yes it is still under hostile attack, it provides a point of interest.</li>
<li>allows for a better explanation of the bridge collapse then it just fell down.</li>
<li>a flare calling in the copter would make more sense then it just happening on the situation… either that or having a soldier say something like “call the chopper we got freeman on the dam” but the player would likely shoot the soldier before this is finished.</li>
</ol>
<p>minor suggestion</p>
<ol>
<li>if something like this is done give the soldiers using the TOW a minimalist load out, aka no helmet, just a vest, and glocks. As the soldiers are implied to have been unloading the m1075.</li>
</ol>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/suggestions-for-bm/14046/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/suggestions-for-bm/14046/1</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 May 2015 03:12:01 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14046-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/suggestions-for-bm/14046.rss">suggestions for BM</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
