<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Black Mesa Deathmatch</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/black-mesa-deathmatch/13995</link>
    <description>Hi,

Nightmare asked me to comment the early release of BM Deathmatch. Not sure what to tell.
Personally i&#39;m very curious how this DM will be. But i&#39;m not sure what to expect of this DM.
But i welcome BM :smiley: M. Surely i would play it .

Why is AG awesome? Coz it is great,the movement and ofc the gauss gun for killing and jumping. Thats why Bullit it  named &quot;Adrenaline Gamer&quot; i presume.
During all these years some great players have been playing HLDM/AG. But skills have evolved more since in 2001 AG was released and still today great skilled players play HLDM/AG.
And hope they will do this for much longer.
Coz of the love for HL/AG i upload time to time AG demos form recent times and from the good oldies to youtube. This also so people can see what AG is about back then and now.
So maybe people maybe are attracted this way to play HLDM/AG even for a game 16 yrs old.
Age doesn&#39;t mean anything for a game as this one,it was great in 1998 t&#39;ill today and beyond.
Half-Life is an virus,if it catches u,it is for life !

So BM :smiley: M will be like the original HL1DM?

By making it simular to HLDM probably not many HL2DM players will stay long to try out. This only because of the freedom of movement and tricks while playing HL2DM.
Below is what we have in HL2DM/CTF 1.7/AG².
Movement : the easiests way by now is bunnyhopping made easy with the aux key. In HL/AG scripts are more usefull coz of the speed cap
Weapons /skills   : Cooking nades,reflecting arrows on walls,floors or objects.
Fast orbs,swinging the RPG rocket towards or around...
Nade jump or use physics to jump while holding a radiator or by other ways. Wille we have the gravity gun like in HL2 or the gauss gun like in HL1?

Weapon damage is also different in HLDM . Will the weapon damages be like in HL2DM?

If all here from above still is be possbile with BM :smiley: M probably HL2DM players will be attracted to play it.

This all is for the developers to solve this or to sourt out how to make this a attactive version of Deathmatch.

So hope the developers team do a great job with creating this and have tested it by players who have played both HLDM and HL2DM coz the experience is different. And a good mix will be needed.
I wish you good luck  !

Sincerely yours,

Abu*</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 11 May 2015 20:44:41 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>The Cafeteria</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/black-mesa-deathmatch/13995.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Black Mesa Deathmatch</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[N1ghtM]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Thanks for taking the time to write and post this thread as it’s greatly appreciated. It’s important to remember that this game is a remake of HL1, not HL2. The mechanics and gameplay must remain the same as or be nearly identical to HL1, or consequently, it would become some hybrid that would be an extreme injustice to the original. It’s a remarkable achievement to implement the HLDM style into a newer engine with modern graphics, which is compromising as it is, being visually appealing to players of today’s day and age.</p>
<p>Here’s a post I made in response to the question, “Why can it not be “a different game in a different spirit than half-life”? AND a fast paced game, skilled one, allowing creative moves and frags?You know, without that noob bit.”, taken from this thread: <a href="https://forums.blackmesasource.com/index.php/Thread/28062-What-s-the-point-of-this-remake-BM-BMDM/?postID=608201#post608201" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">What’s the point of this remake (BM, BMDM)?</a></p>
<p>I would like to point out the vision of BM <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/smiley.png?v=9" title=":smiley:" class="emoji" alt=":smiley:"> M and why it’s not intended to be a different game in a different spirit other than Half-Life.</p>
<p>Black Mesa: Deathmatch<br>
The adrenaline pumping, bullet dodging, rockets-flying, big-red-button riddled deathmatch is back in classic Half-Life style, featuring graphically enhanced multiplayer maps and the full lineup of weapons. You’ll find yourself having more fun blowing away your friends than, well, anything.</p>
<p>Overview<br>
Black Mesa Deathmatch is speculated to be similar to HL <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/smiley.png?v=9" title=":smiley:" class="emoji" alt=":smiley:"> eathmatch. Players will compete with each other online, attempting to do 100 points of damage to their foes with various weapons while remaining above 0 health themselves. However, Deathmatch may not ship with the initial BM release, as development is being focused on completing the Single Player campaign.</p>
<p>Please note when the developers said it’s back in “classic Half-Life style”, the vision of this project is explicitly defined.</p>
<p><a href="https://wiki.blackmesasource.com/Category%20:smiley:%20eathmatch" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener"><span class="bbcode-u">wiki.blackmesasource.com/Category <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/smiley.png?v=9" title=":smiley:" class="emoji" alt=":smiley:"> eathmatch</span></a></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/black-mesa-deathmatch/13995/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/black-mesa-deathmatch/13995/2</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 11 May 2015 20:44:41 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13995-2</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/black-mesa-deathmatch/13995.rss">Black Mesa Deathmatch</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Black Mesa Deathmatch</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[thesacrisant]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Hi,</p>
<p>Nightmare asked me to comment the early release of BM Deathmatch. Not sure what to tell.<br>
Personally i’m very curious how this DM will be. But i’m not sure what to expect of this DM.<br>
But i welcome BM <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/smiley.png?v=9" title=":smiley:" class="emoji" alt=":smiley:"> M. Surely i would play it .</p>
<p>Why is AG awesome? Coz it is great,the movement and ofc the gauss gun for killing and jumping. Thats why Bullit it  named “Adrenaline Gamer” i presume.<br>
During all these years some great players have been playing HLDM/AG. But skills have evolved more since in 2001 AG was released and still today great skilled players play HLDM/AG.<br>
And hope they will do this for much longer.<br>
Coz of the love for HL/AG i upload time to time AG demos form recent times and from the good oldies to youtube. This also so people can see what AG is about back then and now.<br>
So maybe people maybe are attracted this way to play HLDM/AG even for a game 16 yrs old.<br>
Age doesn’t mean anything for a game as this one,it was great in 1998 t’ill today and beyond.<br>
Half-Life is an virus,if it catches u,it is for life !</p>
<p>So BM <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/smiley.png?v=9" title=":smiley:" class="emoji" alt=":smiley:"> M will be like the original HL1DM?</p>
<p>By making it simular to HLDM probably not many HL2DM players will stay long to try out. This only because of the freedom of movement and tricks while playing HL2DM.<br>
Below is what we have in HL2DM/CTF 1.7/AG².<br>
Movement : the easiests way by now is bunnyhopping made easy with the aux key. In HL/AG scripts are more usefull coz of the speed cap<br>
Weapons /skills   : Cooking nades,reflecting arrows on walls,floors or objects.<br>
Fast orbs,swinging the RPG rocket towards or around…<br>
Nade jump or use physics to jump while holding a radiator or by other ways. Wille we have the gravity gun like in HL2 or the gauss gun like in HL1?</p>
<p>Weapon damage is also different in HLDM . Will the weapon damages be like in HL2DM?</p>
<p>If all here from above still is be possbile with BM <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/smiley.png?v=9" title=":smiley:" class="emoji" alt=":smiley:"> M probably HL2DM players will be attracted to play it.</p>
<p>This all is for the developers to solve this or to sourt out how to make this a attactive version of Deathmatch.</p>
<p>So hope the developers team do a great job with creating this and have tested it by players who have played both HLDM and HL2DM coz the experience is different. And a good mix will be needed.<br>
I wish you good luck  !</p>
<p>Sincerely yours,</p>
<p>Abu*</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/black-mesa-deathmatch/13995/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/black-mesa-deathmatch/13995/1</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 11 May 2015 19:34:42 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13995-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/black-mesa-deathmatch/13995.rss">Black Mesa Deathmatch</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
