<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Head Set Issues</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/head-set-issues/6222</link>
    <description>I bought a Turtle Beach 5.1 surround sound head set a while back, and it worked fine. A couple days ago, it started having this high pitched noise that would occur if the bass settings were louder than a certain volume. Then, all of a sudden, that stopped and the sound quality is back to normal except for two things: the microphone doesn&#39;t work anymore, and the rear right speaker plays the subwoofer instead of the rear right sounds. Is there some way I can get in the settings and fix this stuff? I haven&#39;t been able to do anything with my Realtek HD audio manager.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Jan 2011 01:29:18 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Help and Support</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/head-set-issues/6222.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Head Set Issues</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[sersoft]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>If you don’t have warranty check for any dents/rips in the cable, you might get away with just replacing that.</p>
<p>Also it might be the sound card, test your headset on another PC to see if the microphone works at least.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/head-set-issues/6222/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/head-set-issues/6222/4</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 08 Jan 2011 01:29:18 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-6222-4</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/head-set-issues/6222.rss">Head Set Issues</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Head Set Issues</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Repzik]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Blech, dammit. Thanks for the reply sersoft. I’ll see if I can fiddle with it, I don’t think I got a warranty. Wasn’t too expensive though, so not too much of a loss.</p>
<p>EDIT: Appears I have a warranty, thank christ for that.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/head-set-issues/6222/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/head-set-issues/6222/3</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 08 Jan 2011 01:27:04 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-6222-3</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/head-set-issues/6222.rss">Head Set Issues</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Head Set Issues</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[sersoft]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Sounds like it shorted on the inside and some things got fried, I hope you have warranty.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/head-set-issues/6222/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/head-set-issues/6222/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 08 Jan 2011 01:18:29 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-6222-2</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/head-set-issues/6222.rss">Head Set Issues</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Head Set Issues</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Repzik]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I bought a Turtle Beach 5.1 surround sound head set a while back, and it worked fine. A couple days ago, it started having this high pitched noise that would occur if the bass settings were louder than a certain volume. Then, all of a sudden, that stopped and the sound quality is back to normal except for two things: the microphone doesn’t work anymore, and the rear right speaker plays the subwoofer instead of the rear right sounds. Is there some way I can get in the settings and fix this stuff? I haven’t been able to do anything with my Realtek HD audio manager.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/head-set-issues/6222/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/head-set-issues/6222/1</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Jan 2011 17:21:55 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-6222-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/head-set-issues/6222.rss">Head Set Issues</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
