<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Story-Picture Projects</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/story-picture-projects/4179</link>
    <description>To start this off, I&#39;ll point out two things. I love to write, and I like photography, real or virtual. So, my thing is this: Sometimes, to test myself, I&#39;ll go into to Gmod and put together scenes. Then, I&#39;ll take a screenshot and write a small story for the picture. Surely you get the idea so far (I hope). So I was wondering if, possibly, some people could find/take/retrieve screenshots from any sort of game (preferably Half-Life related for the sake of the forums) and I want to see if I can make any good stories. You can just email the pictures to me or PM me, then I can post them here, or you can post the pictures here and I can reply to the posts with the typed up story. I can&#39;t write too many stories at a time, much less do I have the spare time to get on every single day, so if this DOES work (which I doubt) don&#39;t expect constant, by the hour, updates. If you disagree with the idea, plainly state. If I could use improvement, plainly state. I&#39;m currently in production of a book, so I can use criticism. Thoughts/pictures?</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 18 May 2010 02:47:41 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Show Off</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/story-picture-projects/4179.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Story-Picture Projects</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Jonny_Nibbz]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Here’s the finished, (unpolished) product:<br>
There was loud banging outside the door.  Jeff, one of our roommates, was up against the door, trying to listen for what was going on. Suddenly, he bolted up and braced himself, holding his arm over the doorknob. There was a loud bang, followed by another, followed by another. Trying his best, he turned and screamed for the others to get away. I got up, and ran down the hallway, my girlfriend in tow. We rounded a few corners as we heard the police kick down a door. There was a tingling sensation in the air, followed quickly by the smell of electrocuted flesh. As we heard Jimmy fall screaming, I looked around quickly. Having no idea what to do, I turned over towards the TV. Breen was giving another speech, so I grabbed the small box. Giving a heave, I turned and threw it with all my might. An unlucky Civil Protection Officer rounded a corner, landing face first with the blacked out screen. Letting out a strongly electronic influenced scream, he collapsed. I took hold of my girlfriend’s hand and sprinted down the hallway.<br>
Rounding another corner, I saw another friend wiring something by a door in a cardboard box. We didn’t look back, but he ran ahead, screaming an illegible warning. As I looked for an exit, I listened with the thought of impending doom as the footsteps of several officers followed me. I was sweating, worrying about nothing but escape. Running around another corner, I stopped short, slid, and was hit in the gut by a railing of a balcony. Looking out, I glimpsed with envy as a pigeon fluttered off in the distance. My envy was suddenly crushed as a bullet rang out, landing on its mark. I sighed, and turned for a last hug from my companion. Then something alerted me. As several officers rounded a corner, there was a loud explosion as the contraption did its handiwork. The flames blew several officers into walls, breaking their skulls audibly. I turned away, as the force of the explosion sent me flying into the air, crashing headfirst into a bush.<br>
Arriving back into consciousness with a flash, I saw two other solemn figures leaned over me. “Are you okay?” one of the concerned faces was shaking me.<br>
“Obviously he is not okay! Get him to shelter, before the officers come snooping around again!” Dragging slowly away, I was being pulled into a small gutter. I began to regain movement, and sounds became less blurred. I got back up, and went towards where the two were taking me, suddenly falling into blackness. Getting back on my feet, I shook myself back awake, hoping no one saw me trip on a toy. I headed into the near building, suddenly aware of something missing. Looking around, I realized there were no women around. Rushing in towards the door, I caught a glimpse of long hair. Hoping it was her, I sprinted into the door, but my dreams were crushed as I saw she was accompanied by another, consoling her about her lost child.<br>
Again, there was the all too familiar radio chatter as the Civil Protection began a relentless search for the terrorist. I collapsed to the floor, and as the officers bashed through the door, I welcomed the tingling sensation of the metallic stun baton as it landed on the back of my skull, hopefully erasing my pitiful memories of oppression.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/story-picture-projects/4179/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/story-picture-projects/4179/3</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 18 May 2010 02:47:41 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-4179-3</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/story-picture-projects/4179.rss">Story-Picture Projects</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Story-Picture Projects</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Imonfire]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Well here’s a couple of screenshots I took years ago when I tried (without any real succes) to make artsy-like screenies.</p>
<p><div class="lightbox-wrapper"><a class="lightbox" href="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/original/2X/c/c3515c021a98d51f4b53cd710c68f09df36fc5f7.jpeg" data-download-href="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/c3515c021a98d51f4b53cd710c68f09df36fc5f7" title=""><img src="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/original/2X/c/c3515c021a98d51f4b53cd710c68f09df36fc5f7.jpeg" alt="" data-base62-sha1="rRRpWzxiKrtLhAN5kXnfZad0Noj" width="666" height="500" data-small-upload="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/optimized/2X/c/c3515c021a98d51f4b53cd710c68f09df36fc5f7_2_10x10.png"><div class="meta"><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-far-image svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#far-image"></use></svg><span class="filename"></span><span class="informations">1280×960 103 KB</span><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-discourse-expand svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#discourse-expand"></use></svg></div></a></div><br>
<div class="lightbox-wrapper"><a class="lightbox" href="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/original/2X/1/16ded0d8685858828b0cbfaab96639e9f991665e.jpeg" data-download-href="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/16ded0d8685858828b0cbfaab96639e9f991665e" title=""><img src="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/original/2X/1/16ded0d8685858828b0cbfaab96639e9f991665e.jpeg" alt="" data-base62-sha1="3gjSRXijLQgNgUEQ3HXEoLTUUb4" width="666" height="500" data-small-upload="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/optimized/2X/1/16ded0d8685858828b0cbfaab96639e9f991665e_2_10x10.png"><div class="meta"><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-far-image svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#far-image"></use></svg><span class="filename"></span><span class="informations">1280×960 139 KB</span><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-discourse-expand svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#discourse-expand"></use></svg></div></a></div><br>
<div class="lightbox-wrapper"><a class="lightbox" href="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/original/2X/a/ad3fbf46e7a52608a9ded70f05b7e30e3f07a9cc.jpeg" data-download-href="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/ad3fbf46e7a52608a9ded70f05b7e30e3f07a9cc" title=""><img src="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/original/2X/a/ad3fbf46e7a52608a9ded70f05b7e30e3f07a9cc.jpeg" alt="" data-base62-sha1="oIDbaevky9zyZt2mKkUNUPmmaV6" width="666" height="500" data-small-upload="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/optimized/2X/a/ad3fbf46e7a52608a9ded70f05b7e30e3f07a9cc_2_10x10.png"><div class="meta"><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-far-image svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#far-image"></use></svg><span class="filename"></span><span class="informations">1280×960 133 KB</span><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-discourse-expand svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#discourse-expand"></use></svg></div></a></div><br>
<div class="lightbox-wrapper"><a class="lightbox" href="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/original/2X/4/4e92d829620e67d2528145f258e8ec3aea292e1a.jpeg" data-download-href="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/4e92d829620e67d2528145f258e8ec3aea292e1a" title=""><img src="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/original/2X/4/4e92d829620e67d2528145f258e8ec3aea292e1a.jpeg" alt="" data-base62-sha1="bd5R1ToUl2STXOAkebiYz0TWTVg" width="666" height="500" data-small-upload="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/optimized/2X/4/4e92d829620e67d2528145f258e8ec3aea292e1a_2_10x10.png"><div class="meta"><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-far-image svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#far-image"></use></svg><span class="filename"></span><span class="informations">1280×960 96.3 KB</span><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-discourse-expand svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#discourse-expand"></use></svg></div></a></div></p>
<p>They’re pretty basic, so let’s see how you deal with them.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/story-picture-projects/4179/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/story-picture-projects/4179/2</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 18 May 2010 02:08:22 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-4179-2</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/story-picture-projects/4179.rss">Story-Picture Projects</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Story-Picture Projects</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Jonny_Nibbz]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>To start this off, I’ll point out two things. I love to write, and I like photography, real or virtual. So, my thing is this: Sometimes, to test myself, I’ll go into to Gmod and put together scenes. Then, I’ll take a screenshot and write a small story for the picture. Surely you get the idea so far (I hope). So I was wondering if, possibly, some people could find/take/retrieve screenshots from any sort of game (preferably Half-Life related for the sake of the forums) and I want to see if I can make any good stories. You can just email the pictures to me or PM me, then I can post them here, or you can post the pictures here and I can reply to the posts with the typed up story. I can’t write too many stories at a time, much less do I have the spare time to get on every single day, so if this DOES work (which I doubt) don’t expect constant, by the hour, updates. If you disagree with the idea, plainly state. If I could use improvement, plainly state. I’m currently in production of a book, so I can use criticism. Thoughts/pictures?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/story-picture-projects/4179/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/story-picture-projects/4179/1</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 17 May 2010 22:47:10 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-4179-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/story-picture-projects/4179.rss">Story-Picture Projects</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
