<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Anyone knows what&#39;s wrong?</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/anyone-knows-whats-wrong/2823</link>
    <description>Okay.

I&#39;ve been trying to decompile a custom smg model for Half-life 2. The problem? I can&#39;t get the damn decompiler to work. Everytime I try to load a .mdl and extracting it, the decompiler crashes, throwing one of those &quot;This program has stopped working&quot; errors.

I&#39;ve been trying pretty much everything, changing the gameinfo file in ep1 folder like some suggested, using cannonfodders fixed version of his decompiler, using studio compiler (the one that has a decompiler, compiler, vtf converter), or running the decompiler with source model viewer and SDK open. All of these options failed, I haven&#39;t got the damn thing to not crash.

Can anyone help?</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 29 Jan 2010 16:24:55 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Help and Support</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/anyone-knows-whats-wrong/2823.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Anyone knows what&#39;s wrong?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[ManlyStump]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>No idea  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/wink.png?v=9" title=":wink:" class="emoji" alt=":wink:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/anyone-knows-whats-wrong/2823/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/anyone-knows-whats-wrong/2823/2</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jan 2010 16:24:55 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2823-2</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/anyone-knows-whats-wrong/2823.rss">Anyone knows what&#39;s wrong?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Anyone knows what&#39;s wrong?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Llewen_Ebag]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Okay.</p>
<p>I’ve been trying to decompile a custom smg model for Half-life 2. The problem? I can’t get the damn decompiler to work. Everytime I try to load a .mdl and extracting it, the decompiler crashes, throwing one of those “This program has stopped working” errors.</p>
<p>I’ve been trying pretty much everything, changing the gameinfo file in ep1 folder like some suggested, using cannonfodders fixed version of his decompiler, using studio compiler (the one that has a decompiler, compiler, vtf converter), or running the decompiler with source model viewer and SDK open. All of these options failed, I haven’t got the damn thing to not crash.</p>
<p>Can anyone help?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/anyone-knows-whats-wrong/2823/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/anyone-knows-whats-wrong/2823/1</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jan 2010 15:35:59 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2823-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/anyone-knows-whats-wrong/2823.rss">Anyone knows what&#39;s wrong?</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
