<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>How to change certain enemy properties?</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/how-to-change-certain-enemy-properties/10660</link>
    <description>I&#39;ve been working on a all-round balance tweak for myself (I&#39;ll probably upload an &quot;alpha&quot; once the basic tweaks are tuned to a level I find comfortable) but there are a few big edits I want to do that I can&#39;t seem to work out, as they are apparently hard-coded in some way:

1. How do I make the Vortiguants take longer to charge up? None of the settings in skill.cfg seem to change this, unless there&#39;s something I&#39;m missing?

2. Is there a simple way to remove the HL2 &quot;feature&quot; that makes the Crowbar automatically kill Headcrabs in one hit? I&#39;ve tried giving Headcrabs absurd health values as an experiment and they still get one-shot by the Crowbar, it would be nice to get rid of this to see how well making the crowbar like the HL1 version works.

3. How can I increase the damage Barnacles do? My idea is to make Barnacles more like the HL1 versions where they are weaker but do FAR more damage if they catch you, but there seems to be no way to control Barnacle damage in skill.cfg.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 18 Sep 2012 23:05:06 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Help!</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/how-to-change-certain-enemy-properties/10660.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>How to change certain enemy properties?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Mman]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Is there no way to modify the code of a mod? Looking around that appears to be the only way to change some of this stuff, but based on the instructions I’ve seen you can only do that with the base HL2 code unless there’s something I’m missing. I probably wouldn’t be able to pull off these kind of changes myself even if I could open the code, but it would be nice to know a way that I could try.</p>
<p>Unless there’s an alternative anyway.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/how-to-change-certain-enemy-properties/10660/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/how-to-change-certain-enemy-properties/10660/3</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 18 Sep 2012 23:05:06 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-10660-3</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/how-to-change-certain-enemy-properties/10660.rss">How to change certain enemy properties?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How to change certain enemy properties?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[David_VI]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Subscribing to this thread because I’m interested in your tweaks and have been doing a few myself.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/how-to-change-certain-enemy-properties/10660/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/how-to-change-certain-enemy-properties/10660/2</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 18 Sep 2012 01:19:10 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-10660-2</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/how-to-change-certain-enemy-properties/10660.rss">How to change certain enemy properties?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How to change certain enemy properties?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Mman]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I’ve been working on a all-round balance tweak for myself (I’ll probably upload an “alpha” once the basic tweaks are tuned to a level I find comfortable) but there are a few big edits I want to do that I can’t seem to work out, as they are apparently hard-coded in some way:</p>
<ol>
<li>
<p>How do I make the Vortiguants take longer to charge up? None of the settings in skill.cfg seem to change this, unless there’s something I’m missing?</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Is there a simple way to remove the HL2 “feature” that makes the Crowbar automatically kill Headcrabs in one hit? I’ve tried giving Headcrabs absurd health values as an experiment and they still get one-shot by the Crowbar, it would be nice to get rid of this to see how well making the crowbar like the HL1 version works.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>How can I increase the damage Barnacles do? My idea is to make Barnacles more like the HL1 versions where they are weaker but do FAR more damage if they catch you, but there seems to be no way to control Barnacle damage in skill.cfg.</p>
</li>
</ol>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/how-to-change-certain-enemy-properties/10660/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/how-to-change-certain-enemy-properties/10660/1</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 18 Sep 2012 00:14:50 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-10660-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/how-to-change-certain-enemy-properties/10660.rss">How to change certain enemy properties?</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
