<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Jurassic Park is real 0_0</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/jurassic-park-is-real-0-0/6354</link>
    <description>[url]https://io9.com/5738260/extinct-animals-we-could-+-and-should-+-clone-tomorrow[/url]

They may bring extinct animals back...I&#39;d like a pet velociraptor to be honest</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 25 Jan 2011 09:21:55 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Off Topic</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/jurassic-park-is-real-0-0/6354.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Jurassic Park is real 0_0</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Piefish]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><span alt="" class="broken-image" title="This image is broken"><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-unlink svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#unlink"></use></svg></span></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/jurassic-park-is-real-0-0/6354/62">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/jurassic-park-is-real-0-0/6354/62</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 25 Jan 2011 09:21:55 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-6354-62</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/jurassic-park-is-real-0-0/6354.rss">Jurassic Park is real 0_0</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Jurassic Park is real 0_0</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Chickenprotector]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="gugamilare">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/g/f04885/40.png" class="avatar"> gugamilare:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Yes, yes I know, you don’t need to explain this to me again. And, yes, I read the entire post.</p>
<p>However, as I said, this does not mean we should lead species to extinction. That is actually against evolution. And <span class="bbcode-b"><span class="bbcode-i">nature is not sacred</span></span>. If you think nature is sacred, you should stop using computers, televisions, condoms and go to live in the forest so you would be subject to natural selection.</p>
<p>What nature does and what we should or can do or not do are two separate things. Why? Because nature is not sacred. We need to do what is best for us, humans, and that means:</p>
<ul>
<li>allowing nature to continue instead of vanquishing it from the face of the world;</li>
<li>clone extinct species so we could study them and (why not) entertain ourselves in zoos of extinct species.</li>
</ul>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I’m not stating that Nature fears anything. I’m simply stating that there’s more to it than that, in the short-term mentally this generation is different from the last. Genes take longer to spread.</p>
<p>Actually Nature is so resilient I wouldn’t be surprised that it will crop back up even if we do stomp it out… which I doubt, the treehuggers will make sure of that.</p>
<p>Over all, you seem to mis-underestimate the hardiness of some creatures. Mice, rats, etc are so successful because of the amount of young per litter. All critters will eventually adapt to their new surroundings, it’s a matter of time. Rattle Snakes are doing that now actually, some of them have stopped using their rattle and just strike now. Ftw; I’m all for saving the environment and renewable resources, I’m simply stating a point.</p>
<p>Cloned animals, some of them you <span class="bbcode-b">won’t</span> want in the environment… in fact some of them you don’t want to at all outside of a controlled container. They’ll throw off the ecosystem in the area they’re in. Invasive species are a case of that. Look up the <a href="https://fishing.about.com/cs/fishfactsinfo/a/aa092703a.htm" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Snakehead fish in America</a>.</p>
<p>Introducing new and extinct species that haven’t been around for hundreds or even thousands of years will throw it out of whack, and could re-introduce a new disease that was in the DNA sequence (however unlikely) for instance that will have a devastating effect on the environment they’re in.</p>
<p>I’m all for disease research, but look at the bigger picture.</p>
<p>Edit: I just realized that I just said what I said the last time…</p>
<p>In short; Those animals haven’t been around for hundreds or even thousands of years, introducing new animals will throw that balance out of whack and destroy the native ecosystem, but creating a totally new one. That’s going on in several places around the world even as we speak.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>I already had read this because I’m a cool guy and doesn’t afraid of wall of texts :3. Although that is not exactly right, as I said above, this has nothing to do with the point in question.</p>
<p>The actual sequence of events is this:</p>
<ul>
<li>T-rexes eat a lot of elephants and procriate, leading T-rexes to increase their population and elephants to decrease theirs;</li>
<li>as there are few elephants, T-rexes begin to starve to death, therefore leading the population of T-rexes to decrease and the population of elephants to increase.</li>
</ul>
<p>With time and genetic mutation, the elephants that are (slightly) faster have a higher <span class="bbcode-u">chance</span> of surviving and procreating, therefore leading the population of elephants to have faster and faster elephants.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Agreed. There was actually a pygmy mammoth and elephant, but they went extinct a couple hundred years ago.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/jurassic-park-is-real-0-0/6354/61">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/jurassic-park-is-real-0-0/6354/61</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jan 2011 13:41:42 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-6354-61</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/jurassic-park-is-real-0-0/6354.rss">Jurassic Park is real 0_0</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Jurassic Park is real 0_0</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Piefish]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="YARO">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/y/bb73d2/40.png" class="avatar"> YARO:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Yeah, then put him into a trial and sentence him to death…</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Or give him ironic punishments, everytime we bring him back</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/jurassic-park-is-real-0-0/6354/60">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/jurassic-park-is-real-0-0/6354/60</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jan 2011 13:30:23 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-6354-60</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/jurassic-park-is-real-0-0/6354.rss">Jurassic Park is real 0_0</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Jurassic Park is real 0_0</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[YARO]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Yeah, then put him into a trial and sentence him to death…</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/jurassic-park-is-real-0-0/6354/59">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/jurassic-park-is-real-0-0/6354/59</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jan 2011 13:17:56 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-6354-59</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/jurassic-park-is-real-0-0/6354.rss">Jurassic Park is real 0_0</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Jurassic Park is real 0_0</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Piefish]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>If we can bring back Mammoths…then we can bring back hitler</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/jurassic-park-is-real-0-0/6354/58">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/jurassic-park-is-real-0-0/6354/58</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jan 2011 09:03:52 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-6354-58</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/jurassic-park-is-real-0-0/6354.rss">Jurassic Park is real 0_0</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Jurassic Park is real 0_0</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Jeannotvb]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Fixed just for you!</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/jurassic-park-is-real-0-0/6354/57">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/jurassic-park-is-real-0-0/6354/57</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jan 2011 02:50:35 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-6354-57</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/jurassic-park-is-real-0-0/6354.rss">Jurassic Park is real 0_0</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Jurassic Park is real 0_0</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Comrade_Tiki]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>All I saw in Jeannotvb’s self-quoted post was “<span class="bbcode-i">abdunant</span>”.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/jurassic-park-is-real-0-0/6354/56">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/jurassic-park-is-real-0-0/6354/56</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jan 2011 00:40:21 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-6354-56</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/jurassic-park-is-real-0-0/6354.rss">Jurassic Park is real 0_0</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Jurassic Park is real 0_0</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[gugamilare]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Chickenprotector">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/user_avatar/leakfree.org/chickenprotector/40/5653_2.png" class="avatar"> Chickenprotector:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Natural selection is inevitable with or with out human intervention. Specific traits from the last generation will carry over to the next generation. The cycle continues till you have a drastically different population of animals (or people) than today.</p>
<p>It’s been proven time and again through out history.[…]</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Yes, yes I know, you don’t need to explain this to me again. And, yes, I read the entire post.</p>
<p>However, as I said, this does not mean we should lead species to extinction. That is actually against evolution. And <span class="bbcode-b"><span class="bbcode-i">nature is not sacred</span></span>. If you think nature is sacred, you should stop using computers, televisions, condoms and go to live in the forest so you would be subject to natural selection.</p>
<p>What nature does and what we should or can do or not do are two separate things. Why? Because nature is not sacred. We need to do what is best for us, humans, and that means:</p>
<ul>
<li>allowing nature to continue instead of vanquishing it from the face of the world;</li>
<li>clone extinct species so we could study them and (why not) entertain ourselves in zoos of extinct species.</li>
</ul>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Jeannotvb">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/j/90ced4/40.png" class="avatar"> Jeannotvb:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I know it’s a wall of text, but please read:</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I already had read this because I’m a cool guy and doesn’t afraid of wall of texts :3. Although that is not exactly right, as I said above, this has nothing to do with the point in question.</p>
<p>The actual sequence of events is this:</p>
<ul>
<li>T-rexes eat a lot of elephants and procriate, leading T-rexes to increase their population and elephants to decrease theirs;</li>
<li>as there are few elephants, T-rexes begin to starve to death, therefore leading the population of T-rexes to decrease and the population of elephants to increase.</li>
</ul>
<p>With time and genetic mutation, the elephants that are (slightly) faster have a higher <span class="bbcode-u">chance</span> of surviving and procreating, therefore leading the population of elephants to have faster and faster elephants.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/jurassic-park-is-real-0-0/6354/55">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/jurassic-park-is-real-0-0/6354/55</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 23 Jan 2011 23:58:40 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-6354-55</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/jurassic-park-is-real-0-0/6354.rss">Jurassic Park is real 0_0</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Jurassic Park is real 0_0</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Jeannotvb]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="gugamilare">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/g/f04885/40.png" class="avatar"> gugamilare:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Oh, all right, let’s just let thousands of species go extinct and do nothing about it, then.</p>
<p>I guess I failed to see your point.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I know it’s a wall of text, but please read:</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Jeannotvb">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/j/90ced4/40.png" class="avatar"> Jeannotvb:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>What is the problem? Animals with the highest rate of success in reproduction are favoured by evolution and become more abundant. Our species gained the upper hand thanks to our large brains, hands etc.</p>
<p>Imagine you have two islands, one island has a large population of Elephants, the other has a small population of Tyrannosaurus rex (yeah I know it’s rather unrealistic, just use your imagination here). Over the course of a few thousand years the sea level in between the island drops, thus connecting the two islands. Now the T.rex population can migrate to the second island where they will find large and easy prey (the Elephants). Because of the arrival of the T.rex’s the elephants are less likely to survive long and therefor they will not have much reproductive success. The T.rex on the other hand has a good source of food ensuring its survival and thus they are very likely to reproduce. This increases their population until at one point the Elephants either adapt or go extinct (in this case the Elephants would most likely go extinct because of their large size). It’s possible that the very smallest but fastest Elephants can escape the giant T.rex’s. This means the only Elephants that get to reproduce are the small but fast ones. Over time that would mean the Elephants would become much smaller as evolution favours them due to those specific traits that give them the highest rate of success in reproduction.</p>
<p>This is just a small example, it happens ALL the time, EVERYWHERE, with every organism. Whether it’s human intervention, natural disasters, or simply nature going about its business (movement of the continents and so on) it doesn’t matter. Dinosaurs went extinct because a giant asteroid crashed into the Earth. This drastically changed the Earth’s environment in a very short time span. It was impossible for the large non-avian dinosaurs, marine reptiles and pterosaurs to adapt and because they require such large amounts of food they quickly died and eventually went extinct. Smaller animals like mammals at that time (they were no larger than rats on average) managed to survive because they require little food. Their reproductive success increased a lot now that the dinosaurs were gone. This eventually led to all life we see today including humans.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Or read this:</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Chickenprotector">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/user_avatar/leakfree.org/chickenprotector/40/5653_2.png" class="avatar"> Chickenprotector:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Natural selection is inevitable with or with out human intervention. Specific traits from the last generation will carry over to the next generation. The cycle continues till you have a drastically different population of animals (or people) than today.</p>
<p>It’s been proven time and again through out history.</p>
<p>A good example is compare the 1950s America to now; not gene-wise, but mentally, it’s much quicker to give an example in terms of years like that. 1950s; Racism was abundant, tech isn’t what it is today, and the civil rights movement was going on.</p>
<p>Now; Less Racial violence, tech is advancing at an accelerated rate, there are civil rights in place. It’s a simple comparison, but that’s 2 drastically different generations.</p>
<p>It’s the same in terms of animals. Overtime critters with specific traits I.E. a mini-elephant as Jeannotvb explained will survive long enough to pass their genes on to the next generation.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<hr>
<p>99% of all life in Earth’s history is extinct. You can’t do anything about it. This is nature.</p>
<p>edit:</p>
<p>Turns out my Elephant example wasn’t so crazy after all, there is a species of Mammoth that gradually became smaller, scientists believe it has to do with the fact that food was available only higher up the mountains. This made it impossible for the large and heavy Mammoths to reach there and thus they died. The smaller, lighter ones on the other hand could easily reach up and get the food. They survived and reproduced, passing on their genes to the next generation which gradually decreased the average size of the Mammoths in that area.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/jurassic-park-is-real-0-0/6354/54">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/jurassic-park-is-real-0-0/6354/54</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 23 Jan 2011 23:02:46 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-6354-54</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/jurassic-park-is-real-0-0/6354.rss">Jurassic Park is real 0_0</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Jurassic Park is real 0_0</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Chickenprotector]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="gugamilare">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/g/f04885/40.png" class="avatar"> gugamilare:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>You are wrong. You are forgetting about the most powerful weapon of cavemen: fire. And, of course, intelligence. Animals have instinct fear of fire, they run away from it. Cavemen could use that fear to push mammoths to the edge of abysses and make them fall. They pushed entire herds of mammoths, most of the meat would rot before the human tribe could eat it. IIRC, one mammoth would be sufficient to feed the entire tribe.</p>
<p>That is how humans invented greed. And mammoths paid the price.</p>
<p>Oh, all right, let’s just let thousands of species go extinct and do nothing about it, then.</p>
<p>I guess I failed to see your point.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Natural selection is inevitable with or with out human intervention. Specific traits from the last generation will carry over to the next generation. The cycle continues till you have a drastically different population of animals (or people) than today.</p>
<p>It’s been proven time and again through out history.</p>
<p>A good example is compare the 1950s America to now; not gene-wise, but mentally, it’s much quicker to give an example in terms of years like that. 1950s; Racism was abundant, tech isn’t what it is today, and the civil rights movement was going on.</p>
<p>Now; Less Racial violence, tech is advancing at an accelerated rate, there are civil rights in place. It’s a simple comparison, but that’s 2 drastically different generations.</p>
<p>It’s the same in terms of animals. Overtime critters with specific traits I.E. a mini-elephant as Jeannotvb explained will survive long enough to pass their genes on to the next generation.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/jurassic-park-is-real-0-0/6354/53">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/jurassic-park-is-real-0-0/6354/53</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 23 Jan 2011 22:54:37 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-6354-53</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/jurassic-park-is-real-0-0/6354.rss">Jurassic Park is real 0_0</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Jurassic Park is real 0_0</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[bur]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Mammoth#Extinction" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Mammoth#Extinction</a></p>
<p>“Whether the general mammoth population died out for climatic reasons or due to overhunting by humans is controversial.[26] Another theory suggests that mammoths may have fallen victim to an infectious disease. A combination of climate change and hunting by humans has been suggested[by whom?] as the most likely explanation for their extinction.”</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/jurassic-park-is-real-0-0/6354/52">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/jurassic-park-is-real-0-0/6354/52</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 23 Jan 2011 22:54:19 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-6354-52</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/jurassic-park-is-real-0-0/6354.rss">Jurassic Park is real 0_0</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Jurassic Park is real 0_0</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[gugamilare]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Someonerandm">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/s/d78d45/40.png" class="avatar"> Someonerandm:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I don’t believe humans are entirely to blame for mammoth extinction. Their weapons weren’t powerful enough to really damage them, for starters. I think it was ultimately a general warming trend that killed them off.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>You are wrong. You are forgetting about the most powerful weapon of cavemen: fire. And, of course, intelligence. Animals have instinct fear of fire, they run away from it. Cavemen could use that fear to push mammoths to the edge of abysses and make them fall. They pushed entire herds of mammoths, most of the meat would rot before the human tribe could eat it. IIRC, one mammoth would be sufficient to feed the entire tribe.</p>
<p>That is how humans invented greed. And mammoths paid the price.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Jeannotvb">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/j/90ced4/40.png" class="avatar"> Jeannotvb:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>So what if humans were the primary cause of their extinction? I’m not happy many species are facing extinction within 100 years because of human presence but in the end it’s just how nature works.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Oh, all right, let’s just let thousands of species go extinct and do nothing about it, then.</p>
<p>I guess I failed to see your point.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/jurassic-park-is-real-0-0/6354/51">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/jurassic-park-is-real-0-0/6354/51</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 23 Jan 2011 22:35:03 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-6354-51</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/jurassic-park-is-real-0-0/6354.rss">Jurassic Park is real 0_0</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Jurassic Park is real 0_0</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Comrade_Tiki]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Humans are part of nature.</p>
<p>…</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-i">Death</span> is a disease.</p>
<p>…</p>
<p><span alt="" class="broken-image" title="This image is broken"><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-unlink svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#unlink"></use></svg></span></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/jurassic-park-is-real-0-0/6354/50">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/jurassic-park-is-real-0-0/6354/50</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 23 Jan 2011 19:40:23 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-6354-50</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/jurassic-park-is-real-0-0/6354.rss">Jurassic Park is real 0_0</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Jurassic Park is real 0_0</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Omega_Absolute]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <pre><code class="lang-auto"></code></pre>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="danielsangeo">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/user_avatar/leakfree.org/danielsangeo/40/4347_2.png" class="avatar"> danielsangeo:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>No no.  Humans are a disease.</p>
<p><span alt="" class="broken-image" title="This image is broken"><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-unlink svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#unlink"></use></svg></span></p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Smith said virus AND disease in the movie.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/jurassic-park-is-real-0-0/6354/49">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/jurassic-park-is-real-0-0/6354/49</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 23 Jan 2011 08:23:46 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-6354-49</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/jurassic-park-is-real-0-0/6354.rss">Jurassic Park is real 0_0</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Jurassic Park is real 0_0</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[danielsangeo]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Shadi">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/s/858c86/40.png" class="avatar"> Shadi:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Humans are Viruses</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>No no.  Humans are a disease.</p>
<p><span alt="" class="broken-image" title="This image is broken"><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-unlink svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#unlink"></use></svg></span></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/jurassic-park-is-real-0-0/6354/48">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/jurassic-park-is-real-0-0/6354/48</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 23 Jan 2011 07:37:49 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-6354-48</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/jurassic-park-is-real-0-0/6354.rss">Jurassic Park is real 0_0</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Jurassic Park is real 0_0</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Jeannotvb]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Shadi">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/s/858c86/40.png" class="avatar"> Shadi:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Humans are Viruses</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>What is the problem? Animals with the highest rate of success in reproduction are favoured by evolution and become more abundant. Our species gained the upper hand thanks to our large brains, hands etc.</p>
<p>Imagine you have two islands, one island has a large population of Elephants, the other has a small population of Tyrannosaurus rex (yeah I know it’s rather unrealistic, just use your imagination here). Over the course of a few thousand years the sea level in between the island drops, thus connecting the two islands. Now the T.rex population can migrate to the second island where they will find large and easy prey (the Elephants). Because of the arrival of the T.rex’s the elephants are less likely to survive long and therefor they will not have much reproductive success. The T.rex on the other hand has a good source of food ensuring its survival and thus they are very likely to reproduce. This increases their population until at one point the Elephants either adapt or go extinct (in this case the Elephants would most likely go extinct because of their large size). It’s possible that the very smallest but fastest Elephants can escape the giant T.rex’s. This means the only Elephants that get to reproduce are the small but fast ones. Over time that would mean the Elephants would become much smaller as evolution favours them due to those specific traits that give them the highest rate of success in reproduction.</p>
<p>This is just a small example, it happens ALL the time, EVERYWHERE, with every organism. Whether it’s human intervention, natural disasters, or simply nature going about its business (movement of the continents and so on) it doesn’t matter. Dinosaurs went extinct because a giant asteroid crashed into the Earth. This drastically changed the Earth’s environment in a very short time span. It was impossible for the large non-avian dinosaurs, marine reptiles and pterosaurs to adapt and because they require such large amounts of food they quickly died and eventually went extinct. Smaller animals like mammals at that time (they were no larger than rats on average) managed to survive because they require little food. Their reproductive success increased a lot now that the dinosaurs were gone. This eventually led to all life we see today including humans.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/jurassic-park-is-real-0-0/6354/47">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/jurassic-park-is-real-0-0/6354/47</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 23 Jan 2011 07:17:02 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-6354-47</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/jurassic-park-is-real-0-0/6354.rss">Jurassic Park is real 0_0</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Jurassic Park is real 0_0</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Shadi]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Humans are Viruses</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/jurassic-park-is-real-0-0/6354/46">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/jurassic-park-is-real-0-0/6354/46</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 23 Jan 2011 06:10:20 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-6354-46</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/jurassic-park-is-real-0-0/6354.rss">Jurassic Park is real 0_0</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Jurassic Park is real 0_0</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Someonerandm]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>That too.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/jurassic-park-is-real-0-0/6354/45">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/jurassic-park-is-real-0-0/6354/45</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 23 Jan 2011 05:24:52 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-6354-45</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/jurassic-park-is-real-0-0/6354.rss">Jurassic Park is real 0_0</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Jurassic Park is real 0_0</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Jeannotvb]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>So what if humans were the primary cause of their extinction? I’m not happy many species are facing extinction within 100 years because of human presence but in the end it’s just how nature works.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/jurassic-park-is-real-0-0/6354/44">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/jurassic-park-is-real-0-0/6354/44</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 23 Jan 2011 04:43:16 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-6354-44</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/jurassic-park-is-real-0-0/6354.rss">Jurassic Park is real 0_0</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Jurassic Park is real 0_0</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Someonerandm]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I don’t believe humans are entirely to blame for mammoth extinction. Their weapons weren’t powerful enough to really damage them, for starters. I think it was ultimately a general warming trend that killed them off.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/jurassic-park-is-real-0-0/6354/43">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/jurassic-park-is-real-0-0/6354/43</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 23 Jan 2011 04:36:17 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-6354-43</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/jurassic-park-is-real-0-0/6354.rss">Jurassic Park is real 0_0</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Jurassic Park is real 0_0</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[gugamilare]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Jeannotvb">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/j/90ced4/40.png" class="avatar"> Jeannotvb:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Birds most likely evolved from smaller raptors. Giving back certain dinosaurian features like long tails, teeth and claws is not the same as creating the actual species that lived millions of years ago.</p>
<p>There’s no point in bringing back extinct animals, that’s not how evolution is supposed to work. 99% of all life in Earths history is extinct, that’s just the way it is. Eventually all current species will be extinct while new ones thrive.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Dinosaurs are extinct because a fucking meteor fell on Earth, Mammoths are extinct because humans killed them mercilessly. Sometimes natural selection doesn’t work for the best, it is not sacred. But, actually, that is not the point. The point in bringing back extinct species is to study them, not because they are better than current species.</p>
<p>Arg, :ninja:, damn you burb  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=9" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/jurassic-park-is-real-0-0/6354/42">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/jurassic-park-is-real-0-0/6354/42</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 23 Jan 2011 01:43:26 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-6354-42</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/jurassic-park-is-real-0-0/6354.rss">Jurassic Park is real 0_0</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Jurassic Park is real 0_0</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[bur]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>There <span class="bbcode-i">is</span> a point: knowledge.<br>
If no one in history had ever researched or developed anything other than things with a practical application, we’d be nowhere right now.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/jurassic-park-is-real-0-0/6354/41">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/jurassic-park-is-real-0-0/6354/41</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jan 2011 18:47:41 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-6354-41</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/jurassic-park-is-real-0-0/6354.rss">Jurassic Park is real 0_0</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Jurassic Park is real 0_0</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Deathmonkey7]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Never said it was a good idea. And who says its not the same? Genetically they would be identical enough to count as close ancestors.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/jurassic-park-is-real-0-0/6354/40">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/jurassic-park-is-real-0-0/6354/40</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jan 2011 18:07:10 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-6354-40</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/jurassic-park-is-real-0-0/6354.rss">Jurassic Park is real 0_0</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Jurassic Park is real 0_0</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Jeannotvb]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Deathmonkey7">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/user_avatar/leakfree.org/deathmonkey7/40/5247_2.png" class="avatar"> Deathmonkey7:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>It’s entirely possible to bring back dinosaurs and you don’t need their DNA. All that has to be done is to genetically engineer the evolutionary changes in birds until they revert to back to their formerly dinosaur selves. Work has already been done and they’ve found how to reverse shorter tails, feathers, beaks, you name it.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Birds most likely evolved from smaller raptors. Giving back certain dinosaurian features like long tails, teeth and claws is not the same as creating the actual species that lived millions of years ago.</p>
<p>There’s no point in bringing back extinct animals, that’s not how evolution is supposed to work. 99% of all life in Earths history is extinct, that’s just the way it is. Eventually all current species will be extinct while new ones thrive.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/jurassic-park-is-real-0-0/6354/39">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/jurassic-park-is-real-0-0/6354/39</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jan 2011 17:58:49 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-6354-39</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/jurassic-park-is-real-0-0/6354.rss">Jurassic Park is real 0_0</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Jurassic Park is real 0_0</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[gugamilare]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Maxey">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/user_avatar/leakfree.org/maxey/40/4358_2.png" class="avatar"> Maxey:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Leave the past alone. How about investing some of the millions of dollars invested trying to recreate ancient creatures into advancing medicine instead. There’s like a few diseases and viruses that still have no cure or effective treatments.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Science does not work that way. You can’t dictate what scientists should be studying or that resources would be better spent elsewhere. Science works because scientists shoot theories wherever they feel like shooting. That helps with enthusiasm: you are much more excited and efficient doing what you choose to do.</p>
<p>Also, scientific theories and technology development is done in the same way that evolution developed species. Species evolved because various individuals had slight <span class="bbcode-i"><span class="bbcode-b">random</span></span> mutations in their DNA, then the best ones were selected.</p>
<p>That is how science works as well: each scientist grab a few theories and use pieces of those (like in a sexual procreation) and put a few new pieces that he made himself (that is mutation) to develop a new theory. What “dictates” if that theory will be used by other scientists to develop new theories or technologies is natural selection.</p>
<p>Now, imagine how much pieces of knowledge would cloning an extinct animal bring to science. For instance, it would increase the understanding of how DNA works. Also, the instruments developed to recreate those animals could be used elsewhere. And that certainly includes medicine.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/jurassic-park-is-real-0-0/6354/38">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/jurassic-park-is-real-0-0/6354/38</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jan 2011 13:56:58 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-6354-38</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/jurassic-park-is-real-0-0/6354.rss">Jurassic Park is real 0_0</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
