<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Uninstalled- Computer Won&#39;t Boot</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/uninstalled-computer-wont-boot/12480</link>
    <description>Okay, I made a boo-boo. Last night, I was doing some &quot;routine&quot; maintenance, deleting programs I no longer need in order to free up space on my disk and in the registry. I was using Revo Uninstaller in order to do a thorough sweep (most uninstallers leave folders/registry items behind, which slows down the system over time) and now I can&#39;t seem to boot it up.

When I went through the leftover files and folders in RU last night, three of them (I can&#39;t recall which, but I think it was for one of the old flash player versions) said &quot;Changes will be made on next system startup&quot;, which indicates that the system was still using them. 

I&#39;ve put the drive in my external enclosure and have it up and running as E:/ on this machine, so I&#39;m looking for a way to undelete things from the recycle bin. So far when I go to E:/RECYCLER, it shows up blank (Doing the same for C:/ does the same thing, though I know I have stuff in the recycle bin on this machine as well) and E:/RECYCLED gives me a non-existent directory error.

At this stage I&#39;m just hoping I didn&#39;t fuck the registry up, because not only can I not afford a new OS key right now, I can&#39;t currently reinstall all my stuff due to lack of a stable internet connection.

Any help is appreciated.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2013 13:27:13 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Help and Support</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/uninstalled-computer-wont-boot/12480.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Uninstalled- Computer Won&#39;t Boot</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[JeffMOD]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Here is (as far as I can remember) a list of all the things I axed last night;<br>
<span class="bbcode-i">Italics = notes</span><br>
<span class="bbcode-b">Bold = unsure exact name</span><br>
*Sony Playstation Store<br>
*Sony <span class="bbcode-b">something or other</span> <span class="bbcode-i">- both from my Mp3 player, never used them</span><br>
*Adobe Flash Player 6<br>
*Adobe Flash Player 6 Update <span class="bbcode-b">18</span> <span class="bbcode-i">- I have FP 7 installed, shouldn’t need these anymore</span><br>
*Star Wars: Knights of the Old Republic<span class="bbcode-i"> - Posted in here for completion’s sake, not taking the disc to university with me, so the install is useless</span></p>
<p>That’s all I can remember at the moment.</p>
<p>[b]EDIT:<br>
Okay, so after a great deal of searching, safe mode attempts, and liberal use of curses, I appear to have somehow fixed the problem.</p>
<p>I’d prefer if the mods kept this thread open for a few days in case the problem returns/I have a false positive fix, but otherwise we should be done here.[/b]</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/uninstalled-computer-wont-boot/12480/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/uninstalled-computer-wont-boot/12480/2</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2013 13:27:13 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12480-2</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/uninstalled-computer-wont-boot/12480.rss">Uninstalled- Computer Won&#39;t Boot</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Uninstalled- Computer Won&#39;t Boot</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[JeffMOD]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Okay, I made a boo-boo. Last night, I was doing some “routine” maintenance, deleting programs I no longer need in order to free up space on my disk and in the registry. I was using Revo Uninstaller in order to do a thorough sweep (most uninstallers leave folders/registry items behind, which slows down the system over time) and now I can’t seem to boot it up.</p>
<p>When I went through the leftover files and folders in RU last night, three of them (I can’t recall which, but I think it was for one of the old flash player versions) said “Changes will be made on next system startup”, which indicates that the system was still using them.</p>
<p>I’ve put the drive in my external enclosure and have it up and running as E:/ on this machine, so I’m looking for a way to undelete things from the recycle bin. So far when I go to E:/RECYCLER, it shows up blank (Doing the same for C:/ does the same thing, though I know I have stuff in the recycle bin on this machine as well) and E:/RECYCLED gives me a non-existent directory error.</p>
<p>At this stage I’m just hoping I didn’t fuck the registry up, because not only can I not afford a new OS key right now, I can’t currently reinstall all my stuff due to lack of a stable internet connection.</p>
<p>Any help is appreciated.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/uninstalled-computer-wont-boot/12480/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/uninstalled-computer-wont-boot/12480/1</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2013 13:11:21 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12480-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/uninstalled-computer-wont-boot/12480.rss">Uninstalled- Computer Won&#39;t Boot</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
