<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Particle editing</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/particle-editing/3498</link>
    <description>I know what do you think about the title, again another noob who can&#39;t add the &quot;-tools&quot; to the Ep2 startup commands. No! I will not ask about using the OB Particle Editor, but I will ask about editing it with hands!

There was a video, what showed us as one of the dev&#39;s is using their own version of the Particle Editor. It was a lot better looking (I think) than the current official one, but I still don&#39;t want to ask for it (but if it was released, please tell me  :smiley:  ). I would like to ask about the file specification. How to edit existing particles, how to create new ones from scratch, but the best would be a library what can read, write, and update PCF files (and as I&#39;m a C# developer, it would be the best in C#  :smiley:  ).

So, anyone got info about it?</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 22 Mar 2010 18:30:12 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Help and Support</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/particle-editing/3498.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Particle editing</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[fonix232]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I know what do you think about the title, again another noob who can’t add the “-tools” to the Ep2 startup commands. No! I will not ask about using the OB Particle Editor, but I will ask about editing it with hands!</p>
<p>There was a video, what showed us as one of the dev’s is using their own version of the Particle Editor. It was a lot better looking (I think) than the current official one, but I still don’t want to ask for it (but if it was released, please tell me  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/smiley.png?v=9" title=":smiley:" class="emoji" alt=":smiley:">  ). I would like to ask about the file specification. How to edit existing particles, how to create new ones from scratch, but the best would be a library what can read, write, and update PCF files (and as I’m a C# developer, it would be the best in C#  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/smiley.png?v=9" title=":smiley:" class="emoji" alt=":smiley:">  ).</p>
<p>So, anyone got info about it?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/particle-editing/3498/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/particle-editing/3498/1</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 22 Mar 2010 18:30:12 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3498-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/particle-editing/3498.rss">Particle editing</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
