<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Windows 7 Help</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/windows-7-help/2822</link>
    <description>Ok, first of all I am really REALLY digging Windows 7.


Now that we have that out of the way, WHY THE HELL IS THERE PERMISSIONS AND ACCESS ISSUES ALL THE TIME!!!???AND WHY THE HELL ARE MY ICONS SCREWY!!??  

I am the owner of the computer, I am the only user on the computer, there are no others, so why does everything have to be granted administration rights or permissions or access when I move or change a file?  sheesh!

Yesterday, I got tired of getting blocked by this insanity and I went into my computer, right clicked, and reassigned ownership of the c drive to my user profile rather than to the &quot;administrator&quot;.  It took a couple minutes and it rejected the change on a handful of files, but it made the change.

Now this morning, some of my icons on my desktop are not assigned.  Steam, document.docx, hp photosmart, and other icons.  They are there, and the shortcuts work, but the icons are the blank icons rather than the icons they should be assigned to.

I broke it didnt I.  :fffuuu:</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 30 Jan 2010 17:35:52 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Help and Support</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/windows-7-help/2822.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Windows 7 Help</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[CatzEyes93]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I am unsure what did it, whether a third time of refreshing the icon cache, a reboot for the 5th time after doing a bunch of things, or the installation of the free trial icon program…</p>
<p>But now I can change my icons.</p>
<p>Strange times indeed.</p>
<p>A big thank you to everyone here by the way.  IN CASE this problem resolved as a result of that stupid free trial program, and IN CASE 6 months from now that ability all goes away…</p>
<p>This thread is now available for times that the kitty catz goes crazy over the icons again.</p>
<p>Again, a big thank you to all that participated in this experiment of insanity.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/windows-7-help/2822/24">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/windows-7-help/2822/24</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 30 Jan 2010 17:35:52 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2822-24</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/windows-7-help/2822.rss">Windows 7 Help</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Windows 7 Help</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Mental_Ninja]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="DaftMink">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/d/8e7dd6/40.png" class="avatar"> DaftMink:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I use windows 7 ultimate and icon’s are easy to change.</p>
<p>Just right click on the icon and select properties… the middle button changes the icon.</p>
<p><a href="https://mgofiles.com/Mink/Pictures/Icon.png" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Properties menu</a></p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Charli">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/c/d6d6ee/40.png" class="avatar"> Charli:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>You could try to rebuild your icon cache</p>
<p><a href="https://www.chip.de/downloads/TuneUp-Utilities-2010_12993392.html" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Tune UP Utilities</a> can do that, it has a trial version  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/wink.png?v=9" title=":wink:" class="emoji" alt=":wink:">  (yieks, I just figured this piece of software might only be available in German… not quite sure though)<br>
maybe just try to google rebuild icon cache, there certainly are other programs capable of doing the job.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Both of these guys are right, and both techniques should work. I personally use Tune-Up Utilities to fix errors like this, and I’ve used the program for 3 years. Using this method should work just fine. The program is offered as a trial version in English as well, when you download it you don’t have to fill out the email field if you don’t like using trial software, just click accept and download. I also have a keygen for anyone who wants to use it for free. This is a great program for a lot more than just repairing your icon cache. Version 2010 cleans, defrags, and optimizes your system. I use the advanced system control utility to completely customize windows inside and out. But this is up to you. And if anyone was wondering i am running Windows 7 Ultimate x64 bit.</p>
<p>ANYWAY.</p>
<p>The manual method might be eaiser if your only missing a few icons. Simply right click on the icon (if its a shortcut) and select properties, then click on the shortcut tab and click the change icon button. Navigate to where the program is located (e.g. c\program files\steam) and click on the steam.exe to replace the icon. Just follow this procedure for whatever else you are missing. If this doesn’t work, then you might be better off repairing your icon cache like someone else said using Tune-Up Utilites.</p>
<p>I really think there should be a pc help section in this forum, i love doing this stuff o_0</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/windows-7-help/2822/23">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/windows-7-help/2822/23</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 30 Jan 2010 16:55:08 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2822-23</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/windows-7-help/2822.rss">Windows 7 Help</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Windows 7 Help</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[MechUnit]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>the shortcuts are looking like that there was an installation error with the software, but if office runs proberly it coulnd’t be that problem.</p>
<p>you could try this: right click on desktop =&gt; new =&gt; folder, then name it: name.{ED7BA470-8E54-465E-825C-99712043E01C} - then you got the so called “god mode” (i’m not kidding) and the item of your folder will change in a system control panel icon. for “name” you can insert a name you want, but the .{ED7BA470-8E54-465E-825C-99712043E01C} has to be exactly the same - including the dot before {.</p>
<p>if you’ve done that and start the new control panel, you will see an overview with a huge list where you can check, set and control EVERYTHING what’s win 7 doing - but be warned: wrong settings could lead your system to malfunction. but don’t worry, it’s easy to use if you don’t set too much - a lot of the functions you’ll know already from the “normal” control panel.</p>
<p>the other thing you could check ist the microsoft management console (mmc). just click on start =&gt; in the search field of the start menu type mmc and press enter. when the mmc opened hit “file” and then “add/delete snap in”. in the opening window select “services” in the left menu and “add”. then close the window with “ok”. in the next window just click “finish”. in the mmc you will see “services” in the left field. click it and then you will see a whole list of services in the middle field of the mmc that are starting automatically, manually or are deactiveted when running windows. just check if the right services are activated/deactivated. you can do so if you double click on a service. in the opening window there you can set the values of a service. the services are also described very good if you just click them with a single mouse click.</p>
<p>another thing is just to click start and enter “msconfig” in the search field, press enter and click in that window on the tab “services” but i prefer to use the mmc because it’s better to use. but in the msconfig you can check your autostart-programs and activate those you need and deactivte those you don’t need to start automatically with windows. you will find them on the tab “systemstart”.</p>
<p>but i got to warn you again: wrong setting in the mmc or the msconfig coul lead your system to malfunction, too. so try carefully and click only that wht you know you’re clicking.</p>
<p>i hope the hints are of some help and if not, you got to check your registry with “regedit” and the dll’s and windows values there - but that goes very deep into the system and could also crash it and would be the last option if any other hints or workarounds don’t help.</p>
<p>also i must say that i’m wondering that people are using tune up utilities and stuff like that when running windows 7 - it does not much more then the tools are already build in with windows and they’ve done a lotta optimizations with windows 7 that it will run faster and more safe and stable. but i think cleaning programs for the trash are windows collecting are making still making sense, but only for that tune up or other tools like that are not needed. for that only there are so much tools who are much slimmer and faster and who don’t need an installation, for example “Clear Prog”.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/windows-7-help/2822/22">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/windows-7-help/2822/22</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 30 Jan 2010 15:28:15 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2822-22</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/windows-7-help/2822.rss">Windows 7 Help</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Windows 7 Help</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Jingles]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Revert to a backup?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/windows-7-help/2822/21">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/windows-7-help/2822/21</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 30 Jan 2010 15:16:12 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2822-21</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/windows-7-help/2822.rss">Windows 7 Help</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Windows 7 Help</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Charli]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>You could try to rebuild your icon cache</p>
<p><a href="https://www.chip.de/downloads/TuneUp-Utilities-2010_12993392.html" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Tune UP Utilities</a> can do that, it has a trial version  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/wink.png?v=9" title=":wink:" class="emoji" alt=":wink:">  (yieks, I just figured this piece of software might only be available in German… not quite sure though)<br>
maybe just try to google rebuild icon cache, there certainly are other programs capable of doing the job.</p>
<p>gl :3</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Edit:</span> Here’s a guide explaining how to rebuild it manually. <a href="https://www.winhelponline.com/blog/how-to-rebuild-the-icon-cache-in-windows-vista/" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener"><span class="bbcode-i">Link</span></a></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/windows-7-help/2822/20">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/windows-7-help/2822/20</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 30 Jan 2010 12:48:46 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2822-20</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/windows-7-help/2822.rss">Windows 7 Help</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Windows 7 Help</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Lord_Grievous]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I know on WinXP you could repair your shortcuts with TweakUI, maybe there’s something like that for Vista/7?</p>
<p>EDIT: I found this power tool for tweaking Vista/7 maybe you could give it a go?<br>
<a href="https://www.thewindowsclub.com/ultimate-windows-tweaker-v2-a-tweak-ui-for-windows-7-vista" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://www.thewindowsclub.com/ultimate-windows-tweaker-v2-a-tweak-ui-for-windows-7-vista</a><br>
<a href="https://www.thewindowsclub.com/repair-fix-windows-7-vista-problems-with-fixwin-utility" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://www.thewindowsclub.com/repair-fix-windows-7-vista-problems-with-fixwin-utility</a></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/windows-7-help/2822/19">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/windows-7-help/2822/19</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 30 Jan 2010 11:37:53 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2822-19</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/windows-7-help/2822.rss">Windows 7 Help</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Windows 7 Help</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[sersoft]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Lord Grievous">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Lord Grievous:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Why can’t you change the icons, if you just right-click them and choose Change Icon you can point it to the icon file.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>That doesn’t work for every type of icon. Only shortcuts and folders.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/windows-7-help/2822/18">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/windows-7-help/2822/18</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 30 Jan 2010 10:10:20 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2822-18</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/windows-7-help/2822.rss">Windows 7 Help</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Windows 7 Help</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Lord_Grievous]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Why can’t you change the icons, if you just right-click them and choose Change Icon you can point it to the icon file.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/windows-7-help/2822/17">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/windows-7-help/2822/17</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 30 Jan 2010 09:58:01 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2822-17</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/windows-7-help/2822.rss">Windows 7 Help</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Windows 7 Help</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[sersoft]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="CatzEyes93">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/user_avatar/leakfree.org/catzeyes93/40/4402_2.png" class="avatar"> CatzEyes93:</div>
<blockquote>
<p><a href="https://www.winhelponline.com/blog/change-file-type-icon-windows-7-and-vista/" rel="nofollow noopener">https://www.winhelponline.com/blog/change-file-type-icon-windows-7-and-vista/</a></p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>regedit</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p><span class="bbcode-u"><span class="bbcode-b"><span class="bbcode-u">Fuck</span></span> <span class="bbcode-i"><span class="bbcode-b">That</span></span>.</span></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/windows-7-help/2822/16">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/windows-7-help/2822/16</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 30 Jan 2010 06:35:28 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2822-16</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/windows-7-help/2822.rss">Windows 7 Help</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Windows 7 Help</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[DaftMink]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I use windows 7 ultimate and icon’s are easy to change.</p>
<p>Just right click on the icon and select properties… the middle button changes the icon.</p>
<p><a href="https://mgofiles.com/Mink/Pictures/Icon.png" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Properties menu</a></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/windows-7-help/2822/15">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/windows-7-help/2822/15</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 30 Jan 2010 06:27:08 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2822-15</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/windows-7-help/2822.rss">Windows 7 Help</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Windows 7 Help</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Door]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>That’s really strange, I was able to change icons in the RC…</p>
<p>Have you right-clicked on the shortcuts then pressed properties? There should be a customize tab with a “Folder Icon” sub-heading that has a “Change Icon…” button under it… if it doesn’t I don’t know what Microsoft were thinking  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/frowning.png?v=9" title=":frowning:" class="emoji" alt=":frowning:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/windows-7-help/2822/14">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/windows-7-help/2822/14</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 30 Jan 2010 04:10:43 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2822-14</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/windows-7-help/2822.rss">Windows 7 Help</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Windows 7 Help</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[CatzEyes93]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I reverted the ownership, but the icons are still at the ‘default’ white icon.</p>
<p>Googling icon issues for windows 7, it appears mr. gates felt it was too big of a responsibility for users to be able to change the icon, so in short you cant. To not have the ability to change the icon in windows 7 <a href="https://www.winhelponline.com/blog/change-file-type-icon-windows-7-and-vista/" data-bbcode="true">is functioning as designed</a>.  GRR!</p>
<p>I tried what that guide says, and it works… however I wonder do I really have to go in and edit the registry for all of the shortcuts that are missing an icon!!!</p>
<p>Have you tried ending the explorer.exe process and restarting it?<br>
Yup.</p>
<p>windows rule <span class="hashtag">#1</span> = Never use trial software<br>
Normally I dont, but I was curious if this would let me fix it and it does.  However I have the feeling the icons will revert back once the trial is up.</p>
<p>This is insane. GAH!</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/windows-7-help/2822/13">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/windows-7-help/2822/13</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 30 Jan 2010 00:21:32 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2822-13</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/windows-7-help/2822.rss">Windows 7 Help</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Windows 7 Help</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[bur]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>No, it’s just annoying as hell, and it’s not necessary if you have sense.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/windows-7-help/2822/12">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/windows-7-help/2822/12</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jan 2010 23:32:42 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2822-12</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/windows-7-help/2822.rss">Windows 7 Help</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Windows 7 Help</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Zageron]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><span class="bbcode-i">Yesterday, I got tired of getting blocked by this insanity and I went into my computer, right clicked, and reassigned ownership of the c drive to my user profile rather than to the “administrator”. It took a couple minutes and it rejected the change on a handful of files, but it made the change.</span></p>
<p>Revert this to the way it was before. Either by a Recovery Console or just switching it back. Your icons should fix themselves.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/windows-7-help/2822/11">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/windows-7-help/2822/11</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jan 2010 23:27:01 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2822-11</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/windows-7-help/2822.rss">Windows 7 Help</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Windows 7 Help</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crunchy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Just so you know, UAC isn’t to protect you from other users on the pc, that’s what your password is for.  UAC is to prevent programs themselves from doing nasty things on your pc, which is why it pops and up says “Allow program X to make changes to your computer” or some such thing.  It’s really a GOOD thing, but most people don’t understand it.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/windows-7-help/2822/10">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/windows-7-help/2822/10</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jan 2010 22:10:07 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2822-10</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/windows-7-help/2822.rss">Windows 7 Help</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Windows 7 Help</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[sersoft]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>windows rule <span class="hashtag">#1</span> = Never use trial software</p>
<p>it has the built in option to change the default icon, in the properties menu choose the shortcut tab or the customize tab and the “change icon” button should be there.</p>
<p>in XP there was also the ability to change the icon for any extension but I can’t find it in 7.</p>
<p>From here it looks like a registry bug or an error occured while office was being installed.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/windows-7-help/2822/9">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/windows-7-help/2822/9</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jan 2010 21:15:38 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2822-9</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/windows-7-help/2822.rss">Windows 7 Help</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Windows 7 Help</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Lord_Grievous]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Have you tried ending the explorer.exe process and restarting it?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/windows-7-help/2822/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/windows-7-help/2822/8</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jan 2010 18:21:08 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2822-8</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/windows-7-help/2822.rss">Windows 7 Help</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Windows 7 Help</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[CatzEyes93]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>okey dokey. I reassigned the c drive to “administrator” to be the owner, and my UAC is all the way down/off.</p>
<p>My icons are still wrong tho.  Any other ideas perhaps?</p>
<p>EDIT: Used a free trial period program called <a href="https://www.microangelo.us/" data-bbcode="true">https://www.microangelo.us/</a> and it allows me to choose the icon by right click / Appearance</p>
<p>I would still be curious to know why they all wigged out in the first place.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/windows-7-help/2822/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/windows-7-help/2822/7</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jan 2010 18:20:43 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2822-7</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/windows-7-help/2822.rss">Windows 7 Help</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Windows 7 Help</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Paddy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>No one is ever really logged on as an admin within 7. If you didn’t create a password, it’ll just ask you for permission to continue. The background will grey out, and a box will appear saying “This software wants to …blah… Click ok to allow”.</p>
<p>That means your the administrator. If it asks for a password, then your not.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/windows-7-help/2822/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/windows-7-help/2822/6</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jan 2010 18:00:49 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2822-6</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/windows-7-help/2822.rss">Windows 7 Help</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Windows 7 Help</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[CatzEyes93]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Ok, I think I know how to change it back, however how do I assign the administrator a password?  The only “profile” on this computer is mine and THAT is an administration user. (gah!?)</p>
<p>Meanwhile, here is a pic of the problem I was trying to describe. Oh, and notice how the steam icon is wrong, yet the steam game “plants vs. zombies” has the correct icon. And is that the right icon for Office?  There are two shown in the start menu.</p>
<p><span alt="" class="broken-image" title="This image is broken"><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-unlink svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#unlink"></use></svg></span></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/windows-7-help/2822/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/windows-7-help/2822/5</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jan 2010 17:56:02 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2822-5</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/windows-7-help/2822.rss">Windows 7 Help</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Windows 7 Help</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Paddy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Reasighn the permissions, then disable UAC. It works in the way that no account is the administrator, but you just use the administrator password when a system wide change needs permission to continue.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/windows-7-help/2822/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/windows-7-help/2822/4</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jan 2010 17:51:46 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2822-4</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/windows-7-help/2822.rss">Windows 7 Help</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Windows 7 Help</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[CatzEyes93]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Welcome to the forums and thanks for making your first post a HELP post!</p>
<p>So here is few more stupid questions:</p>
<ol>
<li>
<p>Why disable the UAC and will this fix my icon problem?</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>My icons are the missing/default/error icons for both my desktop AND my start menu.  EVEN my Microsoft office icons.  (Go figure!)</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Should I also go back to the c drive and reassign the “owner” to the “administrator” listing rather than my own profile listing?  Would that have ANYthing to do with my icon problem I wonder?</p>
</li>
</ol>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/windows-7-help/2822/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/windows-7-help/2822/3</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jan 2010 17:43:23 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2822-3</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/windows-7-help/2822.rss">Windows 7 Help</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Windows 7 Help</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Mental_Ninja]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="CatzEyes93">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/user_avatar/leakfree.org/catzeyes93/40/4402_2.png" class="avatar"> CatzEyes93:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I broke it didn’t I.  :fffuuu:</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>You didn’t break it, you just temporarily messed it up  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=9" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:">  Windows 7 is a lot like Windows Vista when it first came out, in the sense that Microsoft is trying to create more user-friendly (well more like retard-friendly) operating systems. Meaning they come cram packed with a lot of features for the inexperienced user, even if we aren’t. But its built a lot more solidly than Vista or XP, so i’d stick with it once you can customize it the way you want.</p>
<p>Anyway, to fix the annoyance (UAC - User Account Control):</p>
<ol>
<li>
<p>Just type UAC into the start menu or Control Panel search box.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Click on the link with the little flag that says “Change User Account Control Settings”</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>You can simply drag the slider up or down, depending on how often you want to be alerted.</p>
</li>
</ol>
<p>If you drag it all the way down to the bottom, you’ll have disabled it entirely.</p>
<hr>
<p>As for your icons, i know this might be an annoying way to do it, but if you still have the shortcuts located in you start menu (and they appear correctly), then it should be as simple ans deleting the ones on your desktop, and moving the ones from you start menu onto your desktop. If not, we will tackle that later.</p>
<hr>
<p>Also, just wanted to say HELLO. I’ve been browsing these forums for a little over 2 years now, and finally decided to register.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/windows-7-help/2822/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/windows-7-help/2822/2</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jan 2010 16:58:53 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2822-2</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/windows-7-help/2822.rss">Windows 7 Help</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Windows 7 Help</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[CatzEyes93]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Ok, first of all I am really REALLY digging Windows 7.</p>
<p>Now that we have that out of the way, WHY THE HELL IS THERE PERMISSIONS AND ACCESS ISSUES ALL THE TIME!!!???AND WHY THE HELL ARE MY ICONS SCREWY!!??</p>
<p>I am the owner of the computer, I am the only user on the computer, there are no others, so why does everything have to be granted administration rights or permissions or access when I move or change a file?  sheesh!</p>
<p>Yesterday, I got tired of getting blocked by this insanity and I went into my computer, right clicked, and reassigned ownership of the c drive to my user profile rather than to the “administrator”.  It took a couple minutes and it rejected the change on a handful of files, but it made the change.</p>
<p>Now this morning, some of my icons on my desktop are not assigned.  Steam, document.docx, hp photosmart, and other icons.  They are there, and the shortcuts work, but the icons are the blank icons rather than the icons they should be assigned to.</p>
<p>I broke it didnt I.  :fffuuu:</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/windows-7-help/2822/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/windows-7-help/2822/1</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jan 2010 15:24:06 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2822-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/windows-7-help/2822.rss">Windows 7 Help</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
