<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>PC gaming: Not just still alive, but still dominant.</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/pc-gaming-not-just-still-alive-but-still-dominant/13172</link>
    <description>PC gaming: Not just still alive, but still dominant, says PAX East panel


[url=&#39;https://arstechnica.com/gaming/2014/04/pc-gaming-not-just-still-alive-but-still-dominant-says-pax-east-panel/&#39;]https://arstechnica.com/gaming/2014/04/pc-gaming-not-just-still-alive-but-still-dominant-says-pax-east-panel/[/url]</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 15 Jun 2014 17:01:17 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Technology and Gaming</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/pc-gaming-not-just-still-alive-but-still-dominant/13172.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>PC gaming: Not just still alive, but still dominant.</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Pyroclase]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Plenty of great games have come out recently. The reason you think they aren’t as good as classic games is because nostalgia always gives you a positive view of the past. Actually go and play an old, classic game, and I guarantee you that for every two fond memories there’ll be some major gripe you don’t remember having. And that’s just for the really good old games - who remembers all the generic games that came out back then?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/pc-gaming-not-just-still-alive-but-still-dominant/13172/86">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/pc-gaming-not-just-still-alive-but-still-dominant/13172/86</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 15 Jun 2014 17:01:17 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13172-86</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/pc-gaming-not-just-still-alive-but-still-dominant/13172.rss">PC gaming: Not just still alive, but still dominant.</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>PC gaming: Not just still alive, but still dominant.</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Grach]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>It would be easy just saying that games should just get smaller budgets then, but we all know that’s not going to happen anytime soon. I kinda see why people keep talking about a 2nd videogame crash (although I still consider it unlikely).</p>
<p>The trend of gaming homogenization is, I think, not killing games. Well, it is for US, long time gamers who’ve been with the classics when they were spanking new (remember when Half-life was a benchmark?). It’s just making them blander and blingier, since it’s been proven that simple games with drop-in drop-out gameplay move simply massive numbers.</p>
<p>But not all is lost. The AAA industry will keep churning out mediocrity with some high notes here and there, but there will always be someone developing games out of heart instead of sole purpose of making money. It’ll become like the movie industry, where you know what you’re in for when you hear the words “Hollywood production” in the same way when you hear say, “an Infinity Ward game”.</p>
<p>The heart won’t go away is what I’m saying. I mean, look at Valve, still nOT RELEASING FUCKIN EPISODE 3 OR HALFLIFE 3 OR WHATEVER THE FUCKING HELL AGHHH</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/pc-gaming-not-just-still-alive-but-still-dominant/13172/85">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/pc-gaming-not-just-still-alive-but-still-dominant/13172/85</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 14 Jun 2014 23:13:02 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13172-85</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/pc-gaming-not-just-still-alive-but-still-dominant/13172.rss">PC gaming: Not just still alive, but still dominant.</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>PC gaming: Not just still alive, but still dominant.</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Kairouseki]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Having good graphics doesn’t make a game cost $100 million+ to make. Most of the games that are used as examples for this have marketing budgets making up most of their budget. I’m not arguing with you that graphics should be the most important thing but they should evolve just like everything else. And not focusing on graphics (and even games that are used as examples of games that do focus on graphics end up looking average because they’re designed for consoles) wouldn’t magically make games play better. I’ve had to tell so many people this that I honestly don’t know how it even became a belief. Devs are so stuck in their ways of making homogenized games that need to appeal to everyone that even if they were told they could make their games look like they were running on the PS1 the games still wouldn’t be good because of this and other flaws in the development process. Not to mention the plethora of redundant staff further bloating the budget. Wanting to have good graphics in a game in 2014 is the least of the worries of the industry right now.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/pc-gaming-not-just-still-alive-but-still-dominant/13172/84">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/pc-gaming-not-just-still-alive-but-still-dominant/13172/84</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2014 02:46:46 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13172-84</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/pc-gaming-not-just-still-alive-but-still-dominant/13172.rss">PC gaming: Not just still alive, but still dominant.</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>PC gaming: Not just still alive, but still dominant.</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Grach]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Thats because in that time games were a lot cheaper to make, thus making risks not as damaging if they flopped. Nowadays a game is considered a failure if it sells less than 7 million cocking units.</p>
<p>How about worrying less about the grain in the wood textures and more in the gameplay?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/pc-gaming-not-just-still-alive-but-still-dominant/13172/83">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/pc-gaming-not-just-still-alive-but-still-dominant/13172/83</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2014 02:41:18 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13172-83</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/pc-gaming-not-just-still-alive-but-still-dominant/13172.rss">PC gaming: Not just still alive, but still dominant.</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>PC gaming: Not just still alive, but still dominant.</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[OldDirtyBastard]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>6th was the last generation when shit actually mattered.<br>
It actually fucking hurts now, booting up HL1/2, Red Alert, Quake 3, Diablo 2, MGS, GoW or DMC and not being able to help but reminiscing that 2001-2006 period. Face it, gaming in general has seen its best days go by already. Now it’s just forever 8 hours for 60 bucks, with rare moments of bliss like Saints Row 3 or Alan Wake.</p>
<p>I dunno what is going to come out for it to change.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/pc-gaming-not-just-still-alive-but-still-dominant/13172/82">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/pc-gaming-not-just-still-alive-but-still-dominant/13172/82</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 08 Jun 2014 23:41:03 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13172-82</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/pc-gaming-not-just-still-alive-but-still-dominant/13172.rss">PC gaming: Not just still alive, but still dominant.</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>PC gaming: Not just still alive, but still dominant.</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Maxey]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Can everyone just shut up about what’s dying or what’s reigning? Does it really matter? Is it a matter of pride? Just enjoy videogames on whatever platform they’re on.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/pc-gaming-not-just-still-alive-but-still-dominant/13172/81">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/pc-gaming-not-just-still-alive-but-still-dominant/13172/81</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2014 11:15:16 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13172-81</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/pc-gaming-not-just-still-alive-but-still-dominant/13172.rss">PC gaming: Not just still alive, but still dominant.</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>PC gaming: Not just still alive, but still dominant.</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Lemonz_amp_amp_orang]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>in the end, the golden age of the consoles was just a diversion, pc has always reigned supreme</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/pc-gaming-not-just-still-alive-but-still-dominant/13172/80">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/pc-gaming-not-just-still-alive-but-still-dominant/13172/80</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2014 09:29:39 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13172-80</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/pc-gaming-not-just-still-alive-but-still-dominant/13172.rss">PC gaming: Not just still alive, but still dominant.</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>PC gaming: Not just still alive, but still dominant.</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Dadster]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>State of Gaming 2014: PC Gaming Is (still) on the Rise.</p>
<p><a href="https://dealnews.com/features/State-of-Gaming-2014-PC-Gaming-Is-on-the-Rise/1062249.html" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://dealnews.com/features/State-of-Gaming-2014-PC-Gaming-Is-on-the-Rise/1062249.html</a></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/pc-gaming-not-just-still-alive-but-still-dominant/13172/79">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/pc-gaming-not-just-still-alive-but-still-dominant/13172/79</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2014 00:11:19 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13172-79</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/pc-gaming-not-just-still-alive-but-still-dominant/13172.rss">PC gaming: Not just still alive, but still dominant.</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>PC gaming: Not just still alive, but still dominant.</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Alyxx]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I edited my post a bit after I reflected a bit on that particular scene in the game and it actually makes more sense to me now.</p>
<p>And no, I’m not trying to say the game is so bad it’s good, I’m trying to say that to me the game is just good but it has its own unique style that some people might find bad. I didn’t.</p>
<p>Regarding the claims that the gameplay is outdated and stuff, I don’t see how that necessarily makes the game bad unless you just personally feel tired of it.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/pc-gaming-not-just-still-alive-but-still-dominant/13172/78">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/pc-gaming-not-just-still-alive-but-still-dominant/13172/78</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2014 04:09:47 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13172-78</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/pc-gaming-not-just-still-alive-but-still-dominant/13172.rss">PC gaming: Not just still alive, but still dominant.</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>PC gaming: Not just still alive, but still dominant.</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[k3nny1550]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Yeah, I get the whole “so bad it’s good” thing that you’re trying to explain. I didn’t feel that way about DNF, but there are games I do that with. Custom Robo for the GameCube had some fun gameplay, but the story is laughably awful and eminently MST3Kable. You basically have to snark your way through the game because the mind numbing shoe-horning of tutorial into dialog will otherwise kill brain cells.</p>
<p>It also helps that Harry’s walking animation in that game looks like he’s walking around sticking his dong in people’s faces.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/pc-gaming-not-just-still-alive-but-still-dominant/13172/77">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/pc-gaming-not-just-still-alive-but-still-dominant/13172/77</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2014 22:28:01 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13172-77</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/pc-gaming-not-just-still-alive-but-still-dominant/13172.rss">PC gaming: Not just still alive, but still dominant.</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>PC gaming: Not just still alive, but still dominant.</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Alyxx]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Well, I disagree with you, I thought it was a good game. Not great or anything but I had fun with it, I enjoyed it and in the end I felt like this was something unique. If you think it’s a bad game, sure, go ahead. Not going to change my opinion.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/pc-gaming-not-just-still-alive-but-still-dominant/13172/76">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/pc-gaming-not-just-still-alive-but-still-dominant/13172/76</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2014 15:23:17 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13172-76</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/pc-gaming-not-just-still-alive-but-still-dominant/13172.rss">PC gaming: Not just still alive, but still dominant.</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>PC gaming: Not just still alive, but still dominant.</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Maxey]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I get the DNF “humor”. Maybe it would’ve been funny when it was originally supposed to release but nowadays that’s just Epic Movie-level of bad humor.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/pc-gaming-not-just-still-alive-but-still-dominant/13172/75">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/pc-gaming-not-just-still-alive-but-still-dominant/13172/75</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2014 15:21:54 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13172-75</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/pc-gaming-not-just-still-alive-but-still-dominant/13172.rss">PC gaming: Not just still alive, but still dominant.</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>PC gaming: Not just still alive, but still dominant.</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Alyxx]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Sure, it’s a mess, but it’s a mess I enjoyed. I actually thought the graphics were pretty good for the most part, the only thing that felt off was the character animations really. But otherwise I enjoyed the details and the overall designs. Especially the alien hive level gave me serious HR Giger vibes and I loved that. Seriously we need more levels like that. Dunno if I’m just a sick girl or something but I enjoyed slapping wall tits and it made me giggle cause I was like “this is so wrong but it’s so wrong it’s funny”.</p>
<p>Regarding the Holsom twins… I didn’t really like them as characters, I thought they were kinda bland so when they died I just went “huh, so that happened”. Wasn’t really disturbed by it, and it felt pretty much in tune with the game’s atmosphere and b-movie feel. It’s what I could expect happening in a sci-fi exploitation flick so to me it just felt, you know, kind of expectable. Duke’s line made me giggle cause of how inappropriate it was and I loved that. Actually he did say it before they died so maybe it was just him trying to tell them in his own way that there was nothing he could do. They were fucked, they were doomed and his joke was just his way of saying that. That actually makes the scene have a bit more depth to me and I think people just totally misunderstand it.</p>
<p>As “bad” as DNF is, to me it is at least unique and memorable and that goes a long way for me. As much as I can say Call of Duty Ghosts is a good game, it’s not as memorable as DNF to me. DNF stays with me in a way no other games have. Sure it’s got its flaws and stuff, but the PC version at least for me was a highly enjoyable experience and I had a blast with it. I enjoyed it on a different level than I enjoy something like Bioshock or Deus Ex.</p>
<p>I think if you don’t get Duke Nukem or get the style of humor they were going for, the game is going to rub you the wrong way. It all depends on who’s playing it I think. I totally got it and dug it.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/pc-gaming-not-just-still-alive-but-still-dominant/13172/74">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/pc-gaming-not-just-still-alive-but-still-dominant/13172/74</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2014 15:12:21 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13172-74</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/pc-gaming-not-just-still-alive-but-still-dominant/13172.rss">PC gaming: Not just still alive, but still dominant.</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>PC gaming: Not just still alive, but still dominant.</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Maxey]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>You can like bad games all you want but don’t say to me they’re objectively good, because they’re not. DNF is a mess in nearly every way and you can’t spin that shit otherwise.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/pc-gaming-not-just-still-alive-but-still-dominant/13172/73">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/pc-gaming-not-just-still-alive-but-still-dominant/13172/73</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2014 15:08:21 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13172-73</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/pc-gaming-not-just-still-alive-but-still-dominant/13172.rss">PC gaming: Not just still alive, but still dominant.</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>PC gaming: Not just still alive, but still dominant.</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[k3nny1550]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Well when you try to pitch games as an art form to someone outside the medium, DNF would basically be one of the easiest counter-examples. Granted, they’d probably bring up GTA first, but I can at least point to GTA IV’s fantastic story to refute it. DNF, I literally would have no defense. You weren’t in the least bit weirded out by the Holsom Twins being impregnated by aliens and dying, and then Duke is all “Looks like you’re… fucked?” Like, at all? I wish I had your intellectual stamina. Maybe shit like that wouldn’t burn me out so quickly.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/pc-gaming-not-just-still-alive-but-still-dominant/13172/72">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/pc-gaming-not-just-still-alive-but-still-dominant/13172/72</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2014 15:00:03 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13172-72</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/pc-gaming-not-just-still-alive-but-still-dominant/13172.rss">PC gaming: Not just still alive, but still dominant.</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>PC gaming: Not just still alive, but still dominant.</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Alyxx]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="k3nny1550">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/user_avatar/leakfree.org/k3nny1550/40/4952_2.png" class="avatar"> k3nny1550:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>When I said you were trolling, it’s because I, too, tried DNF. I found it to be incredibly dull, poorly designed, visually bland, and overtly misogynistic. Seriously, wall boobs? Really? Load times were ridiculous, too. I was glad it was only a rental, because if I’d had the misfortune of buying it, it would be shameful to take it back, as an admission of having bought it and tried it.</p>
<p>It’s games like DNF that give the industry at large a bad name.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I found it fun, intense and I genuinely laughed at the jokes. I’m a terrible person I guess.</p>
<p>And misogynistic? I’m a woman and I didn’t feel offended playing it, I just found it funny.</p>
<p>I had a great time with DNF, it’s one of the few games I’ve 100%'d on Steam and to this day I still play it now and then. I consider it the ultimate Duke Nukem game. Can totally see why it’s not for everyone though but I think it’s surprising how good it is considering how much development hell it had.</p>
<p>But that’s just how people are, we experience things differently. You’re free to dislike the game as far as I’m concerned. I didn’t see it the way you did and I’m kinda glad I didn’t.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/pc-gaming-not-just-still-alive-but-still-dominant/13172/71">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/pc-gaming-not-just-still-alive-but-still-dominant/13172/71</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2014 08:25:58 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13172-71</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/pc-gaming-not-just-still-alive-but-still-dominant/13172.rss">PC gaming: Not just still alive, but still dominant.</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>PC gaming: Not just still alive, but still dominant.</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Surplus]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I played some of Duke Nukem 3D and some of Forever and I have no clue why people where upset with that game no idea why they wanted it in the first place but still no clue for the backlash.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/pc-gaming-not-just-still-alive-but-still-dominant/13172/70">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/pc-gaming-not-just-still-alive-but-still-dominant/13172/70</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2014 05:40:43 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13172-70</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/pc-gaming-not-just-still-alive-but-still-dominant/13172.rss">PC gaming: Not just still alive, but still dominant.</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>PC gaming: Not just still alive, but still dominant.</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Ramirezoid]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>definitely. It’s at that shady area where it’s not pushing the right switches to qualify as satire. It’s just an amalgam of shit you aint supposed to do</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/pc-gaming-not-just-still-alive-but-still-dominant/13172/69">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/pc-gaming-not-just-still-alive-but-still-dominant/13172/69</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2014 01:29:20 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13172-69</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/pc-gaming-not-just-still-alive-but-still-dominant/13172.rss">PC gaming: Not just still alive, but still dominant.</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>PC gaming: Not just still alive, but still dominant.</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[k3nny1550]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>When I said you were trolling, it’s because I, too, tried DNF. I found it to be incredibly dull, poorly designed, visually bland, and overtly misogynistic. Seriously, wall boobs? Really? Load times were ridiculous, too. I was glad it was only a rental, because if I’d had the misfortune of buying it, it would be shameful to take it back, as an admission of having bought it and tried it.</p>
<p>It’s games like DNF that give the industry at large a bad name.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/pc-gaming-not-just-still-alive-but-still-dominant/13172/68">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/pc-gaming-not-just-still-alive-but-still-dominant/13172/68</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2014 00:55:28 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13172-68</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/pc-gaming-not-just-still-alive-but-still-dominant/13172.rss">PC gaming: Not just still alive, but still dominant.</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>PC gaming: Not just still alive, but still dominant.</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Alyxx]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Ramirezoid">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/r/ba9def/40.png" class="avatar"> Ramirezoid:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>this is why i hate my peers. fucking hive-minded xenophobic rats who seek to destroy people for liking the wrong things.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>If it bothered me I wouldn’t admit it as casually as I do. If people dislike something, it’s not gonna keep me from enjoying it.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/pc-gaming-not-just-still-alive-but-still-dominant/13172/67">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/pc-gaming-not-just-still-alive-but-still-dominant/13172/67</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2014 18:23:23 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13172-67</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/pc-gaming-not-just-still-alive-but-still-dominant/13172.rss">PC gaming: Not just still alive, but still dominant.</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>PC gaming: Not just still alive, but still dominant.</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Ramirezoid]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>this is why i hate my peers. fucking hive-minded xenophobic rats who seek to destroy people for liking the wrong things.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/pc-gaming-not-just-still-alive-but-still-dominant/13172/66">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/pc-gaming-not-just-still-alive-but-still-dominant/13172/66</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2014 13:38:40 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13172-66</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/pc-gaming-not-just-still-alive-but-still-dominant/13172.rss">PC gaming: Not just still alive, but still dominant.</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>PC gaming: Not just still alive, but still dominant.</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Alyxx]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Actually I’m serious. That’s my opinion. Not saying it just to troll.</p>
<p>I’m not into fighting games so I dunno about Shaq Fu. I would probably rather play Mortal Kombat.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/pc-gaming-not-just-still-alive-but-still-dominant/13172/65">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/pc-gaming-not-just-still-alive-but-still-dominant/13172/65</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2014 05:00:17 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13172-65</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/pc-gaming-not-just-still-alive-but-still-dominant/13172.rss">PC gaming: Not just still alive, but still dominant.</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>PC gaming: Not just still alive, but still dominant.</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[k3nny1550]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Obvious troll is obvious.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/pc-gaming-not-just-still-alive-but-still-dominant/13172/64">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/pc-gaming-not-just-still-alive-but-still-dominant/13172/64</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2014 01:40:15 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13172-64</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/pc-gaming-not-just-still-alive-but-still-dominant/13172.rss">PC gaming: Not just still alive, but still dominant.</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>PC gaming: Not just still alive, but still dominant.</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Shaddy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Alyxx">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/a/b77776/40.png" class="avatar"> Alyxx:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I’m also a big fan of Duke Nukem Forever (seriously, it’s my 2nd favourite game ever) and I think Aliens: Colonial Marines is a decent game despite the bugs.</p>
<p>I also consider Daikatana one of the most underrated shooters of all time.</p>
<p>Come at me, bro.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p><a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Big_Rigs:_Over_the_Road_Racing" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Seriously?</a><a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Superman_(1999_video_game)" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">What</a><a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/South_Park_(video_game)" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">next,</a><a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Sonic_the_Hedgehog_(2006_video_game)" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">fucking</a><a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/E.T._the_Extra-Terrestrial_(video_game)" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Shaq Fu?</a>[COLOR=‘Black’]God damn it Shaq Fu was a terrible game.[/SIZE]</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/pc-gaming-not-just-still-alive-but-still-dominant/13172/63">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/pc-gaming-not-just-still-alive-but-still-dominant/13172/63</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2014 01:27:49 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13172-63</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/pc-gaming-not-just-still-alive-but-still-dominant/13172.rss">PC gaming: Not just still alive, but still dominant.</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>PC gaming: Not just still alive, but still dominant.</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Alyxx]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Yes, I am very much doomed I’m afraid.  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/wink.png?v=9" title=":wink:" class="emoji" alt=":wink:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/pc-gaming-not-just-still-alive-but-still-dominant/13172/62">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/pc-gaming-not-just-still-alive-but-still-dominant/13172/62</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2014 21:50:02 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13172-62</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/pc-gaming-not-just-still-alive-but-still-dominant/13172.rss">PC gaming: Not just still alive, but still dominant.</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
