<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Diablo 3 Real Money AH</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/diablo-3-real-money-ah/7612</link>
    <description>Diablo 3 now has a REAL MONEY AUCTION HOUSE. 

Players can put items they find into the auction house and you buy it with REAL MONEY. Activision has taken a hold of Blizzard, all the news on Diablo 3 has just been letdown after letdown. No mods, full DRM with no offline support, real money AH, and no LAN.

I honestly feel like I might just buy Torchlight 2, Diablo 2 was one of, if not my favorite game ever, and Diablo 3 is just turning out to be such a huge letdown.

Edit: Now I also need a new forum avatar!

Edit2: Oh, and I forgot the mention the shitty art style and lack of detail in the environments, I mean, just look! [url]https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=NSsgs1Q0d3s[/url]</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 05 Aug 2011 21:36:20 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Technology and Gaming</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/diablo-3-real-money-ah/7612.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Diablo 3 Real Money AH</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[OldDirtyBastard]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>it’s a smart move by Blizzard both from a business standpoint</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>no shit it is</p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>as a customer service standpoint.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Here’s where it’s dubious. Customer service that changes little to nothing.</p>
<p>I don’t know - it would good on paper for hamsters, but after <a href="http://battle.net" rel="nofollow noopener">battle.net</a> experience in D2 it’s hard to trust these guys.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="MaxTheLimit">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/m/0ea827/40.png" class="avatar"> MaxTheLimit:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I’m more for the steel aged ( later iron age ) crypt crawler style myself as well. I could get behind a more bronze age tribal setup if it were consistent, but it isn’t. I mean you have the barbarian which is mostly a bronze age / early iron age character. Then there is the witch doctor and monk, that have a distinct pre-bronze age style. So already it’s kinda all over the place. Then you throw in the demon hunter with grenades and automatic mechanized devices that are looking almost like they are from an age with gunpowder.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>that’s why I hate it when they pull that ‘baaawwwww don’t limit our creativity’ bullshit on me and their retarded fanboys then start parroting them. Shit, you want to be fucking creative - <span class="bbcode-i">create </span>another franchise.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/diablo-3-real-money-ah/7612/79">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/diablo-3-real-money-ah/7612/79</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 05 Aug 2011 21:36:20 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7612-79</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/diablo-3-real-money-ah/7612.rss">Diablo 3 Real Money AH</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Diablo 3 Real Money AH</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[BahamutBBob]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="OldDirtyBastard">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/o/dec6dc/40.png" class="avatar"> OldDirtyBastard:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>This is exactly the kind of screwy mindset that is laying crap on everything nowadays.</p>
<p>“Hey, we can’t battle AIDS, so we might as well just fucking kill everyone infected as soon as they get a positive, as an alternate solution. They’re going to fucking die anyway. <span class="bbcode-i"><span class="bbcode-b">And hey, we should also take the money they pay for treatment. Serves them squalids right.</span></span><br>
Epic win.”</p>
<p>Know what, do whatever you feel right about all this. You like and support this time-serving, I’m not judging you.<br>
As for me, I’m not touching that POS for life, leave alone 1st day</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I never said I agree with the cash auctions, I just think it’s a smart move by Blizzard both from a business standpoint, and as a customer service standpoint.  If I ran a gaming company, if I said it was going to be free after purchase, I would make it 100% free.  Everything I added to the game would be obtainable only in the game.</p>
<p>At the same time, Blizzard knows people are going to sell this shit on eBay anyway, so they’re legitimizing it while protecting the customers.  I think that’s good because it’ll be impossible to screw the other guy over unless you list it and it doesn’t get up to the price you want.</p>
<p>I am mostly against the cash auctions, but I can see the (limited) good aspects of them.  Personally, I’ll either trade for stuff in-game, or find it myself.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/diablo-3-real-money-ah/7612/78">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/diablo-3-real-money-ah/7612/78</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 05 Aug 2011 17:08:31 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7612-78</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/diablo-3-real-money-ah/7612.rss">Diablo 3 Real Money AH</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Diablo 3 Real Money AH</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[MaxTheLimit]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I’m more for the steel aged ( later iron age ) crypt crawler style myself as well. I could get behind a more bronze age tribal setup if it were consistent, but it isn’t. I mean you have the barbarian which is mostly a bronze age / early iron age character. Then there is the witch doctor and monk, that have a distinct pre-bronze age style. So already it’s kinda all over the place. Then you throw in the demon hunter with grenades and automatic mechanized devices that are looking almost like they are from an age with gunpowder.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/diablo-3-real-money-ah/7612/77">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/diablo-3-real-money-ah/7612/77</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 05 Aug 2011 15:56:54 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7612-77</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/diablo-3-real-money-ah/7612.rss">Diablo 3 Real Money AH</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Diablo 3 Real Money AH</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[OldDirtyBastard]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>It takes a dark and moody style and replaces it with an exaggerated cartoonish style, odd proportions, and an over the top design.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I’ve always said that D3 is watercolor/classic fantasy/tribal bullshit and D1-D2 was european (and asian with D2) medieval filled-with-daemons goodness (dorks like to say gothic alot, which isn’t really true).</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/diablo-3-real-money-ah/7612/76">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/diablo-3-real-money-ah/7612/76</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 05 Aug 2011 14:58:14 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7612-76</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/diablo-3-real-money-ah/7612.rss">Diablo 3 Real Money AH</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Diablo 3 Real Money AH</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[MaxTheLimit]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>There is a lot of reason I’m not happy with Diablo 3 and how it seems to be coming along. I guess it all boils down to it not being the game I was expecting and hoping for. The art style is the obvious starting point. When I say the art style, people automatically assume that I mean that it’s not dark enough. That’s not it though. It’s the style of the game that’s bothering me. Not only does it not look very attractive ( it looks dated, and it’s not even released yet ), but it deviates wildly from what was established in the previous 2 games. It takes a dark and moody style and replaces it with an exaggerated cartoonish style, odd proportions, and an over the top design. A lot of people say that it worked okay for TF2, so why not Diablo3, but that isn’t comparable because anyone who actually played team fortress in the old days would have noticed an obvious dark comedy to the violence. I’m not for or against investing so heavily in this, but at least with TF2 I can see why. It’s been said that the art style was chosen because it would be easier to distinguish characters and objects. I don’t think that is true at all, because it is a fairly simple task of making an art style similar to the original work.</p>
<p>This new announcement of the transactions, I can see the reasoning for, but I don’t support accepting a problem, and simply integrating it as part of the game. Fixing or finding a way of balancing or a way to make the game work in spite of what people may do. In truth though it’s not a big deal in my mind. It might impact others more though.</p>
<p>I am VERY disappointed to hear that the levelling system where you customize your character build is removed. Planning a character was something I enjoyed.</p>
<p>I do like the female and Male variants of characters, but I’m not liking a lot of the way the combat looks right now. It seems to lack that certain something that made the combat satisfying. Then again, maybe that’s just because it doesn’t translate to video very well. I just notice that the person playing seems to be a bit unskilled with the 'ol mouse movement. So it’s either not as crisply controlled or they have a fellow playing the game with motor control issues playing the game during the videos ( very possible, lots of times people selected to play game demonstrations are inept ).</p>
<p>Anyhoo, just my thoughts. I’m just glad that there looks to be alternatives that are more directed at the type of game I wanted. I’m sure on reputation alone Diablo 3 will do well. It just doesn’t seem like the game for me though.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/diablo-3-real-money-ah/7612/75">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/diablo-3-real-money-ah/7612/75</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 05 Aug 2011 12:46:41 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7612-75</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/diablo-3-real-money-ah/7612.rss">Diablo 3 Real Money AH</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Diablo 3 Real Money AH</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Evod]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Blizzard screwing diablo aside.</p>
<p>Is there really going to be money for people selling their items?<br>
Theres got to be some downside here. Well other than screwing up the game.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/diablo-3-real-money-ah/7612/74">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/diablo-3-real-money-ah/7612/74</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 05 Aug 2011 02:12:21 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7612-74</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/diablo-3-real-money-ah/7612.rss">Diablo 3 Real Money AH</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Diablo 3 Real Money AH</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[OldDirtyBastard]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I meant that Blizzard were clearly not morons to not exploit this situation with dupers.<br>
hence ‘only morons wouldn’t get advantage of this’ - but aye, I threw the logical chain away there. My bad.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>Additionally if Blizzard really wanted to they could ban by IP as well as CDKey.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>But they didn’t. Hence my previous post. They were exploiting that scheme for years.<br>
This current Blizzard lot isn’t trustworthy at all.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/diablo-3-real-money-ah/7612/73">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/diablo-3-real-money-ah/7612/73</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 05 Aug 2011 01:24:22 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7612-73</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/diablo-3-real-money-ah/7612.rss">Diablo 3 Real Money AH</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Diablo 3 Real Money AH</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Chickenprotector]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>That post was a bit vague. Care to elaborate?</p>
<p>I understand the duping part, and the rest of the enterprise shit, but “only morons wouldn’t get advantage of this.”</p>
<p>Who’re the morons you’re referring to, Blizzard or the player base?</p>
<p>Edit: Considering the context, I think you’re referring to the player base.</p>
<p>Edit <span class="hashtag">#2:</span> Additionally if Blizzard really wanted to they could ban by IP as well as CDKey.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/diablo-3-real-money-ah/7612/72">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/diablo-3-real-money-ah/7612/72</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 05 Aug 2011 00:43:47 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7612-72</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/diablo-3-real-money-ah/7612.rss">Diablo 3 Real Money AH</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Diablo 3 Real Money AH</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[OldDirtyBastard]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I think we know what to expect, with known precedents with Diablo 2 such as forcing the purchase of more and more cd-keys by banning dupers (even honest players) and then doing nothing more. They are already the part of embezzlement by letting the dupers do their business - but on their terms.<br>
Come think of it - only morons wouldn’t get advantage of this.<br>
They are simply exploiting the loopholes in the law… which doesn’t really even exist.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/diablo-3-real-money-ah/7612/71">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/diablo-3-real-money-ah/7612/71</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 04 Aug 2011 22:56:16 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7612-71</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/diablo-3-real-money-ah/7612.rss">Diablo 3 Real Money AH</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Diablo 3 Real Money AH</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Chickenprotector]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>^ I think they will likely foresee this and modify the ToU accordingly in-order to prevent them getting sued. But I could be plausibly wrong.</p>
<p>In all reality, you bring up a very valid point ODB. Only time will tell if you’re right or not.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/diablo-3-real-money-ah/7612/70">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/diablo-3-real-money-ah/7612/70</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 04 Aug 2011 22:38:33 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7612-70</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/diablo-3-real-money-ah/7612.rss">Diablo 3 Real Money AH</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Diablo 3 Real Money AH</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[OldDirtyBastard]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>All I’m saying - it’s the same as trying to treat acne on epidermic level while still munching on McDonalds and Coke.<br>
They are facilitating more morons with this. And I don’t think the item turnover is fixed now - there’s always dupers.<br>
And really, people were doing fine trading non-duped (hypothetically) items in D2.<br>
Now they’re possibly dragging themselves directly into embezzlement schemes with simply introducing IRL currency and microtransactions into the mix- nothing more - with advantages and huge disadvantages.</p>
<p>It’s also pretty much like govt. legalizing cocaine and then taxing both the sellers and buyers - basically admitting themselves as pathetic and worthless in curing the cancer that is killing D2.</p>
<p>At the very least - it is completely useless.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/diablo-3-real-money-ah/7612/69">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/diablo-3-real-money-ah/7612/69</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 04 Aug 2011 20:39:03 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7612-69</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/diablo-3-real-money-ah/7612.rss">Diablo 3 Real Money AH</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Diablo 3 Real Money AH</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Chickenprotector]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="OldDirtyBastard">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/o/dec6dc/40.png" class="avatar"> OldDirtyBastard:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Morons are made not born.<br>
Retards, on the other side…</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Touche ODB touche.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/diablo-3-real-money-ah/7612/68">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/diablo-3-real-money-ah/7612/68</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 04 Aug 2011 20:14:46 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7612-68</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/diablo-3-real-money-ah/7612.rss">Diablo 3 Real Money AH</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Diablo 3 Real Money AH</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[OldDirtyBastard]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="MaxTheLimit">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/m/0ea827/40.png" class="avatar"> MaxTheLimit:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Thank you for the Path of Exile find ODB.</p>
<p>I like the way it looks, and I find the gem and quest skill set up an interesting twist.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Well, youtube comments aren’t always worthless after all.<br>
It really needs help and support though. With only 12 men, they lack artists and they’re stretched out.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/diablo-3-real-money-ah/7612/67">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/diablo-3-real-money-ah/7612/67</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 04 Aug 2011 19:56:11 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7612-67</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/diablo-3-real-money-ah/7612.rss">Diablo 3 Real Money AH</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Diablo 3 Real Money AH</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[MaxTheLimit]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Thank you for the Path of Exile find ODB.</p>
<p>I like the way it looks, and I find the gem and quest skill set up an interesting twist.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/diablo-3-real-money-ah/7612/66">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/diablo-3-real-money-ah/7612/66</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 04 Aug 2011 19:54:43 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7612-66</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/diablo-3-real-money-ah/7612.rss">Diablo 3 Real Money AH</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Diablo 3 Real Money AH</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[OldDirtyBastard]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>Tell that to the shit ton of morons who buy it with their moms credit cards everyday…</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Morons are made not born.<br>
Retards, on the other side…</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/diablo-3-real-money-ah/7612/65">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/diablo-3-real-money-ah/7612/65</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 04 Aug 2011 18:38:59 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7612-65</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/diablo-3-real-money-ah/7612.rss">Diablo 3 Real Money AH</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Diablo 3 Real Money AH</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Chickenprotector]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Fuskox">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/f/ea666f/40.png" class="avatar"> Fuskox:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>When I play D2 MP, all I see is bots spamming, not hackers running around at high levels with extra awesome weapons. I see bots and regular players, are you just listing a single person you ran across so that automatically equals everyone hacks and cheats in D2?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Go to the PvP Community. You’ll find that there are A LOT of hackers on there, ladder or non. I’ve been playing for a good 2 years on the PvP circuit I can tell you there are quite a few.</p>
<p>You may have seen me around: Uber_Reviver (NL Summoning Necromancer US-East)</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="kaikarden">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/k/a9a28c/40.png" class="avatar"> kaikarden:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>no dude, i’ve seen plenty of them, regardless, that doesn’t, however, dismiss the fact that the new auction systems are not mandatory and even at that, they’re really not as bad as you made them out to be.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>This. They are a gold sink among other things, you can also make cash off of the useless (good) items you find in game for the char you have. What’s not to like?</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Bluemen230">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Bluemen230:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I have never seen any hackers whenever I play D2.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Again PvP Circuit. And you need to play/get out more…</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="kaikarden">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/k/a9a28c/40.png" class="avatar"> kaikarden:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>okay lets get off the subject of hackers and back on the subject of how people will buy characters, items, and ingame gold regardless of the venue.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I’m not one who buys into that bullshit, but I can see the direction it’s taking. It’s a good thing, but it may prompt <span class="bbcode-i">far</span> more spam bots than Diablo II has now as they will likely go out of business pretty quickly on that game.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>if you’re a player that buys it from the new auction system, you’re probably a player who would go to a third party website. My point is, nothing has changed, this has merely made the transactions guaranteed, secure, and beneficial to other players that are selling the items. If you don’t like the new system, then don’t use it, use the gold only auction, or don’t even use that. I just find it ridiculous how much flak blizzard is receiving for adding a way to play the game for free essentially.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>^ This.</p>
<p>I don’t think there would be so much complaining if they would allow players to modify models, sounds, textures, etc to some extent so players don’t bitch so much.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="OldDirtyBastard">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/o/dec6dc/40.png" class="avatar"> OldDirtyBastard:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Haha just gtfo you fucking fail<br>
Now who are you trying to troll here, you stupid little chimp?  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=9" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
<p>I never participated in video game microtransactions. Your argument is invalid.<br>
And btw, when I buy something online with a credit card, I buy a specific product (usually physical), not some bits of code at some remote server.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Tell that to the shit ton of morons who buy it with their moms credit cards everyday…</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/diablo-3-real-money-ah/7612/64">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/diablo-3-real-money-ah/7612/64</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 04 Aug 2011 18:05:22 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7612-64</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/diablo-3-real-money-ah/7612.rss">Diablo 3 Real Money AH</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Diablo 3 Real Money AH</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[OldDirtyBastard]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="kaikarden">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/k/a9a28c/40.png" class="avatar"> kaikarden:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>If you’ve ever purchased ANYTHING online with a credit card then you’re only supporting this worthless and jewish conspiracy lol. That is all. Rant over.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Haha just gtfo you fucking fail<br>
Now who are you trying to troll here, you stupid little chimp?  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=9" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
<p>I never participated in video game microtransactions. Your argument is invalid.<br>
And btw, when I buy something online with a credit card, I buy a specific product (usually physical), not some bits of code at some remote server.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/diablo-3-real-money-ah/7612/63">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/diablo-3-real-money-ah/7612/63</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 04 Aug 2011 13:12:41 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7612-63</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/diablo-3-real-money-ah/7612.rss">Diablo 3 Real Money AH</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Diablo 3 Real Money AH</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[kaikarden]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="OldDirtyBastard">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/o/dec6dc/40.png" class="avatar"> OldDirtyBastard:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Doesn’t make them any less worseless and jewish.<br>
Guess why I quit my BA in e-business after not even having studied half the credits and applied for BA in Cinema &amp; Photography?<br>
<em>spit</em></p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>If you’ve ever purchased ANYTHING online with a credit card then you’re only supporting this worthless and jewish conspiracy lol. That is all. Rant over.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/diablo-3-real-money-ah/7612/62">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/diablo-3-real-money-ah/7612/62</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 04 Aug 2011 05:48:30 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7612-62</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/diablo-3-real-money-ah/7612.rss">Diablo 3 Real Money AH</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Diablo 3 Real Money AH</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[OldDirtyBastard]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>I find it incredibly amusing that people were perfectly fine with playing Diablo 2 and were so engrossed with it’s multiplayer when everywhere you look (at least every time i’ve played) there’s nothing but level 127’s with gear that’s obviously third party fab gear.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Yeah. Big fucking words.<br>
I was totally not pissed off when <span class="bbcode-b">two days</span> (which were rendered fucking unplayable by the duper faggots lagging the shit out of realms) after the ladder reset the <span class="bbcode-b">item turnover was skullfucked beyong fucking recognition</span> - that all happening in one of my favourite games (for which I payed 60 bucks back in the day, btw). But hey, why would I care anyway, it’s just a game…</p>
<p>I was so not fucking pissed off when everything that Blizz did was only pretending to do shit about it for 10 fucking years, instead introducing the world events which further stimulated dupes.</p>
<p>Right. Go fuck yourself, cunt.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>About the cash shop: people would sell the items anyway. Doing it officially helps keep people from getting screwed over.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>This is exactly the kind of screwy mindset that is laying crap on everything nowadays.</p>
<p>“Hey, we can’t battle AIDS, so we might as well just fucking kill everyone infected as soon as they get a positive, as an alternate solution. They’re going to fucking die anyway. <span class="bbcode-i"><span class="bbcode-b">And hey, we should also take the money they pay for treatment. Serves them squalids right.</span></span><br>
Epic win.”</p>
<p>Know what, do whatever you feel right about all this. You like and support this time-serving, I’m not judging you.<br>
As for me, I’m not touching that POS for life, leave alone 1st day.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>That Path of Exile game looks fucking shit</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>If looking like shit means looking like Diablo (even remotely), I’ll take that poor squalor with me and nurture it. Even if it has one tile for a whole game, half a character, fubar skill system or no lore at all. But thanks for your insight.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>any sensible broker does that after all</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Doesn’t make them any less worseless and jewish.<br>
Guess why I quit my BA in e-business after not even having studied half the credits and applied for BA in Cinema &amp; Photography?<br>
<em>spit</em></p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>Diablo 3’s art direction is fantastic and you people have no art sensibility at all.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Know what, Spooks, I don’t give a fuck how fucking fantastic, beautiful and creative it is. Neither, in my view, should I give a fuck over sensibility to some recycled POS that isn’t Diablo, but being marketed as one.<br>
Now take a rough guess, do I really give a fuck about Blizzard and their sad shit now that there is Grim Dawn and PoE?</p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>In short: Blizzard, &lt;…&gt; you’re still finding ways to run your damn franchise - which I adore by the way - in the fucking ground. Good job.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>This one I can agree with.</p>
<p>That is all. Rant over.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/diablo-3-real-money-ah/7612/61">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/diablo-3-real-money-ah/7612/61</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 03 Aug 2011 22:39:39 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7612-61</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/diablo-3-real-money-ah/7612.rss">Diablo 3 Real Money AH</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Diablo 3 Real Money AH</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Surplus]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Awesomeness!">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Awesomeness!:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>T-T-T-TRIPLE POST</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>What he posted was worth it.  More excited for that game than Diablo 3 now.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/diablo-3-real-money-ah/7612/60">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/diablo-3-real-money-ah/7612/60</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 03 Aug 2011 20:31:19 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7612-60</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/diablo-3-real-money-ah/7612.rss">Diablo 3 Real Money AH</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Diablo 3 Real Money AH</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Ham_Solo]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Well, seeing as how I enjoy crappy internet in the military barracks I inhabit most of the week I can kiss that game goodbye. Thanks, Blizzard/Activision.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/diablo-3-real-money-ah/7612/59">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/diablo-3-real-money-ah/7612/59</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 03 Aug 2011 19:50:46 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7612-59</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/diablo-3-real-money-ah/7612.rss">Diablo 3 Real Money AH</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Diablo 3 Real Money AH</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[BaTz281]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Samapico">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/s/839c29/40.png" class="avatar"> Samapico:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I really don’t care about the money thing… but really… no LAN? This is official?<br>
And WTF @ no stat distribution?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Yes, it is true, for more information you could search for the dozens of posts on the D3 general forums (edit: Blizzard’s forums) that discuss LAN and auto-stats.  To quote Metallica, “Sad but true.”</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="brokenfridgehinge">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/b/87869e/40.png" class="avatar"> brokenfridgehinge:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Is it bad that I think that game looks more like what I think Diablo 3 should look like than what it looks like now?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>My thoughts exactly.  I watched those PoE videos and said, “Hey, a modern-looking, 3D reincarnation of Diablo 1…but…wait, it’s not by Blizzard.”</p>
<p>Eh, we’ll see what happens with D3 beta (should be soon) and go from there.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/diablo-3-real-money-ah/7612/58">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/diablo-3-real-money-ah/7612/58</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 03 Aug 2011 19:49:33 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7612-58</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/diablo-3-real-money-ah/7612.rss">Diablo 3 Real Money AH</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Diablo 3 Real Money AH</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[kaikarden]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Bluemen230">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Bluemen230:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I have never seen any hackers whenever I play D2.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>okay lets get off the subject of hackers and back on the subject of how people will buy characters, items, and ingame gold regardless of the venue. if you’re a player that buys it from the new auction system, you’re probably a player who would go to a third party website. My point is, nothing has changed, this has merely made the transactions guaranteed, secure, and beneficial to other players that are selling the items. If you don’t like the new system, then don’t use it, use the gold only auction, or don’t even use that. I just find it ridiculous how much flak blizzard is receiving for adding a way to play the game for free essentially.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/diablo-3-real-money-ah/7612/57">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/diablo-3-real-money-ah/7612/57</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 03 Aug 2011 18:37:44 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7612-57</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/diablo-3-real-money-ah/7612.rss">Diablo 3 Real Money AH</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Diablo 3 Real Money AH</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Spooks]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>That Path of Exile game <span class="bbcode-i">looks</span> fucking shit, Torchlight’s art direction was fucking awful in the sense that encounters were a visual clusterfuck and if they don’t fix that in the sequel good job on them and Grim Dawn is a spiritual successor to Titan Quest - a very pleasant game which, while being a Diablo clone, had a completely different feel to it and therefore both it and Grim Dawn (which retains that feel) are not comparable to Diablo 3 for me.</p>
<p>Diablo 3’s art direction is fantastic and you people have no art sensibility at all. The auction house thing is <span class="bbcode-i">great</span> on paper and I do like the idea but that doesn’t mean it won’t probably be fucking awful in execution. What’s the point of random drops if you can just hop the fuck in ye item store and twink out a character with the exact stuff you need. There goes the fucking PvP arena balance (lol pvp arenas, nice one Blizz). “Legalizing” this sort of stuff doesn’t make it any damn better. I’m not complaining about fees, any sensible broker does that after all. Removing moddability in a game is a sad thing to hear no matter what, though it’s been brought to my attention that mods have caused more harm than good when it’s come to D2 so all in all I guess one shouldn’t be too bitter about that decision. Always on-line social gaming? Fuck off, Blizzard, you don’t have the right to shove that down my throat, at least in SC2 the perceived notion is that multiplayer is the main focus (while ironically 50% of Wings of Liberty players haven’t even touched it, only delving in SP) so you know fuck that, always on-line is passable, but Diablo 3? Yeah up yours, Pardo.</p>
<p>In short: Blizzard, despite having some of the best artists and designers in the industry you’re still finding ways to run your damn franchise - which I adore by the way - in the fucking ground. Good job.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/diablo-3-real-money-ah/7612/56">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/diablo-3-real-money-ah/7612/56</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 03 Aug 2011 18:27:26 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7612-56</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/diablo-3-real-money-ah/7612.rss">Diablo 3 Real Money AH</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Diablo 3 Real Money AH</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[DeleteThis]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I have never seen any hackers whenever I play D2.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/diablo-3-real-money-ah/7612/55">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/diablo-3-real-money-ah/7612/55</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 03 Aug 2011 17:48:50 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7612-55</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/diablo-3-real-money-ah/7612.rss">Diablo 3 Real Money AH</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
