<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Things that don&#39;t work...</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/things-that-dont-work/9589</link>
    <description>I am in Office Complex right now.
 1. Upstairs, after a serious firefight, behind a barricated door I find two surviving scientist, I just killed the male one.... and the female one didn&#39;t care, she joined me when I asked her right after.
 2. There is that scientist with some basic radio device under a stairway (after that serious firefight place) ... in HL he says &quot;I just overheard a secure access transmission: soldiers have arrived and they&#39;re coming to rescue us&quot; 
   - [i]Here he does some explaining moves, but remains silent. He doesn&#39;t say a thing.[/i]
 3.. Towards the end of the chapter, in the freezer room, I can&#39;t close any of the doors inside there. The handles do give an operating sound, but nothing happens.


Sorry, co-ordinates come later.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 14 Sep 2012 23:11:03 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>In-game Issues (Mod)</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/things-that-dont-work/9589.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Things that don&#39;t work...</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[kaksikasvoinen]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Yes, the female scientist tends to ignore team kills, it was sort of funny at the final elevator shaft, where I decided to test few things, and killed all the four surviving guards I had with me in front of her. She kindly reminded me to reload, and was wondering would I need more ammo soon.</p>
<p>Also, the male scientist ignores grenades after sequence has started, other NPC :s  seem to react regardless of the script, this is a minor thing though.</p>
<p>I didn’t personally have any other issues reported by Medkit, few others minor tweaks there were, like cockroaches going wild on certain solids, and some ragdoll wtf moments.</p>
<p>I still enjoyed every god damn minute.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/things-that-dont-work/9589/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/things-that-dont-work/9589/2</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 14 Sep 2012 23:11:03 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9589-2</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/things-that-dont-work/9589.rss">Things that don&#39;t work...</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Things that don&#39;t work...</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Medkit]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I am in Office Complex right now.</p>
<ol>
<li>Upstairs, after a serious firefight, behind a barricated door I find two surviving scientist, I just killed the male one… and the female one didn’t care, she joined me when I asked her right after.</li>
<li>There is that scientist with some basic radio device under a stairway (after that serious firefight place) … in HL he says “I just overheard a secure access transmission: soldiers have arrived and they’re coming to rescue us”</li>
</ol>
<ul>
<li>
<span class="bbcode-i">Here he does some explaining moves, but remains silent. He doesn’t say a thing.</span><br>
3… Towards the end of the chapter, in the freezer room, I can’t close any of the doors inside there. The handles do give an operating sound, but nothing happens.</li>
</ul>
<p>Sorry, co-ordinates come later.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/things-that-dont-work/9589/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/things-that-dont-work/9589/1</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 14 Sep 2012 22:46:04 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9589-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/things-that-dont-work/9589.rss">Things that don&#39;t work...</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
