<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Your opinion on Steam</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/your-opinion-on-steam/6875</link>
    <description>NOTE: This is NOT a dig at Steam, nor a thread to dump your complaints into, unless relevant to the discussion. Neither is it an excuse to rag on Steam, nor somewhere to vent hate for Steam/me/anyone/anything else you feel like. Keep that shit out and keep the topic friendly. This is a discussion thread, nothing more, nothing less. Apologies if this is in the wrong place, seemed most appropriate here.

What is your opinion on the Steam platform as a whole? My opinion of it is, that as software, it is an excellent platform and does what it sets out to do pretty well. I.e. One handy place to buy and manage your games. But my father has pointed out two main problems with it, both of which I agree with him on.

1. If you buy a Steam integrated game, you cannot install and play on an offline machine. What happens if your gaming PC isn&#39;t connected to the internet? What if you have no internet (by whatever happenstance)? You are then denied the game you rightfully own and paid money for in good faith. You are also forced to register with Steam and (assuming you make further purchases with Steam) divulge personal information.

2. Game licences are linked by account, meaning that if two people on the same machine want to play the same game, they either have to use the same account (not ideal), or, in the case of my household, the same person has to buy something again that they&#39;ve already paid for. This is, quite frankly, a shady business practice and I do wonder if the EU trading standards board are entirely aware of it. My dad actually tried to bring this up with Steam Support recently. The conversation went like this:

Dad: Posed above problem, asked if this is in fact, correct.
Steam: Canned response 101.
Dad: Pursues the issue politely, asking for more information.
Steam: Closes thread without another reply.

Now, my dad&#39;s job is basically glorified tech support, and if he handled a support call like that, he&#39;d get the sack pretty damned quick.

Now I&#39;m not saying that Valve engage in dodgy business practices, but all it takes is one greedy fucker on the board of directors to chance their arm, and it&#39;s not like large corporations are exactly unknown to dally on the fringes of the law (or engage in outright illegal activities).

Another point that I just thought of: If you buy a non-Steam game through Steam, say for the sake of argument, Unreal Tourney 99, you can&#39;t launch the game without first logging into Steam, meaning you are tied into Steam and the platform, something which not everyone wants to do. Now, admittedly, yes you can go download a non-Steam launcher, but most people wouldn&#39;t know those things existed, and it quite frankly is a pain in the arse waiting for Steam to load, before I can play a game that only ever required a CD before.

Thoughts and opinions pl0x.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 08 Apr 2011 23:03:47 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Technology and Gaming</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/your-opinion-on-steam/6875.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Your opinion on Steam</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[genericenemy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I’m generally happy with steam but there are a few niggles, firstly i think that the drm means that gamers have to take a gamble over whether that software will be available in the future I believe steam could be a threat to the future use of that software should it go down without no patch.</p>
<p>Secondly I really hate the fact there is no native client for Linux, which forces me to go through the slow route of wine and if that fails I have to go back to windows. Steam for Linux would really make steam more useful for me.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/your-opinion-on-steam/6875/55">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/your-opinion-on-steam/6875/55</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Apr 2011 23:03:47 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-6875-55</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/your-opinion-on-steam/6875.rss">Your opinion on Steam</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Your opinion on Steam</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Harun]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>only that both the VPN(provided I would like to get an actually usable one) and the Visacard cost money and I don’t buy games so often that the saving compensates for the expenses. Besides I think I could (at least) get my steam-account banned with that.<br>
The downsides I stated weren’t meant to give an overall bad image on steam. I definitely like it.<br>
I find myself looking through the shop, like, every day at least one time</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/your-opinion-on-steam/6875/54">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/your-opinion-on-steam/6875/54</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Apr 2011 21:05:23 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-6875-54</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/your-opinion-on-steam/6875.rss">Your opinion on Steam</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Your opinion on Steam</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Saftle]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Harun, just get a VPN, use a Visa, and buy US games while living in Germany. Cheaper (dollar &lt; euro), uncensored, and no dubs.</p>
<p>Back to the steam topic. I think Steam has revolutionized gaming, and the people that don’t like it either are not very familiar with the interwebs, too cheap to pay for internet, or have the disadvantage of being in a country that has internet issues.</p>
<p>The argument of Steam being bullshit, etc, is null and void. Just like saying, damn you linux for being not so user friendly, when there are other solutions like Windows for those not willing to think or learn. Not a Windows bash, I use it as well. Just stating that there is a choice, and one choice will allow you to not have to leave your comfort zone.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/your-opinion-on-steam/6875/53">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/your-opinion-on-steam/6875/53</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Apr 2011 20:48:51 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-6875-53</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/your-opinion-on-steam/6875.rss">Your opinion on Steam</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Your opinion on Steam</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Harun]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="striker">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 striker:</div>
<blockquote>
<ol start="4">
<li>savegames are still saved locally - would be cool if my saves where available everywhere I play</li>
</ol>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Ever heard of the magnificient piece of hardware called FLASH DRIVE?<br>
Sorry for sarcasm. You could ask the internet where your game of choice saves your savegames. Go into that folder, copy what you find onto a flash drive and import the files to the same folder on your other pc. Usually works.</p>
<p>My opinion on steam is mixed, if I would live in the US I could clearly claim a positive view… Sadly I live in goddamn fascist(not the old fashioned way) game hater state of Germany where the state thinks it knows what is best for you even if you are “adult”.<br>
Good aspects of steam are:<br>
-Instantly being able to buy stuff and finding out about new stuff in the shop<br>
-Metascore and links to reviews<br>
-community stuff/functions in general<br>
-news even though they’re sometimes quite late<br>
-simplicity and ingenuity of UI<br>
-Most games in multilanguage</p>
<p>downsides:<br>
-Price differences in different regions<br>
-No “hard copy” of the game if you buy it(of course shipping hard copies would push the price again, I find it kinda sad anyway)<br>
-censorship and not being able to buy some games with multilang due to that(cuz I fucking hate german synchro for 90% of the games)<br>
-Always having to download all the languages. it would be smarter if you could choose before downloading, maybe in the settings<br>
-Forcing online activation</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/your-opinion-on-steam/6875/52">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/your-opinion-on-steam/6875/52</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Apr 2011 19:17:06 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-6875-52</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/your-opinion-on-steam/6875.rss">Your opinion on Steam</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Your opinion on Steam</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Mith]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>oh boy i remember when steam was first released when cs 1.6 came out and they shut down the WON servers</p>
<p>the constant crashing, the 100% RAM usage, friend system that never worked for 2 straight years</p>
<p>steam sure sucked huge ass balls back then, everyone hated it</p>
<p>nowadays it runs on my pc 100% of the time and i’m fine with it, and i haven’t bought a physical copy of a game for probably 6 or 7 years now</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/your-opinion-on-steam/6875/51">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/your-opinion-on-steam/6875/51</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Apr 2011 18:13:34 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-6875-51</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/your-opinion-on-steam/6875.rss">Your opinion on Steam</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Your opinion on Steam</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Steppenwolf]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>When Steam was first released, I hated it for being very unstable. But since they fixed that problem soon after, I fell in love with it an try to only buy games over it.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/your-opinion-on-steam/6875/50">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/your-opinion-on-steam/6875/50</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Apr 2011 17:29:12 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-6875-50</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/your-opinion-on-steam/6875.rss">Your opinion on Steam</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Your opinion on Steam</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Guzzi]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Skilgannon">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/s/edb3f5/40.png" class="avatar"> Skilgannon:</div>
<blockquote>
<ol>
<li>
<p>If you buy a Steam integrated game, you cannot install and play on an offline machine. What happens if your gaming PC isn’t connected to the internet? What if you have no internet (by whatever happenstance)? You are then denied the game you rightfully own and paid money for in good faith. You are also forced to register with Steam and (assuming you make further purchases with Steam) divulge personal information.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Game licences are linked by account, meaning that if two people on the same machine want to play the same game, they either have to use the same account (not ideal), or, in the case of my household, the same person has to buy something again that they’ve already paid for. This is, quite frankly, a shady business practice and I do wonder if the EU trading standards board are entirely aware of it.</p>
</li>
</ol>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>First point is = Not true. I’ve played plenty of games offline since steam showed it’s face alongside HL2. You didn’t know you can do that?</p>
<p>Second point) What exactly is your situation that is bothersome? You want to play a single player game in your own account or multilayer account and don’t want to share? I don’t understand. Just like if you were to buy a hard copy you buy the license which is technically only for the person who bought the game. Like going out to a restaurant to eat. You buy a meal for one person, but you can share if you like. If you want the full meal buy your own.</p>
<p>Also, I have no issues with steam. Shady doesn’t really come to mind when I start steam up and jump on any of the games I can play for the rest of my life without worrying about scratching up the hard copy disc. I guess Steam is meant for a single gamer. Not household family leisure gaming.</p>
<pre><code>PS. I haven't read through the whole thread so I do apologize if I'm repeating what others have said.</code></pre>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/your-opinion-on-steam/6875/49">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/your-opinion-on-steam/6875/49</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Apr 2011 17:18:58 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-6875-49</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/your-opinion-on-steam/6875.rss">Your opinion on Steam</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Your opinion on Steam</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Someonerandm]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Companies don’t like other companies getting monopolies.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/your-opinion-on-steam/6875/48">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/your-opinion-on-steam/6875/48</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Apr 2011 15:21:03 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-6875-48</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/your-opinion-on-steam/6875.rss">Your opinion on Steam</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Your opinion on Steam</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Orpheon]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I love Steam, and I can’t imagine PC gaming without it anymore. The thing that bugs ME, is that in this day and age, when Steam controls 50 to 70% of the digital distribution market, companies like EA are still using ass-backwards ways of online play like forcing you to register with freaking gamespy of all things. They already are selling games and offering demos through Steam, couldn’t they just work with Valve a little more and use Steam for their multiplayer? Or is Valve just keeping it for themselves? Either way, I wish more games would better integrate with Steam.</p>
<p>Some people might not want PC gaming to become too consolized, and neither do I, but there’s really no benefit to signing up for dozens of different services to play each online game you own.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/your-opinion-on-steam/6875/47">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/your-opinion-on-steam/6875/47</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Apr 2011 06:43:37 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-6875-47</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/your-opinion-on-steam/6875.rss">Your opinion on Steam</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Your opinion on Steam</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Skilgannon]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><span class="mention">@someonerandom</span>: You shouldn’t <span class="bbcode-i">need</span> additional software to play a game, this is the problem I have with it. Especially if the game isn’t MP like HL2. Remember Half-Life? Didn’t need anything else to run that. Black &amp; White? Nope. Commandos 2? Nyet.</p>
<p>Also, this household only has one pc. My steam account contains games that have all been bought for me (birthday and xmas presents), all except one by my dad. Thusly, the games are all on one machine. If he should choose to want to play any of the games I own, my dad either has to use my account (neither of us want that due to friends networking and achievements) or BUY THE GAMES AGAIN. Which is bullshit. He’s already bought the games once, why should he have to pay again for something he’s already paid for?</p>
<p><a class="mention" href="/u/medevilae">@medevilae</a>: If you can’t keep it civil, don’t post please. But in reply to you, see above.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/your-opinion-on-steam/6875/46">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/your-opinion-on-steam/6875/46</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Apr 2011 03:55:18 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-6875-46</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/your-opinion-on-steam/6875.rss">Your opinion on Steam</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Your opinion on Steam</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[bobbo]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>steam can get hot</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/your-opinion-on-steam/6875/45">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/your-opinion-on-steam/6875/45</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Apr 2011 03:27:42 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-6875-45</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/your-opinion-on-steam/6875.rss">Your opinion on Steam</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Your opinion on Steam</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Medevilae]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="mgmartin">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/m/848f3c/40.png" class="avatar"> mgmartin:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I believe you are mistaken, sir.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Steam did bog down my ol’ mono core 7600 GT computer back in 05’, but it’s came a long way- and so has my computer.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/your-opinion-on-steam/6875/44">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/your-opinion-on-steam/6875/44</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Apr 2011 01:53:07 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-6875-44</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/your-opinion-on-steam/6875.rss">Your opinion on Steam</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Your opinion on Steam</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Someonerandm]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Not about the first part at least.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/your-opinion-on-steam/6875/43">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/your-opinion-on-steam/6875/43</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Apr 2011 00:04:57 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-6875-43</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/your-opinion-on-steam/6875.rss">Your opinion on Steam</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Your opinion on Steam</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[mgmartin]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="fx.">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 fx.:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Only for you.</p>
<p>Those must’ve been hella slow computers then.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I believe you are mistaken, sir.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/your-opinion-on-steam/6875/42">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/your-opinion-on-steam/6875/42</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 07 Apr 2011 23:51:53 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-6875-42</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/your-opinion-on-steam/6875.rss">Your opinion on Steam</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Your opinion on Steam</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[BaTz281]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Door">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/d/b4bc9f/40.png" class="avatar"> Door:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>They’ve said on numerous occasions that if they were to become bankrupt and Steam would become defunct; they would release one last patch for Steam to remove the need for an internet connection at launch.<br>
While this would be ideal from a consumer perspective, they’ve remained reserved about this and rightly so; they’re making tonnes of money and not really anywhere near bankruptcy.</p>
<p>My opinion on Steam is that for all of it’s flaws, I’ve grown to like it; it has community features that I use to quite an extent, and it’s a central hub for my games library. If the internet is out I just play something like TTD if Steam decides that I’m not allowed to play my games.<br>
While the above is frustrating, it’s also a godsend; I’d merely launch that game to be bored with it on the occasions that it <span class="bbcode-i">has</span> happened.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I researched this myself a week or so ago, and you will find MANY threads on the Valve forums (with NO official responses) about this topic.  In other words, the “last patch to remove DRM” is an unfounded rumor that nobody can find proof for.  Evidently, there was a vague mention in a sidebar of some magazine by Gabe Newell (that’s the best I’ve found as far as “fact”) but no one can seem to remember the magazine, issue #, etc.</p>
<p>Wish Valve would have an official standpoint on this. I think I’ll just install Steam on my home server and download every game I own to it so I can do a backup.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/your-opinion-on-steam/6875/41">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/your-opinion-on-steam/6875/41</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 07 Apr 2011 23:25:06 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-6875-41</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/your-opinion-on-steam/6875.rss">Your opinion on Steam</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Your opinion on Steam</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Medevilae]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Skilgannon">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/s/edb3f5/40.png" class="avatar"> Skilgannon:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>blah blah offline mode blah blah</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>What is this, 1995? If you don’t have a internet connection or one you can rely on, get a fucking console you dunce.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/your-opinion-on-steam/6875/40">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/your-opinion-on-steam/6875/40</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 07 Apr 2011 20:27:54 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-6875-40</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/your-opinion-on-steam/6875.rss">Your opinion on Steam</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Your opinion on Steam</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[dookiebot]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>When Steam first launched oh man was that program buggy. I didn’t care much for it at the time. As a matter of fact the only thing it had going for it was I didn’t have to play TFC on <a href="http://WON.net" rel="nofollow noopener">WON.net</a> anymore.<br>
Over time it got better and I seriously hate to think what the PC gaming industry would look like today if Steam didn’t exist. It has benefited Valve to work on their games without pressure by a publisher to release the game and “Patch it later”, it has allowed small time developers to do well for themselves who would have otherwise been ignored by big corporate publishers, It has grown into a community tool for gamers, ect  there are other things it has done to change the eroding landscape of PC gaming.</p>
<p>Just the other week I was looking at some games on my Steam account I have paid money for and haven’t installed yet (due to the great deals they have time to time). WTF. Dunno if that is a pro or a con. A Pro for the Dev for sure, they got free money so to speak.</p>
<p>My biggest con is different accounts on the same computer. One person’s Steam account “sees” the other games on a different account and it’s annoying. For example L4D2 was in my favorites so when my 7 year old logs into his steam account my L4D2 game is also in his favorites. Also I see his “Plants Vs Zombies” in my favorites even though I don’t own the game.  Valve bandaided this issue with allowing users to set categories. So I worked out a back ally solution so I don’t see my kids games and they don’t see mine using categories.</p>
<p>And if Valve closed their doors tomorrow and shut steam down? There would be a crack out in 2 days so I am not worried about that. I would be more worried about my account info being hacked and stolen before that happened.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/your-opinion-on-steam/6875/39">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/your-opinion-on-steam/6875/39</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 07 Apr 2011 20:11:05 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-6875-39</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/your-opinion-on-steam/6875.rss">Your opinion on Steam</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Your opinion on Steam</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[rx33gundam]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I love steam.</p>
<p>I’m in the Philippines and I’m telling you now that there are no local game store even in our largest MALL. I found no Gamestop even in our Wallmart. NOBODY EVER TRIED TO SELL GAMES BECAUSE THERE WERE NO CUSTOMERS. Most Filipino gamers are poor. They can’t buy games $30+. I remember a game store (where I usually buy) closing down because of lack of customers. Most Filipinos complained that the games are not worth it and will pollute your mind. (bullshit?) I interviewed Filipino gamers with internet connection. VERY FEW of them have steam. We all agreed that steam was the best thing that happened to us.</p>
<p>I didn’t even discovered HL2 until 2007 when we got internet connection. I discovered steam and used it to buy my games. I didn’t have to spend money on transportation to get my game. Also… my dvd rom got busted but since I only have to download… a dvd rom wasn’t needed. The time of the downloads are just about the same as traveling back and forth and installing it to my computer.</p>
<p>BTW… Philippines is not listed under the countries with xbox live. WE ARE MISSING OUT!!! We steam owners know about other services other countries have that we don’t. We never played Halo, Call of Duty or any other great xbox multiplayer games online. We can only wait for it to come to PC. I’m still waiting for Halo 3 to come to PC so I can stop playing the campaign and have some real fun with multiplayer. LAN? like 1 house can own 8 xbox and 8 discs and 8 TVs and 8 people who knows how to play, interested, or even knows halo at all.</p>
<p>Steam offers free service, unlike xbox live which is 50$ a year? excluding the internet with that $50. Xbox live and steam are different platforms but still… we want to experience both.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/your-opinion-on-steam/6875/38">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/your-opinion-on-steam/6875/38</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 07 Apr 2011 16:37:36 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-6875-38</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/your-opinion-on-steam/6875.rss">Your opinion on Steam</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Your opinion on Steam</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Deutscher_Scharfschu]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>the only thing i don’t like is every time i install non-valve software via steam i have to install C++ 2005 redistributable. i swear at one point i had like 8 of them installed at once. five of which were the same version too. I just want this issue addressed.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/your-opinion-on-steam/6875/37">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/your-opinion-on-steam/6875/37</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 07 Apr 2011 16:04:20 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-6875-37</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/your-opinion-on-steam/6875.rss">Your opinion on Steam</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Your opinion on Steam</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[mankyman6]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Skilgannon">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/s/edb3f5/40.png" class="avatar"> Skilgannon:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Yeah, but it’s a bs “feature” and completely unfair to the consumer. You may have your gaming PC not connected to the net to try and keep it free from viruses, or you may not be interested in multiplayer, so don’t see a point to connecting it in the first place, yet you are forced to have to download and install Steam to play single player games like HL2 which could just as easily run off the disk.</p>
<p>Take the Orange Box for example. 4 out of those 5 games are offline only games, yet you are still forced to use Steam to play them, even if you don’t install TF2. All the content for those games is on the disc, so why should the consumer be forced to download a piece of software they neither need, nor probably want?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>However, this is an age where almost everyone in modern countries have an internet connection, so Steam is not generally frowned upon for it’s internet only service.</p>
<p>I don’t mean to sound like a hippy here, but no discs means saving on natural resources, albeit a little.</p>
<p>Also, if you’re not connecting to the internet in fear of viruses then you must not be smart enough to figure out what’s a damned virus and what’s not. Hell, I’ve been downloading torrents since I’ve figured out how and I haven’t received a single virus from it, why? Because I’m actually smart enough to figure out what’s safe and what’s not.</p>
<p>Steam is the best piece of software I have on my computer, second best only to Windows.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/your-opinion-on-steam/6875/36">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/your-opinion-on-steam/6875/36</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 07 Apr 2011 15:37:03 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-6875-36</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/your-opinion-on-steam/6875.rss">Your opinion on Steam</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Your opinion on Steam</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Someonerandm]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Its an online service. It requires internet. Deal with it. Valve wants to centralize, get more steam users and thus grow. Its only reasonable.</p>
<p>Also, it is in no way unfair to the consumer. Unfair is if you payed for something and then without warning discovered you needed internet. Telling you “you need internet to play this”, and then requiring it is in no way unfair.</p>
<p>EDIT: Just read the point about steam requiring purchasing two games. What? If you are on one computer, you need only one game. If someone moves away, you’d have to buy it again anyway. There is nothing problematic about that, and certainly nothing against trade agreements there. Again, its all in the not so fine print, nothing shady, and not even debatably unethical.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/your-opinion-on-steam/6875/35">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/your-opinion-on-steam/6875/35</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 07 Apr 2011 15:32:50 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-6875-35</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/your-opinion-on-steam/6875.rss">Your opinion on Steam</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Your opinion on Steam</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Skilgannon]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Yeah, but it’s a bs “feature” and completely unfair to the consumer. You may have your gaming PC not connected to the net to try and keep it free from viruses, or you may not be interested in multiplayer, so don’t see a point to connecting it in the first place, yet you are forced to have to download and install Steam to play single player games like HL2 which could just as easily run off the disk.</p>
<p>Take the Orange Box for example. 4 out of those 5 games are offline only games, yet you are still forced to use Steam to play them, even if you don’t install TF2. All the content for those games is on the disc, so why should the consumer be forced to download a piece of software they neither need, nor probably want?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/your-opinion-on-steam/6875/34">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/your-opinion-on-steam/6875/34</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 07 Apr 2011 13:12:39 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-6875-34</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/your-opinion-on-steam/6875.rss">Your opinion on Steam</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Your opinion on Steam</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[jambo]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Skilgannon">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/s/edb3f5/40.png" class="avatar"> Skilgannon:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I’m not talking about previously installed games, I’m talking about brand new ones. Read again.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>It’s a digital service, of course if there isn’t an Internet connection you won’t be able to get the game. That’s not Valve’s fault.</p>
<p>That’s like signing up for streaming online radio and then complaining to the site when you tell them you don’t have an Internet connection.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/your-opinion-on-steam/6875/33">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/your-opinion-on-steam/6875/33</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 07 Apr 2011 13:05:45 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-6875-33</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/your-opinion-on-steam/6875.rss">Your opinion on Steam</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Your opinion on Steam</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[fx1]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="mgmartin">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/m/848f3c/40.png" class="avatar"> mgmartin:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Steam is a great platform, but there are some problems with it.</p>
<p>It´s unstable and slow, and tends to freeze up all the time. Happens on every computer I´ve used it on.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Only for you.</p>
<p>Those must’ve been hella slow computers then.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/your-opinion-on-steam/6875/32">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/your-opinion-on-steam/6875/32</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 07 Apr 2011 12:30:52 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-6875-32</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/your-opinion-on-steam/6875.rss">Your opinion on Steam</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Your opinion on Steam</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[mgmartin]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Steam is a great platform, but there are some problems with it.</p>
<p>It´s unstable and slow, and tends to freeze up all the time. Happens on every computer I´ve used it on.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/your-opinion-on-steam/6875/31">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/your-opinion-on-steam/6875/31</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 07 Apr 2011 09:57:59 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-6875-31</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/your-opinion-on-steam/6875.rss">Your opinion on Steam</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
