<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>comunity project - black mesa stories (consept)</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/comunity-project-black-mesa-stories-consept/11767</link>
    <description>(conespt stage)

black mesa stories is to be a set of short stories of survival in the Black mesa research facility, problem I can&#39;t map and I have fail to learn many times so I am posting this hear as the concept for a mod that focuses on many characters and their struggles to get out of the BM facility.


story one: the last shift
main character: a security guard named ________
start weapons: pistol
plot: the last shift starts with ________ arriving at his post in a top side tram hub. after a few minutes watching people enter and leave the facility via the tram the cascade happens, this is shown by a eye hound teleporting into a tram car that is about to enter the facility, its attack blows out all the windows of the car and kills the 3 passengers(2 scientists and a gaurd). at this point the armory behind ________ opens and a emergency lock down is triggered. at the same time ________ is called back to the main hub, at this point its all about getting to the other gaurds and regrouping to reinforce and protect the science team. over this story the main character runs mostly zombies and hound eyes. the only human enemy the main character runs into during this part is a half crazed scientist that has taken up a shotgun and is shooting anything that moves. the main part of this story ends with the main character getting to the security hub to find it mostly over run by zombies.. at this point he is guided by one of the surviving guards to get up to the com center of the hub and call the hecu in to clean up this mess. the story ends with that call.


story two: clean up
main character: a standard hecu grunt
start weapons: mp5, glock and 2 grenades
plot: clean up starts a hour after the last shift with one of the military teams entering the compound, on entry the player is told all none hecu personnel are to be considered hostile until told other wise. at this point the main character along with 5 other hecu grunts and a lav enter a above ground part of the BM facility this area is mostly over run by headcrabs and some zombies, an easy clear. the characters team then enters the facility via a large cargo ellevator (lav is on it), upon getting to the bottom they LAV is blocked and the team must move through the cargo point to the main area 2 dormitories.. this is where you run into the first group of survivors who you unfortunately have to gun down do to orders. as you move through the facility you mission changes from clean up to get to the security hub and reprogram the automated defenses of the facility. during this part the player ends up on the same path as they did during the first story only this time it is destroyed and most hall ways are in accessible forcing the player to take another path. upon getting to the security hub your squad is ambushed by the surviving security force of which you easily over run. you then make your way up to the com center where you run into a guard(first story) that as locked the door. at this point a A-grunt teleports in and the gaurd fires upon it only to be badly hurt, the player must then kill the a-grunt and disable the security system(big red button). this story ends with the hecu grunt getting shot by the wounded guard.


story three: dr. not a dr.
main character: sector A scientist
plot: this story starts in the middle of clean up, with you being a scientist that was hurt in a blast caused by the cascade. in this story the player isn&#39;t armed and only gets a pistol near the end. in this story your objective is to get from the safe point your team has set up to the security hub and warn the guard force that the hecu are on a torch and burn op not a rescue mission. through this story you do not directly play a role in the fighting but instead must sneak your way through vents and dark areas to avoid the fighting all together that is till you get to a security check point near the end that still has a hand gun in it. once you get to this point that hand gun will be your only weapon while you can gain ammo for it you do not run into many hecu and the ones you do you can&#39;t takes weapons(example your on a tram port and tehy are in a tram). any way as you fight your way to the security hub you make it there just in time to see the end of a battle between 4 hecu grunts and 3 hurt and badly armed guards. once you clear the hecu, you move to the com room in hopes of warning the others.. you get there in time to see the guard kill the grunt.


story four: help
main character: teh gaurd
weapons:pistol, revolver, shotgun.(picked up at the end of the first story)
plot: story starts off with you waking up in the com room with a scientist near you, the scientist explains that the hecu teams are getting there asses handed to them and they you need to get out of the facility....

(this is the point where I realized I will never be able to do this and I doubt any one here will want to pick up on this as I suck at detail with my ideas)</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 01 Dec 2012 21:36:47 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Source 1</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/comunity-project-black-mesa-stories-consept/11767.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>comunity project - black mesa stories (consept)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[D3lta]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I’d suggest you look up basic video tutorials of hammer, and then decompile some Half-Life 2 or Black Mesa maps and figure out how they did things.Thats what I did then :p.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/comunity-project-black-mesa-stories-consept/11767/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/comunity-project-black-mesa-stories-consept/11767/5</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 01 Dec 2012 21:36:47 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11767-5</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/comunity-project-black-mesa-stories-consept/11767.rss">comunity project - black mesa stories (consept)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>comunity project - black mesa stories (consept)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[darkone]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>wouldn’t need hand models for the scientist for the most part, only weapon he woudl gets a pistol near the end. the gaurd just use a blue skin for the hands, the only problem would be the hecu grunt… which has the most problems for his section.</p>
<p>If I could map or even under stand how to map (yes I have tried learning) I would be making this as I suck at putting ideas on paper but I can’t map.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/comunity-project-black-mesa-stories-consept/11767/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/comunity-project-black-mesa-stories-consept/11767/4</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 01 Dec 2012 02:14:12 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11767-4</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/comunity-project-black-mesa-stories-consept/11767.rss">comunity project - black mesa stories (consept)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>comunity project - black mesa stories (consept)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[D3lta]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="ojcoolj">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/o/ecb155/40.png" class="avatar"> ojcoolj:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Considering that there’s no viewmodels for Guards, Marines or Scientists and making one would be a pain, if this does happen you’ll have to just believe that they magically have orange armor on their hands</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>There is a shitload of HEV hands on gamebanana…</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/comunity-project-black-mesa-stories-consept/11767/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/comunity-project-black-mesa-stories-consept/11767/3</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2012 20:59:10 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11767-3</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/comunity-project-black-mesa-stories-consept/11767.rss">comunity project - black mesa stories (consept)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>comunity project - black mesa stories (consept)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[ojcoolj]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Considering that there’s no viewmodels for Guards, Marines or Scientists and making one would be a pain, if this does happen you’ll have to just believe that they magically have orange armor on their hands</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/comunity-project-black-mesa-stories-consept/11767/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/comunity-project-black-mesa-stories-consept/11767/2</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2012 07:31:45 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11767-2</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/comunity-project-black-mesa-stories-consept/11767.rss">comunity project - black mesa stories (consept)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>comunity project - black mesa stories (consept)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[darkone]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>(conespt stage)</p>
<p>black mesa stories is to be a set of short stories of survival in the Black mesa research facility, problem I can’t map and I have fail to learn many times so I am posting this hear as the concept for a mod that focuses on many characters and their struggles to get out of the BM facility.</p>
<p>story one: the last shift<br>
main character: a security guard named ________<br>
start weapons: pistol<br>
plot: the last shift starts with ________ arriving at his post in a top side tram hub. after a few minutes watching people enter and leave the facility via the tram the cascade happens, this is shown by a eye hound teleporting into a tram car that is about to enter the facility, its attack blows out all the windows of the car and kills the 3 passengers(2 scientists and a gaurd). at this point the armory behind ________ opens and a emergency lock down is triggered. at the same time ________ is called back to the main hub, at this point its all about getting to the other gaurds and regrouping to reinforce and protect the science team. over this story the main character runs mostly zombies and hound eyes. the only human enemy the main character runs into during this part is a half crazed scientist that has taken up a shotgun and is shooting anything that moves. the main part of this story ends with the main character getting to the security hub to find it mostly over run by zombies… at this point he is guided by one of the surviving guards to get up to the com center of the hub and call the hecu in to clean up this mess. the story ends with that call.</p>
<p>story two: clean up<br>
main character: a standard hecu grunt<br>
start weapons: mp5, glock and 2 grenades<br>
plot: clean up starts a hour after the last shift with one of the military teams entering the compound, on entry the player is told all none hecu personnel are to be considered hostile until told other wise. at this point the main character along with 5 other hecu grunts and a lav enter a above ground part of the BM facility this area is mostly over run by headcrabs and some zombies, an easy clear. the characters team then enters the facility via a large cargo ellevator (lav is on it), upon getting to the bottom they LAV is blocked and the team must move through the cargo point to the main area 2 dormitories… this is where you run into the first group of survivors who you unfortunately have to gun down do to orders. as you move through the facility you mission changes from clean up to get to the security hub and reprogram the automated defenses of the facility. during this part the player ends up on the same path as they did during the first story only this time it is destroyed and most hall ways are in accessible forcing the player to take another path. upon getting to the security hub your squad is ambushed by the surviving security force of which you easily over run. you then make your way up to the com center where you run into a guard(first story) that as locked the door. at this point a A-grunt teleports in and the gaurd fires upon it only to be badly hurt, the player must then kill the a-grunt and disable the security system(big red button). this story ends with the hecu grunt getting shot by the wounded guard.</p>
<p>story three: dr. not a dr.<br>
main character: sector A scientist<br>
plot: this story starts in the middle of clean up, with you being a scientist that was hurt in a blast caused by the cascade. in this story the player isn’t armed and only gets a pistol near the end. in this story your objective is to get from the safe point your team has set up to the security hub and warn the guard force that the hecu are on a torch and burn op not a rescue mission. through this story you do not directly play a role in the fighting but instead must sneak your way through vents and dark areas to avoid the fighting all together that is till you get to a security check point near the end that still has a hand gun in it. once you get to this point that hand gun will be your only weapon while you can gain ammo for it you do not run into many hecu and the ones you do you can’t takes weapons(example your on a tram port and tehy are in a tram). any way as you fight your way to the security hub you make it there just in time to see the end of a battle between 4 hecu grunts and 3 hurt and badly armed guards. once you clear the hecu, you move to the com room in hopes of warning the others… you get there in time to see the guard kill the grunt.</p>
<p>story four: help<br>
main character: teh gaurd<br>
weapons:pistol, revolver, shotgun.(picked up at the end of the first story)<br>
plot: story starts off with you waking up in the com room with a scientist near you, the scientist explains that the hecu teams are getting there asses handed to them and they you need to get out of the facility…</p>
<p>(this is the point where I realized I will never be able to do this and I doubt any one here will want to pick up on this as I suck at detail with my ideas)</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/comunity-project-black-mesa-stories-consept/11767/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/comunity-project-black-mesa-stories-consept/11767/1</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2012 03:00:21 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11767-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/comunity-project-black-mesa-stories-consept/11767.rss">comunity project - black mesa stories (consept)</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
