<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Nightmare</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/nightmare/8348</link>
    <description>[b](What ever I wrote inside this form here is what I thought in a first person perspective at the time)[/b] - The &quot;dots&quot; were NOT an outline, they seemed to be in place of what it would look like if something happened. They were sort of orangy-yellow and literaly dots, not circles. 

I&#39;m in a house near a beach [b](rental or owned I don&#39;t know)[/b]. Across the &quot;beach&quot; is a body of water [b](I thought it was an ocean, then I saw the river.)[/b] and for some reason I can see a city over there. I&#39;m looking at the sky for whatever reason when suddenly the skylights up with first a little bunch of orange(yellow-orange? Yellow?) dots in one little part of the sky [b](from a single plane? I thought it was the usual plane that caries people around, then there was another dot right beside it and it&#39;s &quot;I&#39;m here&quot; lights went out and there were a few falling dots)[/b], then the entire sky is sort of filled with these dots... but the dots are spaced out across the sky in a reasonable manner and [b](there is some sort of battle?)[/b]. [i][I don&#39;t recall which came first, a quick flashing of the sky/clouds or the sots being arranged to slightly resemble a motar firing/missle launch][/i] After something is launched [b](At first I thought it was at another plane and I want the battle to keep going to help save us.)[/b] Now when the sky lit up the first time I immediatly tried to get in contact with my [relative who is a cop] I try to find my mom&#39;s cell phone becasue I don&#39;t have one. I scamble all over the house and in a radius around the house, looking for my mom&#39;s phone. But I never do find it. Eventualy I pour out how much I love my mom to her (&quot;...becasue I just should have said this years ago...&quot;). Now the next time I look up into the sky the MOST of sky flashes, I don&#39;t know why. I&#39;m standing on the wodden steps that leads down to the beach, I see an enveloping flash of light and some expanding crater. Everything is slow motion. Knowing what is happening I lay down on the space between the door and the stars (I gave up.) and then I try to scamble inside (I regret giving up), but I know it is too late. As my fate approches I try to scream, but I know it is too late. I wake up and I don&#39;t move at all at first. My mouth is open to continue a scream that was cut off. I am afraid of what I saw. 

For I saw a nuke. 

[/panic]</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 21 Jan 2012 19:37:20 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Off Topic</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/nightmare/8348.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Nightmare</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Eric_Fong]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>The evening early I was taking my little nap and had a dream about me and my family go out for Picnic, suddenly we got attacked by Swarms of fire ants. The nightmare end with me and my father being the survivors.</p>
<p>I can still feel them crawling in my skin lol.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/nightmare/8348/42">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/nightmare/8348/42</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 21 Jan 2012 19:37:20 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8348-42</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/nightmare/8348.rss">Nightmare</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Nightmare</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[eyvn]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I used to have nightmares all the time when I was a kid.  The worst was when a skeleton came into my room and attacked me in my bed (probably after some faithful toy turned on me, this was how many of my nightmares went). I was screaming and trying to fight the skeleton off when I saw three horrid creatures come through the door.  As it turned out the skeleton was really my mom trying to wake me up and the creatures in the doorway were my brothers who had run to my room to see what was happening.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/nightmare/8348/41">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/nightmare/8348/41</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2012 18:08:18 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8348-41</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/nightmare/8348.rss">Nightmare</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Nightmare</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Bolteh]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I hardly ever remember a dream or nightmare. I often wake up with that feeling that I had one, but I simply can’t recall what it was about.</p>
<p>The only one I remember vividly was when I was very young (like 7 or 8 or so). Nothing really happened, apart from me being at the bottom of a sewer, with a couple of mutant rats staring down at me from the hole above.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/nightmare/8348/40">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/nightmare/8348/40</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2012 14:00:18 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8348-40</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/nightmare/8348.rss">Nightmare</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Nightmare</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[amazingcomedy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Once, I had a really odd dream. My dreams tend to be very abstract, like once, I dreamed of a fat guy getting beat up by two police officers for trying to kill a toaster (I know, laugh as much as you want.), but once, I had this really weird dream.<br>
I was in like some sort of abandoned house, but it looked like the one I was living in at the time, just abandoned, in ruins, etc. And on the walls, there was writing, it looked like spray paint writing. The writing was pretty disturbing, and almost satanic. There was a drawing of some sort of “thing” that had a VERY weird looking head, with glowing red eyes. I remember just looking at this thing, feeling terrified about it. Then, I felt this big rush of fear, and ran out of the house. That’s when I woke up. In sleep paralysis.<br>
I remember opening my eyes, and looking forward. And that “thing” that was in the drawing was now in front of me. Except it looked real, like skin and everything, but it was still in darkness, with those red eyes. And then, it disappeared. Scary huh?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/nightmare/8348/39">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/nightmare/8348/39</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2012 02:38:35 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8348-39</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/nightmare/8348.rss">Nightmare</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Nightmare</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Krazor]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I get sleep paralysis a lot, and it used to be okay, (if a little freaky), until this:</p>
<p>I sleep on my back on two fairly fluffy pillows that lift my head just high enough off of the bed that I am kind of looking forward, instead of straight up at the ceiling. One morning, a little after two, I wake up sleep paralyzed. My eyes can only open halfway, and I can’t move, or make any noise. My eyes slowly adjust as I wait to wake up completely. As they do, I realize I am not alone.</p>
<p>Standing in the doorway to the immediate right of my bed is a dark, human figure. Nothing remarkable, or particularly horrific about. But the fact that it’s in my room is disconcerting. You see, I lock my room thoroughly every night before I get in bed. And yet, it’s in. It’s in, and it’s watching me. Closely. Like it’s been there for a long time. If it wanted to, it could reach out from where it stood, and grab my foot with ease.</p>
<p>This thought occurs to me, and I draw in a huge, sharp breath to gasp, or yell, but when I try to cry out, all that comes out is a long hard exhale, kind of like a little hum through my nose. A whimper.</p>
<p>This is taking way longer than usual. Now the figure twitches just once- an unnatural sort of shiver and walks with decided urgency to the opposite side of my bed and stops. He’s standing right over me, but my eyelids won’t open enough. I can’t look up to see him. I can very clearly, however, see the silvery glint off of the knife in his right hand.</p>
<p>Abruptly, he lowers his face right into mine. I won’t waste any more text than I already have describing what he looked like, but know that at this moment I can recall every detail as if it were happening now. He wasn’t some hell beast, or demon, or anything like that. He was just a man. And he was very, very angry. His teeth were clenched HARD, and his brow was bent. All of a sudden, his knife raised out of my line of sight, and then plunged, directly into my gut. Hard. I swear to god, it felt in my mind like the mattress compressed underneath me and bounced back from the force.</p>
<p>At the same time that happened, I was entirely awake. My eyes tore open as far as they would go, and I loudly sucked down a lungful of air that would have shamed a drowning man. I balled both hands into fists above my stomach and pulled the air at the same, very specific place- one over the other- around the grip of a knife that wasn’t there. I bolted upright, and tore off my shirt with one hand, turned on the light with the other, and spent a solid minute inspecting my abdomen. I didn’t sleep the rest of the night.</p>
<p>I rarely have dreams I remember. But when I do, I remember them extremely clearly. In cases like this, I wish I didn’t.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/nightmare/8348/38">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/nightmare/8348/38</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2012 02:09:56 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8348-38</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/nightmare/8348.rss">Nightmare</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Nightmare</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Kairouseki]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I think I’ve only had one lucid dream in my life and I’m not even sure if it was one. I mean from what I’ve heard lucid dreams happen when you become aware that you’re dreaming but I do that a lot and it still doesn’t become lucid. I’ll be like “This is a dream, now do x” but I won’t do it  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/frowning.png?v=9" title=":frowning:" class="emoji" alt=":frowning:">  .</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/nightmare/8348/37">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/nightmare/8348/37</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jan 2012 21:36:40 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8348-37</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/nightmare/8348.rss">Nightmare</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Nightmare</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[BahamutBBob]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I’ve never had sleep paralysis or a lucid dream.  It’s also been a while since I’ve had a nightmare.</p>
<p>Maybe I’ll try and force some lucid dreams, just to see what it’s like.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/nightmare/8348/36">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/nightmare/8348/36</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jan 2012 21:00:03 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8348-36</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/nightmare/8348.rss">Nightmare</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Nightmare</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[sersoft]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Never had sleep paralysis, if I wake up too fast though I usually feel like going back to sleep around 3pm for a couple of hours.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/nightmare/8348/35">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/nightmare/8348/35</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jan 2012 17:12:33 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8348-35</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/nightmare/8348.rss">Nightmare</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Nightmare</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Kairouseki]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="(rot)(fodder">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 (rot)(fodder:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Damn, so that is what that was. One level of my worst nightmare was like that, although now I really don’t know what to think about it, Sleep paralysis seems to occour in people who are awake?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I think sleep paralysis only happens when you’re awake, there might be another name for it when you’re still asleep.</p>
<p>Sleep paralysis is pretty much you are physically awake but your brain is slow to catch up. Your brain paralyzes you while you’re asleep so you don’t act out what you’re dreaming about. So when your brain is lagging behind it hasn’t unparalized you. And also since your brain is still technically asleep it sees the environment that you’re sleeping in but it causes dreamlike hallucinations.</p>
<p>But even though I understand what it is it’s still fucking scary when you’re in the moment.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/nightmare/8348/34">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/nightmare/8348/34</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jan 2012 19:29:58 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8348-34</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/nightmare/8348.rss">Nightmare</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Nightmare</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[geekofalltrades]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I remember a grand total of three dreams I’ve ever had, and only one of them was a nightmare.  It’s the only nightmare I can ever remember having.  Brace yourselves for this shit:</p>
<p>I was surrounded by complete pitch black, but still somehow lit.  I could look down and see myself.  Anyway, I was turning around and around, looking for anything that wasn’t just pitch blackness, and at one point I turned around and there was someone standing nose to nose with me, and they went, “BOO!”  I woke up instantly with my entire body clenched up and just terrified.  That’s a true story.  I started laughing about four seconds later.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/nightmare/8348/33">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/nightmare/8348/33</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jan 2012 18:35:32 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8348-33</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/nightmare/8348.rss">Nightmare</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Nightmare</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[ac3d]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Bloodshot">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/b/839c29/40.png" class="avatar"> Bloodshot:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I was going to post about a nightmare I had a while back but then I thought “Fuck it, it’s way too long to write about”</p>
<p>So here’s my other one: I was flying around my house on a bed into pitch black rooms with red eyes.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p><img src="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/original/3X/0/1/018caa116c8e595a45aafe4be8583b012ca053c1.jpeg" alt="" data-base62-sha1="dHQF6LVh8uJlEfQZBQmV1kfkiJ" width="640" height="480"></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/nightmare/8348/32">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/nightmare/8348/32</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jan 2012 14:05:30 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8348-32</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/nightmare/8348.rss">Nightmare</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Nightmare</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Eric_Fong]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>^ Yup</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="sersoft">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/user_avatar/leakfree.org/sersoft/40/5837_2.png" class="avatar"> sersoft:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>One time while waking up from a lucid dream I just barely had time to move the sheets so that all the jizz went on the floor instead.</p>
<p>A lot less messy that way.</p>
<p>In normal passive dreams I’m either shoplifting or finding some crazy electronics at a second hand store somewhere.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Lucid dream is fun, no?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/nightmare/8348/31">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/nightmare/8348/31</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jan 2012 13:16:42 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8348-31</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/nightmare/8348.rss">Nightmare</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Nightmare</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Trigger_Proximity]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>So I guess this is now the Nightmare general thread?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/nightmare/8348/30">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/nightmare/8348/30</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jan 2012 09:14:51 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8348-30</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/nightmare/8348.rss">Nightmare</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Nightmare</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Nerdguy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I had a nightmare in which i was chased by a guy that looks like a rapist<br>
That nightmare never finished tho, but I got sleep paralyzed in return</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/nightmare/8348/29">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/nightmare/8348/29</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jan 2012 08:57:52 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8348-29</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/nightmare/8348.rss">Nightmare</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Nightmare</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[_rot_fodder]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I used to have reoccurring dreams about a dark forest. The trees were all tall and thin, and there wern’t any leaves except for the tops, where the branches were full, but the leaves were all dead. Different stuff happened depending on my dream, and there was a thin road that had wrought iron, lampposts somewhere in there, though I only ever saw the road a few times.</p>
<p>I do consistantly dream about a certain bridge that I used to have to cross every day while growing up. It doesn’t matter how good or bad my dream is, or how sure footed I feel, I am almost certainly going to end up in the river way below. Either it’s a gust of wind, or the bridge falls apart, or it becomes to slippery and the guard rails dissapear, but I am almost always going to fall off of it.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Kairouseki">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/k/57b2e6/40.png" class="avatar"> Kairouseki:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I don’t have nightmares very often. I’ve had sleep paralysis once though. Scary as hell. I woke up in the middle of the night not being able to move anything but my head (slightly) and I looked over and saw five or six people in shadows standing there looking at me. I tried to scream but couldn’t.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Damn, so that is what that was. One level of my worst nightmare was like that, although now I really don’t know what to think about it, Sleep paralysis seems to occour in people who are awake?</p>
<p>So my worst nightmare that I can remember. I used to sleep in a camper trailer during the summer out at my grandparents place, and this is where my dream took place. My dream happened in levels, and I don’t totally remember what happened on each one, or which order they all came in. There were about five though, if I recall correctly.</p>
<p>I would “wake up” in different versions of the camper I was sleeping in, and along with a sense of unease, something would be off slightly. The first time I think it was something simple like there was no bathroom door. Enough that I eventually would realise that it was a dream, and try to wake myself up though. I would “wake up”, except that each time I woke up stuff got more wrong, and scarier. At one point I woke up and the sky was a glowing liquid of some kind, another I woke up unable to move with a massive black cat stalking up to my bed. The only other one that I remember was when I woke up, there was no light at all outside and the camper door was wide open. There were creatures howling outside, so I got up to shut the door, and as I reached out for it I heard something jump out of the invisible foliage right beside the door.</p>
<p>I don’t remember which one I actually woke up on, the Black cat or the open door. When I did wake up though, my lungs were completely empty, and it felt like I had just came up out of water. I do not ever want to experience that again.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/nightmare/8348/28">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/nightmare/8348/28</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jan 2012 08:51:50 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8348-28</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/nightmare/8348.rss">Nightmare</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Nightmare</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Trigger_Proximity]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I had a dream recently. Not a nightmare as such but it still really disturbed me.<br>
I lost a friend to cancer a few months ago and basically this dream was me and some friends standing around talking and he was there too, just standing next to us not moving or saying anything, just staring forwards, ignoring everything that was going on. Nobody but me seemed to notice him standing there and it really disturbed me when I woke up.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/nightmare/8348/27">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/nightmare/8348/27</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jan 2012 06:58:40 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8348-27</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/nightmare/8348.rss">Nightmare</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Nightmare</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Bloodshot]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I was going to post about a nightmare I had a while back but then I thought “Fuck it, it’s way too long to write about”</p>
<p>So here’s my other one: I was flying around my house on a bed into pitch black rooms with red eyes.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/nightmare/8348/26">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/nightmare/8348/26</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jan 2012 04:25:04 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8348-26</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/nightmare/8348.rss">Nightmare</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Nightmare</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Eion_Kilant_739]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Ramirezoid">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/r/ba9def/40.png" class="avatar"> Ramirezoid:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I hate when you wake up from a nightmare but your brain doesn’t want to join you, and you end up paralyzed in bed for ten minutes unable to breathe or scream for help you’re not sure you even need</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>That must be terrible, good thing that has never happened to me. (I woke up motionless, not unable to move.)</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/nightmare/8348/25">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/nightmare/8348/25</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jan 2012 02:05:12 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8348-25</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/nightmare/8348.rss">Nightmare</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Nightmare</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Kairouseki]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I don’t have nightmares very often. I’ve had sleep paralysis once though. Scary as hell. I woke up in the middle of the night not being able to move anything but my head (slightly) and I looked over and saw five or six people in shadows standing there looking at me. I tried to scream but couldn’t.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/nightmare/8348/24">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/nightmare/8348/24</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jan 2012 01:47:46 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8348-24</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/nightmare/8348.rss">Nightmare</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Nightmare</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Siggs]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>FML</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/nightmare/8348/23">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/nightmare/8348/23</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jan 2012 01:41:23 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8348-23</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/nightmare/8348.rss">Nightmare</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Nightmare</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Triage]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I once had a nightmare that Slenderman was chasing me everywhere.</p>
<p>After that I started hallucinating. I still do.</p>
<p>FML</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/nightmare/8348/22">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/nightmare/8348/22</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jan 2012 01:02:09 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8348-22</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/nightmare/8348.rss">Nightmare</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Nightmare</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[k3nny1550]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Sometimes I’ll go through half of a day in a dream- imagining conversations with other people going badly, screwing up in various catastrophic ways, etc.</p>
<p>Then there was that one when the fucking ninja cloaking asshole from the original F.E.A.R. shocked me out of my sleep. I literally did that “instant waking skills” thing you see in lots of hollywood dream sequences.</p>
<p>I haven’t really had them lately though. Dunno why.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/nightmare/8348/21">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/nightmare/8348/21</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jan 2012 00:48:39 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8348-21</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/nightmare/8348.rss">Nightmare</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Nightmare</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[danielsangeo]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>My most vivid dreams always has me either walking through this outstanding haunted Halloween attraction, right before opening time where the actors are getting ready and there’s huge flood lights on everything; riding on a roller coaster where the car falls apart and I’m forced to hold onto the axles for the remainder of the ride, the hills getting very tall and steep as the ride progresses; or toilets.</p>
<p>Let me explain that last one.  I have a recurring dream about toilets either being installed where they shouldn’t be installed (such as on very large elevators/lifts that has other stuff like rows of seats, couches, or whatever without a door so you can see the masonry and floors going by the opening) or bathrooms in various states of filth and disrepair including toilets knocked off their base and needing to have another one replaced it and so on…  I do NOT know what this means but I’ve had the toilets dream so often that I’m starting to recognize it when I see it and I realize I’m dreaming…but I can’t change how things go in the dream.</p>
<p>Yeah.  I’m fucked up.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/nightmare/8348/20">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/nightmare/8348/20</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jan 2012 00:10:08 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8348-20</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/nightmare/8348.rss">Nightmare</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Nightmare</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Kaweebo]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I once had a nightmare that turned awesome where I fell into the lake in my neighborhood and almost drowned, but somehow I found that water backpack from Super Mario Sunshine and water jetpacked out.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/nightmare/8348/19">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/nightmare/8348/19</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 16 Jan 2012 23:49:03 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8348-19</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/nightmare/8348.rss">Nightmare</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Nightmare</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[sersoft]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>One time while waking up from a lucid dream I just barely had time to move the sheets so that all the jizz went on the floor instead.</p>
<p>A lot less messy that way.</p>
<p>In normal passive dreams I’m either shoplifting or finding some crazy electronics at a second hand store somewhere.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/nightmare/8348/18">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/nightmare/8348/18</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 16 Jan 2012 22:38:44 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8348-18</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/nightmare/8348.rss">Nightmare</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
