<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Can&#39;t change privacy on uploaded workshop addon</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/cant-change-privacy-on-uploaded-workshop-addon/15186</link>
    <description>Hello, I&#39;ve uploaded my Black Mesa addon to the workshop via the tool, and I cannot change it to public or friends-only because of the lack of a privacy change button. I can see change buttons on my other non-BMS addons and this issue is occuring across all of my devices, I&#39;ve tried using the Steam client, Chrome, and my mobile client on my iPad. The workshop URL is [url]https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=940555166[/url]. I&#39;ve tried reuploading the addon and trying different combinations of options in the uploader such as tags, no tags, uploading the image later, leaving out the description, etc. It&#39;d be much appreciated if someone could assist with this, thanks.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2017 07:13:44 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>In-game Issues</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/cant-change-privacy-on-uploaded-workshop-addon/15186.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Can&#39;t change privacy on uploaded workshop addon</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[CitadelCore]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><span class="bbcode-s">I fixed it temporarily by running the JavaScript function SelectVisibility(‘0’); in Chrome’s developer console (I’m a fullstack developer). This seems to be a problem on steam’s end.</span><br>
EDIT: I spoke too soon. Even though the request to <a href="https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/itemsetvisibility" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/itemsetvisibility</a> completes successfully and the “Hidden” tag disappears, it still cannot be accessed by the public.</p>
<p>Second edit: Apparently the addon isn’t even being downloaded by BMS?</p>
<p>[tt]saWorkshopBase::OnQuerySusbcribedAddons[/tt]<br>
[tt]You are subscribed to 3 addons.[/tt]<br>
[tt]---------------------------------------[/tt]<br>
[tt]UGC item: Wind Tunnel[/tt]<br>
[tt]UGC path:[/tt]<br>
[tt]UGC size: 0[/tt]</p>
<p>Third edit: It’s also worth noting that after the addon is uploaded the title is blank, the description is blank, and the image is blank unless I save UGC a second time, even though I provided valid information for all of those (including a valid 512x512px PNG thumbnail) in the uploader. And yes, the folder I selected does indeed contain my VPK, which is around 9mb.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/cant-change-privacy-on-uploaded-workshop-addon/15186/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/cant-change-privacy-on-uploaded-workshop-addon/15186/2</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2017 07:13:44 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-15186-2</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/cant-change-privacy-on-uploaded-workshop-addon/15186.rss">Can&#39;t change privacy on uploaded workshop addon</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Can&#39;t change privacy on uploaded workshop addon</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[CitadelCore]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Hello, I’ve uploaded my Black Mesa addon to the workshop via the tool, and I cannot change it to public or friends-only because of the lack of a privacy change button. I can see change buttons on my other non-BMS addons and this issue is occuring across all of my devices, I’ve tried using the Steam client, Chrome, and my mobile client on my iPad. The workshop URL is <a href="https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=940555166" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=940555166</a>. I’ve tried reuploading the addon and trying different combinations of options in the uploader such as tags, no tags, uploading the image later, leaving out the description, etc. It’d be much appreciated if someone could assist with this, thanks.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/cant-change-privacy-on-uploaded-workshop-addon/15186/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/cant-change-privacy-on-uploaded-workshop-addon/15186/1</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2017 20:56:30 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-15186-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/cant-change-privacy-on-uploaded-workshop-addon/15186.rss">Can&#39;t change privacy on uploaded workshop addon</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
