<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Many bugs\suggestions</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/many-bugs-suggestions/9973</link>
    <description>Bugs:
- The &quot;disable view bob&quot; option in the &quot;Black Mesa&quot; options section doesn&#39;t disable view bob because there is no view bob in the first place. It&#39;s weapon bob and should be renamed as such
- Audio stutters for me, but much less frequently after setting cl_forcepreload and sv_forcepreload to 1
- Under options -&gt; Keyboard -&gt; Advanced, fast weapon switch doesn&#39;t do anything, it doesn&#39;t even save.  I suggest removing it if you can, besides Black Mesa already has it&#39;s own option
- A  lot of the time there is a significant delay for weapons to go to the sprinting position, especially with the shotgun (for me atleast), as well as returning to the idle position
- Ignore input when loading, since when I&#39;m loading and I click a shot is fired off when the game loads
- Under options -&gt; combat difficulty, the easy option says that the computer helps you aim. This should be removed as BM has it&#39;s own option
- Enable creature gibbing should be renamed to &quot;Enable gibbing&quot; for clarity

Suggestions:
- Reduce the default amount of view roll and add view bob
- Add more recoil to the Glock
- Add a firing rate limiter to the Glock
- Add specularity to the green goop which appears on your gun/hands after killing something that bleeds green
- Increase green blood texture resolution
- Add crosshairs to grenades (haven&#39;t really thought this through)
- Unlock viewmodel_fov
- Make aim down sights disabled by default as it&#39;s only used on one weapon, doesn&#39;t really fit in, and furthermore is almost completely useless as the revolver has pinpoint accuracy anyways
- Add mouse over descriptions of all BM options, especially for things such as houndeye tinnitus and chromatic abberation which most people have no knowledge of
- Add &quot;Maximum FPS&quot; option under Black Mesa which would just set fps_max. I already have mine set to 120, matching my refresh rate, to prevent tearing, although it is a big helper in lowering CPU temps for people wanting that.
- Decrease options menu oppacity as it&#39;s hard to read some things, mainly the hardware DX level under advanced video options
- Remove the echo which happens when you click on something in the pause menu such as &quot;Load game&quot;, one beep at it&#39;s intended volume is enough imo
- Implement custom menu/subtitle font to match the HUD font elements more, the current font works but a better font would definately help with immersion

Can&#39;t think of anything else at the moment, but just want to say this mod is fantastic anyways and I can&#39;t thank you enough for it.

EDIT: The ladder is incredibly annoying, lots of people I know are having issues with it where they fall off and die.

EDIT 2: Explosive barrels shouldn&#39;t explode when you jump on them, it just makes no sense and leads to aggrevation.

EDIT 3: View rolll should happen when the player turns with his mouse, not jusst when strafing, and should have a dynamic magnitude based on the turn&#39;s tightness.

EDIT 4: Couple more bugs

- In this image notice how the shotgun is half illuminated by it&#39;s own light, it screws with immersion imo [url]https://img407.imageshack.us/img407/7758/72467312.png[/url]
- The injured scientist who offers to spin the circular platform for the train says go on without me when I initiallly went up to him, but he said the exact same thing when I was laterally close to him but not in the control room (on the track)
- The large creature with the flamethrower has really bad AI, doesn&#39;t even attempt to use it&#39;s flamethrowers when I&#39;m on the platform to activate the static charge. Additionally it&#39;s flamethrowers don&#39;t really illuminate much, unlike the rocket engine which was absolutely brilliant to watch.
- The railroad car turns aren&#39;t smooth at all, same with the train. For example, a 45 degree turn should be done in at minimum 45 steps, optimally 90, but it seems like 10 or so steps in BM, which makes it feel cheap. Additionally when the train is moving through the water waves from it&#39;s path would be nice.

Edit 5 (lol): The HEV voice could be refined in terms of picking up things. For example when I pick up 2 health packs at the same time I don&#39;t need the voice to say &quot;Power 50 percent&quot;, then &quot;Power 75 percent&quot; 1 second later. Just the latter would be needed.

EDIT 6: You can sprint on ladders, no need to explain why it should be removed (it doesn&#39;t even affect your speed).

EDIT 7: You can&#39;t scream out in pain 1 second after you got hit in the face with a grenade launcher.

EDIT 8: The yellow freight transit train&#39;s throttle doesn&#39;t even move.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 16 Sep 2012 17:38:09 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>In-game Issues (Mod)</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/many-bugs-suggestions/9973.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Many bugs\suggestions</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Pyroh]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>If only more people would respond though  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=9" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/many-bugs-suggestions/9973/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/many-bugs-suggestions/9973/3</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 16 Sep 2012 17:38:09 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9973-3</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/many-bugs-suggestions/9973.rss">Many bugs\suggestions</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Many bugs\suggestions</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[vktech]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Thanks for the input! I’m sure the developers appreciate it.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/many-bugs-suggestions/9973/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/many-bugs-suggestions/9973/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 16 Sep 2012 15:55:24 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9973-2</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/many-bugs-suggestions/9973.rss">Many bugs\suggestions</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Many bugs\suggestions</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Pyroh]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Bugs:</p>
<ul>
<li>The “disable view bob” option in the “Black Mesa” options section doesn’t disable view bob because there is no view bob in the first place. It’s weapon bob and should be renamed as such</li>
<li>Audio stutters for me, but much less frequently after setting cl_forcepreload and sv_forcepreload to 1</li>
<li>Under options -&gt; Keyboard -&gt; Advanced, fast weapon switch doesn’t do anything, it doesn’t even save.  I suggest removing it if you can, besides Black Mesa already has it’s own option</li>
<li>A  lot of the time there is a significant delay for weapons to go to the sprinting position, especially with the shotgun (for me atleast), as well as returning to the idle position</li>
<li>Ignore input when loading, since when I’m loading and I click a shot is fired off when the game loads</li>
<li>Under options -&gt; combat difficulty, the easy option says that the computer helps you aim. This should be removed as BM has it’s own option</li>
<li>Enable creature gibbing should be renamed to “Enable gibbing” for clarity</li>
</ul>
<p>Suggestions:</p>
<ul>
<li>Reduce the default amount of view roll and add view bob</li>
<li>Add more recoil to the Glock</li>
<li>Add a firing rate limiter to the Glock</li>
<li>Add specularity to the green goop which appears on your gun/hands after killing something that bleeds green</li>
<li>Increase green blood texture resolution</li>
<li>Add crosshairs to grenades (haven’t really thought this through)</li>
<li>Unlock viewmodel_fov</li>
<li>Make aim down sights disabled by default as it’s only used on one weapon, doesn’t really fit in, and furthermore is almost completely useless as the revolver has pinpoint accuracy anyways</li>
<li>Add mouse over descriptions of all BM options, especially for things such as houndeye tinnitus and chromatic abberation which most people have no knowledge of</li>
<li>Add “Maximum FPS” option under Black Mesa which would just set fps_max. I already have mine set to 120, matching my refresh rate, to prevent tearing, although it is a big helper in lowering CPU temps for people wanting that.</li>
<li>Decrease options menu oppacity as it’s hard to read some things, mainly the hardware DX level under advanced video options</li>
<li>Remove the echo which happens when you click on something in the pause menu such as “Load game”, one beep at it’s intended volume is enough imo</li>
<li>Implement custom menu/subtitle font to match the HUD font elements more, the current font works but a better font would definately help with immersion</li>
</ul>
<p>Can’t think of anything else at the moment, but just want to say this mod is fantastic anyways and I can’t thank you enough for it.</p>
<p>EDIT: The ladder is incredibly annoying, lots of people I know are having issues with it where they fall off and die.</p>
<p>EDIT 2: Explosive barrels shouldn’t explode when you jump on them, it just makes no sense and leads to aggrevation.</p>
<p>EDIT 3: View rolll should happen when the player turns with his mouse, not jusst when strafing, and should have a dynamic magnitude based on the turn’s tightness.</p>
<p>EDIT 4: Couple more bugs</p>
<ul>
<li>In this image notice how the shotgun is half illuminated by it’s own light, it screws with immersion imo <a href="https://img407.imageshack.us/img407/7758/72467312.png" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://img407.imageshack.us/img407/7758/72467312.png</a>
</li>
<li>The injured scientist who offers to spin the circular platform for the train says go on without me when I initiallly went up to him, but he said the exact same thing when I was laterally close to him but not in the control room (on the track)</li>
<li>The large creature with the flamethrower has really bad AI, doesn’t even attempt to use it’s flamethrowers when I’m on the platform to activate the static charge. Additionally it’s flamethrowers don’t really illuminate much, unlike the rocket engine which was absolutely brilliant to watch.</li>
<li>The railroad car turns aren’t smooth at all, same with the train. For example, a 45 degree turn should be done in at minimum 45 steps, optimally 90, but it seems like 10 or so steps in BM, which makes it feel cheap. Additionally when the train is moving through the water waves from it’s path would be nice.</li>
</ul>
<p>Edit 5 (lol): The HEV voice could be refined in terms of picking up things. For example when I pick up 2 health packs at the same time I don’t need the voice to say “Power 50 percent”, then “Power 75 percent” 1 second later. Just the latter would be needed.</p>
<p>EDIT 6: You can sprint on ladders, no need to explain why it should be removed (it doesn’t even affect your speed).</p>
<p>EDIT 7: You can’t scream out in pain 1 second after you got hit in the face with a grenade launcher.</p>
<p>EDIT 8: The yellow freight transit train’s throttle doesn’t even move.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/many-bugs-suggestions/9973/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/many-bugs-suggestions/9973/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 15 Sep 2012 19:25:27 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9973-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/many-bugs-suggestions/9973.rss">Many bugs\suggestions</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
