<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Android and microSD</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/android-and-microsd/4792</link>
    <description>While I&#39;m quite satisfied with the performance of my HTC Wildfire (Android 2.1) in general, there&#39;s still a bunch of things that annoy me slightly.

Amongst things (but not limited to): the scrolling of long lists (like contact list with thumbnail pictures) or galleries. These tend to lag slightly and feel a bit unresponsive because of that (unable to stop at the right time during &quot;high-speed scrolling&quot;).

People have told me that getting a Class 6 or higher microSD is a must for Android devices (currently sporting the default Class 2) and that it should fix the lagginess. But I can&#39;t seem to find any official word on that (or review or anything at all).

So I was wondering if any of you could tell me whether a Class 6 microSD would do wonders for the speed of the device, or should I wait for Android 2.2 to hit the Wildfire (should be soon, according to HTC)?</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 14 Jul 2010 11:15:55 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Help and Support</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/android-and-microsd/4792.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Android and microSD</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[johnyo]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Not really. I’ve only ever had Symbian so I don’t know shit about Android [COLOR=‘Black’]and I have no money for a new phone so I haven’t got a clue about the new phones.</p>
<p>[edit] A very informative post, isn’t it? :retard:</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/android-and-microsd/4792/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/android-and-microsd/4792/3</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jul 2010 11:15:55 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-4792-3</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/android-and-microsd/4792.rss">Android and microSD</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Android and microSD</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Bolteh]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Psht, here you people are, shitting all over the iPhone and praising Android, but when someone asks something about Android/non-iPhone, nobody answers.</p>
<p>Admit it, you’re all hidden iPhone lovers, but are afraid of being called applefag.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/android-and-microsd/4792/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/android-and-microsd/4792/2</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jul 2010 08:25:49 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-4792-2</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/android-and-microsd/4792.rss">Android and microSD</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Android and microSD</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Bolteh]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>While I’m quite satisfied with the performance of my HTC Wildfire (Android 2.1) in general, there’s still a bunch of things that annoy me slightly.</p>
<p>Amongst things (but not limited to): the scrolling of long lists (like contact list with thumbnail pictures) or galleries. These tend to lag slightly and feel a bit unresponsive because of that (unable to stop at the right time during “high-speed scrolling”).</p>
<p>People have told me that getting a Class 6 or higher microSD is a must for Android devices (currently sporting the default Class 2) and that it should fix the lagginess. But I can’t seem to find any official word on that (or review or anything at all).</p>
<p>So I was wondering if any of you could tell me whether a Class 6 microSD would do wonders for the speed of the device, or should I wait for Android 2.2 to hit the Wildfire (should be soon, according to HTC)?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/android-and-microsd/4792/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/android-and-microsd/4792/1</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jul 2010 09:48:58 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-4792-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/android-and-microsd/4792.rss">Android and microSD</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
