<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Bugs I&#39;ve found so far during my Live-streams</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/bugs-ive-found-so-far-during-my-live-streams/14630</link>
    <description>A few months ago I started making Live-Streams , usually of a different game each time, which would be more interesting for viewers. At some point, I got the idea of playing the entire Black Mesa carrying that hat, for the achievement. What made it even more dumb, was the fact that one of my followers told me there was a Steam Workshop mod that would change the hat to the Half-Life 2 Episode 2 gnome, which was kind of a running joke on my videos... And I noticed multiple bugs during the three (and a half) Live-Streams I&#39;ve done on it thus far. The Live-Streams are on Spanish, but I decided to put subtitles on this video as it could be more easy to understand for everybody.

I asked the official Black Mesa twitter account if I should or not post them here, and that gave me the idea of just picking the interesting parts of the video on a shorter one, thus I decided to share it here. Hopefully, it will help find those issues and problems faster, and improve the game.

[youtube.com/watch?v=JdsvRn9mKpk](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=JdsvRn9mKpk)

Now, to make the dev&#39;s life easier, I decided to also put here the parts with the bugs, glitches or problems I found on it, so you can just skip ahead to them:

[spoiler]
* 0:34 The AI of the NPC decides to not shoot at the zombie which is attacking him. After the zombie burns to death, he also reloads on a glitchy-looking animation.
* 1:53 Shooting the zombie while it gets up made it glitch for a split-second. The next clip has a similar thing, but I believe that&#39;s caused by the headcrab drowning, although it shouldn&#39;t get thrown into the wall like that.
* 2:13 The stuff inside a crate starts glitching up when touching each other, causing a ton of sparks to appear out of nowhere.
* 2:15 After the loading screen, the game gives me another pistol clip for no reason at all. There was no ammo when I got on it, neither when I got out of it.
* 2:23 I was kind of pissed off at the NPC, which started talking as I was explaining some stuff about Black Mesa. I shot him in the face, and he kept talking like that never happend... Should that happend?
* 2:33 Found this NPC who seems unable to fire his weapon.
* 2:50 Now if that wasn&#39;t weird enough, that same NPC decides to run away from a fight, to hides on a nearby room.
* 3:12 Same NPC, keeps being a pacifist.
* 4:11 The NPC randomy appears to stand up, then resumes the animation which was supposed to be running at that moment.
* 4:19 A headcrab jumps over my head, to the NPC&#39;s following me. Four of them had guns and noone seems to care one bit about the hostile crab nearby.
* 4:51 Went into the room as the NPC&#39;s were talking about jumping on the elevator hole, one of the guards closed by and trapped me in the room for a while.
* 5:05 I had previously jumped back on the room because I forgot about the gnome. Turns out, NPC&#39;s get near it as soon as you jump off, and at times they won&#39;t let you go right on it.
* 5:23 If I have learn something about this whole &quot;finish the game with a gnome&quot;, is that it&#39;s nearly IMPOSSIBLE to carry it on ladders. Half the time it will fall down.
* 5:57 While carrying a turret, the gun decided to ignore enemies and instead shoot me to death. Now, I don&#39;t know if that&#39;s a bug or not, but you should totally make it stay like that, it was seriously hilarious.
* 6:17 I know this was changed on an update, now shotguns can gib NPC&#39;s... I personally think it doesn&#39;t fit too well.IT&#39;S A SHOTGUN, NOT UNREAL TOURNAMENT&#39;S FLAK-CANNON!
* 6:29 That thing on the wall seems to have some weird lightning errors.
* 6:40 Probably the weirdest and hilarious bug so far: killed a Houndeye, it started sliding away on the floor, OVER the gigantic elevtator hole, WENT THROUGH the elevator, and stopped floating as soon as it hit the wall. My followers have already named him the &quot;Annoying Houndog&quot;.
* 7:59 First, two houndeyes spawn, but one of them seems to jump over my head, which is weird. Second, the vortigaunt starts swinging like crazy on the floor.
* 9:45 I keep having issues with the ladders. It&#39;s extremely difficult to get on them with the gnome, and don&#39;t drop it randomly while traveling on them.
* 10:04 While struggling to get up to the ledge with the gnome on my hands, the gnome randomly falls down and drowns on it&#39;s own tears.
* 10:25 Again, I end up smashing my head on the floor because of the ladders. I didn&#39;t even had the gnome on my hands. It happens again on the next clip, too.
* 10:56 I later realized that the Barney NPC on that area drops the revolver on that place, but... It still looks really weird because his hand still shows as if he was holding it.
* 11:14 A vortigaunt decides to ignore me. It might had something to do with that box... But after killing the other vortigaunt next to him, he should have just moved to the side and tried to kill me.
* 11:45 As I was shooting those marines, one of them just started screaming and stood frozen in place for a second. After killing him, his shotgun felt to the ground and stood on a really weird way.
* 12:03 Okay, I swear I&#39;m not crazy. The game has a bunch of potato chip bags across the game, and the soda cans are still WAY bigger than them. Not sure if they&#39;re like that on New Mexico, or my imagination is running wild, but that&#39;s some crappy sized chips right there. Shouldn&#39;t they be bigger?
* 13:01 Just as I&#39;m done explaining how I feel like the old-looking trains on this chapter remind me of Steam, and the yellow cart feels like EA, the train bugged out and killed me for no reason at all.
* 13:27 Not happy with that, the EA train strikes back: SOMEHOW I started sinking into it, and I couldn&#39;t move an inch until it crashed on the pool later on. Can I ask for a refund on the EA train?
* 14:26 The gnome was done with my shit and  got stuck between these machines, making me unable to get across. I ended up loading the save and trying to pile up boxes to get up the ledge, as trying those jumps with the gnome was impossible.
* 15:16 As I was talking about NPC&#39;s ignoring me, I found a Vortigaunt who completely refused to attack me. I believe it has to do with the hat/gnome, as it was between him and me (yet it was lying on the floor, not on my hands).
* 16:00 Searching some boxes looking for ammo, I broke a box filled with parachutes... On an underground facility. Dunno, that just felt weird. Things like that should appear in later stages of the game, like in the cliff.
* 16:10 I swear this still happend on the original Half-Life anyway, but Barney dies before the Assassin even gets in the room.
* 16:58 The gnome appears on the map with it&#39;s legs going through the map... Although that&#39;s likely because of the gnome model.
* 17:01 This has always looked wrong on so many levels for me... The smashing machine throws all of the bits and pieces into a puddle of water in the middle of nowhere. Shouldn&#39;t they have like, a recycling bin there or something? Green-Peace would flip the hell out just with that!
* 17:24 Here we have again a gnome breaking crushing machines. Instead of being smashed, the gnome just casually bounces back on me. Which is weird. Maybe the hat/gnome should be made to explode into a million pieces when that stuff happens?
* 17:33 I&#39;ve had this problem for a while, the hitbox of the Trip-mines seems to be way too small, or in the wrong place. I keep having problems shooting them.
* 17:52 And yet again I fail to figure out how ladders work, and splatter my legs on the floor.
* 17:57 This one seems to be a real problem for people who are trying to get this achievement. You see, the ladder has a loading screen mid-way, but you can&#39;t break the thing blocking the way without dropping the gnome. But dropping the gnome and getting it back will most likely cause ANOTHER loading screen, and going up will cause YET ANOTHER LOADING SCREEN. My suggestion would be to take that thing blocking the way to begin with, as it&#39;s already tough getting the gnome to go through tight spaces like that without falling.
* 18:41 A screen on this office area has missing textures.
* 18:53 After a loading screen, the Barney NPC seems to be not only stuck, but floating. Getting close to him so he stops being Jesus Christ and keeps following you causes another loading screen, and I&#39;ve had it with the loading screens already, I swear.
* 19:00 Remember the floating shotgun from before? Well, now it&#39;s a crossbow.
* 19:11 This area seems to give some sick frame-rate drops. I was playing through the entire thing with a stable frame-rate of over 30, but looking at this room drops it to nearly 20, and going inside lowers it to 10 or so. Which is kinda weird.
* 19:51 After dying, I loaded a save in which I had the snarks selected on my hand. When the save loaded, the snarks were invisible. It does like a good force-choke animation, though.

There also was the lost Episode 2. You see, one of the episodes went just right after the Crossfire update, and the save was on the Hydra chapter. The thing is, that chapter was UNPLAYABLE and completely BROKEN, but that bug has been reported here already, so I won&#39;t bother anymore with it. Luckily I had other games to play for emergencies like that.
[/spoiler]
I will also say: sorry for killing so many Barneys and scientist on the Live-Streams.I was still extremely pissed off for problems I had with my job, and I ended up paying it with them. Also, please excuse the extreme abuse of vulgar language, and any possible loud noise you might hear on the video. I would also love to hope that the updates stop breaking old saves, as these Live-Streams have been ruined twice already because of it and it&#39;s kind of getting old. Oh, and sorry for not posting here more information about each bug. As you would understand, I didn&#39;t open the console after each bug to read and save somewhere what the console had to say about them... I was in the middle of a Live-Stream, and I don&#39;t think people wanted to see that, anyway.

Keep up the good work!</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 25 Jan 2016 23:59:20 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>In-game Issues</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/bugs-ive-found-so-far-during-my-live-streams/14630.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Bugs I&#39;ve found so far during my Live-streams</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[BadassFreeman]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>A few months ago I started making Live-Streams , usually of a different game each time, which would be more interesting for viewers. At some point, I got the idea of playing the entire Black Mesa carrying that hat, for the achievement. What made it even more dumb, was the fact that one of my followers told me there was a Steam Workshop mod that would change the hat to the Half-Life 2 Episode 2 gnome, which was kind of a running joke on my videos… And I noticed multiple bugs during the three (and a half) Live-Streams I’ve done on it thus far. The Live-Streams are on Spanish, but I decided to put subtitles on this video as it could be more easy to understand for everybody.</p>
<p>I asked the official Black Mesa twitter account if I should or not post them here, and that gave me the idea of just picking the interesting parts of the video on a shorter one, thus I decided to share it here. Hopefully, it will help find those issues and problems faster, and improve the game.</p>
<p><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=JdsvRn9mKpk" rel="nofollow noopener">youtube.com/watch?v=JdsvRn9mKpk</a></p>
<p>Now, to make the dev’s life easier, I decided to also put here the parts with the bugs, glitches or problems I found on it, so you can just skip ahead to them:</p>
<div class="spoiler">
<ul>
<li>0:34 The AI of the NPC decides to not shoot at the zombie which is attacking him. After the zombie burns to death, he also reloads on a glitchy-looking animation.</li>
<li>1:53 Shooting the zombie while it gets up made it glitch for a split-second. The next clip has a similar thing, but I believe that’s caused by the headcrab drowning, although it shouldn’t get thrown into the wall like that.</li>
<li>2:13 The stuff inside a crate starts glitching up when touching each other, causing a ton of sparks to appear out of nowhere.</li>
<li>2:15 After the loading screen, the game gives me another pistol clip for no reason at all. There was no ammo when I got on it, neither when I got out of it.</li>
<li>2:23 I was kind of pissed off at the NPC, which started talking as I was explaining some stuff about Black Mesa. I shot him in the face, and he kept talking like that never happend… Should that happend?</li>
<li>2:33 Found this NPC who seems unable to fire his weapon.</li>
<li>2:50 Now if that wasn’t weird enough, that same NPC decides to run away from a fight, to hides on a nearby room.</li>
<li>3:12 Same NPC, keeps being a pacifist.</li>
<li>4:11 The NPC randomy appears to stand up, then resumes the animation which was supposed to be running at that moment.</li>
<li>4:19 A headcrab jumps over my head, to the NPC’s following me. Four of them had guns and noone seems to care one bit about the hostile crab nearby.</li>
<li>4:51 Went into the room as the NPC’s were talking about jumping on the elevator hole, one of the guards closed by and trapped me in the room for a while.</li>
<li>5:05 I had previously jumped back on the room because I forgot about the gnome. Turns out, NPC’s get near it as soon as you jump off, and at times they won’t let you go right on it.</li>
<li>5:23 If I have learn something about this whole “finish the game with a gnome”, is that it’s nearly IMPOSSIBLE to carry it on ladders. Half the time it will fall down.</li>
<li>5:57 While carrying a turret, the gun decided to ignore enemies and instead shoot me to death. Now, I don’t know if that’s a bug or not, but you should totally make it stay like that, it was seriously hilarious.</li>
<li>6:17 I know this was changed on an update, now shotguns can gib NPC’s… I personally think it doesn’t fit too well.IT’S A SHOTGUN, NOT UNREAL TOURNAMENT’S FLAK-CANNON!</li>
<li>6:29 That thing on the wall seems to have some weird lightning errors.</li>
<li>6:40 Probably the weirdest and hilarious bug so far: killed a Houndeye, it started sliding away on the floor, OVER the gigantic elevtator hole, WENT THROUGH the elevator, and stopped floating as soon as it hit the wall. My followers have already named him the “Annoying Houndog”.</li>
<li>7:59 First, two houndeyes spawn, but one of them seems to jump over my head, which is weird. Second, the vortigaunt starts swinging like crazy on the floor.</li>
<li>9:45 I keep having issues with the ladders. It’s extremely difficult to get on them with the gnome, and don’t drop it randomly while traveling on them.</li>
<li>10:04 While struggling to get up to the ledge with the gnome on my hands, the gnome randomly falls down and drowns on it’s own tears.</li>
<li>10:25 Again, I end up smashing my head on the floor because of the ladders. I didn’t even had the gnome on my hands. It happens again on the next clip, too.</li>
<li>10:56 I later realized that the Barney NPC on that area drops the revolver on that place, but… It still looks really weird because his hand still shows as if he was holding it.</li>
<li>11:14 A vortigaunt decides to ignore me. It might had something to do with that box… But after killing the other vortigaunt next to him, he should have just moved to the side and tried to kill me.</li>
<li>11:45 As I was shooting those marines, one of them just started screaming and stood frozen in place for a second. After killing him, his shotgun felt to the ground and stood on a really weird way.</li>
<li>12:03 Okay, I swear I’m not crazy. The game has a bunch of potato chip bags across the game, and the soda cans are still WAY bigger than them. Not sure if they’re like that on New Mexico, or my imagination is running wild, but that’s some crappy sized chips right there. Shouldn’t they be bigger?</li>
<li>13:01 Just as I’m done explaining how I feel like the old-looking trains on this chapter remind me of Steam, and the yellow cart feels like EA, the train bugged out and killed me for no reason at all.</li>
<li>13:27 Not happy with that, the EA train strikes back: SOMEHOW I started sinking into it, and I couldn’t move an inch until it crashed on the pool later on. Can I ask for a refund on the EA train?</li>
<li>14:26 The gnome was done with my shit and  got stuck between these machines, making me unable to get across. I ended up loading the save and trying to pile up boxes to get up the ledge, as trying those jumps with the gnome was impossible.</li>
<li>15:16 As I was talking about NPC’s ignoring me, I found a Vortigaunt who completely refused to attack me. I believe it has to do with the hat/gnome, as it was between him and me (yet it was lying on the floor, not on my hands).</li>
<li>16:00 Searching some boxes looking for ammo, I broke a box filled with parachutes… On an underground facility. Dunno, that just felt weird. Things like that should appear in later stages of the game, like in the cliff.</li>
<li>16:10 I swear this still happend on the original Half-Life anyway, but Barney dies before the Assassin even gets in the room.</li>
<li>16:58 The gnome appears on the map with it’s legs going through the map… Although that’s likely because of the gnome model.</li>
<li>17:01 This has always looked wrong on so many levels for me… The smashing machine throws all of the bits and pieces into a puddle of water in the middle of nowhere. Shouldn’t they have like, a recycling bin there or something? Green-Peace would flip the hell out just with that!</li>
<li>17:24 Here we have again a gnome breaking crushing machines. Instead of being smashed, the gnome just casually bounces back on me. Which is weird. Maybe the hat/gnome should be made to explode into a million pieces when that stuff happens?</li>
<li>17:33 I’ve had this problem for a while, the hitbox of the Trip-mines seems to be way too small, or in the wrong place. I keep having problems shooting them.</li>
<li>17:52 And yet again I fail to figure out how ladders work, and splatter my legs on the floor.</li>
<li>17:57 This one seems to be a real problem for people who are trying to get this achievement. You see, the ladder has a loading screen mid-way, but you can’t break the thing blocking the way without dropping the gnome. But dropping the gnome and getting it back will most likely cause ANOTHER loading screen, and going up will cause YET ANOTHER LOADING SCREEN. My suggestion would be to take that thing blocking the way to begin with, as it’s already tough getting the gnome to go through tight spaces like that without falling.</li>
<li>18:41 A screen on this office area has missing textures.</li>
<li>18:53 After a loading screen, the Barney NPC seems to be not only stuck, but floating. Getting close to him so he stops being Jesus Christ and keeps following you causes another loading screen, and I’ve had it with the loading screens already, I swear.</li>
<li>19:00 Remember the floating shotgun from before? Well, now it’s a crossbow.</li>
<li>19:11 This area seems to give some sick frame-rate drops. I was playing through the entire thing with a stable frame-rate of over 30, but looking at this room drops it to nearly 20, and going inside lowers it to 10 or so. Which is kinda weird.</li>
<li>19:51 After dying, I loaded a save in which I had the snarks selected on my hand. When the save loaded, the snarks were invisible. It does like a good force-choke animation, though.</li>
</ul>
<p>There also was the lost Episode 2. You see, one of the episodes went just right after the Crossfire update, and the save was on the Hydra chapter. The thing is, that chapter was UNPLAYABLE and completely BROKEN, but that bug has been reported here already, so I won’t bother anymore with it. Luckily I had other games to play for emergencies like that.</p>
</div>
<p>I will also say: sorry for killing so many Barneys and scientist on the Live-Streams.I was still extremely pissed off for problems I had with my job, and I ended up paying it with them. Also, please excuse the extreme abuse of vulgar language, and any possible loud noise you might hear on the video. I would also love to hope that the updates stop breaking old saves, as these Live-Streams have been ruined twice already because of it and it’s kind of getting old. Oh, and sorry for not posting here more information about each bug. As you would understand, I didn’t open the console after each bug to read and save somewhere what the console had to say about them… I was in the middle of a Live-Stream, and I don’t think people wanted to see that, anyway.</p>
<p>Keep up the good work!</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/bugs-ive-found-so-far-during-my-live-streams/14630/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/bugs-ive-found-so-far-during-my-live-streams/14630/1</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 25 Jan 2016 23:59:20 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14630-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/bugs-ive-found-so-far-during-my-live-streams/14630.rss">Bugs I&#39;ve found so far during my Live-streams</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
