<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Problems I still have with Black Mesa (minor complaints)</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/problems-i-still-have-with-black-mesa-minor-complaints/15239</link>
    <description>Okay first of all: I love Black Mesa. Just want to make that clear and emphasize that THAT is the reason these small things are even a problem for me.
There are a lot of small things in the game that ruin it a little for me. Maybe some of these are even intended. I just have to bring these up. Again, no offense.

1. Gib sounds. When an NPC explodes into gibs and those gibs fly around, they make extremely stupid noises when they hit other objects. The sound doesn&#39;t fit, and it sounds goofy. It&#39;s way too loud most of the time as well.

2. Some gib parts look ridiculous, like the eyes and brains and the torso, that are in perfect shape for some reason. Are the devs doing this intentionally? Do they want to make the violence goofy? It almost seems like it. I&#39;m not a fan of that though. Half-Life was supposed to be a horror game. You might say that it
also looks goofy in Half-Life 1, but that is just because the game is centuries old, it wasn&#39;t supposed to look goofy. It doesn&#39;t fit the tone of the rest of the game, the tone of the story and the atmosphere the game is trying to convey.

3. Crowbar animation and sound. I think this is something that was mentioned a lot by other people already.

4. Sound when you hit a headcrab with the crowbar. When a headcrab jumps at you and you hit it with the crowbar, there should be a loud devastating smashing sound. In Black Mesa it&#39;s just a very quiet tap. In Half-Life 2 it sounds like you actually are doing so much damage that it would kill the headcrab.

5. Some of the animations where scientist get pulled into vents or similar and get killed look like they are out of slapstick comedy. This one is probably not so simple to fix though, cause it probably would require completely new animations, so I could live with this one. The other things should be easy to fix though.

6. Finally, a small game design decision: In Black Mesa you are very slow, but can sprint. Problem is you can only sprint forwards. In Half-Life 2 you can sprint to any direction. I think this is the main reason Black Mesa feels so off in its combat. Simply changing this to the way it is in Half-Life 2 wouldn&#39;t solve it probably, cause the enemies are balanced with this is mind (especially Vortigaunts). I still hope that there will be a mod or something that will allow sprinting to any direction.

7. Don&#39;t like the new Shotgun design  :stuck_out_tongue:  What&#39;s wrong with the classic Spas-12?

Again, these are just minor nitpicks in an otherwise fantastic game. Can&#39;t wait for Xen, which looks mind blowing in the screenshots.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2017 10:34:02 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>The Cafeteria</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/problems-i-still-have-with-black-mesa-minor-complaints/15239.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Problems I still have with Black Mesa (minor complaints)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[LordDz]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>About the shotgun, anyone noticed that if you held the fire button when it starts the automatic reloading and then release it, it will fire a shot after fully reloading, even if you switch weapons during the reload.<br>
An annoying thing.</p>
<p>If you zoom in while firing the Gluon gun and release your fire button, you get an infinite gluon beam. It won’t damage anything, but still a weird bug.</p>
<p>Why doesn’t the crossbow use the SP zoom in multiplayer? It looks a lot better than the zoom it currently has.</p>
<p>Problem with using snd_restart to get custom sounds to load is that you have to do it everytime the player loads the map fresh.<br>
Which means you have to play all looping sounds after loading the command as it stops all playing sounds, so you can never have any looping sounds playing from the mapstart.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/problems-i-still-have-with-black-mesa-minor-complaints/15239/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/problems-i-still-have-with-black-mesa-minor-complaints/15239/5</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2017 10:34:02 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-15239-5</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/problems-i-still-have-with-black-mesa-minor-complaints/15239.rss">Problems I still have with Black Mesa (minor complaints)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Problems I still have with Black Mesa (minor complaints)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[ghostboy1225]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>BTW if you want to modify them easily search “black mesa custom file setup” in the steam guides and it should appear allows really easy development of sound mods you can search the game files with GCFscape look inside this file “bms_textures_dir.vpk” find the relevant sound effects recreate the directory in the custom folder so</p>
<p>common\black mesa\bms\custom\PUT_YOUR_MOD_NAME_HERE\sound\RELEVANT SOUND DIRECTORYS WOULD BE HERE</p>
<p>if you cant find the sound for it in the BMS directory search the HL2 directory for its sound files</p>
<p>also if the sound isnt playing or is silent use snd_restart</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/problems-i-still-have-with-black-mesa-minor-complaints/15239/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/problems-i-still-have-with-black-mesa-minor-complaints/15239/4</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2017 01:10:33 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-15239-4</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/problems-i-still-have-with-black-mesa-minor-complaints/15239.rss">Problems I still have with Black Mesa (minor complaints)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Problems I still have with Black Mesa (minor complaints)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[crowbAr11]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>yeah the shotgun is okay, I can live with it  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=9" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"><br>
Only things that really annoy me are gib sounds and crowbar related stuff.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/problems-i-still-have-with-black-mesa-minor-complaints/15239/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/problems-i-still-have-with-black-mesa-minor-complaints/15239/3</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2017 15:17:12 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-15239-3</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/problems-i-still-have-with-black-mesa-minor-complaints/15239.rss">Problems I still have with Black Mesa (minor complaints)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Problems I still have with Black Mesa (minor complaints)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[ghostboy1225]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>on the spas-12 the new version was to make it more like the half-life 1 spas than HL2’s also it was redone due to the optimiztion jacking it up (backface model destruction i think is the proccess name very promemnant on HL2’s AR2) i do agree that some weapons sound off</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/problems-i-still-have-with-black-mesa-minor-complaints/15239/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/problems-i-still-have-with-black-mesa-minor-complaints/15239/2</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2017 15:07:39 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-15239-2</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/problems-i-still-have-with-black-mesa-minor-complaints/15239.rss">Problems I still have with Black Mesa (minor complaints)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Problems I still have with Black Mesa (minor complaints)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[crowbAr11]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Okay first of all: I love Black Mesa. Just want to make that clear and emphasize that THAT is the reason these small things are even a problem for me.<br>
There are a lot of small things in the game that ruin it a little for me. Maybe some of these are even intended. I just have to bring these up. Again, no offense.</p>
<ol>
<li>
<p>Gib sounds. When an NPC explodes into gibs and those gibs fly around, they make extremely stupid noises when they hit other objects. The sound doesn’t fit, and it sounds goofy. It’s way too loud most of the time as well.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Some gib parts look ridiculous, like the eyes and brains and the torso, that are in perfect shape for some reason. Are the devs doing this intentionally? Do they want to make the violence goofy? It almost seems like it. I’m not a fan of that though. Half-Life was supposed to be a horror game. You might say that it<br>
also looks goofy in Half-Life 1, but that is just because the game is centuries old, it wasn’t supposed to look goofy. It doesn’t fit the tone of the rest of the game, the tone of the story and the atmosphere the game is trying to convey.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Crowbar animation and sound. I think this is something that was mentioned a lot by other people already.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Sound when you hit a headcrab with the crowbar. When a headcrab jumps at you and you hit it with the crowbar, there should be a loud devastating smashing sound. In Black Mesa it’s just a very quiet tap. In Half-Life 2 it sounds like you actually are doing so much damage that it would kill the headcrab.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Some of the animations where scientist get pulled into vents or similar and get killed look like they are out of slapstick comedy. This one is probably not so simple to fix though, cause it probably would require completely new animations, so I could live with this one. The other things should be easy to fix though.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Finally, a small game design decision: In Black Mesa you are very slow, but can sprint. Problem is you can only sprint forwards. In Half-Life 2 you can sprint to any direction. I think this is the main reason Black Mesa feels so off in its combat. Simply changing this to the way it is in Half-Life 2 wouldn’t solve it probably, cause the enemies are balanced with this is mind (especially Vortigaunts). I still hope that there will be a mod or something that will allow sprinting to any direction.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Don’t like the new Shotgun design  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=9" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:">  What’s wrong with the classic Spas-12?</p>
</li>
</ol>
<p>Again, these are just minor nitpicks in an otherwise fantastic game. Can’t wait for Xen, which looks mind blowing in the screenshots.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/problems-i-still-have-with-black-mesa-minor-complaints/15239/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/problems-i-still-have-with-black-mesa-minor-complaints/15239/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 30 Jul 2017 19:43:52 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-15239-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/problems-i-still-have-with-black-mesa-minor-complaints/15239.rss">Problems I still have with Black Mesa (minor complaints)</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
