<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Source SDK 2007 in Linux</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/source-sdk-2007-in-linux/12719</link>
    <description>Recently, I was checking the list of available tools on the steam client in my Linux machine. I was doing that while I was downloading a recently purchased game with the Halloween specials. Now, I saw on the list Source SDK 2007, marked as &quot;not installed&quot;, not as &quot;not available&quot;. I Google it, and there were no Valve&#39;s announcement, but a few sites noticed it. I&#39;ll try to installing it this afternoon.

Now, my question. The dev have stated in multiple times that a Linux port of BMS is not in the near future, citing multiple reasons. During recent months, some of those limits are no longer there. Valve released a Linux client, they are supporting it, they release a SDK 2009 and 2013 for linux. And the devs said that porting from one SDK to another it&#39;s too complicated (I agreed). Now, with SDK 2007 (allegedly) available in Linux, what would change? There&#39;s no SDK porting required? The only step would be compile the code on Linux, to generate the binaries? With only, I&#39;m not saying that this step is easy, just that the total amount of work is less than the one required with a change of SDK.

Could somebody confirm that what I saw with SDK 2007 is real, and it is actually available. If it&#39;s real, how this would change the perspective of a Linux port?</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2013 04:52:35 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>The Cafeteria</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/source-sdk-2007-in-linux/12719.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Source SDK 2007 in Linux</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[sersoft]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>You could always put the BMS folder in /SourceMods/ and report back on your degree of success.</p>
<p>I’d say you’re not likely to get it running due to the fact that it was specifically written for Windows (namely the dll files for client and server) so you might be able to load most maps and some models but you’ll be missing all the coded modifications like the Black Mesa HUD, guns, npc’s, scripted events, and additional graphics fx.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/source-sdk-2007-in-linux/12719/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/source-sdk-2007-in-linux/12719/5</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2013 04:52:35 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12719-5</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/source-sdk-2007-in-linux/12719.rss">Source SDK 2007 in Linux</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Source SDK 2007 in Linux</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Kenley]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>They’ve ported it to the new engine, but haven’t released that version yet.  When the Steam release of BM comes out, it will use Source 2013.  There’s no news yet on when that will happen.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/source-sdk-2007-in-linux/12719/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/source-sdk-2007-in-linux/12719/4</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 30 Oct 2013 21:14:13 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12719-4</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/source-sdk-2007-in-linux/12719.rss">Source SDK 2007 in Linux</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Source SDK 2007 in Linux</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[phollox]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Keresh">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/k/85f322/40.png" class="avatar"> Keresh:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>It doesn’t matter cause they’ve already ported BM to 2013.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>That’s cool. I look for it, but couldn’t find anything. Although, I haven’t been following updates closely these last months.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/source-sdk-2007-in-linux/12719/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/source-sdk-2007-in-linux/12719/3</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 30 Oct 2013 18:53:19 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12719-3</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/source-sdk-2007-in-linux/12719.rss">Source SDK 2007 in Linux</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Source SDK 2007 in Linux</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Keresh]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>It doesn’t matter cause they’ve already ported BM to 2013.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/source-sdk-2007-in-linux/12719/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/source-sdk-2007-in-linux/12719/2</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 30 Oct 2013 18:48:58 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12719-2</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/source-sdk-2007-in-linux/12719.rss">Source SDK 2007 in Linux</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Source SDK 2007 in Linux</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[phollox]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Recently, I was checking the list of available tools on the steam client in my Linux machine. I was doing that while I was downloading a recently purchased game with the Halloween specials. Now, I saw on the list Source SDK 2007, marked as “not installed”, not as “not available”. I Google it, and there were no Valve’s announcement, but a few sites noticed it. I’ll try to installing it this afternoon.</p>
<p>Now, my question. The dev have stated in multiple times that a Linux port of BMS is not in the near future, citing multiple reasons. During recent months, some of those limits are no longer there. Valve released a Linux client, they are supporting it, they release a SDK 2009 and 2013 for linux. And the devs said that porting from one SDK to another it’s too complicated (I agreed). Now, with SDK 2007 (allegedly) available in Linux, what would change? There’s no SDK porting required? The only step would be compile the code on Linux, to generate the binaries? With only, I’m not saying that this step is easy, just that the total amount of work is less than the one required with a change of SDK.</p>
<p>Could somebody confirm that what I saw with SDK 2007 is real, and it is actually available. If it’s real, how this would change the perspective of a Linux port?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/source-sdk-2007-in-linux/12719/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/source-sdk-2007-in-linux/12719/1</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 30 Oct 2013 18:42:52 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12719-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/source-sdk-2007-in-linux/12719.rss">Source SDK 2007 in Linux</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
