<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Sony Vegas Uninstall Assistance</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/sony-vegas-uninstall-assistance/3435</link>
    <description>I recently tried to run an installation of sony vegas 9.0 on my computer only to find that it had become corrupted. I went to try and uninstall it via the windows add/remove programs dialog, and it popped up with a dialog box asking for a file called &quot;moviestudiope09_enu.msi&quot;. I located that file and pointed the windows uninstaller to it, however it says that it is not a valid installation package. I tried three other versions of this same file, and nothing worked. 
Since that did not work I tried removing the files manually and then removing all associated registry keys. It still remains in the add/remove programs list and when I try to re-install the program, it says that I have a newer version of Sony Vegas installed, and to uninstall that one before continuing. I also tried using ccleaner and Revo uninstaller to no avail. I cannot get a working copy installed without uninstalling my old one, and I have not found a way to uninstall it thus far. If anyone can offer any insights, it would be much appreaciated.


EDIT: 
OS: Windows 7 Home Premium 32-bit

EDIT (again): Someone pointed me in the direction of a few hidden registry keys that didn&#39;t use the same naming convention as the rest of them. After I deleted those, I was able to install a working version again. Thanks anyways guys.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 18 Mar 2010 02:09:52 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Help and Support</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/sony-vegas-uninstall-assistance/3435.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Sony Vegas Uninstall Assistance</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[hypnotek]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I recently tried to run an installation of sony vegas 9.0 on my computer only to find that it had become corrupted. I went to try and uninstall it via the windows add/remove programs dialog, and it popped up with a dialog box asking for a file called “moviestudiope09_enu.msi”. I located that file and pointed the windows uninstaller to it, however it says that it is not a valid installation package. I tried three other versions of this same file, and nothing worked.<br>
Since that did not work I tried removing the files manually and then removing all associated registry keys. It still remains in the add/remove programs list and when I try to re-install the program, it says that I have a newer version of Sony Vegas installed, and to uninstall that one before continuing. I also tried using ccleaner and Revo uninstaller to no avail. I cannot get a working copy installed without uninstalling my old one, and I have not found a way to uninstall it thus far. If anyone can offer any insights, it would be much appreaciated.</p>
<p>EDIT:<br>
OS: Windows 7 Home Premium 32-bit</p>
<p>EDIT (again): Someone pointed me in the direction of a few hidden registry keys that didn’t use the same naming convention as the rest of them. After I deleted those, I was able to install a working version again. Thanks anyways guys.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/sony-vegas-uninstall-assistance/3435/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/sony-vegas-uninstall-assistance/3435/1</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 18 Mar 2010 02:09:52 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3435-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/sony-vegas-uninstall-assistance/3435.rss">Sony Vegas Uninstall Assistance</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
