<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Resident Evil 5 DLC</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/resident-evil-5-dlc/3078</link>
    <description>Is there anyone here which also enjoyed Resident Evil 5 like me?

It was a good game, the gameplay very similar to Resident Evil 4
and in my oppinion that was a good thing ^^

I heard allot of people say: They don&#39;t like the idea of &quot;Having to stand still while aiming&quot;. but in my oppinion that is a very good thing, to have a good aim you have to stand still right?, and Resident Evil has always bein like this.
RE5 is not a action shooter like.. half life 2 where u can run and gun.

Now the game was good and all, but we missed the horror feeling didn&#39;t we?
Well tonight the DLC called &quot;Lost In Nightmares&quot; is going to be released.

It takes place in the past where Chris and Jill Infiltrate the Spencer mansion.

I&#39;m looking forward to this tonight, since it looks so much better then then walking around in Africa. good old Resident Evil Feeling ^^

Anyone else looking forward to this?
And tell me do you agree with me about the Controls?</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 22 Feb 2010 00:58:57 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Technology and Gaming</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/resident-evil-5-dlc/3078.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Resident Evil 5 DLC</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[JamestheDoc]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I have RE5.  Played it through, enjoyed it well enough.  I still play Mercenaries from time to time.  It looks beautiful, has some pretty awesome, but the whole partner thing gets annoying and I still miss zombies.  That and a lot of it reminds me too much of RE4.  The giant Majinji for instance… was just unnecessary.  I’d also liked to have seen some rag-doll physics.</p>
<p>I’ve not gotten the expansion, but I hear it’s pretty good for being only $5 dollars (Lost in Nightmares, that’s not including the Versus stuff and the other characters).  It’s only about an hour long, but good for reminiscing about the way RE used to be.  Slower paced and spotted with puzzles like the good old days.  You also get Barry Burton for Mercenaries, and he’s fuckin’ badass.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/resident-evil-5-dlc/3078/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/resident-evil-5-dlc/3078/3</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 22 Feb 2010 00:58:57 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3078-3</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/resident-evil-5-dlc/3078.rss">Resident Evil 5 DLC</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Resident Evil 5 DLC</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Deimos]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I have it for PS3, it’s enjoyable with a friend. I havn’t finished it yet, but it is good fun sometimes.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/resident-evil-5-dlc/3078/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/resident-evil-5-dlc/3078/2</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 18 Feb 2010 16:03:32 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3078-2</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/resident-evil-5-dlc/3078.rss">Resident Evil 5 DLC</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Resident Evil 5 DLC</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Galbadia]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Is there anyone here which also enjoyed Resident Evil 5 like me?</p>
<p>It was a good game, the gameplay very similar to Resident Evil 4<br>
and in my oppinion that was a good thing ^^</p>
<p>I heard allot of people say: They don’t like the idea of “Having to stand still while aiming”. but in my oppinion that is a very good thing, to have a good aim you have to stand still right?, and Resident Evil has always bein like this.<br>
RE5 is not a action shooter like… half life 2 where u can run and gun.</p>
<p>Now the game was good and all, but we missed the horror feeling didn’t we?<br>
Well tonight the DLC called “Lost In Nightmares” is going to be released.</p>
<p>It takes place in the past where Chris and Jill Infiltrate the Spencer mansion.</p>
<p>I’m looking forward to this tonight, since it looks so much better then then walking around in Africa. good old Resident Evil Feeling ^^</p>
<p>Anyone else looking forward to this?<br>
And tell me do you agree with me about the Controls?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/resident-evil-5-dlc/3078/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/resident-evil-5-dlc/3078/1</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 18 Feb 2010 15:55:31 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3078-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/resident-evil-5-dlc/3078.rss">Resident Evil 5 DLC</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
