<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Black Mesa Won&#39;t Run Offline</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/black-mesa-wont-run-offline/12923</link>
    <description>Hello, fine folks of Steam! I&#39;ve played about 90 minutes of Black Mesa overall, and really enjoyed it, but it was while I was taking advantage of the McWifi that&#39;s about a 30-minute walk from my house (I guess the price of Black Mesa attracted me overall? poverty&#39;s a bitch), and when I tried to play it at home, where I still haven&#39;t figured out my neighbor&#39;s wifi password,  I found myself with something of a problem.

I installed it correctly, restarted Steam, all that jazz. I&#39;ve played it, and loved it so far. It just only plays, as you may have guessed from the thread title, when I&#39;m connected to the internet.

So far, when I&#39;ve tried to play it offline, when I hit Play, nothing happens. if I wait for hours (and days, I think, at one point), nothing happens. If I hit Play again, it tells me that it&#39;s already running, yet nothing shows up in the Task manager, and I don&#39;t even see one bit of slowdown in any other programs I decide to run in the meantime (Brutal Doom isn&#39;t [i]that[/i] processor-intensive, though, is it?), and if I try to close steam to try again, I get a little message that tells me that before I can close Steam, I have to close the Black Mesa program... that shows up in no place (I know of, admittedly my experience is limited to the task manager) I can reach it from.

Now, though, when I&#39;m using the wifi of a friend&#39;s house, it starts up [i]immediately[/i].

Neither Google or a search of these very forums have turned up anything aside from the usual problems that were solved by restarting Steam or not having the SDK installed properly, so if anyone has had this problem, if they could direct me to the solution, I&#39;d be quite grateful, and otherwise, any help that could be offered would be great. Thanks, and sorry for the walls of text!</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 19 Jan 2014 21:21:48 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Help!</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/black-mesa-wont-run-offline/12923.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Black Mesa Won&#39;t Run Offline</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[sersoft]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Steam offline mode is always hit and miss, and its status seems to randomly change between working and not working with every single Steam update.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/black-mesa-wont-run-offline/12923/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/black-mesa-wont-run-offline/12923/5</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 19 Jan 2014 21:21:48 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12923-5</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/black-mesa-wont-run-offline/12923.rss">Black Mesa Won&#39;t Run Offline</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Black Mesa Won&#39;t Run Offline</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[RaiFighter]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Apologies in advance for the double post, but I wasn’t certain if just editing the last one would show any change from the main forum page.</p>
<p>The problem fixed itself, for some reason it’s fired up without hesitation for the past few days, so I’m not entirely certain what exactly happened. Still, might wanna keep an open ear if anyone else has a similar problem? Thanks to all who wanted to help out!</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/black-mesa-wont-run-offline/12923/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/black-mesa-wont-run-offline/12923/4</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2014 21:41:23 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12923-4</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/black-mesa-wont-run-offline/12923.rss">Black Mesa Won&#39;t Run Offline</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Black Mesa Won&#39;t Run Offline</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[RaiFighter]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="danielsangeo">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/user_avatar/leakfree.org/danielsangeo/40/4347_2.png" class="avatar"> danielsangeo:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Quick question:</p>
<p>Can you run Source SDK Base 2007 in offline mode?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Yes, it fired up immediately.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/black-mesa-wont-run-offline/12923/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/black-mesa-wont-run-offline/12923/3</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jan 2014 04:09:13 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12923-3</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/black-mesa-wont-run-offline/12923.rss">Black Mesa Won&#39;t Run Offline</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Black Mesa Won&#39;t Run Offline</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[danielsangeo]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Quick question:</p>
<p>Can you run Source SDK Base 2007 in offline mode?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/black-mesa-wont-run-offline/12923/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/black-mesa-wont-run-offline/12923/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jan 2014 03:57:34 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12923-2</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/black-mesa-wont-run-offline/12923.rss">Black Mesa Won&#39;t Run Offline</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Black Mesa Won&#39;t Run Offline</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[RaiFighter]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Hello, fine folks of Steam! I’ve played about 90 minutes of Black Mesa overall, and really enjoyed it, but it was while I was taking advantage of the McWifi that’s about a 30-minute walk from my house (I guess the price of Black Mesa attracted me overall? poverty’s a bitch), and when I tried to play it at home, where I still haven’t figured out my neighbor’s wifi password,  I found myself with something of a problem.</p>
<p>I installed it correctly, restarted Steam, all that jazz. I’ve played it, and loved it so far. It just only plays, as you may have guessed from the thread title, when I’m connected to the internet.</p>
<p>So far, when I’ve tried to play it offline, when I hit Play, nothing happens. if I wait for hours (and days, I think, at one point), nothing happens. If I hit Play again, it tells me that it’s already running, yet nothing shows up in the Task manager, and I don’t even see one bit of slowdown in any other programs I decide to run in the meantime (Brutal Doom isn’t <span class="bbcode-i">that</span> processor-intensive, though, is it?), and if I try to close steam to try again, I get a little message that tells me that before I can close Steam, I have to close the Black Mesa program… that shows up in no place (I know of, admittedly my experience is limited to the task manager) I can reach it from.</p>
<p>Now, though, when I’m using the wifi of a friend’s house, it starts up <span class="bbcode-i">immediately</span>.</p>
<p>Neither Google or a search of these very forums have turned up anything aside from the usual problems that were solved by restarting Steam or not having the SDK installed properly, so if anyone has had this problem, if they could direct me to the solution, I’d be quite grateful, and otherwise, any help that could be offered would be great. Thanks, and sorry for the walls of text!</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/black-mesa-wont-run-offline/12923/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/black-mesa-wont-run-offline/12923/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jan 2014 03:25:18 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12923-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/black-mesa-wont-run-offline/12923.rss">Black Mesa Won&#39;t Run Offline</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
