<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Oculus RIFT HMD Kickstarter</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/oculus-rift-hmd-kickstarter/9114</link>
    <description>Hey guys,
Long time lurker, first post, can&#39;t wait for BMS like the rest of u.

I thought this news could be very interesting to peeps around here:

[url=&#39;https://www.kickstarter.com/projects/1523379957/oculus-rift-step-into-the-game/&#39;]https://www.kickstarter.com/projects/1523379957/oculus-rift-step-into-the-game/[/url]

This oculus HMD has been developed in collaboration with John Carmack and demo&#39;d to a few other very big names in the industry who seem very excited about it&#39;s capabilities, as am I.
The main things about it are the technical aspects it has addressed, and ofcourse the support it has by game developers going forward.

[b]Low latency:[/b]
This was a major problem (and still is) with other HMD units where the image position wouldn&#39;t update fast enough to maintain the immersion in the world

[b]High FOV[/b]
90degrees horizontal FOV is way above anything I&#39;ve seen out there atm, and this is just the dev kit. This will most likely improve in the near future with new low latency LCD being developed all the time.

[b]Software support[/b]
The dev kit comes with doom3 BFG edition, with JC&#39;s integration work done for the head tracking. The main factor here is that it&#39;s not a hack which emulates the mouse movement! It&#39;s a model of how the head moves seperately from your aim in the game, aswell as how it moves in relation to your neck, so it can mimic this movement within the game world.

[b]Open source development[/b]
An SDK is being prepared to support integration into games, and is being fielded by the likes of Valve, Epic, id, etc

Overall very exciting and long overdue for something like this to make it&#39;s way into the gaming world! :smiley: 

What do you guys think? will it change gaming as we know it?</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 02 Aug 2012 15:09:13 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Technology and Gaming</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/oculus-rift-hmd-kickstarter/9114.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Oculus RIFT HMD Kickstarter</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Deimos]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Evod">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/e/aeb1de/40.png" class="avatar"> Evod:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Until I see an actual holodeck I doubt virtual 3d will catch on especially using head gear. I could be wrong though.</p>
<p>Nintendo tried to use 3d head gear and that failed. I just dont think this will work</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Are you kidding me?</p>
<p>Moving on from this guy, looks pretty amazing. Playing Doom 3 BFG edition on one of these would be pretty badass.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/oculus-rift-hmd-kickstarter/9114/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/oculus-rift-hmd-kickstarter/9114/3</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 02 Aug 2012 15:09:13 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9114-3</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/oculus-rift-hmd-kickstarter/9114.rss">Oculus RIFT HMD Kickstarter</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Oculus RIFT HMD Kickstarter</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Evod]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Until I see an actual holodeck I doubt virtual 3d will catch on especially using head gear. I could be wrong though.</p>
<p>Nintendo tried to use 3d head gear and that failed. I just dont think this will work</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/oculus-rift-hmd-kickstarter/9114/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/oculus-rift-hmd-kickstarter/9114/2</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 02 Aug 2012 05:21:47 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9114-2</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/oculus-rift-hmd-kickstarter/9114.rss">Oculus RIFT HMD Kickstarter</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Oculus RIFT HMD Kickstarter</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Codes]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Hey guys,<br>
Long time lurker, first post, can’t wait for BMS like the rest of u.</p>
<p>I thought this news could be very interesting to peeps around here:</p>
<p><a href="https://www.kickstarter.com/projects/1523379957/oculus-rift-step-into-the-game/" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://www.kickstarter.com/projects/1523379957/oculus-rift-step-into-the-game/</a></p>
<p>This oculus HMD has been developed in collaboration with John Carmack and demo’d to a few other very big names in the industry who seem very excited about it’s capabilities, as am I.<br>
The main things about it are the technical aspects it has addressed, and ofcourse the support it has by game developers going forward.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Low latency:</span><br>
This was a major problem (and still is) with other HMD units where the image position wouldn’t update fast enough to maintain the immersion in the world</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">High FOV</span><br>
90degrees horizontal FOV is way above anything I’ve seen out there atm, and this is just the dev kit. This will most likely improve in the near future with new low latency LCD being developed all the time.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Software support</span><br>
The dev kit comes with doom3 BFG edition, with JC’s integration work done for the head tracking. The main factor here is that it’s not a hack which emulates the mouse movement! It’s a model of how the head moves seperately from your aim in the game, aswell as how it moves in relation to your neck, so it can mimic this movement within the game world.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Open source development</span><br>
An SDK is being prepared to support integration into games, and is being fielded by the likes of Valve, Epic, id, etc</p>
<p>Overall very exciting and long overdue for something like this to make it’s way into the gaming world! <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/smiley.png?v=9" title=":smiley:" class="emoji" alt=":smiley:"></p>
<p>What do you guys think? will it change gaming as we know it?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/oculus-rift-hmd-kickstarter/9114/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/oculus-rift-hmd-kickstarter/9114/1</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 02 Aug 2012 04:13:37 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9114-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/oculus-rift-hmd-kickstarter/9114.rss">Oculus RIFT HMD Kickstarter</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
