<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>HL2 vs HL1?</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/hl2-vs-hl1/6791</link>
    <description>I&#39;m curious, which of the two HL games do you prefer? Not including the episodes. 

I personally prefer HL1, as the game was just more fun and full of variety. I loved the boss fights, the simplistic puzzles, and the mass amounts of enemies.

Personally, i am not a huge fan of HL2. It&#39;s not bad, but it&#39;s not the best game ever. I feel like they spent too much time making you fight the combine, and not enough time exploring the xen monsters. I also miss the scripted events that happened oh so often in HL1, like watching zombies attack scientists and the like.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 03 Apr 2011 01:42:33 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Half-Life Series</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/hl2-vs-hl1/6791.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>HL2 vs HL1?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[sersoft]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Exactly</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Mnax">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/m/ebca7d/40.png" class="avatar"> Mnax:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>HL1? It’s just boring to me!</p>
<p>HL2 rocks! It has the better story and simply more atmosphere! Also it has NPCs with an individual character!</p>
<p>Sry, but in my opinion the movement in HL1 is strange and totally fucked up</p>
<p>And who cares about the multi player? SP and its plot are the most important aspects of a HL game!</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>not once does it state “both are fine games and I simply like HL2 better”</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/hl2-vs-hl1/6791/133">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/hl2-vs-hl1/6791/133</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 03 Apr 2011 01:42:33 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-6791-133</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/hl2-vs-hl1/6791.rss">HL2 vs HL1?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>HL2 vs HL1?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Fuskox]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>It’s not which is better, it’s just which one you like more.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/hl2-vs-hl1/6791/132">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/hl2-vs-hl1/6791/132</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 02 Apr 2011 22:57:03 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-6791-132</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/hl2-vs-hl1/6791.rss">HL2 vs HL1?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>HL2 vs HL1?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[sersoft]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I think both are perfectly fine games, if you like one better than the other, you don’t have to write a book about your reasons, hl2 is more suitable for the newer generation, but both are the adventures of the same hero, so fighting about which is better is pointless.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/hl2-vs-hl1/6791/131">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/hl2-vs-hl1/6791/131</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 02 Apr 2011 21:52:03 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-6791-131</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/hl2-vs-hl1/6791.rss">HL2 vs HL1?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>HL2 vs HL1?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Mnax]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>HL1? It’s just boring to me!</p>
<p>HL2 rocks! It has the better story and simply more atmosphere! Also it has NPCs with an individual character!</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="xtobix">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 xtobix:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>personally i hate hl2, because multiplayer was fkn shit and the whole game doesn’t feel like hl1 felt at all. the movement and weaponbalancing is ridiculous. for me it destroyed what hl was.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Sry, but in my opinion the movement in HL1 is strange and totally fucked up (that’s why the Black Mesa team didn’t implement it for the single player part for example)!</p>
<p>And who cares about the multi player? SP and its plot are the most important aspects of a HL game!</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/hl2-vs-hl1/6791/130">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/hl2-vs-hl1/6791/130</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 02 Apr 2011 15:18:07 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-6791-130</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/hl2-vs-hl1/6791.rss">HL2 vs HL1?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>HL2 vs HL1?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Dr_Rosenberg]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Half-Life 1. It has this great monolithic feeling which Half-Life 2 just lacks of.</p>
<p>Half-Life 1. It has this great monolithic feeling which Half-Life 2 just lacks of. When someone mentions Half-Life 1; I immediately get pictures in my head, thinking of Black Mesa, this huge underground complex somewhere located remotely in the desert, abandoned rooms filled with giant rusty machines and the great feeling of helplessness when you encounter these aliens and soldiers. Don’t get me wrong, a crowbar can kill anything, but Black Mesa is located in the middle of fucking nowhere. There is a great feeling of mystery which fills Black Mesa and you always have this feeling of “but there is more…”.</p>
<p>Thinking of Half-Life 2 I don’t really a get a coherent image of it. Of course I can think of Ravenholm, the citadel or the sewers. But however these themes seem all rather competing with other instead of melting together. The game definitly has it great moments and I like all of them. But looking at all the chapters and summing up the experiences I don’t get a convergent sum. I realized that a couple of other HL2 sceptics share very similar concerns with me. Therefor I think I can find a fundamental explanation which maps on the intersection of our opinions: As we know the development of HL2 was several times paused and then driven into new directions. You can read about this in Raising the Bar or any FanWiki which quotes it. A lot of levels were cut, some chapters completely removed. You see it in a lot of beta material. Eg. most drastically the introduction sequence was changed. Initially it was planned that Gordon arrives at the Ravenholm district of C17 by ship. This introduction was later changed or supposed to be changed into a long train ride trough the outskirts of C17, showing you how the world has changed. However this scene was never made that long or simply shortened. There are also a lot of more things which were completely changed. For instance the Air Exchange level was completely cut and recycled into the Nova Prospekt level. Alot of things in HL2 from cut chapters and levels were recycled. This comes totally natural. Imagine you being mapper having working on entire maps just to trash them. For one point this would be frustrating but also uneconomic for the company. So the game designers did take a second look on the material again looked how to redesign it so it fits into the new plot and world again. I think this is the point where we HL2 sceptics are born. While most of the levels remain their quality of gameplay; I think actually we sceptics unconsciously notice that at some parts HL2 was rearranged out of older material and overworked.</p>
<p>This actually is a quite new and interesting insight into the deep concepts of game design.<br>
Introducing the concept of keeping a game monolithic.</p>
<p>Anyways, thank you for respecting our concerns.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/hl2-vs-hl1/6791/129">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/hl2-vs-hl1/6791/129</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 31 Mar 2011 17:10:42 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-6791-129</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/hl2-vs-hl1/6791.rss">HL2 vs HL1?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>HL2 vs HL1?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[fury]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="ClientxL">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/c/779978/40.png" class="avatar"> ClientxL:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Where are your glasses?</p>
<p>The result says: Half-Life 2 (70) &gt; Half-Life 1 (64)</p>
<p>HL2 is the best game ever made, even better than the first one!<br>
(my opinion)</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>personally i hate hl2, because multiplayer was fkn shit and the whole game doesn’t feel like hl1 felt at all. the movement and weaponbalancing is ridiculous. for me it destroyed what hl was.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/hl2-vs-hl1/6791/128">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/hl2-vs-hl1/6791/128</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 31 Mar 2011 16:55:24 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-6791-128</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/hl2-vs-hl1/6791.rss">HL2 vs HL1?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>HL2 vs HL1?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Dead_Phil]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>They were Both jaw dropping games, both were advanced for their time, and both brought in new ideas that changed gaming.<br>
In my opinion it should be 50/50 because I can’t seem to choose one from another</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/hl2-vs-hl1/6791/127">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/hl2-vs-hl1/6791/127</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 31 Mar 2011 02:57:12 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-6791-127</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/hl2-vs-hl1/6791.rss">HL2 vs HL1?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>HL2 vs HL1?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Peon]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>There’s already a ton of discussion here, but I want to add something for Half-Life 1. The first 40% of HL1 is absolute genius…you can tell that they were in some kind of heavy inspiration phase when you play it. That section has incredible build-up and drama, tons of surprise and tense moments, and most importantly a bunch of non-linear corridor exploration. So many cool elements come together in the first part of that game, that it defies description. Every inch of the beginning is meticulously mapped out with excellent encounters waiting around every corner. Couple all that with the non-linearity that allows you to take alternate paths, and the experience can’t be matched.</p>
<p>The problem is, all that genius takes time, and you can tell that the game was taking too long to develop, so the last 60% takes a decidedly linear feel to it. Oh sure, it’s some of the most classic linear FPS action ever, but it starts to feel like they just had to get it done.</p>
<p>Of everything Half-Life, I treasure that first 40% of HL1 above all else, and that’s why I pick it.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/hl2-vs-hl1/6791/126">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/hl2-vs-hl1/6791/126</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 30 Mar 2011 23:52:16 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-6791-126</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/hl2-vs-hl1/6791.rss">HL2 vs HL1?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>HL2 vs HL1?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[wheybags]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Medkit">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/m/57b2e6/40.png" class="avatar"> Medkit:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Just bubble gum</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>So you can use it all and be all out of gum, amirite?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/hl2-vs-hl1/6791/125">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/hl2-vs-hl1/6791/125</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 30 Mar 2011 19:15:06 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-6791-125</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/hl2-vs-hl1/6791.rss">HL2 vs HL1?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>HL2 vs HL1?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Medkit]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Ryλn">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Ryλn:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Hahaha. Just remove the two rebel npc’s if they are annoying you. Or just continue that part disregarding your health being healed. and once you step in the elevator, knock it back down to 1hp again via console or upcoming antlion battle.</p>
<p>What i don’t get is why don’t you just go through the game like how i did with 100hp. If you get hit knocking your health down to 99 and lower, then just quickload the previous save. Plus that way, you don’t accidentally quicksave as soon as a soldier is pointing his barrel at your face and robbing you of your 1hp leaving you fucked forcing you to load a solid save game…</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I don’t want to use any kind of console commands while beating the game this way. Besides, I think playing with 1hp is so much cooler than doing it with 100. It gives me the adrenalin (~) I crave, plus it doesn’t hold any temptation to bypass rules.</p>
<p>If I got hurt, I die. No excuses like “he cheated, this doesn’t count”, I am dead and I have to reload.</p>
<p>Rule <span class="hashtag">#1:</span> 1hp from the beginning up until to the very end. (except for the buggy drop scene in HL 2)<br>
Rule <span class="hashtag">#2:</span> No cheats or console commands.  Just bubble gum and something for anger menagement.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/hl2-vs-hl1/6791/124">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/hl2-vs-hl1/6791/124</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 30 Mar 2011 09:50:44 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-6791-124</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/hl2-vs-hl1/6791.rss">HL2 vs HL1?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>HL2 vs HL1?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Ry_amp_955_n]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Medkit">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/m/57b2e6/40.png" class="avatar"> Medkit:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Now I am defending that rebel holdout where a vortigaunt is tending to Alyx… and I gotta say that medic is an ace with throwing medkits at me. :facepalm:</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Hahaha. Just remove the two rebel npc’s if they are annoying you. Or just continue that part disregarding your health being healed. and once you step in the elevator, knock it back down to 1hp again via console or upcoming antlion battle.</p>
<p>What i don’t get is why don’t you just go through the game like how i did with 100hp. If you get hit knocking your health down to 99 and lower, then just quickload the previous save. Plus that way, you don’t accidentally quicksave as soon as a soldier is pointing his barrel at your face and robbing you of your 1hp leaving you fucked forcing you to load a solid save game…</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/hl2-vs-hl1/6791/123">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/hl2-vs-hl1/6791/123</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 29 Mar 2011 23:59:23 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-6791-123</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/hl2-vs-hl1/6791.rss">HL2 vs HL1?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>HL2 vs HL1?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[MarshmallowRadiation]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Xuri">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/x/df788c/40.png" class="avatar"> Xuri:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Actually HL2 was a big disappointment. Compared to HL1 I mean.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Compared to everything else, though, it was FLIPPIN’ AWESOME</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/hl2-vs-hl1/6791/122">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/hl2-vs-hl1/6791/122</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 29 Mar 2011 22:03:24 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-6791-122</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/hl2-vs-hl1/6791.rss">HL2 vs HL1?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>HL2 vs HL1?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Xuri]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Actually HL2 was a big disappointment. Compared to HL1 I mean.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/hl2-vs-hl1/6791/121">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/hl2-vs-hl1/6791/121</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 29 Mar 2011 21:46:55 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-6791-121</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/hl2-vs-hl1/6791.rss">HL2 vs HL1?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>HL2 vs HL1?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Medkit]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="RestlessMind">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/r/ce7236/40.png" class="avatar"> RestlessMind:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Medkit, post videos of your inevitable rage in trying to beat Episode 2 with 1HP.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Sorry, I had enough of the “fraps and than convert video” business for a time. Anyway, in Episode Two the first major challange is to go down to 1 hp from 72.  I tried throwing rocks on myself, but they cause 5 or 10 hp demage… and it was a quite fustrating. Finally, I’ve decided to proceed to the first zombie encounter, took some falling demage and welcomed some friendly hugs from the “punished for wearing white” dudes. I entered that communication room (where we can also find that damned garden dwarf) with at 1hp.</p>
<p>Now I am defending that rebel holdout where a vortigaunt is tending to Alyx… and I gotta say that medic is an ace with throwing medkits at me. :facepalm:</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/hl2-vs-hl1/6791/120">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/hl2-vs-hl1/6791/120</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 29 Mar 2011 11:02:55 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-6791-120</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/hl2-vs-hl1/6791.rss">HL2 vs HL1?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>HL2 vs HL1?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[ClientxL]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="xtobix">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 xtobix:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Half-Life 1 wins!</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Where are your glasses?</p>
<p>The result says: Half-Life 2 (70) &gt; Half-Life 1 (64)</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="xtobix">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 xtobix:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Well. I think you shouldn’t judge HL1 from playing HL:S imo. I’m a big HL1 fan but I don’t like HL:S at all… HL:S was even more fail than HL2 was…</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>HL2 is the best game ever made, even better than the first one!<br>
(my opinion)</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/hl2-vs-hl1/6791/119">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/hl2-vs-hl1/6791/119</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 29 Mar 2011 11:02:04 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-6791-119</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/hl2-vs-hl1/6791.rss">HL2 vs HL1?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>HL2 vs HL1?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Piefish]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="xtobix">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 xtobix:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Well. I think you shouldn’t judge HL1 from playing HL:S imo. I’m a big HL1 fan but I don’t like HL:S at all… HL:S was even more fail than HL2 was…</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Source is a fail yes.</p>
<p>Half Life 2 a fail?</p>
<p><span alt="" class="broken-image" title="This image is broken"><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-unlink svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#unlink"></use></svg></span></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/hl2-vs-hl1/6791/118">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/hl2-vs-hl1/6791/118</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 29 Mar 2011 08:42:21 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-6791-118</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/hl2-vs-hl1/6791.rss">HL2 vs HL1?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>HL2 vs HL1?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[fury]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="DEATH eVADER">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 DEATH eVADER:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I started playing HL: Source again, and have realised that the character does seem to be going as fast as a gazelle on steroids. Noting this, hopefully the charcter speed in BMS is slowed somewhat (But then I’m sure I remember being 25% slower in HL than that of HL: Source)</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Well. I think you shouldn’t judge HL1 from playing HL:S imo. I’m a big HL1 fan but I don’t like HL:S at all… HL:S was even more fail than HL2 was…</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/hl2-vs-hl1/6791/117">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/hl2-vs-hl1/6791/117</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 29 Mar 2011 07:13:39 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-6791-117</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/hl2-vs-hl1/6791.rss">HL2 vs HL1?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>HL2 vs HL1?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[DEATH_eVADER]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I started playing HL: Source again, and have realised that the character does seem to be going as fast as a gazelle on steroids. Noting this, hopefully the charcter speed in BMS is slowed somewhat (But then I’m sure I remember being 25% slower in HL than that of HL: Source)</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/hl2-vs-hl1/6791/116">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/hl2-vs-hl1/6791/116</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 28 Mar 2011 22:35:05 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-6791-116</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/hl2-vs-hl1/6791.rss">HL2 vs HL1?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>HL2 vs HL1?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[RestlessMind]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Medkit, post videos of your inevitable rage in trying to beat Episode 2 with 1HP.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/hl2-vs-hl1/6791/115">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/hl2-vs-hl1/6791/115</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 28 Mar 2011 22:29:23 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-6791-115</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/hl2-vs-hl1/6791.rss">HL2 vs HL1?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>HL2 vs HL1?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[xalener]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Medkit">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/m/57b2e6/40.png" class="avatar"> Medkit:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>The so called Cinematic Mod tries to deal with that,  but that mod also finds other ways to ruin the game. Black Mesa won’t run with CM installed, right?</p>
<p>Anyway, finished Episode One with 1hp, starting Episode Two.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p><a href="https://forums.blackmesasource.com/showpost.php?p=118430&amp;postcount=18" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://forums.blackmesasource.com/showpost.php?p=118430&amp;postcount=18</a></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/hl2-vs-hl1/6791/114">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/hl2-vs-hl1/6791/114</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 28 Mar 2011 20:28:49 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-6791-114</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/hl2-vs-hl1/6791.rss">HL2 vs HL1?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>HL2 vs HL1?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Medkit]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>The so called Cinematic Mod tries to deal with that,  but that mod also finds other ways to ruin the game. Black Mesa won’t run with CM installed, right?</p>
<p>Anyway, finished Episode One with 1hp, starting Episode Two.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/hl2-vs-hl1/6791/113">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/hl2-vs-hl1/6791/113</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 28 Mar 2011 18:35:22 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-6791-113</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/hl2-vs-hl1/6791.rss">HL2 vs HL1?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>HL2 vs HL1?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[RestlessMind]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Yeah, when you point it out, the lack of diverse wildlife in Half Life 2 kinda sucks.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/hl2-vs-hl1/6791/112">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/hl2-vs-hl1/6791/112</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 28 Mar 2011 16:53:17 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-6791-112</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/hl2-vs-hl1/6791.rss">HL2 vs HL1?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>HL2 vs HL1?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Xuri]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="higgsboson">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/h/8dc957/40.png" class="avatar"> higgsboson:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I preferred HL1 when HL1 was new, compared to HL2 when HL2 was new. Now I would find it more interesting to replay HL2, just because I have played HL1 way too much and I know it all by heart. But I agree with you that HL2 doesn’t have the cool monsters of HL1, where’s the freaking Bullsquid, Gargantua, Vortiguants (Yes they’re there but they’re no longer your enemy), Houndeyes, etc? Why on earth did Valve think that replacing all those different kinds of aliens with the Combine will be good enough? I love the Combine, they’re smart and challenging, but there needs to be more wildlife in there.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="higgsboson">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/h/8dc957/40.png" class="avatar"> higgsboson:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I love the Combine, they’re smart and challenging, but there needs to be more wildlife in there.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="higgsboson">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/h/8dc957/40.png" class="avatar"> higgsboson:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>the Combine, they’re smart and challenging</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="higgsboson">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/h/8dc957/40.png" class="avatar"> higgsboson:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>smart and challenging</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>:hmph:</p>
<p><a href="https://www.dailymotion.com/video/xawr98_les-defauts-de-half-life-2_videogames" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://www.dailymotion.com/video/xawr98_les-defauts-de-half-life-2_videogames</a></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/hl2-vs-hl1/6791/111">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/hl2-vs-hl1/6791/111</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 28 Mar 2011 13:07:59 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-6791-111</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/hl2-vs-hl1/6791.rss">HL2 vs HL1?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>HL2 vs HL1?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[fury]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Half-Life 1 wins!</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/hl2-vs-hl1/6791/110">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/hl2-vs-hl1/6791/110</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 28 Mar 2011 12:21:07 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-6791-110</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/hl2-vs-hl1/6791.rss">HL2 vs HL1?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>HL2 vs HL1?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[higgsboson]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I preferred HL1 when HL1 was new, compared to HL2 when HL2 was new. Now I would find it more interesting to replay HL2, just because I have played HL1 way too much and I know it all by heart. But I agree with you that HL2 doesn’t have the cool monsters of HL1, where’s the freaking Bullsquid, Gargantua, Vortiguants (Yes they’re there but they’re no longer your enemy), Houndeyes, etc? Why on earth did Valve think that replacing all those different kinds of aliens with the Combine will be good enough? I love the Combine, they’re smart and challenging, but there needs to be more wildlife in there.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/hl2-vs-hl1/6791/109">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/hl2-vs-hl1/6791/109</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 28 Mar 2011 08:27:55 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-6791-109</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/hl2-vs-hl1/6791.rss">HL2 vs HL1?</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
