<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Are video games getting too easy?</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/are-video-games-getting-too-easy/5653</link>
    <description>When video games were still a new thing, they were very challenging, and entertaining (super metroid, DooM on nightmare.ect) but these days games are just getting too easy. Only a few stand out as at least reasonably challenging (FarCry: could get killed in only a few shots, even on easy, S.T.A.L.K.E.R.ect). So, what does everyone else thing, are they getting too easy? or is it just me?</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 13 Oct 2010 02:59:29 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Technology and Gaming</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/are-video-games-getting-too-easy/5653.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Are video games getting too easy?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[k3nny1550]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I guess the nature of video game difficulty is entirely subjective due to the rate of acquisition of game mechanics. My theory is that as a player plays more games of the same genre, they learn to think in those terms and instinctual figure out control schemes, tactics, and victory conditions at a much faster rate when grouped to the same genre.</p>
<p>After all, that’s the fun part about being human- we’re inherently unpredictable. It’s why we beta-test. What fun would a game be if we couldn’t beat it? Or if it was obscenely hard to beat? (That’s why the entire DMC series is still on my bookshelf, leering at me.) And yet, I managed to pick up Metal Gear gameplay very quickly after having been tested in Splinter Cell games. They have very different mechanics, but ultimately you use similar tactics across games, and the AI behaves similarly. By contrast, Splinter Cell Conviction is not your average stealth game, being more in the vein of Rainbow Six Vegas and Batman: Arkham Asylum.</p>
<p>Now in bringing up game difficulty, I love F.E.A.R. because it’s a very smartly designed shooter. The AI is relentless, flawless, and completely ruthless when dealing with the player. They flank, flush with grenades, retreat with covering fire, and navigate complex terrain with surprising efficiency (hopping railings, crawling under storm drains, rappelling in from helicopters, busting down doors, etc.) Obviously there were scripted sequences governing them but in general it’s a very flexible set of AI controls and parameters. They made F.E.A.R. punishingly difficult at times, but rewarding to fight because of how smart you feel when you manage to out-think them.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/are-video-games-getting-too-easy/5653/35">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/are-video-games-getting-too-easy/5653/35</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 13 Oct 2010 02:59:29 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-5653-35</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/are-video-games-getting-too-easy/5653.rss">Are video games getting too easy?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Are video games getting too easy?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Vitriol]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>The ORIGINAL Prince of Persia. Very challenging, frustrating at times, but a true classic.<br>
I never could work out how get passed my shadow on what I think was the second last level (still had 12 minutes on the clock usually).</p>
<p>I’ve now lost the copy I had. It was a sad day when my backup drive got a virus and I lost my backups of quite a few old classics that I had bought overs the years.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/are-video-games-getting-too-easy/5653/34">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/are-video-games-getting-too-easy/5653/34</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 11 Oct 2010 10:44:03 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-5653-34</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/are-video-games-getting-too-easy/5653.rss">Are video games getting too easy?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Are video games getting too easy?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Fungus]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="SURPLUS_NiNjA">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 SURPLUS_NiNjA:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I think games in general are moving away from bosses.  The thing is personally I find things like the end fight in HL2:EP2 way more interesting than a boss.  There’s only so much you can do when you only have 1 enemy to work with.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Theres also only so much you can do when your sent on a gauntlet through the same rabble you have been fighting for the past 6+ hours already. yes Halo, Modern Warfare, I’m looking at you. bosses (if done right) demand unique and different strategies to beat.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/are-video-games-getting-too-easy/5653/33">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/are-video-games-getting-too-easy/5653/33</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 11 Oct 2010 07:12:30 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-5653-33</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/are-video-games-getting-too-easy/5653.rss">Are video games getting too easy?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Are video games getting too easy?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[michel97moreno]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Videos games are not only getting easy…and challenging too…</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/are-video-games-getting-too-easy/5653/32">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/are-video-games-getting-too-easy/5653/32</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 11 Oct 2010 06:29:45 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-5653-32</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/are-video-games-getting-too-easy/5653.rss">Are video games getting too easy?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Are video games getting too easy?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Surplus]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="mental2k">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/m/94ad74/40.png" class="avatar"> mental2k:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>One thing I have noticed in a lot of FPSs now is a lack of a distinct boss, quite often the final level is just another level, with a mediocre challenge at the end of it.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I think games in general are moving away from bosses.  The thing is personally I find things like the end fight in HL2:EP2 way more interesting than a boss.  There’s only so much you can do when you only have 1 enemy to work with.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/are-video-games-getting-too-easy/5653/31">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/are-video-games-getting-too-easy/5653/31</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 11 Oct 2010 00:19:23 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-5653-31</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/are-video-games-getting-too-easy/5653.rss">Are video games getting too easy?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Are video games getting too easy?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[mental2k]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I tend to agree, a lot of old games were hard because the graphics were crap as well.  Especially old FPSs you’d walk about for an hour trying to find some way to progress because you were stuck in a bland grey hell. Although Doom3 has managed to recreate that well.  Especially with respawning demons so you have no idea if you’re goin the right way or not, and waste all your ammo.</p>
<p>One thing I have noticed in a lot of FPSs now is a lack of a distinct boss, quite often the final level is just another level, with a mediocre challenge at the end of it.</p>
<p>As for good old platformers, which were fun and hard? Try metal slug my amigo, hours of fun, can still only get to the second last level without using a continue.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/are-video-games-getting-too-easy/5653/30">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/are-video-games-getting-too-easy/5653/30</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 11 Oct 2010 00:05:59 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-5653-30</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/are-video-games-getting-too-easy/5653.rss">Are video games getting too easy?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Are video games getting too easy?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Surplus]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="higgsboson">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/h/8dc957/40.png" class="avatar"> higgsboson:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Yes, today in a video game, all you do is aim and shoot. Before you actually had to use your mind and think. For example, In HL1, you had to figure out what the hell you have to do and you would get lost and stuck from time to time. In HL2, what you have to do is always obvious and you don’t really have to think that much.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Cryptic != Challenge</p>
<p>The biggest change in difficulty over the years has been the clarity of what you are doing.  Note the original zelda compared to new ones.  If you only booted up the game, didn’t read the manual or hear anything about it, how would you know what to do?  So there is a cave there, but there are also other places one could go ages without finding out the sword is in the cave.  New Zelda games start out with a cut scene and tell you the objective.</p>
<p>If you ever go through the developer commentary on a VALVE game you will find that the put quite a bit of effort into making sure the player knows what they need to do.  IE if the sand trap level in HL2 didn’t have that intro scene it would become much MUCH harder.</p>
<p>Now that games have gotten more story based they can’t just throw random shit at you without explanation as much.  This creates clarity and makes the game easier.  Is it a bad thing?  Fuck no I always hated spending hours trying to figure out what to do.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/are-video-games-getting-too-easy/5653/29">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/are-video-games-getting-too-easy/5653/29</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 10 Oct 2010 23:00:11 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-5653-29</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/are-video-games-getting-too-easy/5653.rss">Are video games getting too easy?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Are video games getting too easy?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[higgsboson]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Yes, today in a video game, all you do is aim and shoot. Before you actually had to use your mind and think. For example, In HL1, you had to figure out what the hell you have to do and you would get lost and stuck from time to time. In HL2, what you have to do is always obvious and you don’t really have to think that much.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/are-video-games-getting-too-easy/5653/28">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/are-video-games-getting-too-easy/5653/28</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 10 Oct 2010 16:47:59 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-5653-28</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/are-video-games-getting-too-easy/5653.rss">Are video games getting too easy?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Are video games getting too easy?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Scrue]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Wolfenstien.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/are-video-games-getting-too-easy/5653/27">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/are-video-games-getting-too-easy/5653/27</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 10 Oct 2010 13:23:29 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-5653-27</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/are-video-games-getting-too-easy/5653.rss">Are video games getting too easy?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Are video games getting too easy?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Someonerandm]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Oblivions leveling was pretty annoying.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/are-video-games-getting-too-easy/5653/26">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/are-video-games-getting-too-easy/5653/26</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Oct 2010 16:19:48 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-5653-26</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/are-video-games-getting-too-easy/5653.rss">Are video games getting too easy?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Are video games getting too easy?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[DethklokSoldier]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I still find it a little bit challenging, mostly because I tend not to play games on their hardest difficulties the first few times around. I haven’t even recruited the second group of followers yet, so that’s probably why it hasn’t gotten any easier for me yet. On another subject of video games and difficulties, did anyone else think the leveling enemies of Oblivion took all the fun out of making your character more powerful? The one thing I always liked about RPGs was finding an area with hard to kill enemies and then training my character so I could defeat them. Then when I played Oblivion’s main story, I decided I would level up my character to at least 15 so that the first few quests wouldn’t be to hard. When I finally started the main quest, thinking it was still going to be scamps in Kvatch, I go there and find the place over run by dremora instead of low level enemies. It kind of annoyed me.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/are-video-games-getting-too-easy/5653/25">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/are-video-games-getting-too-easy/5653/25</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Oct 2010 16:13:28 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-5653-25</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/are-video-games-getting-too-easy/5653.rss">Are video games getting too easy?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Are video games getting too easy?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Someonerandm]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>It wasn’t that hard. The beginning was tough, but by the end my powers made it pretty easy. Also nukes are nice.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/are-video-games-getting-too-easy/5653/24">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/are-video-games-getting-too-easy/5653/24</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Oct 2010 15:42:05 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-5653-24</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/are-video-games-getting-too-easy/5653.rss">Are video games getting too easy?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Are video games getting too easy?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[DethklokSoldier]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Mass Effect 2 on Insanity is no laughing matter. Its taken me at least 4 times longer to beat it on insanity than it did on hardcore. I think that the AI actually gets smarter with each difficulty level. On normal all the enemies tended to stay in one spot until you killed them. On insanity the Vanguards would actually get closer, the adepts and commandos sit back and play as more of a support class, and the soldiers actually move from cover to cover while you’re reloading. Of course I might just not have noticed it as much on the other difficulties, but the enhanced AI along with the fact that enemies have waaaaaayyyyyy more health and they deal far more damage makes for a much harder and, in my opinion, enjoyable experience.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/are-video-games-getting-too-easy/5653/23">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/are-video-games-getting-too-easy/5653/23</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Oct 2010 14:08:12 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-5653-23</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/are-video-games-getting-too-easy/5653.rss">Are video games getting too easy?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Are video games getting too easy?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[taxi_evil]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I’ve noticed that most games I play now have more difficulty settings. I usually play on normal, but looking at Mass Effect 2 and Dirt 2 (the last two games I’ve played) there’s half a dozen difficulty levels above it</p>
<p>I haven’t got the time to play a game on ‘insanity’. I have a couple of hours free in the evening, and it’s not much fun if I just spend that time repeating small sections, especially as I’m supposed to be relaxing…</p>
<p>So the default may have got a bit easier, but the option is usually there for the hard core, along with achievements to show you’ve done it</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/are-video-games-getting-too-easy/5653/22">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/are-video-games-getting-too-easy/5653/22</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Oct 2010 09:12:33 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-5653-22</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/are-video-games-getting-too-easy/5653.rss">Are video games getting too easy?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Are video games getting too easy?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Shadi]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>there’s this one game that I really can’t beat till now, and everytime I play it again I just get bored =/</p>
<p>Codnames: Panzers I</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/are-video-games-getting-too-easy/5653/21">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/are-video-games-getting-too-easy/5653/21</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Oct 2010 08:30:18 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-5653-21</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/are-video-games-getting-too-easy/5653.rss">Are video games getting too easy?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Are video games getting too easy?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[vivanto]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Consolification is making them too easy. Not because of the controls, but because mostly raging kids play with consoles, who suck at difficult games.</p>
<p>In some cases pc fags can mod them harder, like they did with fo3, tough I still find it too easy even with lots of realism mods</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/are-video-games-getting-too-easy/5653/20">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/are-video-games-getting-too-easy/5653/20</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Oct 2010 08:07:30 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-5653-20</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/are-video-games-getting-too-easy/5653.rss">Are video games getting too easy?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Are video games getting too easy?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Ineffable]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Someonerandm">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/s/d78d45/40.png" class="avatar"> Someonerandm:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>As far as I’m concerned, retro games were just too hard.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I’m in total agreement - I remember playing certain old school games for hours (like, for just one example, “Strider” for Sega Genesis), getting to about the 3rd or 4th level every time I played, and then throwing my controller and going to play outside…</p>
<p>Games that difficult are infuriating. It’s like there’s just one perfect way to play it through - absolutely no room for error - and if you don’t know how to play it in this exact way, you’re fucked.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/are-video-games-getting-too-easy/5653/19">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/are-video-games-getting-too-easy/5653/19</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Oct 2010 06:13:44 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-5653-19</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/are-video-games-getting-too-easy/5653.rss">Are video games getting too easy?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Are video games getting too easy?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[deadbubble]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I agree.some seem too easy,but apparently,some developer apparently said that one of their games was too hard(it was &lt;.&lt;) Maybe that’s why,some people who can’t play or suck at it are getting games that are easier,which isn’t fair ;~;</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/are-video-games-getting-too-easy/5653/18">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/are-video-games-getting-too-easy/5653/18</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Oct 2010 05:15:51 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-5653-18</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/are-video-games-getting-too-easy/5653.rss">Are video games getting too easy?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Are video games getting too easy?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[DethklokSoldier]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>One thing that we also have to take into account is that we all have years of experience as gamers, so its probably just that we have gotten more experienced at video games and that video games have simply stayed at the same difficulty. That’s just my opinion.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/are-video-games-getting-too-easy/5653/17">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/are-video-games-getting-too-easy/5653/17</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Oct 2010 04:13:18 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-5653-17</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/are-video-games-getting-too-easy/5653.rss">Are video games getting too easy?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Are video games getting too easy?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Someonerandm]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>As far as I’m concerned, retro games were just too hard. Its not that they could not be beat, it just required endless repetition that made the games just plain boring. I can honestly not think of a pre 1990 platformer that I ever enjoyed like a modern game.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/are-video-games-getting-too-easy/5653/16">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/are-video-games-getting-too-easy/5653/16</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Oct 2010 03:15:15 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-5653-16</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/are-video-games-getting-too-easy/5653.rss">Are video games getting too easy?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Are video games getting too easy?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[gibbelin]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="samuel2213">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/s/958977/40.png" class="avatar"> samuel2213:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>try Quake 2, it is FULL OF MEDKITS<br>
they are around every corner, and masses of them are down every corridor</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>First of all, I was severely disappointed when Quake 2 when it came out, especially the single player portion. But since I’m in the minority on that, I’ll grant that it didn’t suck for the sake of discussion.</p>
<p>It’s still not easy. In fact, it’s one of the more frustrating games I’ve ever played. The backtracking to solve puzzles along with some very challenging enemies make it really tough to play on the harder settings. I mentioned the health and ammo in SS2 because the lack of those things is specifically what made the game difficult. That’s not the case in Quake 2.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/are-video-games-getting-too-easy/5653/15">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/are-video-games-getting-too-easy/5653/15</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Oct 2010 02:47:42 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-5653-15</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/are-video-games-getting-too-easy/5653.rss">Are video games getting too easy?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Are video games getting too easy?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[samuel2213]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Medevilae, yeah the AI is stupid, me and my friend played through most of the spec ops missions on veteren, first time, just by running through spamming flash nades and spraying<br>
XD we got through the “breach and clear” mission with about 0.32 seconds to spare   XD</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/are-video-games-getting-too-easy/5653/14">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/are-video-games-getting-too-easy/5653/14</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Oct 2010 02:44:52 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-5653-14</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/are-video-games-getting-too-easy/5653.rss">Are video games getting too easy?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Are video games getting too easy?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[samuel2213]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>try Quake 2, it is FULL OF MEDKITS<br>
they are around every corner, and masses of them are down every corridor</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/are-video-games-getting-too-easy/5653/13">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/are-video-games-getting-too-easy/5653/13</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Oct 2010 02:40:16 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-5653-13</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/are-video-games-getting-too-easy/5653.rss">Are video games getting too easy?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Are video games getting too easy?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Medevilae]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>It depends what game you play. Mass Effect can be a challenge, S.T.A.L.K.E.R., and Cave Story if you’re into platformers… It’s the better designed games that are challenging when you change difficulty levels, obviously. MW2 lacks a good SP campaign, let alone the atrociously dumb AI.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Ramirezoid">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/r/ba9def/40.png" class="avatar"> Ramirezoid:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Halo on Mythic is essentially childbirth, several hundred times in one sitting.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>This, too.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/are-video-games-getting-too-easy/5653/12">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/are-video-games-getting-too-easy/5653/12</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Oct 2010 02:40:05 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-5653-12</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/are-video-games-getting-too-easy/5653.rss">Are video games getting too easy?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Are video games getting too easy?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[gibbelin]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Katana">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/k/db5fbb/40.png" class="avatar"> Katana:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Most early video games were hard by really cheap methods; aspects of the levels you needed to memorize rather than respond to, working off of glitches or tiny/big hitboxes, etc. I think the fact that games are easier isn’t bad at all; as long as people are able to have fun. I do also think that there should be an appropriate level of challenge and progression; I’ve always had the mantra that every boss fight should kill the player once or twice before they succeed.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>True, but I think a big part of the rewarding (and therefore fun) experience of gameplay is overcoming challenges. Can you imagine playing System Shock 2 if there was ammo and health all over the place and having nearly as much fun? There’s definitely a balance to be struck, but I think where games of the 80’s erred on the side of being too difficult, nearly all modern games are lacking in real challenges for serious gamers. Though there are exceptions.</p>
<p>The excellent social commentary book “Everything Bad is Good For You” has a whole chapter devoted to defending video gaming from its critics in which it raises some very good points about why challenging games are good for the mind AND can be more fun. It’s definitely worth a read.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/are-video-games-getting-too-easy/5653/11">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/are-video-games-getting-too-easy/5653/11</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Oct 2010 02:36:15 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-5653-11</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/are-video-games-getting-too-easy/5653.rss">Are video games getting too easy?</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
