<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Diaspora : Shattered Armistice</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/diaspora-shattered-armistice/11184</link>
    <description>I saw this game/mod reviewed on Good Game (aussie gaming show) and thought I&#39;d post a link [url]https://www.abc.net.a...es/s3597646.htm[/url]

I&#39;ve been playing around with it and Im really enjoying it. Gave me an excuse to dust off the old Wingman 3D  :slight_smile: 

[url=&#39;https://www.hard-light.net/forums/index.php?topic=81859.0&#39;]https://www.hard-light.net/forums/index.php?topic=81859.0[/url]
[quote]
What is Diaspora?

After four long years in the making we are proud to release Diaspora: Shattered Armistice. Diaspora is an episodic-release single and multiplayer space fighter combat game set in the reimagined Battlestar Galactica universe. Diaspora is a standalone freeware game based on the FreeSpace Open Engine, everything needed to play is in the download. The project is not-for-profit and not associated with NBC Universal or Bigpoint&#39;s Battlestar Galactica Online.

Our team opted for episodic releases, each involving short plots surrounding different Colonial or Cylon ships and characters. The first Release, Shattered Armistice, tells the story of the Battlestar Theseus and her crew during the attack on the colonies. Many ships seen in the show are part of the first release but some such as the Viper MK2 and the Battlestar Galactica are going to be seen in later releases where they are part of the main story.

Shattered Armistice has a fully-voice acted 8 mission campaign with an original score and cinematics. Several ships never before seen in the Battlestar Galactica universe such as the Sobek class battlestar and Assault Vipers make an appearance.

If there is continued fan interest and support, future episodic releases will see ships such as Pegasus and Galactica from the show. You&#39;ll also see more ships not from the show that flesh out the Cylon and Colonial fleets.

[url]https://www.diasporagame.com[/url]



The Release Thread

After more than 4 years of development, the Diaspora Development team are proud to release our game.

Posted Image

Background
It has been 40 years since the devastating war between the Colonials and the Cylons. 40 years where no one has seen or heard of the Cylons. 40 years where the armistice has held.



Posted Image

Game Features

    [li]Fly the MK VII Viper, the Raptor or the new MK VIIe strike variant.[/li]
    [li]Take part in furious battles against Cylon forces.[/li]
    [li]Play multiplayer missions against your friends as Colonial or Cylon forces.[/li]
    [li]Completely voice acted throughout.[/li]
    [li]Original soundtrack inspired by the show[/li]
    [li]Create your own missions and share them with the included mission editor.[/li]

Posted Image

System Requirements


Windows

Minimum Recommended Specifications:

Operating System: Windows® XP/Vista/Windows 7
CPU:  Core 2 Duo, i3 or similar
Memory: 2GB Ram
Graphics Card: ATI 9600 or comparable nVidia with 256MB Ram
Sound Card: Windows® compatible sound card
Input Device: Windows® compatible mouse and keyboard
Installation: 3GB free HD space

Mac OS X

(Coming soon, but you can guess them from the PC specs!)

Linux

CPU:  Core 2 Duo, i3 or similar
Memory: 2GB Ram
Graphics Card: OpenGL 3/GLSL 1.5 compatible graphics card.
Sound Card: OpenAL compatible sound card.
Input Device: Mouse and keyboard.
Installation: 3GB free HD space

Posted Image

Known Issues


    [li]Due to the size of the installer it may take a long time for the installer to actually start. This may last several minutes (up to five minutes in some instances). There are reports that virus checkers may extend this delay so you may wish to turn them off during the installation process.[/li]
    [li]Multiplayer is currently very much in beta. Also, in order to enhance the eventual multiplayer experience, the team decided not to finalise the balance between ships. Feedback from players is very welcome. The true multiplayer experience will be available in the next release. Till then, if you wish to experiment, here&#39;s how to get started.[/li]

Installation

Windows

Simply download the installer and run it. The Installer will guide you through installing the game.


Mac OS X


    [li]Mount Diaspora.dmg, and follow instructions within to copy Diaspora to the Applications folder.[/li]
    [li]Note: Before you play for the first time (only need to do this once), please double click on RUN_ME_ONCE.command to install the most appropriate graphics settings.[/li]
    [li]Double click on wxlauncher, and press Play, located in the bottom right corner.[/li]

Linux (Source Only)

(At the moment the team doesn&#39;t have the time or expertise to make proper packages for Linux. We&#39;re hoping someone will be willing to help us out there).

First, open a terminal and change to the directory where you downloaded Diaspora.

Then open the archive by typing
[code]
tar --lzma -xf Diaspora_R1_Linux.tar.lzma
[/code]

or if that command doesn&#39;t work, the following two commands instead:
[code]
unlzma -z -k Diaspora_R1_linux.tar.lzma

tar -xf Diaspora_R1_Linux.tar
[/code]

Then follow the instructions in Diaspora_R1_Linux/Diaspora/README.txt, with one correction: after you start the launcher in step 5, select your screen resolution from the drop down box in the Basic Settings tab before you press Play. Otherwise, you&#39;ll be running in 1024x768.


Posted Image

Downloads

Torrents

Simply download the torrent file for your platform and open in any compatible torrent program. If you don&#39;t have a torrent program, you can try µTorrent for Windows and Mac, or Transmission for Mac and Linux. After downloading, please leave your torrent program running so that others can also download from you.

Windows Torrent
Mac Torrent
Linux Torrent

Download links

Windows  -  [ShackNews] - [FSDownloads] - [FreespaceMods]

Mac  -  [ShackNews] - [FSDownloads] - [FreespaceMods]

Linux  -  [ShackNews] - [FSDownloads] - [FreespaceMods]


Soundtrack

During the time we&#39;ve spent developing Diaspora, we have frequently been asked which songs from the show we&#39;ve used in our trailers. The fact is that almost all the music in the game or trailers has been original. So for that reason, we&#39;re also releasing the soundtrack. You can find details on it here.
[/quote]</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 28 Sep 2012 13:30:48 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Technology and Gaming</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/diaspora-shattered-armistice/11184.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Diaspora : Shattered Armistice</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Vitriol]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I saw this game/mod reviewed on Good Game (aussie gaming show) and thought I’d post a link <a href="https://www.abc.net.a...es/s3597646.htm" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://www.abc.net.a…es/s3597646.htm</a></p>
<p>I’ve been playing around with it and Im really enjoying it. Gave me an excuse to dust off the old Wingman 3D  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=9" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
<p><a href="https://www.hard-light.net/forums/index.php?topic=81859.0" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://www.hard-light.net/forums/index.php?topic=81859.0</a></p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>What is Diaspora?</p>
<p>After four long years in the making we are proud to release Diaspora: Shattered Armistice. Diaspora is an episodic-release single and multiplayer space fighter combat game set in the reimagined Battlestar Galactica universe. Diaspora is a standalone freeware game based on the FreeSpace Open Engine, everything needed to play is in the download. The project is not-for-profit and not associated with NBC Universal or Bigpoint’s Battlestar Galactica Online.</p>
<p>Our team opted for episodic releases, each involving short plots surrounding different Colonial or Cylon ships and characters. The first Release, Shattered Armistice, tells the story of the Battlestar Theseus and her crew during the attack on the colonies. Many ships seen in the show are part of the first release but some such as the Viper MK2 and the Battlestar Galactica are going to be seen in later releases where they are part of the main story.</p>
<p>Shattered Armistice has a fully-voice acted 8 mission campaign with an original score and cinematics. Several ships never before seen in the Battlestar Galactica universe such as the Sobek class battlestar and Assault Vipers make an appearance.</p>
<p>If there is continued fan interest and support, future episodic releases will see ships such as Pegasus and Galactica from the show. You’ll also see more ships not from the show that flesh out the Cylon and Colonial fleets.</p>
<p><a href="https://www.diasporagame.com" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://www.diasporagame.com</a></p>
<p>The Release Thread</p>
<p>After more than 4 years of development, the Diaspora Development team are proud to release our game.</p>
<p>Posted Image</p>
<p>Background<br>
It has been 40 years since the devastating war between the Colonials and the Cylons. 40 years where no one has seen or heard of the Cylons. 40 years where the armistice has held.</p>
<p>Posted Image</p>
<p>Game Features</p>
<pre><code>[li]Fly the MK VII Viper, the Raptor or the new MK VIIe strike variant.[/li]
[li]Take part in furious battles against Cylon forces.[/li]
[li]Play multiplayer missions against your friends as Colonial or Cylon forces.[/li]
[li]Completely voice acted throughout.[/li]
[li]Original soundtrack inspired by the show[/li]
[li]Create your own missions and share them with the included mission editor.[/li]
</code></pre>
<p>Posted Image</p>
<p>System Requirements</p>
<p>Windows</p>
<p>Minimum Recommended Specifications:</p>
<p>Operating System: Windows® XP/Vista/Windows 7<br>
CPU:  Core 2 Duo, i3 or similar<br>
Memory: 2GB Ram<br>
Graphics Card: ATI 9600 or comparable nVidia with 256MB Ram<br>
Sound Card: Windows® compatible sound card<br>
Input Device: Windows® compatible mouse and keyboard<br>
Installation: 3GB free HD space</p>
<p>Mac OS X</p>
<p>(Coming soon, but you can guess them from the PC specs!)</p>
<p>Linux</p>
<p>CPU:  Core 2 Duo, i3 or similar<br>
Memory: 2GB Ram<br>
Graphics Card: OpenGL 3/GLSL 1.5 compatible graphics card.<br>
Sound Card: OpenAL compatible sound card.<br>
Input Device: Mouse and keyboard.<br>
Installation: 3GB free HD space</p>
<p>Posted Image</p>
<p>Known Issues</p>
<pre><code>[li]Due to the size of the installer it may take a long time for the installer to actually start. This may last several minutes (up to five minutes in some instances). There are reports that virus checkers may extend this delay so you may wish to turn them off during the installation process.[/li]
[li]Multiplayer is currently very much in beta. Also, in order to enhance the eventual multiplayer experience, the team decided not to finalise the balance between ships. Feedback from players is very welcome. The true multiplayer experience will be available in the next release. Till then, if you wish to experiment, here's how to get started.[/li]
</code></pre>
<p>Installation</p>
<p>Windows</p>
<p>Simply download the installer and run it. The Installer will guide you through installing the game.</p>
<p>Mac OS X</p>
<pre><code>[li]Mount Diaspora.dmg, and follow instructions within to copy Diaspora to the Applications folder.[/li]
[li]Note: Before you play for the first time (only need to do this once), please double click on RUN_ME_ONCE.command to install the most appropriate graphics settings.[/li]
[li]Double click on wxlauncher, and press Play, located in the bottom right corner.[/li]
</code></pre>
<p>Linux (Source Only)</p>
<p>(At the moment the team doesn’t have the time or expertise to make proper packages for Linux. We’re hoping someone will be willing to help us out there).</p>
<p>First, open a terminal and change to the directory where you downloaded Diaspora.</p>
<p>Then open the archive by typing</p>
<pre><code class="lang-auto">tar --lzma -xf Diaspora_R1_Linux.tar.lzma</code></pre>
<p>or if that command doesn’t work, the following two commands instead:</p>
<pre><code class="lang-auto">unlzma -z -k Diaspora_R1_linux.tar.lzma

tar -xf Diaspora_R1_Linux.tar</code></pre>
<p>Then follow the instructions in Diaspora_R1_Linux/Diaspora/README.txt, with one correction: after you start the launcher in step 5, select your screen resolution from the drop down box in the Basic Settings tab before you press Play. Otherwise, you’ll be running in 1024x768.</p>
<p>Posted Image</p>
<p>Downloads</p>
<p>Torrents</p>
<p>Simply download the torrent file for your platform and open in any compatible torrent program. If you don’t have a torrent program, you can try µTorrent for Windows and Mac, or Transmission for Mac and Linux. After downloading, please leave your torrent program running so that others can also download from you.</p>
<p>Windows Torrent<br>
Mac Torrent<br>
Linux Torrent</p>
<p>Download links</p>
<p>Windows  -  [ShackNews] - [FSDownloads] - [FreespaceMods]</p>
<p>Mac  -  [ShackNews] - [FSDownloads] - [FreespaceMods]</p>
<p>Linux  -  [ShackNews] - [FSDownloads] - [FreespaceMods]</p>
<p>Soundtrack</p>
<p>During the time we’ve spent developing Diaspora, we have frequently been asked which songs from the show we’ve used in our trailers. The fact is that almost all the music in the game or trailers has been original. So for that reason, we’re also releasing the soundtrack. You can find details on it here.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/diaspora-shattered-armistice/11184/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/diaspora-shattered-armistice/11184/1</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Sep 2012 13:30:48 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11184-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/diaspora-shattered-armistice/11184.rss">Diaspora : Shattered Armistice</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
