<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Why mess with the bullsquid eyes?</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/why-mess-with-the-bullsquid-eyes/62345</link>
    <description>So I playing my Half Life Remake called Black Mesa (named after the facility from the game), and suddenly there was the infamous squidchicken monster!!! and I was like &quot;oh my god, there they are again in HD after all these years!!&quot; xD

But then I noticed their eyes were messed with; they no longer looked aquatic and alien with eyes on each side of the head. And they now had like, crocodile-perception and could put both eyes on me like a mean angry head with two really well-toned legs. I&#39;m afraid of them now and I don&#39;t like being afraid

Now hear me out, I know this is a bit stark, but I think everyone involved with this decision should die. I&#39;m new to the forums.
[poll type=regular results=always public=true]
* End the developer&#39;s lives.
* Just be cool with it.
* End my own life.
[/poll]</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2019 08:48:57 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>The Cafeteria</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/why-mess-with-the-bullsquid-eyes/62345.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Why mess with the bullsquid eyes?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[OrderOfDagon]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>This was a troll post, but that’s not true at all.</p>
<p>The amount of predators with varying eye types in the world proves you wrong; ranging from fish, lizards, amphibians, bugs, etc. There’s no reason for it. Some predators don’t even use their eyes. Maybe the bullsquid is all smell and his eyes are vestigial organs that do nothing, which is why they drifted to the sides after centuries of unuse? Maybe they’re not even eyes - they don’t have pupils. Or at least they didn’t before BMS. See what I mean?</p>
<p>It’s an alien squid… why tf does it need binolocular vision? Its world and diet are small, clusted, and shy of open space. Binocular vision with two-eyes meeting on thing creates depth which is usually for predators that stalk their prey over wide distances. Ironically, the bullsquid seems similar to actual squid, picking a spot and eating whatever is foolish enough to come near their den. I’m just playing devil’s advocate, but you can see why pulling on the thread makes this an endless discussion. Biology doesn’t have rules, it has reasons. Not exactly the same.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/why-mess-with-the-bullsquid-eyes/62345/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/why-mess-with-the-bullsquid-eyes/62345/6</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2019 08:48:57 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-62345-6</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/why-mess-with-the-bullsquid-eyes/62345.rss">Why mess with the bullsquid eyes?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Why mess with the bullsquid eyes?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Mr_Someguy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>They were changed to more closely resemble a predator’s eyes. Predators usually have front facing eyes to better seek prey, prey have side eyes to better see predators but cannot see forward as well.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/why-mess-with-the-bullsquid-eyes/62345/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/why-mess-with-the-bullsquid-eyes/62345/5</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2019 07:48:46 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-62345-5</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/why-mess-with-the-bullsquid-eyes/62345.rss">Why mess with the bullsquid eyes?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Why mess with the bullsquid eyes?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[OrderOfDagon]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Oh I use all the mods fam. I use even og footsteps and shit. I switch them on and off depending on what mood I’m in.</p>
<p>This is a joke thread in response to people thinking it’s not okay to criticize things. I think the decision to change bullsquids is totally fine, but the way they did it and for the reasons they did it - it was pretty next level unnecessary. That’s not the point though, I just want people to get on-board with the fact that I think other mods and modders are improving some things that devs have glossed over, and that the devs don’t make all the right decisions all the time. They do such a good job with everything else, is it a harmful thing to say something like that? Games can be improved if they are beta and being tested, no?</p>
<p>Speaking of which, I don’t know if you played it, but I like Xen a lot so far, for instance: it re-imagines rather than remakes. That’s something I wish the mod did more of in the retail release. I find combat and enemy AI is a bit aged for a modern game, same with the 1 voice actor per character type thing. Mods like MMod for HL2 are legit the best way to play those games today because they make the game feel satisfying again by slightly altering all the weapon push, impact sounds, and ragdoll fx of the weapons and enemies. Sometimes I really wish they’d rehaul the game’s combat to be more like MMod, since I’m all for including good ideas into one thing. But lord knows if I made that thread, I’d be banned because about 250 people would take it the wrong way.</p>
<p>“PLAY MMOD IF YOU LIKE MMOD”<br>
I just think there’s always room for improvement, especially over the most basic formula ever: Shoot, kill, next enemy, next area. Examining other mods and modders in the workshop like that one you just mentioned are exactly what I’m trying to say. I think there’s about a dozen mods that should be official at this point because they just pick up the slack the devs can’t afford to spend too much time on right now. That’s what Valve used to do sometimes.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/why-mess-with-the-bullsquid-eyes/62345/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/why-mess-with-the-bullsquid-eyes/62345/4</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2019 09:30:07 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-62345-4</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/why-mess-with-the-bullsquid-eyes/62345.rss">Why mess with the bullsquid eyes?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Why mess with the bullsquid eyes?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[AsinoEsel]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Try <a href="https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=1526473396&amp;searchtext=bullsquid" rel="nofollow noopener">this workshop mod</a></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/why-mess-with-the-bullsquid-eyes/62345/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/why-mess-with-the-bullsquid-eyes/62345/3</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2019 17:07:55 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-62345-3</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/why-mess-with-the-bullsquid-eyes/62345.rss">Why mess with the bullsquid eyes?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Why mess with the bullsquid eyes?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[OrderOfDagon]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>yeah idk I still think ending my own life is the solution here. But I guess I’ll just be cool with it… if that’s what you guys want.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/why-mess-with-the-bullsquid-eyes/62345/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/why-mess-with-the-bullsquid-eyes/62345/2</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2019 15:25:39 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-62345-2</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/why-mess-with-the-bullsquid-eyes/62345.rss">Why mess with the bullsquid eyes?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Why mess with the bullsquid eyes?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[OrderOfDagon]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>So I playing my Half Life Remake called Black Mesa (named after the facility from the game), and suddenly there was the infamous squidchicken monster!!! and I was like “oh my god, there they are again in HD after all these years!!” xD</p>
<p>But then I noticed their eyes were messed with; they no longer looked aquatic and alien with eyes on each side of the head. And they now had like, crocodile-perception and could put both eyes on me like a mean angry head with two really well-toned legs. I’m afraid of them now and I don’t like being afraid</p>
<p>Now hear me out, I know this is a bit stark, but I think everyone involved with this decision should die. I’m new to the forums.</p>
<div class="poll" data-poll-status="open" data-poll-public="true" data-poll-results="always" data-poll-type="regular" data-poll-name="poll">
<div>
<div class="poll-container">
<ul>
<li data-poll-option-id="76bf6d6830ffa0148a4a410eec085323">End the developer’s lives.</li>
<li data-poll-option-id="c76731cb18ff3d0c3458c6213f80be29">Just be cool with it.</li>
<li data-poll-option-id="b2219d3fdaffffa2f1edf28a8a59abd0">End my own life.</li>
</ul>
</div>
<div class="poll-info">
<p>
<span class="info-number">0</span>
<span class="info-label">voters</span>
</p>
</div>
</div>
</div>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/why-mess-with-the-bullsquid-eyes/62345/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/why-mess-with-the-bullsquid-eyes/62345/1</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2019 01:28:48 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-62345-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/why-mess-with-the-bullsquid-eyes/62345.rss">Why mess with the bullsquid eyes?</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
