<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>L4D2 Texture Help (Models, too, possibly)</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/l4d2-texture-help-models-too-possibly/5172</link>
    <description>Hiya, I&#39;m working on a Left 4 Dead 2 mod that my sister suggested (that makes 3 projects, only 2 actually going anywhere), and have a whole level completely orange-mapped, one level half-laid out, and the rest at zero percent.  I keep stopping because I really want to find textures that work with the project I&#39;m doing, which is called [COLOR=&#39;Red&#39;][b]The Crimson Chapel[/b].

I need some textures that really fit the setting and look like... well, what this place is supposed to be.

Before I go on and name exactly what kind of textures I&#39;m looking for, I&#39;m going to wait and see if anybody catches what I&#39;m doing based on the name of the Campaign.

A hint:  The fact that the name is Crimson has nothing to do with the fact that a motif of L4D is lotsa blood&#39;n&#39;guts, it just happens to be a well-placed accidental double-entendre.

Addendum:  At a later date, I might ask for some help with models as well, such as some arched doorjambs and pillars.

[COLOR=&#39;Gray&#39;]NOTE:  Anybody who does contribute (if anybody contributes), just also send me a decal with your name and what you did on it, and I&#39;ll toss it in somewhere.[/SIZE]



UPDATE:  Okay, I figure now I might as well say what it&#39;s a remake of:  The Scarlet Monastery.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2010 03:34:05 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Help and Support</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/l4d2-texture-help-models-too-possibly/5172.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>L4D2 Texture Help (Models, too, possibly)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[GFreeman515]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="bbyoufeng">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 bbyoufeng:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>thanks for your sharing!  i like it!<br>
cheap jerseys, <a href="https://www.4nflshop.com" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">nfl jerseys cheap</a>, <a href="https://www.4nflshop.com" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">nfl jersey</a>, <a href="https://www.4nflshop.com" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">nfl shop</a>,<a href="https://www.4nflshop.com" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">shop nfl</a>, <a href="https://www.4nflshop.com" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">shop nfl</a>, nfl jerseys, <a href="https://www.4nflshop.com" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">nflshop</a>, <a href="https://www.4nflshop.com" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">jersey wholesale</a>,<a href="https://www.4nflshop.com" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">nflshop</a>, <a href="https://www.4nflshop.com" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">nfl jerseys</a> cheap, cheap jerseys,<a href="https://www.4nflshop.com" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">nfl jersey</a>, nfl jerseys cheap, nfl jersey, nfl shop, shop nfl, nfl jerseys, nflshop, jersey wholesale, nfl jerseys cheap.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>[COLOR=‘Red’]BAN HIS ASS NAO</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/l4d2-texture-help-models-too-possibly/5172/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/l4d2-texture-help-models-too-possibly/5172/2</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2010 03:34:05 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-5172-2</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/l4d2-texture-help-models-too-possibly/5172.rss">L4D2 Texture Help (Models, too, possibly)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>L4D2 Texture Help (Models, too, possibly)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Madcat1030]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Hiya, I’m working on a Left 4 Dead 2 mod that my sister suggested (that makes 3 projects, only 2 actually going anywhere), and have a whole level completely orange-mapped, one level half-laid out, and the rest at zero percent.  I keep stopping because I really want to find textures that work with the project I’m doing, which is called [COLOR=‘Red’]<span class="bbcode-b">The Crimson Chapel</span>.</p>
<p>I need some textures that really fit the setting and look like… well, what this place is supposed to be.</p>
<p>Before I go on and name exactly what kind of textures I’m looking for, I’m going to wait and see if anybody catches what I’m doing based on the name of the Campaign.</p>
<p>A hint:  The fact that the name is Crimson has nothing to do with the fact that a motif of L4D is lotsa blood’n’guts, it just happens to be a well-placed accidental double-entendre.</p>
<p>Addendum:  At a later date, I might ask for some help with models as well, such as some arched doorjambs and pillars.</p>
<p>[COLOR=‘Gray’]NOTE:  Anybody who does contribute (if anybody contributes), just also send me a decal with your name and what you did on it, and I’ll toss it in somewhere.[/SIZE]</p>
<p>UPDATE:  Okay, I figure now I might as well say what it’s a remake of:  The Scarlet Monastery.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/l4d2-texture-help-models-too-possibly/5172/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/l4d2-texture-help-models-too-possibly/5172/1</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 Aug 2010 00:57:01 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-5172-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/l4d2-texture-help-models-too-possibly/5172.rss">L4D2 Texture Help (Models, too, possibly)</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
