<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>The Massive Friggin&#39; Xen Thread</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/the-massive-friggin-xen-thread/9423</link>
    <description>The massive friggin&#39; Xen thread

With the impending release of Lambda Core, I think it&#39;s time we brainstormed a [url=&#39;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Screenwriting#Rewriting_and_script_doctoring&#39;]page one rewrite[/url] of the Xen sequences of Half Life. 

Xen, among many gamers, is the most universally derided part of the original Half Life for good reason- the design of the maps pull a stark 180 from the rest of the game and focus a great deal on platforming and resource management, rather than the mix of combat and puzzles inherent to the Black Mesa chapters. 

Questions that have to be considered when redesigning Xen are likely as follows:

I. What is the focus of Xen&#39;s design, and how can we improve the levels while maintaining continuity with the original concept of the game?

II. How much longer should Xen be?

III. How should the boss fights be redesigned to fit Black Mesa&#39;s tweaked-towards-HL2-standards gameplay?

IV. What sort of changes to the enemy roster and layouts would benefit the new design?

----------------

To start things off, I&#39;d like to come up with a new direction for Xen. 

I. Xen&#39;s focus to me is to throw the player into a very alien universe. The player must feel very alone, almost hopeless as he is outnumbered by fearsome adversaries a thousand to one. The levels were designed as platforming maps to contrast the main game and to provide &quot;fresh&quot; gameplay that the player had not seen before. This is made quite obvious through the design, the reduced gravity, and the dead humans in Xen being the only supply drops the player has access to. 

My take on new levels for Xen would follow a drastically different direction. Parts of the Black Mesa facility should be haphazardly teleported to Xen at odd angles in some areas of the map, creating a more dynamic environment for the player to traverse. A close analogue would be an early sequence in Prey where the player finds themselves fighting through the bar they started the game in, only with battle damage, the level rotated at a very odd angle, and using portals to reorient the player to fight along walls. 

My version of Xen wouldn&#39;t precisely use these ideas perse, as this would require extensive re-coding of Source&#39;s physics engine. Maps wouldn&#39;t be &quot;copy-pasted&quot; from the facility to be reused on Xen, they would be more heavily damaged, at different angles, and support a more platforming focused style of play. Imagine hopping between oddly bent, bolted to the floor/ceiling cafeteria tables hanging over a void while a Harrier teleports into the map trailing flames and debris. Or parts of the Office Complex being thrust into Xen, breaking into smaller pieces and floating in Xen&#39;s expansive void, crashing into the rocks already present and allowing the alien architecture to meld seamlessly with parts of the Black Mesa facility. (And then getting chased by a Garg through it!) 

The massive factory spikes in the original Xen would be used by Xenian aliens to &quot;mine&quot; these parts of the facility for raw materials to feed to Nihilianth, who is basically keeping small parts of the borderworld stable (i.e. the floating rocks for the aliens to inhabit). Some of this would likely require cinematic physics, but considering the impressive work on display for the Resonance Cascade and the Blast Pit window crash sequences, this would be fully within the team&#39;s capability. With this scenario&#39;s rendition of Nihilanth&#39;s powers keeping the borderworld stable, when he is killed, the entire map will spin out of control, rocks will collide with each other, and the G-man will teleport Gordon to safety, to continue with the endgame &quot;choice.&quot; 

II. Xen should have a similar amount of maps as the original Half-Life, but take advantage of Source&#39;s larger map sizes to increase the length of the chapters, as well as their geometric complexity. 

III. Gonarch&#39;s fight was a very well-executed part of Xen for me, and I&#39;d try to reproduce the fight in a relatively similar fashion, just redesigned to fit the tweaked art direction and gameplay. (Perhaps Gordon could chase Gonarch through a meteor shower?) Nihilanth&#39;s fight is a bit of a bore, and should be redesigned to take advantage of the new art design to it&#39;s fullest. Nihilanth could teleport Gordon away at any moment, forcing the player to fight back to the center of the map (Nihilanth&#39;s chambers) through new aliens, but also allow the player to resupply along the way. I&#39;m well aware these are drastic redesigns, but considering the absolute horror that is the original Half-Life&#39;s Xen chapters, I feel a radical redesign is absolutely necessary to regain any sense of playability from this part of the game. 

IV. The chapter&#39;s focus on the Xen borderworld basically cuts the enemy roster in half, and spams aliens at the player with little regard for balancing. Supplies are small in number in the original game, and this is very much appropriate. I&#39;d considered having soldiers, scientists, or security guards being teleported in with the pieces of the facility, but this would ruin the solitary feel of Xen and it&#39;s focus on this being Gordon&#39;s mission to kill Nihilanth and, as such, would not be appropriate for inclusion. Some corpses floating through the borderworld with the new architecture, however, would assist in reinforcing this bleak feel, as well as give more areas to explore and loot in search of supplies to continue Gordon&#39;s suicide mission. 

-----------------

This is just my take, however. I really want to hear everybody&#39;s thoughts on the redesign of Xen. Let&#39;s throw our hive mind at the chapters and see what we come up with!</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 26 Oct 2014 19:05:01 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>The Cafeteria</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/the-massive-friggin-xen-thread/9423.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>The Massive Friggin&#39; Xen Thread</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[k3nny1550]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Let’s hope we hear something on November 16th.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/the-massive-friggin-xen-thread/9423/358">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/the-massive-friggin-xen-thread/9423/358</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 26 Oct 2014 19:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9423-358</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/the-massive-friggin-xen-thread/9423.rss">The Massive Friggin&#39; Xen Thread</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The Massive Friggin&#39; Xen Thread</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[DerpyBullsquid]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I hope gonarch is added soon. That was my favorite boss!</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/the-massive-friggin-xen-thread/9423/357">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/the-massive-friggin-xen-thread/9423/357</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 26 Oct 2014 11:52:10 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9423-357</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/the-massive-friggin-xen-thread/9423.rss">The Massive Friggin&#39; Xen Thread</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The Massive Friggin&#39; Xen Thread</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Mr_Sir_Shpee]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>*Hype Train build Steam</p>
<p>FTFY</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/the-massive-friggin-xen-thread/9423/356">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/the-massive-friggin-xen-thread/9423/356</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 21 Sep 2014 20:13:35 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9423-356</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/the-massive-friggin-xen-thread/9423.rss">The Massive Friggin&#39; Xen Thread</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The Massive Friggin&#39; Xen Thread</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Swaggless]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I don’t think it will. I think there will be some warning. You gotta let the Hype Train build steam!</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/the-massive-friggin-xen-thread/9423/355">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/the-massive-friggin-xen-thread/9423/355</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 20 Sep 2014 20:59:21 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9423-355</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/the-massive-friggin-xen-thread/9423.rss">The Massive Friggin&#39; Xen Thread</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The Massive Friggin&#39; Xen Thread</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Dotard]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I’m about to replay Black Mesa again… I truly wish that nothing of the sort of an updated version getting released in a few days happens :d</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/the-massive-friggin-xen-thread/9423/354">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/the-massive-friggin-xen-thread/9423/354</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 20 Sep 2014 19:40:45 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9423-354</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/the-massive-friggin-xen-thread/9423.rss">The Massive Friggin&#39; Xen Thread</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The Massive Friggin&#39; Xen Thread</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Tiki]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>It’s the same suit, but every piece has been replaced one-by-one with upgraded components…</p>
<p><a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Ship_of_Theseus" data-bbcode="true">https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Ship_of_Theseus</a></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/the-massive-friggin-xen-thread/9423/353">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/the-massive-friggin-xen-thread/9423/353</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2014 05:23:38 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9423-353</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/the-massive-friggin-xen-thread/9423.rss">The Massive Friggin&#39; Xen Thread</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The Massive Friggin&#39; Xen Thread</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[bur]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I thought it was established that the suit in HL2 is the same as the one in HL1, just upgraded with parts and technology from 20 years later</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/the-massive-friggin-xen-thread/9423/352">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/the-massive-friggin-xen-thread/9423/352</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2014 16:53:10 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9423-352</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/the-massive-friggin-xen-thread/9423.rss">The Massive Friggin&#39; Xen Thread</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The Massive Friggin&#39; Xen Thread</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[John_Lemon]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I’ll go with that. G-Man definitely likes to hide his actions through many proxies, obviously. The most direct he’s ever been with someone was with Shepherd (and I know dabbling into the ‘canon-unless-otherwise-noted’ territory of OpFor is dangerous), and even then it was only to secure him in stasis permanently.</p>
<p>Honestly, at this point I’d be surprised if Kleiner <em>hasn’t</em> had contact with the G-Man like Eli Vance and others, even in passing. However the hell that suit got to Kleiner, for all we know G-Man also took all those government-owned (and few alien lifeform) weapons and chucked them in a ditch somewhere just to be done with it.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/the-massive-friggin-xen-thread/9423/351">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/the-massive-friggin-xen-thread/9423/351</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2014 14:43:43 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9423-351</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/the-massive-friggin-xen-thread/9423.rss">The Massive Friggin&#39; Xen Thread</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The Massive Friggin&#39; Xen Thread</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Kenley]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>The half-life wiki has this to say about the issue:</p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>In Half-Life 2, despite being allowed to keep it in the previous game, Freeman starts without the suit. After a visit to Dr. Isaac Kleiner, his former colleague from Black Mesa, Freeman receives an upgraded HEV suit, the Mark V.</p>
<p>Dr. Kleiner, as well as other characters occasionally refer to this suit as Gordon’s “old suit,” indicating that it is upgraded from his old Mark IV suit; it isn’t explained how Dr. Kleiner acquired it as Gordon was placed in stasis wearing it. However, the G-Man releases Gordon wearing “civvies” (presumably the blue denim ‘prison’ uniform) in Half-Life 2, so it is likely that he ‘arranged’ it somehow.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p><a href="https://half-life.wikia.com/wiki/HEV_Suit#Mark_V" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://half-life.wikia.com/wiki/HEV_Suit#Mark_V</a></p>
<p>Just food for thought.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/the-massive-friggin-xen-thread/9423/350">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/the-massive-friggin-xen-thread/9423/350</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2014 13:43:35 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9423-350</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/the-massive-friggin-xen-thread/9423.rss">The Massive Friggin&#39; Xen Thread</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The Massive Friggin&#39; Xen Thread</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Dandiest]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Then where does the Mark IV go?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/the-massive-friggin-xen-thread/9423/349">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/the-massive-friggin-xen-thread/9423/349</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2014 09:44:40 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9423-349</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/the-massive-friggin-xen-thread/9423.rss">The Massive Friggin&#39; Xen Thread</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The Massive Friggin&#39; Xen Thread</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Tiki]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Unless Gordon kept the Mk.IV’s documentation in the glovebox.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/the-massive-friggin-xen-thread/9423/348">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/the-massive-friggin-xen-thread/9423/348</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2014 12:02:15 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9423-348</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/the-massive-friggin-xen-thread/9423.rss">The Massive Friggin&#39; Xen Thread</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The Massive Friggin&#39; Xen Thread</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[k3nny1550]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Either that, or it’s a different suit altogether. Considering it had full official documentation, I’d suspect the latter.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/the-massive-friggin-xen-thread/9423/347">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/the-massive-friggin-xen-thread/9423/347</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2014 18:29:47 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9423-347</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/the-massive-friggin-xen-thread/9423.rss">The Massive Friggin&#39; Xen Thread</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The Massive Friggin&#39; Xen Thread</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Kenley]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>However, Kleiner has apparently had it for long enough to upgrade it from the Mark IV used in Half-Life to the new “Mark V,” with slight differences in both appearance and functionality.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/the-massive-friggin-xen-thread/9423/346">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/the-massive-friggin-xen-thread/9423/346</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2014 04:18:24 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9423-346</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/the-massive-friggin-xen-thread/9423.rss">The Massive Friggin&#39; Xen Thread</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The Massive Friggin&#39; Xen Thread</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[JeffMOD]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I always assumed G-man had given Eli the suit, who then gave it to Kleiner, because otherwise when he arrived in C17 he would have been instantly spotted by the Combine and taken out.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/the-massive-friggin-xen-thread/9423/345">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/the-massive-friggin-xen-thread/9423/345</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 31 Aug 2014 12:13:07 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9423-345</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/the-massive-friggin-xen-thread/9423.rss">The Massive Friggin&#39; Xen Thread</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The Massive Friggin&#39; Xen Thread</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Dandiest]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I don’t know if this was pointed out in the thread, but G-Man says “As for your Hazard Suit, I think you’ve earned it.”<br>
This is contradicted in Half-Life 2 because Gordon gets the Hazard Suit back from Kleiner.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/the-massive-friggin-xen-thread/9423/344">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/the-massive-friggin-xen-thread/9423/344</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 31 Aug 2014 02:16:36 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9423-344</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/the-massive-friggin-xen-thread/9423.rss">The Massive Friggin&#39; Xen Thread</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The Massive Friggin&#39; Xen Thread</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Swaggless]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Crypt">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/user_avatar/leakfree.org/crypt/40/4394_2.png" class="avatar"> Crypt:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>FMOD, maybe?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>That’s what I was thinking.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/the-massive-friggin-xen-thread/9423/343">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/the-massive-friggin-xen-thread/9423/343</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2014 23:11:26 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9423-343</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/the-massive-friggin-xen-thread/9423.rss">The Massive Friggin&#39; Xen Thread</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The Massive Friggin&#39; Xen Thread</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypt]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="darkone">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/user_avatar/leakfree.org/darkone/40/4296_2.png" class="avatar"> darkone:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>there was a way to make half life 2 play music through the transitions though I think that was a hack to the game.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>FMOD, maybe?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/the-massive-friggin-xen-thread/9423/342">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/the-massive-friggin-xen-thread/9423/342</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2014 20:54:08 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9423-342</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/the-massive-friggin-xen-thread/9423.rss">The Massive Friggin&#39; Xen Thread</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The Massive Friggin&#39; Xen Thread</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Swaggless]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Scorpion42">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/s/e495f1/40.png" class="avatar"> Scorpion42:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>The reason GoldSrc could do that was because it was playing CD music, like a music player. It wasn’t <span class="bbcode-i">really</span> part of the game. The music in the media folder of Steam Half-Life doesn’t play through transitions, at least in my experience.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>It actually does now. It didn’t in the past, but it does now.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/the-massive-friggin-xen-thread/9423/341">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/the-massive-friggin-xen-thread/9423/341</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2014 15:03:12 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9423-341</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/the-massive-friggin-xen-thread/9423.rss">The Massive Friggin&#39; Xen Thread</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The Massive Friggin&#39; Xen Thread</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[darkone]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>there was a way to make half life 2 play music through the transitions though I think that was a hack to the game.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/the-massive-friggin-xen-thread/9423/340">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/the-massive-friggin-xen-thread/9423/340</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2014 14:53:18 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9423-340</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/the-massive-friggin-xen-thread/9423.rss">The Massive Friggin&#39; Xen Thread</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The Massive Friggin&#39; Xen Thread</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Scorpion42]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Swaggless">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/s/a698b9/40.png" class="avatar"> Swaggless:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>GoldSrc could also have a song play between maps. Source can’t.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>The reason GoldSrc could do that was because it was playing CD music, like a music player. It wasn’t <span class="bbcode-i">really</span> part of the game. The music in the media folder of Steam Half-Life doesn’t play through transitions, at least in my experience.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/the-massive-friggin-xen-thread/9423/339">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/the-massive-friggin-xen-thread/9423/339</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2014 14:46:55 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9423-339</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/the-massive-friggin-xen-thread/9423.rss">The Massive Friggin&#39; Xen Thread</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The Massive Friggin&#39; Xen Thread</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Swaggless]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Scorpion42">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/s/e495f1/40.png" class="avatar"> Scorpion42:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Ouch. But you’re right.</p>
<p>HOWEVER, I <span class="bbcode-i">just</span> remembered that Counter-Strike: Condition Zero: Deleted Scenes has dynamic music, and <span class="bbcode-b">that</span> game was made in the <span class="bbcode-i">GoldSource</span> engine. Does that convince anyone?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>GoldSrc could also have a song play between maps. Source can’t.</p>
<p>I’m certain dynamic music could easily be put into whatever version of Source the devs are using if it’s not in there already, and <span class="bbcode-b"><span class="bbcode-i">I</span></span> believe that the end result would be worth it. However, I’m not optimistic that they’ll do it.</p>
<p>But, you never know!  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=9" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/the-massive-friggin-xen-thread/9423/338">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/the-massive-friggin-xen-thread/9423/338</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2014 18:56:08 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9423-338</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/the-massive-friggin-xen-thread/9423.rss">The Massive Friggin&#39; Xen Thread</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The Massive Friggin&#39; Xen Thread</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Scorpion42]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Swaggless">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/s/a698b9/40.png" class="avatar"> Swaggless:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Was the music there truly dynamic? I thought the Vort Fight music just faded out after the fight was done, and I don’t think Sector Sweep (Post Advisor Barn, pre Rebel Garage) was dynamic at all. It just started when you killed the soldiers that burst in the door, and got cut off at the next map-transition-tunnel. It’s one of my favorite HL songs, so I’d think I would have noticed it…</p>
<p>The songs are COMPOSED specifically for the scene they are used for most of the time, and that can make a song FEEL dynamic.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Ouch. But you’re right.</p>
<p>HOWEVER, I <span class="bbcode-i">just</span> remembered that Counter-Strike: Condition Zero: Deleted Scenes has dynamic music, and <span class="bbcode-b">that</span> game was made in the <span class="bbcode-i">GoldSource</span> engine. Does that convince anyone?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/the-massive-friggin-xen-thread/9423/337">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/the-massive-friggin-xen-thread/9423/337</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2014 18:12:36 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9423-337</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/the-massive-friggin-xen-thread/9423.rss">The Massive Friggin&#39; Xen Thread</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The Massive Friggin&#39; Xen Thread</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Swaggless]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Scorpion42">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/s/e495f1/40.png" class="avatar"> Scorpion42:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I doubt it would be that hard to code, unlike many other Portal 2 features. Actually, there are even af few examples of it in Episode 2 e.g. the Victory Mine Vortigaunt Stand-off and the map before the muscle car breaks.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Was the music there truly dynamic? I thought the Vort Fight music just faded out after the fight was done, and I don’t think Sector Sweep (Post Advisor Barn, pre Rebel Garage) was dynamic at all. It just started when you killed the soldiers that burst in the door, and got cut off at the next map-transition-tunnel. It’s one of my favorite HL songs, so I’d think I would have noticed it…</p>
<p>The songs are COMPOSED specifically for the scene they are used for most of the time, and that can make a song FEEL dynamic.</p>
<p>HOWEVER, to be more on topic: HECK YES I want awesome, dynamic Nihilanth-butt-kicking music! The original fight in HL was incredibly lame. There was no tension, no real suspense, and even hitting the Nihilanth with the Gluon Gun didn’t “feel good”. He was just a bullet sponge that barely even reacted to your attacks. A drastic change from the other enemies in the game which feel very ALIVE and SMART, and seem to react to… being shot with a quantum destabilizer.  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=9" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"></p>
<p>Good music, and an overall better design for the fight would benefit Black Mesa perfectly.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/the-massive-friggin-xen-thread/9423/336">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/the-massive-friggin-xen-thread/9423/336</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 25 May 2014 03:14:37 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9423-336</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/the-massive-friggin-xen-thread/9423.rss">The Massive Friggin&#39; Xen Thread</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The Massive Friggin&#39; Xen Thread</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Kenley]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Oh wow, I don’t think I’d ever noticed there was any music track at all!  But yeah, that seems way too short to last even a fraction of the battle.  The feeling of “Traveling Through Limbo” certainly goes along with the eerie desolation most of Xen evokes, but for a final boss battle?  Come on!</p>
<p>Joel will give us something cool to play while we fight, if the rest of the soundtrack is anything to go by!</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/the-massive-friggin-xen-thread/9423/335">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/the-massive-friggin-xen-thread/9423/335</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 24 May 2014 00:10:43 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9423-335</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/the-massive-friggin-xen-thread/9423.rss">The Massive Friggin&#39; Xen Thread</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The Massive Friggin&#39; Xen Thread</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Scorpion42]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Kenley">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/user_avatar/leakfree.org/kenley/40/4737_2.png" class="avatar"> Kenley:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Yeah, that could be really neat (though I have no idea how hard that could be to implement).</p>
<p>I think it would be good to add in any music there, because IIRC the Nihilanth fight was sort of silent.  You only had the ambiance of Xen and the sounds of the battle itself.  Music would be an easy way to increase the intensity of the moment, even if the battle stayed relatively the same as in Half-Life (which I doubt, anyway).</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I doubt it would be that hard to code, unlike many other Portal 2 features. Actually, there are even af few examples of it in Episode 2 e.g. the Victory Mine Vortigaunt Stand-off and the map before the muscle car breaks.</p>
<p>The problem with the original fight is that it plays Traveling Through Limbo/Singularity when the fight starts, but the track is hilariously short and could be argued as being unfitting.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/the-massive-friggin-xen-thread/9423/334">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/the-massive-friggin-xen-thread/9423/334</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2014 06:41:25 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9423-334</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/the-massive-friggin-xen-thread/9423.rss">The Massive Friggin&#39; Xen Thread</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
