<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Monitor sleep/standby goes to blue?</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/monitor-sleep-standby-goes-to-blue/12429</link>
    <description>So, I have a ViewSonic VS11531 monitor, hooked up via DVI, and would like for it to enter sleep/standby mode and stay in sleep/standby mode until I tell it to &quot;wake up&quot;.

The monitor can and does enter sleep/standby mode (the monitor screen shuts off and blue light on the front of the monitor becomes amber, both working as intended) but for some reason, eventually, the monitor comes back on, the screen a bright blue.

I keep my computer running while I&#39;m asleep or at work and would like for the monitor to stay in sleep/standby mode while I&#39;m away.  The monitor is large and was quite expensive when I bought it and I&#39;d like for it to not be displaying a bright blue screen when I&#39;m at work or whatever, running out its life.

Sure, I can turn the monitor off when leaving the computer, but I&#39;m wondering if there&#39;s something I can do to guarantee that it stays in sleep/standby mode until I do some sort of input into the computer (jiggle the mouse, tap a key on the keyboard).  My other monitor, an Acer X203H, reliably stays in sleep/standby mode.

Thanks!</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2013 19:40:28 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Help and Support</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/monitor-sleep-standby-goes-to-blue/12429.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Monitor sleep/standby goes to blue?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[sersoft]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>maybe your monitor is not a monitor but a TV?</p>
<p>anyway you need to go to your BIOS, change it between S1 or S3 sleep.</p>
<p>also if your monitor is a TV it will probably stay blue for about 15 minutes then go to sleep</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/monitor-sleep-standby-goes-to-blue/12429/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/monitor-sleep-standby-goes-to-blue/12429/2</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2013 19:40:28 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12429-2</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/monitor-sleep-standby-goes-to-blue/12429.rss">Monitor sleep/standby goes to blue?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Monitor sleep/standby goes to blue?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[danielsangeo]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>So, I have a ViewSonic VS11531 monitor, hooked up via DVI, and would like for it to enter sleep/standby mode and stay in sleep/standby mode until I tell it to “wake up”.</p>
<p>The monitor can and does enter sleep/standby mode (the monitor screen shuts off and blue light on the front of the monitor becomes amber, both working as intended) but for some reason, eventually, the monitor comes back on, the screen a bright blue.</p>
<p>I keep my computer running while I’m asleep or at work and would like for the monitor to stay in sleep/standby mode while I’m away.  The monitor is large and was quite expensive when I bought it and I’d like for it to not be displaying a bright blue screen when I’m at work or whatever, running out its life.</p>
<p>Sure, I can turn the monitor off when leaving the computer, but I’m wondering if there’s something I can do to guarantee that it stays in sleep/standby mode until I do some sort of input into the computer (jiggle the mouse, tap a key on the keyboard).  My other monitor, an Acer X203H, reliably stays in sleep/standby mode.</p>
<p>Thanks!</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/monitor-sleep-standby-goes-to-blue/12429/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/monitor-sleep-standby-goes-to-blue/12429/1</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2013 13:14:10 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12429-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/monitor-sleep-standby-goes-to-blue/12429.rss">Monitor sleep/standby goes to blue?</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
