<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:discourse="http://www.discourse.org/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>News &amp; Developer Updates - Leakfree</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/c/black-mesa-archive/news-developer-updates/10</link>
    <description>Topics in the &#39;News &amp; Developer Updates&#39; category Patch information, updates, and interviews with the developers.</description>
    
      <lastBuildDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2018 12:32:34 +0000</lastBuildDate>
      <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/c/black-mesa-archive/news-developer-updates/10.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
        <item>
          <title>Half-Life is 20! - Xen Trailer!</title>
          <dc:creator><![CDATA[TextFAMGUY1]]></dc:creator>
          <category>News &amp; Developer Updates</category>
          <description><![CDATA[
            <p><div class="lightbox-wrapper"><a class="lightbox" href="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/original/2X/3/375e94e5e426b22b22176fcef635f4caba4dfe65.jpeg" data-download-href="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/375e94e5e426b22b22176fcef635f4caba4dfe65" title=""><img src="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/original/2X/3/375e94e5e426b22b22176fcef635f4caba4dfe65.jpeg" alt="" width="690" height="161" data-small-upload="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/optimized/2X/3/375e94e5e426b22b22176fcef635f4caba4dfe65_2_10x10.png"><div class="meta"><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-far-image svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#far-image"></use></svg><span class="filename"></span><span class="informations">920×215 71.1 KB</span><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-discourse-expand svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#discourse-expand"></use></svg></div></a></div></p>
<p>Happy Birthday Half-Life! We’d like to thank Valve for creating this masterpiece; an important part of gaming history. Nobody on this team would be where they are today if it weren’t for this amazing, inspirational game. We are lucky to share in a tiny bit of their legacy.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">The Xen Trailer</span></p>
<p><div class="lightbox-wrapper"><a class="lightbox" href="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/original/2X/c/c2439a7513708b5c112a53c55785f5409fd8c216.jpeg" data-download-href="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/c2439a7513708b5c112a53c55785f5409fd8c216" title=""><img src="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/original/2X/c/c2439a7513708b5c112a53c55785f5409fd8c216.jpeg" alt="" width="690" height="161" data-small-upload="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/optimized/2X/c/c2439a7513708b5c112a53c55785f5409fd8c216_2_10x10.png"><div class="meta"><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-far-image svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#far-image"></use></svg><span class="filename"></span><span class="informations">920×215 50.6 KB</span><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-discourse-expand svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#discourse-expand"></use></svg></div></a></div><br>
<span class="bbcode-i">“The Specimen will be delivered to you in a few (months)”</span></p>
<p>To Celebrate Half-Life’s 20th Anniversary, we have something special to share. <span class="bbcode-b">Our first trailer for Xen!</span> Be sure to go full screen and crank it up to 11!</p>
<div class="onebox lazyYT lazyYT-container" data-youtube-id="TAIJich73NY" data-youtube-title="Black Mesa: Xen Trailer" data-parameters="feature=oembed&amp;wmode=opaque">
  <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=TAIJich73NY" target="_blank" rel="noopener">
    <img class="ytp-thumbnail-image" src="https://i.ytimg.com/vi/TAIJich73NY/maxresdefault.jpg" title="Black Mesa: Xen Trailer" width="690" height="388">
  </a>
</div>

<p><a href="https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCah8NTcZ1Ct5ElESx5cQRlQ" data-bbcode="true">James McVinnie</a> has once again done an amazing job with presenting our game. Everything in the trailer was captured in-game, and we hope to polish and improve our visuals as we get the entirety of Xen up to our standards.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Xen Timeline</span></p>
<p><div class="lightbox-wrapper"><a class="lightbox" href="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/original/2X/2/2ad866ed8c735d1bf0c643a81bf78dcc0686491c.jpeg" data-download-href="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/2ad866ed8c735d1bf0c643a81bf78dcc0686491c" title=""><img src="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/original/2X/2/2ad866ed8c735d1bf0c643a81bf78dcc0686491c.jpeg" alt="" width="690" height="161" data-small-upload="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/optimized/2X/2/2ad866ed8c735d1bf0c643a81bf78dcc0686491c_2_10x10.png"><div class="meta"><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-far-image svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#far-image"></use></svg><span class="filename"></span><span class="informations">920×215 50.8 KB</span><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-discourse-expand svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#discourse-expand"></use></svg></div></a></div><br>
<span class="bbcode-i">“Morning, Mr. Freeman. Looks like you’re running late.”</span></p>
<p>Our goal is to release Xen on Steam in Q2 2019. This will allow us to finish Xen to a place where the entire product is stable, smooth, and most importantly…fun! We are already happy with the design state of Xen as it stands currently: <span class="bbcode-i">almost </span>everything is design locked and functioning as intended. We are going to be using the remaining time between now and launch to bring it up to our art and polish standards.</p>
<p>Playtests show that all of <span class="bbcode-b"><span class="bbcode-u">Xen will take roughly 6 hours to complete</span></span>; longer for those who like to explore. The levels and design for Xen are largely original work (with cues taken from Half-Life), rather than just simply a remake of  Xen.</p>
<p>We are extremely proud of what we have created, and will be showing off some of our deep graphics and NPC changes later in December, as well as a breakdown of where each of the chapters stand.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Thank You</span></p>
<p><div class="lightbox-wrapper"><a class="lightbox" href="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/original/2X/b/b70c496b1c9b3d5033e24734a9f897aad6cb1a1d.jpeg" data-download-href="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/b70c496b1c9b3d5033e24734a9f897aad6cb1a1d" title=""><img src="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/original/2X/b/b70c496b1c9b3d5033e24734a9f897aad6cb1a1d.jpeg" alt="" width="690" height="161" data-small-upload="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/optimized/2X/b/b70c496b1c9b3d5033e24734a9f897aad6cb1a1d_2_10x10.png"><div class="meta"><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-far-image svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#far-image"></use></svg><span class="filename"></span><span class="informations">920×215 34 KB</span><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-discourse-expand svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#discourse-expand"></use></svg></div></a></div><br>
<span class="bbcode-i">“Thanks, Doc.”</span></p>
<p>As always, thank you to our incredible community. The positivity and support is what keeps this team going. I got to go the Retro Game Con here in Syracuse, New York, and it was amazing to meet people who have stuck by our game since the mod days. I really cannot express how it made me feel to have people come up to our table and thank us for our work, and encourage us to keep going. Retro Game Con was a great reminder of just how supportive and positive our community is. Let’s keep that going, not just on Steam or the internet, but everywhere!</p>
<p><div class="lightbox-wrapper"><a class="lightbox" href="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/original/2X/f/f574694879c5768c546189ca7a574ce57ecbcfc4.jpeg" data-download-href="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/f574694879c5768c546189ca7a574ce57ecbcfc4" title=""><img src="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/original/2X/f/f574694879c5768c546189ca7a574ce57ecbcfc4.jpeg" alt="" width="643" height="500" data-small-upload="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/optimized/2X/f/f574694879c5768c546189ca7a574ce57ecbcfc4_2_10x10.png"><div class="meta"><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-far-image svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#far-image"></use></svg><span class="filename"></span><span class="informations">960×746 159 KB</span><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-discourse-expand svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#discourse-expand"></use></svg></div></a></div></p>
<p>Again… a huge thank you to all our fans who have stuck by us through all these years.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Xen <span class="bbcode-i">WILL </span>be out in 2019, Half-Life will turn 21, and we can finally buy it that beer we owed it.</span></p>
            <p><small>75 posts - 41 participants</small></p>
            <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/half-life-is-20-xen-trailer/15420">Read full topic</a></p>
          ]]></description>
          <link>https://leakfree.org/t/half-life-is-20-xen-trailer/15420</link>
          <pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2018 12:32:34 +0000</pubDate>
          <discourse:topicPinned>Yes</discourse:topicPinned>
          <discourse:topicClosed>No</discourse:topicClosed>
          <discourse:topicArchived>No</discourse:topicArchived>
          <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-topic-15420</guid>
          <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/half-life-is-20-xen-trailer/15420.rss">Half-Life is 20! - Xen Trailer!</source>
        </item>
        <item>
          <title>Summer Update 2018</title>
          <dc:creator><![CDATA[TextFAMGUY1]]></dc:creator>
          <category>News &amp; Developer Updates</category>
          <description><![CDATA[
            <p><img alt=""></p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b"><span class="bbcode-u">Summer Sale</span></span><br>
Hope everyone is having a great summer. Black Mesa is now on sale for 60% off! It’s a GREAT time to pick up the game at a discounted price  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/wink.png?v=9" title=":wink:" class="emoji" alt=":wink:"></p>
<p><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/362890/Black_Mesa/" data-bbcode="true"><img src="https://steamcdn-a.akamaihd.net/steamcommunity/public/images/clans/8672783/2e37aea759e0823e7002ee6664946e92ef072b2a.jpg" alt="" width="674" height="228"></a></p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b"><span class="bbcode-u">Xen</span></span><br>
There has been lots of progress on Xen. We have started external playtesting. The first two chapters, “Xen” and “Gonarch’s Lair”, clock in around two hours. For reference, all five chapters of Xen in HL1 can be completed in approximately one hour! We are really excited to show our work to everyone, but we also want to save the majority of Xen as a surprise.</p>
<p>Here is a brief breakdown of our current progress in each chapter:</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-u">Xen - <span class="bbcode-i">Final Polish</span></span><br>
We have locked the majority of the Xen levels. Most of the design and art is completed, and we are polishing one or two rough edges in the design.<br>
<img src="https://steamcdn-a.akamaihd.net/steamcommunity/public/images/clans/8672783/07b94781006865b3d4d8cef42def2cf059f80a2d.jpg" alt="" width="600" height="338"></p>
<p><span class="bbcode-u">Gonarch’s Lair - <span class="bbcode-i">Art</span></span><br>
As you can see, we have a good amount of art completed for Gonarch. We are doing some last minute design revisions to get the gameplay tight and consistent throughout the chapter, and then we can drop in our already created art. As you might guess, this chapter is very heavy on code and animation. The first map is locked, the second map is finishing its main art pass, and the final map is undergoing some design iterations, with some art already implemented.<br>
<img src="https://steamcdn-a.akamaihd.net/steamcommunity/public/images/clans/8672783/9e44c813da89b502309defe1c409890979f05165.jpg" alt="" width="600" height="338"></p>
<p><span class="bbcode-u">Interloper - <span class="bbcode-i">Final Gameplay</span></span><br>
This chapter has gone through a hefty number of positive and ambitious design revisions since we started it. We are really happy with the direction and iterations that have gone in, for all five maps. They are very close to gameplay complete, and are playable start to finish. We are currently finishing the modular art pieces, trimming some of the chapter’s “fat”, and polishing the last of the rough design edges to produce a streamlined and action-packed conclusion to Xen’s main story.</p>
<p>As Interloper is a significant departure from the rest of Xen, our intention is to get Xen and Gonarch’s Lair completed through the final polish stages first, before shifting the entire team onto Interloper at once, to finish this chapter up in one quick fell swoop.<br>
<img src="https://steamcdn-a.akamaihd.net/steamcommunity/public/images/clans/8672783/9c5b82236870e7789af91b75b02e8eaf33c61527.jpg" alt="" width="600" height="338"></p>
<p><span class="bbcode-u">Nihilanth - <span class="bbcode-i">Gameplay/Art</span></span><br>
The art for this level is completed. Without giving too much more away, we have a really exciting evolution for this chapter, and we are starting the final push to get this chapter completely coded, scripted, and animated.<br>
<img src="https://steamcdn-a.akamaihd.net/steamcommunity/public/images/clans/8672783/750c5e0cb829bed834466fd969302f7068ef6e79.jpg" alt="" width="600" height="338"></p>
<p><span class="bbcode-u">Endgame - <span class="bbcode-i">Final Polish</span></span><br>
This chapter is locked. There are some dependency assets and some polish we have to implement once the rest of the game is complete, but other than that, it is ready to go.<br>
<img src="https://steamcdn-a.akamaihd.net/steamcommunity/public/images/clans/8672783/c854bfbda81c1fab0cbc879d208e8f71d621164d.jpg" alt="" width="600" height="338"></p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b"><span class="bbcode-u">Multiplayer Playdate - 6-30-18</span></span><br>
The Black Mesa devs are getting together for a play date on on Saturday June 30th at 12:00 PM EST (midday). We are looking forward to filling some servers, blowing off some steam, and having a good time.<br>
<img alt=""></p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b"><span class="bbcode-u">Celebrating 20 Years of Half-Life</span></span><br>
Oh cool, so it’s already JUNE. Time flies when you are <span class="bbcode-s">grinding toward a deadline</span> having fun. As many of you are probably already aware, Half-Life will be <span class="bbcode-b">TWENTY</span> this November. We obviously plan on doing some BIG THINGS to celebrate the game that inspired us and became such a huge part of all our lives.</p>
<p>One of the events planned is Black Mesa (Crowbar Collective) having a booth at Syracuse’s <a href="https://retrogamecon.com/" data-bbcode="true">Retro Game Con</a> November 3rd and 4th. Stop by if you are in the area and chat with us. I went last year as a guest and had a great time (and got some sweet video game themed magnets too). More info on this event to come.</p>
<p>We are also considering doing a dev marathon stream of Black Mesa, Half-Life 2, Episode 1, and Episode 2. Would anyone be interested in watching us do that? We would have to figure out the logistics, as we are all not in one place, but that is something that sounds like a good time to us.</p>
<p>There are some other big ideas we would really like to do, but can’t talk about just yet. If you have any ideas, please let us know!</p>
            <p><small>135 posts - 46 participants</small></p>
            <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/summer-update-2018/15386">Read full topic</a></p>
          ]]></description>
          <link>https://leakfree.org/t/summer-update-2018/15386</link>
          <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jun 2018 23:33:41 +0000</pubDate>
          <discourse:topicPinned>No</discourse:topicPinned>
          <discourse:topicClosed>No</discourse:topicClosed>
          <discourse:topicArchived>No</discourse:topicArchived>
          <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-topic-15386</guid>
          <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/summer-update-2018/15386.rss">Summer Update 2018</source>
        </item>
        <item>
          <title>Steam Sale, December Update, and Patch Notes</title>
          <dc:creator><![CDATA[TextFAMGUY1]]></dc:creator>
          <category>News &amp; Developer Updates</category>
          <description><![CDATA[
            <p>[align=center]<div class="lightbox-wrapper"><a class="lightbox" href="https://i.imgur.com/FxOjzO3.jpg" title=""><img src="https://i.imgur.com/FxOjzO3.jpg" alt="" width="690" height="388"><div class="meta"><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-far-image svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#far-image"></use></svg><span class="filename"></span><span class="informations">960×540</span><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-discourse-expand svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#discourse-expand"></use></svg></div></a></div>[/align]</p>
<p>Happy Holidays, and happy Steam Winter Sale everyone! <a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/362890/Black_Mesa/" data-bbcode="true">Black Mesa is currently $4.99, our largest discount yet.</a></p>
<p>We released an update for Black Mesa <span class="bbcode-b">(currently on public beta)</span> that adds real-time dynamic lights, lens flares, god rays, and a host of other features to the existing earthbound sections of the game. The goal of this update is to get the released version of the game as close to our internal build as possible. This way, the final Xen release can be closer to a simple map drop; with less potential for engine and code issues affecting players on their first time playing Xen. We are hoping to test the engine and solve all feature and performance problems before the real release, so that everyone can enjoy our definitive vision of the game without issues.</p>
<p>As promised, here is an update on where we are at with developing the Xen chapters.</p>
<p>[align=center]<div class="lightbox-wrapper"><a class="lightbox" href="https://i.imgur.com/6qzNmJD.jpg" title=""><img src="https://i.imgur.com/6qzNmJD.jpg" alt="" width="500" height="500"><div class="meta"><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-far-image svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#far-image"></use></svg><span class="filename"></span><span class="informations">800×800</span><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-discourse-expand svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#discourse-expand"></use></svg></div></a></div>[/align]</p>
<p>We are striving to make sure Xen is fun, well thought-out, and cohesive. Each chapter has its own theme and artstyle, and we are developing them in parallel to ensure they are all at the same high standard of quality. Xen, in its current form, is made up of 14 maps across these final 5 chapters, with each map alone being significantly larger than the originals. We are putting our full effort into completing Xen in a timely manner so that everyone can have the complete Black Mesa experience!</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b"><span class="bbcode-u">Screenshots From the Update[/size]</span></span></p>
<p><img alt=""></p>
<p><img alt=""></p>
<p><img alt=""></p>
<p><span class="bbcode-u">Upcoming Feature</span>[/size]</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Improved Prop Lighting</span><br>
While developing Xen, we realized the existing Source lighting just wasn’t accurate enough. In the original Source, up to 4 lights are allowed per object and there is no self-shadowing. This works fine for small or medium sized objects, but for something like a massive, detailed rock archway, the limitations appear. In the screenshot, the vines hanging under the arch do not appear properly in shadow, and the arch looks strangely flat because only 4 light samples are being taken.</p>
<p>Our new static lighting supports all the nearby lights in the scene, self-shadows correctly, and also works seamlessly with both our new skydome lighting and our new dynamic lights. This makes a big difference “merging” the objects with their environment.</p>
<p>Left is the old style of prop lighting, Right is the new:</p>
<p><img alt=""></p>
<p><img alt=""></p>
<p>The new lighting is much less flat overall, displays colours which are truer to the scene’s real tone, and shadows in a much more appealing and realistic manner.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b"><span class="bbcode-u">Patch Notes[/size]</span></span></p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b"><span class="bbcode-u">New Features</span></span><br>
<span class="bbcode-b">Dynamic Lights</span> - Full featured dynamic lights that are able to cast real time shadows, project textures, and emit volumetric light (godrays). These have been implemented across earthbound to help amp up the visual fidelity and “nextgen-ness”.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Lens Flares</span> - New entity that creates a lens flare with customizable colors, styles, and effects. These have been implemented across earthbound too; only on lights we deemed very bright or important enough to warrant a lens flare.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Overhauled CSM and Godrays</span> - Cascade Shadow Maps (CSM) have been totally rewritten and now run better than before. Godrays are completely overhauled to run smoother and operate off of a new entity that automatically gets the sun angle from the environment light.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">New Crossbow Scope</span> - Crossbow scope no longer uses an in game camera to zoom in. This makes the scope easier to aim and increases performance by removing a second rendering pass. It also fixes a number of visual bugs with using the scope throughout the game.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Image Based Ambient Lighting</span> - Lighting can now be generated based off of the skybox image. This allows mappers to have significantly more accurate environmental lighting, which automatically takes into account the nuances and difference colours of the sky. This is unlike any other version of Source, where environment lighting is simply one flat colour picked by the mapper.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">4 Way Texture Support</span> - 4 way texture blends are now supported in engine, each with their own bump map, specular map, and procedural blending options. This allows for much more variety in texturing natural landscapes, as most older versions of Source only support 2 way texture blends.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Color Correction</span> - All existing earthbound maps now utilize color correction.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Better Hammer Compiles </span>- Hammer now uses current windows themes and the compiler does not block you from continuing to use Hammer; running in a separate batch window (similar to CSGO).</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Added Support for $treesway</span> - Props can now move in the wind using tree sway. This creates more much more dynamic looking natural environments, with a very small performance cost.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Implemented Hammer Instance Support</span> - Hammer can now instance other VMFs to support modular level design.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Improved Blood Particles</span> - Updated and improved blood particle effects for NPCs, to not look as blocky and unrealistic.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">New Long Jump Mechanics</span> - Modified long jump mechanics to be more similar to modern day games (press “jump” twice to long jump). Added a long jump recharge meter and “mana” mechanic to keep people from spamming long jump in both single and multiplayer (the long jump has a limited charge, with a medium base recharge rate, and the jumps consume this charge). Added a small “pop jump” mechanic to allow course corrects while player is mid air.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Dynamic Light Implementation</span> - Moved all existing old Source dynamic lights over to our new dynamic lights system. This should improve visuals and reduce hitching when a dynamic light is activated (such as explosions, flashlight, Xen portal, muzzle flash, etc).</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Doubled Source Displacement Limit </span>- Max number of displacements allowed per map from 2048 to 4096. This allows the creation of more detailed and expansive natural outdoor environments.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Fixed Hammer Shaded Textured View</span> - No more horrendous fullbright mapping!</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b"><span class="bbcode-u">Bug Fixes</span></span><br>
<span class="bbcode-b">NPCs</span><br>
Fixed HECU not holding weapons correctly</p>
<p>Fixed scientist ties jiggling out of control when FPS is low</p>
<p>Fixed instances where Vort would not react to player</p>
<p>Fixed ragdoll errors after loading a saved game</p>
<p>Fixed rappelling HECU sometimes getting stuck in Osprey</p>
<p>Fixed helicopter rockets getting stuck underwater</p>
<p>Fixed grenade throw mechanics, grenades should be much easier to throw now</p>
<p>Fixed crash from blowing up zombie HECU</p>
<p>Fixed HECU turrets not shooting at zombie HECU</p>
<p>Added IK (Inverse Kinematics) setup on Houndeye/Bullsquid</p>
<p>Fixed Houndeye hitboxes, ragdoll, and gibs</p>
<p>Added glow back to Houndeye’s blue stripes</p>
<p>Fixed skinning on Houndeye</p>
<p>Fixed player being able to pick up assassin’s pistol</p>
<p>Fixed and improved Alien Controller AI and combat</p>
<p>Fixed Agrunt hornet tracking to be more fair, making the Agunts more fun to fight</p>
<p>Updated Vort eyes</p>
<p>Fixed Vorts getting stuck after loading a save game</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Multiplayer</span><br>
Added HUD icon for players using voice chat in multiplayer</p>
<p>Added hit indicators in multiplayer</p>
<p>Fixed UI spectate bugs in multiplayer</p>
<p>Increased crossbow zoom sensitivity in multiplayer</p>
<p>Fixed satchel being able to be thrown through the ground</p>
<p>Fixed TOW launchers in Crossfire breaking if you moved them too much</p>
<p>Fix fast weapon switch getting turned off in multiplayer</p>
<p>Fixed ent_create not respecting sv_cheats</p>
<p>Fixed filter_damage being able to crash servers</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Miscellaneous</span><br>
Temporarily removed blood on weapons and hands, to fix the engine hitching when the effect is first applied</p>
<p>Fixed Tau firing with limited ammo. The Tau will not longer auto fire if you do not have enough ammo for a full charge.</p>
<p>Fixed Tau overcharge not hurting the player</p>
<p>Fixed soundscapes not playing underwater</p>
<p>Fixed maps crashing if there were no lights in VMF</p>
<p>Fixed UI errors with certain translation files (Russian, Chinese)</p>
<p>Fixed shotgun shells disappearing during reload animation</p>
<p>Fixed missing translations in Italian closed captions</p>
<p>Split last map of Lambda Core into two maps, for better performance</p>
<p>Fixed VRAD to always pay attention to “Disable Vertex Lighting” in Hammer</p>
<p>Fixed crossbow aiming too high when zoomed in</p>
<p>Fixed various crashes and bugs when using the workshop tools</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b"><span class="bbcode-u">Known Issues[/size]</span></span><br>
Dynamic light shadows sometimes flicker</p>
<p>Wall decals sometimes flicker</p>
<p>Props sometimes “pop” with different lighting values</p>
<p>Shadows from dynamic lights sometimes flicker on surfaces tangent to light, or when light is moving very fast</p>
<p>When using dynamic light godrays, the game is slightly blurred</p>
<p>Player occasionally gets stuck in Inbound tram when turning corner; issue fixes itself</p>
<p>Cameras in game are off angle</p>
<p>Gman gibs are wrong in multiplayer</p>
<p>Crossbow will force you to descope after firing a shot in multiplayer</p>
<p>Thanks!<br>
The Black Mesa Team</p>
            <p><small>94 posts - 35 participants</small></p>
            <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/steam-sale-december-update-and-patch-notes/15312">Read full topic</a></p>
          ]]></description>
          <link>https://leakfree.org/t/steam-sale-december-update-and-patch-notes/15312</link>
          <pubDate>Sun, 24 Dec 2017 08:45:27 +0000</pubDate>
          <discourse:topicPinned>No</discourse:topicPinned>
          <discourse:topicClosed>No</discourse:topicClosed>
          <discourse:topicArchived>No</discourse:topicArchived>
          <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-topic-15312</guid>
          <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/steam-sale-december-update-and-patch-notes/15312.rss">Steam Sale, December Update, and Patch Notes</source>
        </item>
        <item>
          <title>Bad News, Good News</title>
          <dc:creator><![CDATA[TextFAMGUY1]]></dc:creator>
          <category>News &amp; Developer Updates</category>
          <description><![CDATA[
            <p>[align=center]<img src="https://cdn.edgecast.steamstatic.com/steamcommunity/public/images/clans/8672783/1be45c913ae11f9ce1a037c376444aa6cc5f2e2a.jpg" alt="" width="" height="">[/align]<br>
Straight to the bad news: we are pushing back the release of Xen. We are truly sorry for getting everyone’s hopes up and then delaying… again. We worked very hard to make December, but we are not yet ready. As a team, we take FULL responsibility for that. We have an internal deadline we are confident in, and we will be getting everyone more details as we get closer to that date.</p>
<p>Thank you again to our community and Early Access supporters. The funding from Early Access has allowed us to hire many new talented developers, and has allowed older developers to put more time in the project. Simply put, Xen has proven to be an enormous undertaking, and while we are managing it to the best of our ability, it is proving to take longer than we estimated.</p>
<p>The good news is that we will be releasing a large update in December to test all of the new features that have been developed for Xen. We have changed a number of things within the Source Engine, and we want to make sure they all work on the myriad of PCs out there. By enabling the new tech on the Earthbound section of the game, we can get the engine/code fully stabilized on Steam before we drop the final chapters.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">In December we will also have an update on where our Xen chapters stand, show some additional media, and deploy the engine update.</span></p>
<p>Here are some features that will be in the update:</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b"><span class="bbcode-u">Lens Flare</span></span><br>
We’ve created a custom lens flare entity, and have added lens flares to important light sources in the game. Don’t worry, we will spare your eyes and not go overboard with our new lens flare tech. We think it adds a nice layer of polish to the Earthbound lighting and we hope to use it to really sell the alien feel of Xen… and add endless frustration to the debate about whether or not Gordon wears a helmet.</p>
<p><img alt=""></p>
<p><img alt=""></p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b"><span class="bbcode-u">Dynamic Lights</span></span><br>
We’ve shown some dynamic lights in the last update. Here are a few other sections that got the dynamic light treatment. Lights can simply cast light, cast shadows, and even cast volumetric godrays.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-u">Security Joop with Dynamic Lights and Lens Flares</span><br>
<img src="https://cdn.edgecast.steamstatic.com/steamcommunity/public/images/clans/8672783/73339ac40218cae4ce03fdddb481813f2c973019.gif" alt="" width="" height=""></p>
<p><span class="bbcode-u">OAR Rocket Launch with Dynamic Shadows, Light Rays, and a Lens Flare</span><br>
<img src="https://i.imgur.com/RqrmWXc.gif" alt="" width="400" height="300"></p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b"><span class="bbcode-u">4 Way Texture Blends</span></span><br>
We incorporated a 4 way texture blending system like the one seen in Counter Strike: Global Offensive, and improved upon it. Our level designers have 4 texture layers to blend, each with its own bump map and environment map (SSBM OR Normal Bump). Like other versions of the shader, level designers and artists can blend between the 4 layers procedurally using light and dark values of the diffuse textures.</p>
<p><img alt=""></p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b"><span class="bbcode-u">Image Based Ambient Lighting</span></span><br>
Lighting can now be generated from the image of the skybox texture. This gives level designers a very quick and accurate base lighting for outdoor maps. The example below has just a light_env in the scene, with no colors. All colored lighting is created automatically from the skybox image.</p>
<p><img alt=""></p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b"><span class="bbcode-u">CSM and Godray Performance</span></span><br>
We’ve improved the performance on Cascade Shadow Maps and Godrays and made them both more straightforward to implement on the Hammer side. Godrays are now placed with our newLight_Dir entity and automatically get ray angles from the light_env. Rays not only run better, but look smoother as well.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-u">Environment Light Godrays</span><br>
<img alt=""></p>
<p><span class="bbcode-u">Rays From New Dynamic Lights</span><br>
<img alt=""></p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b"><span class="bbcode-u">Xen Concept Art</span></span><br>
Concepts as seen in <a href="https://www.pcgamer.com/the-story-of-half-life-remake-black-mesa/" data-bbcode="true">PCGamer</a>. In addition to the Xen screenshots we have released, these Interloper concepts highlight the difference in environment types we have.</p>
<p><img alt=""><br>
<img alt=""></p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b"><span class="bbcode-u">Black Mesa 60% Of</span></span><span class="bbcode-b"><span class="bbcode-u">f</span></span><br>
We are also on sale until November 28th for the Steam Thanksgiving sale!</p>
<p><img src="https://cdn.edgecast.steamstatic.com/steamcommunity/public/images/clans/8672783/2e37aea759e0823e7002ee6664946e92ef072b2a.jpg" alt="" width="" height=""></p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b"><span class="bbcode-u">Stay Tuned</span></span><br>
We will have a bunch more information next month!</p>
<p><img src="https://i.imgur.com/yGClDsf.gif" alt="" width="610" height="258"></p>
            <p><small>92 posts - 38 participants</small></p>
            <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/bad-news-good-news/15303">Read full topic</a></p>
          ]]></description>
          <link>https://leakfree.org/t/bad-news-good-news/15303</link>
          <pubDate>Sun, 26 Nov 2017 16:28:25 +0000</pubDate>
          <discourse:topicPinned>No</discourse:topicPinned>
          <discourse:topicClosed>No</discourse:topicClosed>
          <discourse:topicArchived>No</discourse:topicArchived>
          <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-topic-15303</guid>
          <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/bad-news-good-news/15303.rss">Bad News, Good News</source>
        </item>
        <item>
          <title>Summer Update</title>
          <dc:creator><![CDATA[TextFAMGUY1]]></dc:creator>
          <category>News &amp; Developer Updates</category>
          <description><![CDATA[
            <p><img alt=""></p>
<p>Happy summer all! We hope that everyone is having a great start to their summer. To celebrate, we proudly present to you our first public screenshots of a Xen exterior. All running real-time, in- game, with no edits.</p>
<p><img alt=""></p>
<p>Unfortunately, as some of you may have already predicted, we are going to need to push back our planned release of Xen to later this year, in December. We know that this is not what anyone would want to hear, but after taking a long and hard look at what we want to achieve, we have decided that this is for the best. We do not want to compromise on Xen’s quality in any way. That said, we consider December to be a do-or-die deadline.</p>
<p>To soften the blow of the bad news, here are some additional tidbits and updates regarding what we have done for Xen so far.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Example of the Level of Detail We Are Going For</span><br>
<img src="https://cdn.edgecast.steamstatic.com/steamcommunity/public/images/clans/8672783/acf583169cb574d192be207b0e7017cb6d2b4eee.jpg" alt="" width="" height=""></p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Interloper Map B Scale</span><br>
<img src="https://cdn.edgecast.steamstatic.com/steamcommunity/public/images/clans/8672783/33c2f236eabd91a4582509a0cac7922ea121c4d5.png" alt="" width="" height=""></p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">New Dynamic Light System</span><br>
As part of our continued efforts to bring Xen’s graphics up to the best possible standard that they can be, we have upgraded Source to a new deferred rendering system that supports fully dynamic lights! These new “next-gen” lights cast real-time light, shadows and god rays. These won’t replace all the lights in the game, but we can use them in many special cases where we want the lights to be particularly gorgeous. These lights are much better optimized than other Source implementations of dynamic lights, and are more robust.</p>
<p><img src="https://cdn.edgecast.steamstatic.com/steamcommunity/public/images/clans/8672783/72537b641624568a7e62616f92bb90af361563f2.gif" alt="" width="" height=""></p>
<p>Not only will this new lighting system help crank parts of the the game up to 11 in terms of graphical fidelity, these will also be powerful tools for modders as well!</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Color Correction</span><br>
We’ve started a color correction pass for the whole game. The goal is to better unify the game’s visual style and to add full screen effects during the more intense sections. Most of these effects will be quite subtle, but here is a more noticeable example.</p>
<p><img src="https://cdn.edgecast.steamstatic.com/steamcommunity/public/images/clans/8672783/c9fada20d4280e33d335e2ef8099c4a5c4143f93.gif" alt="" width="" height=""></p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Weapon Holds</span><br>
We fixed the soldiers holding the weapons wrong. It took some serious animation trickery to retarget the bones on top of the existing Half-Life 2 animation library, but it worked well once we figured it out. No more hands clipping through the guns!</p>
<p><img alt=""></p>
<p>Thanks as always to you guys, our wonderful community, for your support! As always, we will continue to work at full speed on Xen, and we hope to have more updates, information and media for you guys soon.</p>
            <p><small>161 posts - 65 participants</small></p>
            <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/summer-update/15193">Read full topic</a></p>
          ]]></description>
          <link>https://leakfree.org/t/summer-update/15193</link>
          <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2017 08:08:38 +0000</pubDate>
          <discourse:topicPinned>No</discourse:topicPinned>
          <discourse:topicClosed>No</discourse:topicClosed>
          <discourse:topicArchived>No</discourse:topicArchived>
          <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-topic-15193</guid>
          <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/summer-update/15193.rss">Summer Update</source>
        </item>
        <item>
          <title>Community Game - 23rd December 2016 - 9:00PM EST</title>
          <dc:creator><![CDATA[TextFAMGUY1]]></dc:creator>
          <category>News &amp; Developer Updates</category>
          <description><![CDATA[
            <p>This is just a quick heads up to let everyone know that the dev team are going to be holding an impromptu little game of community deathmatch in Black Mesa on Friday! Feel free to hop in and join us, if you fancy chatting with and maybe even killing a few devs! It will be nothing formal and serious, just a fun little community game to celebrate the recent Xen screenshot, and the end to a pretty crazy year! Expect a few devs, maybe a few friends of ours, and hopefully a bunch of you lovely lot!</p>
<p>The game is currently scheduled for:</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Friday 23/12/16 (23rd December) - 9:00PM EST</span></p>
<p>All you have to do to play with us, is to just fire up Black Mesa this time and come find which server we’re on. Shouldn’t be too hard at all! As we move into the New Year, we hope to start doing these community games more regularly again, as well as firing up some live streams again, where we can talk more about the development of Black Mesa, its future, and all that fun stuff.</p>
<p>For those of you who can’t make it, as we’re sure many of you won’t be able to, we wish you all very happy holidays. Fret not; this will happen again in the future too!</p>
            <p><small>8 posts - 6 participants</small></p>
            <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/community-game-23rd-december-2016-9-00pm-est/15035">Read full topic</a></p>
          ]]></description>
          <link>https://leakfree.org/t/community-game-23rd-december-2016-9-00pm-est/15035</link>
          <pubDate>Fri, 23 Dec 2016 11:08:26 +0000</pubDate>
          <discourse:topicPinned>No</discourse:topicPinned>
          <discourse:topicClosed>No</discourse:topicClosed>
          <discourse:topicArchived>No</discourse:topicArchived>
          <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-topic-15035</guid>
          <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/community-game-23rd-december-2016-9-00pm-est/15035.rss">Community Game - 23rd December 2016 - 9:00PM EST</source>
        </item>
        <item>
          <title>Xen Holiday Screenshot</title>
          <dc:creator><![CDATA[TextFAMGUY1]]></dc:creator>
          <category>News &amp; Developer Updates</category>
          <description><![CDATA[
            <p><span class="bbcode-b">Happy Holidays!</span></p>
<p>The team remains, as always, hard at work on Xen! Currently our specific focus is on gameplay: crafting a fun and cohesive experience from start to finish. We want our version of Xen to feel like it really belongs with the rest of the game in terms of mechanics, cohesion and progression. But we also want to push the boundaries and explore this unique and varied setting; to build an experience that feels both fresh and familiar to players from all walks of Half-Life veterancy. While our Xen is certainly going to be gorgeous, we are first and foremost really committed to making sure that the gameplay works on every level.</p>
<p>To give a bit of an exciting tease into what we’re doing at the moment, and as our own little holiday gift to you lot, please enjoy our first ever publicly released screenshot of Xen!</p>
<p>[align=center]<img alt="">[/align]</p>
<p>We will have more media for the community in the coming months, as well as more detailed updates as to how we are progressing. Right now we are up against a tough deadline, but we are committed and excited to work towards it and to finally unveil the definitive Black Mesa experience for everyone to enjoy.</p>
<p>Be kind to each other out there, and again, have a happy holiday!</p>
            <p><small>411 posts - 84 participants</small></p>
            <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/xen-holiday-screenshot/15032">Read full topic</a></p>
          ]]></description>
          <link>https://leakfree.org/t/xen-holiday-screenshot/15032</link>
          <pubDate>Thu, 22 Dec 2016 06:39:39 +0000</pubDate>
          <discourse:topicPinned>No</discourse:topicPinned>
          <discourse:topicClosed>No</discourse:topicClosed>
          <discourse:topicArchived>No</discourse:topicArchived>
          <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-topic-15032</guid>
          <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/xen-holiday-screenshot/15032.rss">Xen Holiday Screenshot</source>
        </item>
        <item>
          <title>Xen Timeline</title>
          <dc:creator><![CDATA[TextFAMGUY1]]></dc:creator>
          <category>News &amp; Developer Updates</category>
          <description><![CDATA[
            <p><span class="bbcode-b">Happy Halloween!</span><br>
We wanted to use the holiday and the sale to announce our rough timeline for Xen. We are currently targeting a summer 2017 release. We will keep you up to date on our progress and we plan to show off some media as we finish developing Xen to give everyone a glimpse at what we are working on.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Why so Long?</span><br>
We can’t overemphasize how much work it was to get the game on Steam. Most of our effort before launching was put into porting to the retail engine and getting the game to work better than it did in the mod. Since release, the team has been focused on developing Xen. We even planned our updates to have features that would help improve the earthbound levels and Xen (for example CSM).</p>
<p>We want to do Xen the justice it deserves, and have it be the definitive climax to the Half-Life 1 story. To do this we have completely redesigned and expanded the Xen levels to what we think Valve would have done without the limitations of the time.</p>
<p>To help illustrate this, here are some comparison shots of our levels to the original Half-Life levels in Hammer. Not only are our maps substantially bigger than the originals, there are more of them as well.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-u"><span class="bbcode-b">Comparison of HL1 and Black Mesa’s first Xen Map</span></span><br>
<div class="lightbox-wrapper"><a class="lightbox" href="https://i.imgur.com/0jsdWcF.png" title=""><img src="https://i.imgur.com/0jsdWcF.png" alt="" width="571" height="499"><div class="meta"><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-far-image svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#far-image"></use></svg><span class="filename"></span><span class="informations">4280×3742</span><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-discourse-expand svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#discourse-expand"></use></svg></div></a></div></p>
<p><span class="bbcode-u"><span class="bbcode-b">Comparison of the first map of Interloper</span></span><br>
<div class="lightbox-wrapper"><a class="lightbox" href="https://i.imgur.com/zx35JxK.jpg" title=""><img src="https://i.imgur.com/zx35JxK.jpg" alt="" width="582" height="500"><div class="meta"><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-far-image svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#far-image"></use></svg><span class="filename"></span><span class="informations">5870×5035</span><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-discourse-expand svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#discourse-expand"></use></svg></div></a></div></p>
<p>As always we want to thank our awesome community for supporting us in Early Access and for being as passionate as us about Half-Life. We have been working really hard on Xen and we hope you are as excited as us to see the full release of Black Mesa. We’ll have more in game media to show off in the near future!</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Patch</span><br>
We also wanted to quickly mention that we have a patch coming for our latest update. This patch fixes:</p>
<ul>
<li>The hitching on Linux multiplayer servers and on Linux single player</li>
<li>Russian closed captions</li>
<li>UI fonts being broken for people that do not have Steam set to English</li>
<li>Workshop publish tool not launching</li>
<li>ZECU torso crashing hammer and the game</li>
</ul>
<p>Thanks!</p>
<p>-The Black Mesa Team</p>
            <p><small>161 posts - 60 participants</small></p>
            <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/xen-timeline/14963">Read full topic</a></p>
          ]]></description>
          <link>https://leakfree.org/t/xen-timeline/14963</link>
          <pubDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2016 09:56:22 +0000</pubDate>
          <discourse:topicPinned>No</discourse:topicPinned>
          <discourse:topicClosed>No</discourse:topicClosed>
          <discourse:topicArchived>No</discourse:topicArchived>
          <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-topic-14963</guid>
          <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/xen-timeline/14963.rss">Xen Timeline</source>
        </item>
        <item>
          <title>Current Source Engine Server Exploit - Proceed with Caution, Mr. Freeman.</title>
          <dc:creator><![CDATA[Fr0z3n]]></dc:creator>
          <category>News &amp; Developer Updates</category>
          <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Hey everyone.</p>
<p>I hate having to write posts like this, but I’ve had a few people come to me over the past few days warning me about a new Source Engine Server exploit that is making the rounds across various games. There has been some reports that Black Mesa MP Servers<span class="bbcode-i"> could</span> be the target of the exploit, if someone with malicious intent wants it to. Until Valve (and then us) patch a fix in, I’ve made this post to inform everyone of potential danger and steps on how to avoid infection.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">What is the exploit?</span><br>
I don’t want to go into details on how to replicate the exploit, but I will say what it does, as I understand it. If you load up into an infected Source Server, the exploit allows the server to inject a file into your computers start up folder. You won’t know this happens. When you launch your computer again (ie, it starts up again) the file will be executed and bad stuff happens. This exploit/infection can only occur if the server is set up to do it, that is someone needs to set up the server to cause it to happen.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">How do I know if a server is infected?</span><br>
As far as I know, there is nothing that says “THIS SERVER IS INFECTED!” I don’t know of any current ways to check. Your best bet is to make sure that you are connecting to our official servers, or servers where you know that the server host has personally checked to make sure the exploit is not active. A list of our official servers are listed below, with IP. Additionally, when you connect to a server, connect to it directly via IP, not via the server browser list.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">What can I do to prevent getting hit by this exploit?</span><br>
Like I mentioned before, only connect to trusted servers via the console command “connect .”  Additionally, make sure that the server you’re connected to is trusted to not be infected and if you can check with the server admin to check, that is even better. Since it’s very easy to make a server with the same name as your favourite server, this will  ensure that you are connecting to the server you want to connect to. Also, check to see if the server you’re connecting to has a name that is an exact copy. If there are two servers with the same name, it’s possible that one could be infected. Use caution or avoid the server entirely.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">What should I do if I think I’ve been infected?</span><br>
Immediately run a virus scan. There are many free antivirus scanners online. I personally have used AVG and Avast! but if you have a favourite, then you can use that. Additionally check your start up folder to make sure that any files in there are not suspicious or malicious.</p>
<p>While we all know that Black Mesa has the biggest MP population of any MP game ever (that was sarcasm and a joke, by the way), we can make sure everyone stays safe. If everyone is vigilant and careful with the servers they connect to, follow the steps I’ve provided above and just use a little bit of common sense, no one will be infected.</p>
<p>If you have any questions, please ask them in this thread.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b"><span class="bbcode-i">- Joe</span></span></p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Full list of Official, Crowbar Collective Black Mesa Multiplayer Servers:</span><br>
<span class="bbcode-b"><span class="bbcode-i">New York City:</span></span><br>
<a href="http://nyc3.game.blackmesagame.com:27015" rel="nofollow noopener">nyc3.game.blackmesagame.com:27015</a> - Deathmatch<br>
<a href="http://nyc3.game.blackmesagame.com:27016" rel="nofollow noopener">nyc3.game.blackmesagame.com:27016</a> - Team Deathmatch<br>
<a href="http://nyc2.game.blackmesagame.com:27015" rel="nofollow noopener">nyc2.game.blackmesagame.com:27015</a> - Deathmatch (Beta)<br>
<a href="http://nyc2.game.blackmesagame.com:27016" rel="nofollow noopener">nyc2.game.blackmesagame.com:27016</a> - Team Deathmatch (Beta)</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b"><span class="bbcode-i">San Francisco:</span></span><br>
<a href="http://sfo1.game.blackmesagame.com:27015" rel="nofollow noopener">sfo1.game.blackmesagame.com:27015</a> - Deathmatch<br>
<a href="http://sfo1.game.blackmesagame.com:27016" rel="nofollow noopener">sfo1.game.blackmesagame.com:27016</a> - Team Deathmatch</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b"><span class="bbcode-i">London:</span></span><br>
<a href="http://lon1.game.blackmesagame.com:27015" rel="nofollow noopener">lon1.game.blackmesagame.com:27015</a> - Deathmatch<br>
<a href="http://lon1.game.blackmesagame.com:27016" rel="nofollow noopener">lon1.game.blackmesagame.com:27016</a> - Team Deathmatch</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b"><span class="bbcode-i">Amsterdam:</span></span><br>
<a href="http://ams2.game.blackmesagame.com:27015" rel="nofollow noopener">ams2.game.blackmesagame.com:27015</a> - Deathmatch<br>
<a href="http://ams2.game.blackmesagame.com:27016" rel="nofollow noopener">ams2.game.blackmesagame.com:27016</a>  - Team Deathmatch</p>
            <p><small>12 posts - 10 participants</small></p>
            <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/current-source-engine-server-exploit-proceed-with-caution-mr-freeman/14694">Read full topic</a></p>
          ]]></description>
          <link>https://leakfree.org/t/current-source-engine-server-exploit-proceed-with-caution-mr-freeman/14694</link>
          <pubDate>Wed, 24 Feb 2016 17:02:43 +0000</pubDate>
          <discourse:topicPinned>No</discourse:topicPinned>
          <discourse:topicClosed>No</discourse:topicClosed>
          <discourse:topicArchived>No</discourse:topicArchived>
          <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-topic-14694</guid>
          <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/current-source-engine-server-exploit-proceed-with-caution-mr-freeman/14694.rss">Current Source Engine Server Exploit - Proceed with Caution, Mr. Freeman.</source>
        </item>
        <item>
          <title>[WORKAROUND] How to enable supported Closed Captions.</title>
          <dc:creator><![CDATA[Fr0z3n]]></dc:creator>
          <category>News &amp; Developer Updates</category>
          <description><![CDATA[
            <p><span class="bbcode-b"><span class="bbcode-i"><span class="bbcode-u">Closed Captions forBlack Mesa Work-around:</span></span></span></p>
<p>Hey guys, in theCrossfire Update we updated all our currently supported closedcaptions. Unfortunately, we thought that Black Mesa would pick up onyour steam language preference, and would automatically change yourBlack Mesa closed captions. This has since proven that this isincorrect. Until we can get an officially support UI option forclosed captions, I have a work around for you that is 10 easy steps!</p>
<ol>
<li>Launch Black Mesa</li>
<li>Click Options</li>
<li>Selection theKeyboard Tab, then click “Advanced…”</li>
<li>Check “EnableDeveloper console (~)</li>
<li>Click “OK”then “OK” again.</li>
<li>Click ~ to openyour developer console</li>
<li>type cc_lang</li>
</ol>
<ul>
<li>For example, if you wanted finnish, type cc_lang Finnish.</li>
<li>We currently support English, Italian, Spanish, German, Finnish and Norwegian Languages.</li>
<li>You will most likely get a missing resources error. THIS IS NORMAL. KEEP FOLLOWING THE INSTRUCTIONS.</li>
</ul>
<ol>
<li>Close Black Mesa</li>
<li>Exit Steamcompletely. That is, completely close everything down and end the steamprocesses.</li>
<li>Re launch steam.</li>
<li>Launch BlackMesa. Your closed captions should now be in the language that youwant. Enjoy!</li>
</ol>
<p>We apologize for this inconvenience.</p>
<p>GERMAN: (Thanks yrr!)</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-u">UNTERTITEL IN BLACK MESA AKTIVIEREN - WORKAROUND</span></p>
<ol>
<li>Black Mesa öffnen</li>
<li>Auf <span class="bbcode-i">Optionen</span> klicken</li>
<li>
<span class="bbcode-i">Tastatur</span>-Reiter auswählen, <span class="bbcode-i">weiteres</span> klicken</li>
<li>Haken bei <span class="bbcode-i">Entwickler Konsole aktivieren (~)</span> setzen</li>
<li>
<span class="bbcode-i">OK </span>klicken, dann nochmal <span class="bbcode-i">OK</span> klicken</li>
<li>~ drücken, um Entwickler Konsole zu öffnen</li>
<li>cc_lang eingeben, <span class="bbcode-i">Enter </span>drücken</li>
</ol>
<ul>
<li>Beispiel: Für Finnisch, <span class="bbcode-i">cc_lang Finnish </span>eingeben</li>
<li>Bisher werden Englisch, Italienisch, Spanisch, Deutsch, Finnisch und Norwegisch unterstütz (Achtung ! Dies sind die alten Mod-Versionen !)</li>
</ul>
<ol>
<li>Black Mesa komplett schließen</li>
<li>Steam ebenfalls komplett schließen (Taskmanager um ebenfalls Prozesse zu beenden und sicherzugehen, dass nichts mehr im Hintergrund läuft)</li>
<li>Steam neu öffnen</li>
<li>Black Mesa öffnen. Die Untertitel sollten nun aktiviert sein<br>
(Alle Schritte unter Vorbehalt und ohne Gewähr ! Dieser Post bzw. die Schritte können in Zukunft geändert und aktualisiert werden!)</li>
</ol>
<p>(If someone cantranslate this for me into the aforementioned languages, that wouldbe awesome!)</p>
            <p><small>13 posts - 4 participants</small></p>
            <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/workaround-how-to-enable-supported-closed-captions/14520">Read full topic</a></p>
          ]]></description>
          <link>https://leakfree.org/t/workaround-how-to-enable-supported-closed-captions/14520</link>
          <pubDate>Wed, 23 Dec 2015 04:03:16 +0000</pubDate>
          <discourse:topicPinned>No</discourse:topicPinned>
          <discourse:topicClosed>No</discourse:topicClosed>
          <discourse:topicArchived>No</discourse:topicArchived>
          <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-topic-14520</guid>
          <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/workaround-how-to-enable-supported-closed-captions/14520.rss">[WORKAROUND] How to enable supported Closed Captions.</source>
        </item>
        <item>
          <title>Black Mesa Public Beta</title>
          <dc:creator><![CDATA[Fr0z3n]]></dc:creator>
          <category>News &amp; Developer Updates</category>
          <description><![CDATA[
            <p>[align=center]Black Mesa Public Beta [/size]<br>
Now in… well… beta.[/size][/align]<br>
Hey guys!</p>
<p>Today we’re starting a small scale launch of the Black Mesa Public Beta. We’re hoping to use for more larger scale things, and more consistently in the future, but we’re going to let you guys try it out first and let us know… it’s like we’re Beta’ing a beta ish… thing… Yea. It’s Meta. If you like it, let us know. If you don’t like it, DEFINITELY let us know.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">What is the Public Beta?</span><br>
Much like other public betas you’ll see in other games, this beta is for testing out patches before they go live to the full client. This beta is completely optional and not recommended for people who don’t want to play potentially buggy aspects of the game.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Why are we doing this?</span><br>
We’re busy folks and sometimes, we miss things. Sometimes, we miss a lot of things. This beta is just one more additional step to insuring we miss as little things as possible, after we test things. More importantly this allows us to test things on a wider range of computers and hardware than we currently have on our team. We said we wanted to try and include all you guys (yes, you. You in the chair) in development and be more transparent with how things are working behind the scenes.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">If I find some bugs, where should I post about it?</span><br>
We’ll be putting together a centralized place for you to put and report BUGS soon. This will not be for feature requests. If you have an idea for a feature that you think might help better and improve the game, let us know on one of the other subforums. For now, we just need you to check to make sure everything is working with our current patches. You can post any issues here, for now.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">What does the Public Beta mean for the future?</span><br>
For now, we’re just doing it to test patches, but that is not to say we MIGHT be using it to test Multiplayer maps, new gamemodes, or more… <span class="bbcode-i">That “or more” bit, doesn’t include testing Xen. Sorry guys!</span> When a public beta patch is dropped, there will be a post about it, and you’ll be able to play with it if you want. Right now, you cannot play multiplayer while in the Public Beta Branch, unless explicitly said, or you’re playing on a Beta Server… There are currently no Beta servers, so you won’t be doing anything with Multiplayer, just yet.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Awesome! How can I participate in Beta?</span><br>
Glad you asked, Black Mesa fan! First off, you’ll need Black Mesa on Steam. If you don’t have that already, might want to get it. Right click on in your steam browser, click “Properties.” Go to the Beta Tab. Select “Public Beta.” You’re now in the Public Beta! If you no longer want to be part of the public beta branch, you can go back to the Beta’s tab under properties, and set your beta to “none - Opt out of all betas”</p>
<p>There’s more info coming along with this feature, if you guys like it, so let us know (also in this thread) what you think, or how we can use this better. If there’s something you think we should pay attention to, or use this for in the future (not for Xen!) let us know.</p>
            <p><small>44 posts - 17 participants</small></p>
            <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/black-mesa-public-beta/14285">Read full topic</a></p>
          ]]></description>
          <link>https://leakfree.org/t/black-mesa-public-beta/14285</link>
          <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jul 2015 00:21:01 +0000</pubDate>
          <discourse:topicPinned>No</discourse:topicPinned>
          <discourse:topicClosed>No</discourse:topicClosed>
          <discourse:topicArchived>No</discourse:topicArchived>
          <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-topic-14285</guid>
          <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/black-mesa-public-beta/14285.rss">Black Mesa Public Beta</source>
        </item>
        <item>
          <title>Official Black Mesa Workshop Collection - Now Online</title>
          <dc:creator><![CDATA[Fr0z3n]]></dc:creator>
          <category>News &amp; Developer Updates</category>
          <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Hey guys!</p>
<p>I’m proud to announce that the <a href="https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=455703316" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Black Mesa Workshop Showcase Collection</a> is now online. This is a workshop collection of mods that the Crowbar team feels are above average or have been featured on <a href="https://forums.blackmesasource.com/index.php/Thread/28041-Introducing-The-Test-Chamber-The-Black-Mesa-Livestream-Show/" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">The Test Chamber Livestream</a>.</p>
<p>Over the life of Black Mesa, we plan to add more and more workshop contributions to this list, all of which are made by you. We’re still a growing modding community, and we hope to use this collection as sort of a scrap book of the highlights of that growth. There’s more plans for the modding side of Black Mesa coming in the next coming weeks.</p>
<p>Stay tuned, and as always: continue creating, Black Mesa!</p>
            <p><small>6 posts - 6 participants</small></p>
            <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/official-black-mesa-workshop-collection-now-online/14173">Read full topic</a></p>
          ]]></description>
          <link>https://leakfree.org/t/official-black-mesa-workshop-collection-now-online/14173</link>
          <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jun 2015 17:59:04 +0000</pubDate>
          <discourse:topicPinned>No</discourse:topicPinned>
          <discourse:topicClosed>No</discourse:topicClosed>
          <discourse:topicArchived>No</discourse:topicArchived>
          <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-topic-14173</guid>
          <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/official-black-mesa-workshop-collection-now-online/14173.rss">Official Black Mesa Workshop Collection - Now Online</source>
        </item>
        <item>
          <title>Introducing The Test Chamber, The Black Mesa Livestream Show</title>
          <dc:creator><![CDATA[Fr0z3n]]></dc:creator>
          <category>News &amp; Developer Updates</category>
          <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Hey guys!</p>
<p>I’m Joe ‘Fr0z3nR’ Radak, Multiplayer Level designer for Black Mesa. Launch has been totally wicked, and thats all because of you guys, so thank  you so much. Some of you have noticed that since launch we’ve been really open and active across community fronts: this forum, reddit, steam forums, ingame, facepunch and more. This is something that we at Crowbar have wanted to do for a while: be more active within the community and break that iron veil we had during pre-steam development. We have a lot more community events planned for the future but, I’m happy to announce one of our recurring events now, <span class="bbcode-i">The Test Chamber.</span></p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">What is <span class="bbcode-i">The Test Chamber</span>?</span><br>
<span class="bbcode-i">The Test Chamber </span>is a regular livestream that I will be hosting every-other week. For each episode, the first half of the stream will have either community mod spotlights or artwork, chats about development updates, preview of content patches, and more. Whatever remaining time we have, myself and whoever else is on the stream will pop onto a server where you can come play some MP with us … if you can find the server we’re on! (MUH HAAA MUUHHA HA HA <span class="bbcode-b">cough cough</span>). That can also run as a pseudo Q&amp;A session for whatever topic we were talking about during the stream.<br>
What do I need from you?<br>
Suggestions, ideas, topics! Do you think this format works? We want the communities feedback on this stream.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-i"><span class="bbcode-b">To review:</span></span><br>
A livestream show, every-other-week. Time/Day to be determined.<br>
Hour long. First half is topic of the week, second half is community MP play<br>
Community Mod Spotlights or/and Artwork, Development updates, content patch previews, and more.</p>
<p>So this is our current plan. We’d like to start doing this in the next week or so, once we get a good idea of this is a format ya’ll will like. Let us know in this thread.</p>
<p>EDIT: The stream will happen at our official twitch channel, <a href="https://www.twitch.tv/blackmesagame" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">twitch.tv/blackmesagame</a></p>
            <p><small>118 posts - 32 participants</small></p>
            <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/introducing-the-test-chamber-the-black-mesa-livestream-show/13947">Read full topic</a></p>
          ]]></description>
          <link>https://leakfree.org/t/introducing-the-test-chamber-the-black-mesa-livestream-show/13947</link>
          <pubDate>Sat, 09 May 2015 20:15:03 +0000</pubDate>
          <discourse:topicPinned>No</discourse:topicPinned>
          <discourse:topicClosed>No</discourse:topicClosed>
          <discourse:topicArchived>No</discourse:topicArchived>
          <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-topic-13947</guid>
          <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/introducing-the-test-chamber-the-black-mesa-livestream-show/13947.rss">Introducing The Test Chamber, The Black Mesa Livestream Show</source>
        </item>
        <item>
          <title>Black Mesa is now available on Steam as an early access title!</title>
          <dc:creator><![CDATA[TextFAMGUY1]]></dc:creator>
          <category>News &amp; Developer Updates</category>
          <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Black Mesa is now available for purchase on Steam early access for $19.99. Please <a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/362890/" data-bbcode="true">visit our store page</a> to find out more!</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b"><span class="bbcode-u">What’s new in the steam release?[/size]</span></span><br>
The Steam release of Black Mesa includes various fixes, upgrades, and new features compared to Black Mesa’s mod release.</p>
<ul>
<li>
<span class="bbcode-b">Heavily updated single player experience </span>- The Black Mesa singleplayer experience has greatly improved from the mod release; new visuals, new voiceover, updated gameplay encounters, stability changes and more. <span class="bbcode-b">Xen is not a part of the Steam release of Black Mesa, but it will be included as a free update to the retail title when it is ready.</span>
</li>
<li>
<span class="bbcode-b">Black Mesa Multiplayer - </span>Fight with or against your friends, in two game modes (deathmatch and team deathmatch) across six iconic maps from the Half-Life universe: Bounce, Gasworks, Lambdabunker, Stalkyard, Subtransit and Undertow.</li>
<li>
<span class="bbcode-b">Custom Modding Tools </span>- Use the same tools the developers used to create your own mods, modes and maps for Black Mesa and Black Mesa Multiplayer.</li>
<li>
<span class="bbcode-b">Fully integrated Workshop</span> - And then share your work on the fully integrated workshop!</li>
<li>
<span class="bbcode-b">Complete Steam Integration</span> - Collect trading cards, backgrounds, emoticons, achievements, and everything else you would expect out of a Steam integrated game<br>
<span class="bbcode-u"><span class="bbcode-b">Why Early Access?</span></span>[/size]<br>
Making a game with the scope and scale of Black Mesa is a massive undertaking. Back in 2012 we made the decision to release what we had completed up to that point, and were blown away by the community’s response, feedback, and improvements to our work. We want to keep that relationship alive and well by using Early Access as a tool for allowing our community to participate in the final phase of Black Mesa’s development.</li>
</ul>
<p>In addition, our ambitions go beyond the original Xen chapters found in Half-Life. We have a standard of quality that we have to achieve. Early Access allows us to commit resources to bring you the remaining chapters with the quality that you expect.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-u"><span class="bbcode-b">How is the full version planned to differ from the Early Access version?</span></span>[/size]</p>
<ul>
<li>The conclusion of the single player campaign, with the addition of the Xen chapters</li>
<li>Final polish on the Earth-based chapters of the single player campaign</li>
<li>More multiplayer maps, both remakes and new layouts</li>
<li>More multiplayer gameplay modes<br>
<span class="bbcode-b"><span class="bbcode-u">What is the current state of the Early Access version?</span>[/size]</span><br>
Over 10 hours of single player campaign. Multiplayer deathmatch and team deathmatch with 6 completely re-imagined Half-Life 1 maps on the Source Engine.</li>
</ul>
<p><span class="bbcode-u"><span class="bbcode-b">Will the game be priced differently during and after Early Access?</span></span>[/size]<br>
Black Mesa will be $19.99 USD during the Early Access phase. The game may go slightly higher once out of Early Access (or we may keep it at $19.99).</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-u"><span class="bbcode-b">How are you planning on involving the Community in your development process?</span></span>[/size]<br>
We intend to work closely with our community as we complete the final portions of Black Mesa. We started out as a modding team aiming to do true justice to a Half-Life: Source port, and we won’t forget our roots.</p>
<p>The Black Mesa game hub and forums will be the primary points of interaction with our users. Many team members regularly browse these areas to discuss ideas with the community, and to show progress on game development. Community feedback will be sorted into groups and taken into account as we develop.</p>
<p>We also support Steam Workshop, and will be watching and encouraging developments there.</p>
            <p><small>1 post - 1 participant</small></p>
            <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/black-mesa-is-now-available-on-steam-as-an-early-access-title/13819">Read full topic</a></p>
          ]]></description>
          <link>https://leakfree.org/t/black-mesa-is-now-available-on-steam-as-an-early-access-title/13819</link>
          <pubDate>Wed, 06 May 2015 00:36:56 +0000</pubDate>
          <discourse:topicPinned>No</discourse:topicPinned>
          <discourse:topicClosed>No</discourse:topicClosed>
          <discourse:topicArchived>No</discourse:topicArchived>
          <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-topic-13819</guid>
          <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/black-mesa-is-now-available-on-steam-as-an-early-access-title/13819.rss">Black Mesa is now available on Steam as an early access title!</source>
        </item>
        <item>
          <title>Happy Birthday Half-life!</title>
          <dc:creator><![CDATA[cman2k]]></dc:creator>
          <category>News &amp; Developer Updates</category>
          <description><![CDATA[
            <p>HAPPY 15TH BIRTHDAY HALF-LIFE! We here at Black Mesa have some big news![/size]</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">The Big News:</span><br>
Last year, Black Mesa was one of the first Steam games to be Greenlit by you, our amazing fans. We’ve had quite a year since then, with a lot happening internally that we haven’t been able to talk about… until now. Black Mesa has been given the opportunity to be <span class="bbcode-b">sold as a retail product on Steam!</span>  This is an incredible honor - one we never expected - but also one we found hard to accept.</p>
<p>We never developed Black Mesa with money in mind.  Our team is made up of average, hardworking people, and no one joined the team to make money. For us, Black Mesa is purely a labor of love. We believe this philosophy has significantly contributed to the overall quality and feel of the game.</p>
<p>Our decision to sell Black Mesa rests on two key points. One is we believe we can make the game even better by having full access to the Source engine. This lets us tackle and fix limitations instead of working around them. The second is because frankly, our team could really use the financial help.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">The Plan:</span><br>
Soon you’ll see Black Mesa available on Steam for a relatively low price. But we aren’t dropping all support for the free version.  In fact shortly after the Steam release there will be a completely new free version of the game. We also plan to <span class="bbcode-b">open source our maps and some game assets</span> to the modding community!</p>
<p>Purchasing the Steam version of Black Mesa is more about supporting the team and our efforts than anything else. However, the Steam version will include features that the free version simply can not have.  We will be paying careful attention to feedback, and you’ll have a very real say in how the final game turns out.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Long-Term Plans and Xen:</span><br>
We’ve been overwhelmed by fan anticipation for Xen, and we’re excited so many people are eager to conclude the game.  To be totally honest however, Xen is still a ways off.  Over the past year, we have spent a HUGE amount of time porting the game to a new engine and fixing hundreds of bugs.  The work to port to the new engine was not because of the decision to go retail, this was work that had to be done to get Black Mesa onto Steam and support our future plans.</p>
<p>So, please be patient with us as we work to make Xen a stunning and worthy conclusion to Black Mesa. Until Xen is completed, we have multiple interesting additions planned for the Steam version of Black Mesa, which we will announce later on down the road.</p>
<p>Thanks,<br>
The Black Mesa Dev Team</p>
            <p><small>468 posts - 146 participants</small></p>
            <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/happy-birthday-half-life/12776">Read full topic</a></p>
          ]]></description>
          <link>https://leakfree.org/t/happy-birthday-half-life/12776</link>
          <pubDate>Tue, 19 Nov 2013 16:48:28 +0000</pubDate>
          <discourse:topicPinned>No</discourse:topicPinned>
          <discourse:topicClosed>No</discourse:topicClosed>
          <discourse:topicArchived>No</discourse:topicArchived>
          <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-topic-12776</guid>
          <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/happy-birthday-half-life/12776.rss">Happy Birthday Half-life!</source>
        </item>
        <item>
          <title>Black Mesa is released!</title>
          <dc:creator><![CDATA[cman2k]]></dc:creator>
          <category>News &amp; Developer Updates</category>
          <description><![CDATA[
            <p>It’s been a long time coming, and we had a rough start this morning, but it’s out in the wild!  Black Mesa is released!  If you are having trouble with our mirrors on the main site, try the torrent, and help us seed!</p>
<p>More than anything, SPREAD THE WORD!  We are giving this all away to the community, but the best payment we can possibly get is that we get as many people to download and play this game as possible!  HELP US PROMOTE IT, EVERYWHERE!</p>
<p>Thanks guys!  Today is a good day!</p>
            <p><small>721 posts - 377 participants</small></p>
            <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/black-mesa-is-released/9488">Read full topic</a></p>
          ]]></description>
          <link>https://leakfree.org/t/black-mesa-is-released/9488</link>
          <pubDate>Fri, 14 Sep 2012 18:06:41 +0000</pubDate>
          <discourse:topicPinned>No</discourse:topicPinned>
          <discourse:topicClosed>No</discourse:topicClosed>
          <discourse:topicArchived>No</discourse:topicArchived>
          <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-topic-9488</guid>
          <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/black-mesa-is-released/9488.rss">Black Mesa is released!</source>
        </item>
        <item>
          <title>We got Black Mesa on Steam!</title>
          <dc:creator><![CDATA[cman2k]]></dc:creator>
          <category>News &amp; Developer Updates</category>
          <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Hey everyone!</p>
<p>Black Mesa officially just got GREENLIT!  Thanks so much for all of your support! This has been a wild ride, and this is just as much your victory as ours!</p>
<p>EDIT:<br>
For everyone asking, you guys know about as much as we do.  We WILL be releasing on Friday, in some form or another, no matter what.</p>
<p>There’s a lot of talking and figuring out stuff ahead of us before the game actually gets on Steam. We really don’t know exactly how long that will take, so we will all have to wait and see. We’re doing our best, we are as excited about it as you are!</p>
            <p><small>254 posts - 172 participants</small></p>
            <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/we-got-black-mesa-on-steam/9384">Read full topic</a></p>
          ]]></description>
          <link>https://leakfree.org/t/we-got-black-mesa-on-steam/9384</link>
          <pubDate>Tue, 11 Sep 2012 19:34:52 +0000</pubDate>
          <discourse:topicPinned>No</discourse:topicPinned>
          <discourse:topicClosed>No</discourse:topicClosed>
          <discourse:topicArchived>No</discourse:topicArchived>
          <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-topic-9384</guid>
          <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/we-got-black-mesa-on-steam/9384.rss">We got Black Mesa on Steam!</source>
        </item>
        <item>
          <title>Launch Maintenance (9/7/2012)</title>
          <dc:creator><![CDATA[Hubicorn]]></dc:creator>
          <category>News &amp; Developer Updates</category>
          <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Hello Scientists!</p>
<p>We are just about a week away and I am sure many of you shipped away the girlfriend to a remote island, called out from work, moved into a man cave of some sort, or even teleported yourself to XEN in order to get ready for the big day. Well, now it’s our turn.</p>
<p>Over the next few days, we will be initiating our release plan to ensure that our web servers can handle all the expected load during the launch weekend. Part of this plan, is moving the forums off to a separate server and load balancing the release website between two. With that being said, access to both the website and forums over the weekend might be slightly interrupted during the move. However, we plan to do this all with little to no interruption.</p>
<p>At some point after we are finished building the new infrastructure, the forums will be taken temporary offline to allow your DNS to refresh and grab the new information for the server. We would hate to have your very important forum posts get lost.</p>
<p>See you all on the other side!</p>
<p>-Hubi</p>
            <p><small>83 posts - 50 participants</small></p>
            <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/launch-maintenance-9-7-2012/9339">Read full topic</a></p>
          ]]></description>
          <link>https://leakfree.org/t/launch-maintenance-9-7-2012/9339</link>
          <pubDate>Fri, 07 Sep 2012 06:13:25 +0000</pubDate>
          <discourse:topicPinned>Yes</discourse:topicPinned>
          <discourse:topicClosed>No</discourse:topicClosed>
          <discourse:topicArchived>No</discourse:topicArchived>
          <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-topic-9339</guid>
          <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/launch-maintenance-9-7-2012/9339.rss">Launch Maintenance (9/7/2012)</source>
        </item>
        <item>
          <title>Get Black Mesa on Steam! We can do it!</title>
          <dc:creator><![CDATA[cman2k]]></dc:creator>
          <category>News &amp; Developer Updates</category>
          <description><![CDATA[
            <p><a href="https://bit.ly/SiEHZo" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">VOTE FOR BLACK MESA ON STEAM GREENLIGHT![/SIZE]</a></p>
<p>Fellow Scientists,</p>
<p>We have gotten a lot of remarks, questions and demands that we get Black Mesa on Steam.  In the past, the answer has always been the same…“It’s not our decision!”  Well, it still isn’t our decision.  But now it’s yours.</p>
<p>Black Mesa is now on the Steam Greenlight service.  YOU can now be a part of helping get the game on Steam.  Not only through your votes but through your help in getting all your friends and peers to vote for Black Mesa!</p>
<p>The more votes we get, the closer we will be to not only getting the game on Steam, but getting Steam integration.  This doesn’t just mean easier installation and updates for everyone, but it means a host of other advantages such as Achievement Tracking, Stat tracking, Steam Cloud, (eventual) Matchmaking services, Steam Community features, and a host of other useful things.</p>
<p>In short, it will help us make Black Mesa more awesome for you guys!  So get out there and help us do this!</p>
<p>[COLOR=‘YellowGreen’]You can follow the stats ],{}]"]here and <a href="https://www.stewartatkins.co.uk/greenlight/" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">here</a>.</p>
<p>Note: Your Steam client or browser page must be set to English in order to vote.</p>
<hr>
<p>Help us out on reddit!<br>
<a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/gaming/comments/zdptj/go_thumbs_up_black_mesa_source_on_steam/" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://www.reddit.com/r/gaming/comments/zdptj/go_thumbs_up_black_mesa_source_on_steam/</a></p>
            <p><small>853 posts - 202 participants</small></p>
            <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/get-black-mesa-on-steam-we-can-do-it/9311">Read full topic</a></p>
          ]]></description>
          <link>https://leakfree.org/t/get-black-mesa-on-steam-we-can-do-it/9311</link>
          <pubDate>Wed, 05 Sep 2012 06:00:51 +0000</pubDate>
          <discourse:topicPinned>No</discourse:topicPinned>
          <discourse:topicClosed>No</discourse:topicClosed>
          <discourse:topicArchived>No</discourse:topicArchived>
          <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-topic-9311</guid>
          <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/get-black-mesa-on-steam-we-can-do-it/9311.rss">Get Black Mesa on Steam! We can do it!</source>
        </item>
        <item>
          <title>Launch Details Discussion</title>
          <dc:creator><![CDATA[Hubicorn]]></dc:creator>
          <category>News &amp; Developer Updates</category>
          <description><![CDATA[
            <p>We want to make sure all of you are ready for the big day. If you don’t already know, Black Mesa will require the FREE Source SDK Base 2007 to run. If you are not too sure that you have Source SDK Base 2007 installed or you don’t own any source based games, please click here to download and install the Source SDK Base via Steam for FREE.</p>
<p>I know many of you loyal Half Life fans are planning on taking a vacation day from work, calling out sick for school, or even both. We are working very hard to ensure your day off does not go in vain, and that every person trying to download Black Mesa will undergo a smooth and fast downloading experience. The approximate download size will be <span class="bbcode-b">3.03 GB</span>, <span class="bbcode-b">8 GB</span> uncompressed. At launch, a launch pad will be available offering multiple mirrors and options for download.  These options shall be revealed during launch. So go ahead, take that day off and <a href="https://www.facebook.com/events/179981922137074/" data-bbcode="true">join us</a>!</p>
<p>We know you all are very excited and we want to you share your gameplay experiences as soon as you finish playing. We also want to make sure to collect any bug reporting and get any resolved as quickly as possible. With that being said, the forums shall be moved to it’s own separate server. So when you are finished re-visiting Black Mesa, we’ll be here to hear all about it.</p>
<p>We are very excited and we are counting down the days right along with you!</p>
<ul>
<li>Hubi</li>
</ul>
            <p><small>283 posts - 119 participants</small></p>
            <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/launch-details-discussion/9307">Read full topic</a></p>
          ]]></description>
          <link>https://leakfree.org/t/launch-details-discussion/9307</link>
          <pubDate>Mon, 03 Sep 2012 22:51:44 +0000</pubDate>
          <discourse:topicPinned>No</discourse:topicPinned>
          <discourse:topicClosed>No</discourse:topicClosed>
          <discourse:topicArchived>No</discourse:topicArchived>
          <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-topic-9307</guid>
          <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/launch-details-discussion/9307.rss">Launch Details Discussion</source>
        </item>
        <item>
          <title>Community Update</title>
          <dc:creator><![CDATA[cman2k]]></dc:creator>
          <category>News &amp; Developer Updates</category>
          <description><![CDATA[
            <p>We’re freaking out over here! It is so exciting to share this news with you!</p>
<ul>
<li>You can now Download the Black Mesa Soundtrack, courtesy of our very own Joel Nielsen, at the very generous price of whatever you want! Enjoy and share!</li>
<li>In the near future you’ll see our Website, Wiki and Forums all taken down temporarily for renovations.</li>
<li>On September 14th you will see the first release of Black Mesa! This will include our re-envisioning of Half-Life all the way up to Lambda Core. We believe this is a great way to provide a complete-feeling 8-10 hour experience with a solid ending, make our fans happy and help us make the best overall game possible.</li>
</ul>
<p>We are still working hard on Xen and BMDM, but instead of making you wait we are giving you Black Mesa as soon as it’s ready! We’re doing our best to help bring the immense vision of this project into reality, and we are very excited for what the future brings!</p>
<p>High-Fives Yo,<br>
Carlos Montero - Project Leader</p>
            <p><small>1011 posts - 443 participants</small></p>
            <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/community-update/9267">Read full topic</a></p>
          ]]></description>
          <link>https://leakfree.org/t/community-update/9267</link>
          <pubDate>Sun, 02 Sep 2012 05:40:34 +0000</pubDate>
          <discourse:topicPinned>No</discourse:topicPinned>
          <discourse:topicClosed>No</discourse:topicClosed>
          <discourse:topicArchived>No</discourse:topicArchived>
          <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-topic-9267</guid>
          <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/community-update/9267.rss">Community Update</source>
        </item>
        <item>
          <title>28/8/12 Interview with The Verge</title>
          <dc:creator><![CDATA[ac3d]]></dc:creator>
          <category>News &amp; Developer Updates</category>
          <description><![CDATA[
            <p><a href="https://www.theverge.com/gaming/2012/8/28/3275083/black-mesa-project-preservers" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://www.theverge.com/gaming/2012/8/28/3275083/black-mesa-project-preservers</a></p>
<p><span alt="" class="broken-image" title="This image is broken"><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-unlink svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#unlink"></use></svg></span><br>
<span alt="" class="broken-image" title="This image is broken"><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-unlink svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#unlink"></use></svg></span><br>
<span alt="" class="broken-image" title="This image is broken"><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-unlink svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#unlink"></use></svg></span><br>
<span alt="" class="broken-image" title="This image is broken"><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-unlink svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#unlink"></use></svg></span><br>
<span alt="" class="broken-image" title="This image is broken"><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-unlink svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#unlink"></use></svg></span><br>
<span alt="" class="broken-image" title="This image is broken"><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-unlink svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#unlink"></use></svg></span></p>
            <p><small>75 posts - 43 participants</small></p>
            <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/28-8-12-interview-with-the-verge/9245">Read full topic</a></p>
          ]]></description>
          <link>https://leakfree.org/t/28-8-12-interview-with-the-verge/9245</link>
          <pubDate>Wed, 29 Aug 2012 06:53:03 +0000</pubDate>
          <discourse:topicPinned>No</discourse:topicPinned>
          <discourse:topicClosed>No</discourse:topicClosed>
          <discourse:topicArchived>No</discourse:topicArchived>
          <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-topic-9245</guid>
          <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/28-8-12-interview-with-the-verge/9245.rss">28/8/12 Interview with The Verge</source>
        </item>
        <item>
          <title>Social media campaign starts on Facebook</title>
          <dc:creator><![CDATA[JamesKane]]></dc:creator>
          <category>News &amp; Developer Updates</category>
          <description><![CDATA[
            <p>When the Black Mesa facebook page hits 20,000 likes we’ll be posting some exciting new media! Care to help?</p>
<p><a href="https://www.facebook.com/BlackMesaDevs" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://www.facebook.com/BlackMesaDevs</a></p>
            <p><small>570 posts - 155 participants</small></p>
            <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/social-media-campaign-starts-on-facebook/8880">Read full topic</a></p>
          ]]></description>
          <link>https://leakfree.org/t/social-media-campaign-starts-on-facebook/8880</link>
          <pubDate>Sun, 10 Jun 2012 00:49:31 +0000</pubDate>
          <discourse:topicPinned>No</discourse:topicPinned>
          <discourse:topicClosed>No</discourse:topicClosed>
          <discourse:topicArchived>No</discourse:topicArchived>
          <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-topic-8880</guid>
          <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/social-media-campaign-starts-on-facebook/8880.rss">Social media campaign starts on Facebook</source>
        </item>
        <item>
          <title>Black Mesa interview on Rock Paper Shotgun</title>
          <dc:creator><![CDATA[Maxey]]></dc:creator>
          <category>News &amp; Developer Updates</category>
          <description><![CDATA[
            <p><a href="https://www.rockpapershotgun.com/2012/05/09/interview-what-happened-to-black-mesa-source-part-1/" data-bbcode="true">https://www.rockpapershotgun.com/2012/05/09/interview-what-happened-to-black-mesa-source-part-1/</a></p>
<p>Carlos Montero talks about how it is to work on a mod of such magnitude and the whole malarkey surrounding the 2009 deadline.</p>
            <p><small>166 posts - 81 participants</small></p>
            <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/black-mesa-interview-on-rock-paper-shotgun/8741">Read full topic</a></p>
          ]]></description>
          <link>https://leakfree.org/t/black-mesa-interview-on-rock-paper-shotgun/8741</link>
          <pubDate>Wed, 09 May 2012 11:09:24 +0000</pubDate>
          <discourse:topicPinned>No</discourse:topicPinned>
          <discourse:topicClosed>No</discourse:topicClosed>
          <discourse:topicArchived>No</discourse:topicArchived>
          <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-topic-8741</guid>
          <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/black-mesa-interview-on-rock-paper-shotgun/8741.rss">Black Mesa interview on Rock Paper Shotgun</source>
        </item>
        <item>
          <title>Steamcast (2 hour)</title>
          <dc:creator><![CDATA[JamesKane]]></dc:creator>
          <category>News &amp; Developer Updates</category>
          <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Steamcast recently held a podcast with Mike Hillard ( voice ), Kevin Sisk ( voice, scripting &amp; choreo ), &amp; Ben Truman ( story lead, scripting, &amp; choreo ).<br>
Unfortunately, Steamcast is a bit behind on episodes but you can <a href="https://www.twitch.tv/steamcast/b/291991707" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">listen on the unedited stream. ( skip to 14m )</a></p>
<p><a href="https://www.thesteamcast.com/" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">SteamCast</a></p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>Welcome to the official Steamcast website. Steamcast is a fan-made podcast, generally recorded on a weekly basis every Sunday, that hosts a wide range of gaming related topics. Contrary to its name, the podcast does not focus strictly on Valve or Steam related topics but aims to cover as much of the entire gaming industry as possible including gaming digital distribution, major gaming press conferences, and other relevant news. As a community-founded podcast, Steamcast places high importance on community participation. Members of the community are welcome to join the hosts and share their thoughts and opinions on specific topics. This gives the community — everyday gamers — the opportunity to voice their opinions and concerns…</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
            <p><small>121 posts - 61 participants</small></p>
            <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/steamcast-2-hour/7641">Read full topic</a></p>
          ]]></description>
          <link>https://leakfree.org/t/steamcast-2-hour/7641</link>
          <pubDate>Mon, 08 Aug 2011 04:58:24 +0000</pubDate>
          <discourse:topicPinned>No</discourse:topicPinned>
          <discourse:topicClosed>No</discourse:topicClosed>
          <discourse:topicArchived>No</discourse:topicArchived>
          <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-topic-7641</guid>
          <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/steamcast-2-hour/7641.rss">Steamcast (2 hour)</source>
        </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
