<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>My thoughts on the MOVEMENT and where BM:DM should go with it.</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/my-thoughts-on-the-movement-and-where-bm-dm-should-go-with-it/14026</link>
    <description>Hi guys,
 My name is Brian, and I&#39;ve been a long time player of Half life, CS, and adrenaline gamer.
 
 I know there was a long and tedious thread you guys closed recently, and I didn&#39;t get a chance to add my two cents worth before the topic was closed.
 
 I&#39;d like to say that I&#39;m excited that you guys are making this game, and look forward to playing it more, IF the movement becomes more similar to HL1.
 
 Now I know some of you guys keep bringing up the point of &quot;spamming LJ&quot; and that its noob or whatever. For most of the guys that played HL years after everyone else quit, we started to learn how high the skill cap really was. We started to learn that Half life, isn&#39;t just a straight forward , run in a line, jump a few times shooter. The movement that you could do in half life 1 was artful. Even long jumping excessively to evade and dodge was part of the excitement and faced paced atmosphere of the game. Theres actually many different variations and ways to jump and move in the air with the long jump. Half life 1, with its movement, allows players to pick and choose their style of play, whether it be the assassin style ( silent long jumping, sneaking around and jumping around corners to crossbow headshot an enemy) , or it could be full balls to the wall aggression and speed style. The ability to &quot;VERY quickly&quot; move around the map with true purpose, picking up what you need, shooting off weapons on the fly.
 Id like to post a couple links to videos, and I really insist you all watch them. If by the end of watching them, you aren&#39;t impressed, excited, in awe of the speed and movement, in love with the ARTFUL movement and skilful kills, evasions, escapes, multikills etc. Then I would be very suprised, and I will no longer talk about the subject.
 [url=&#39;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=HwbS55a8WDw&#39;]youtube.com/watch?v=HwbS55a8WDw[/url]
 [url=&#39;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=qLeL-0_kgVE&#39;]youtube.com/watch?v=qLeL-0_kgVE[/url]
 [url=&#39;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=N2FZuzaTaBI&#39;]youtube.com/watch?v=N2FZuzaTaBI[/url]
 [url=&#39;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=mm5Zk9SRPds&#39;]youtube.com/watch?v=mm5Zk9SRPds[/url]
 [url=&#39;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=wWM1i_8sJ88%C3%A2%C2%80%C2%8B&#39;]https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=wWM1i_8sJ88[/url]
 
 In my eyes, the movement should be almost a 100% replication of movement in HL1.
 
 I know there has been a lot of discussion regarding, lets please the majority of players, which normally lie in the mediochre or decent skill levels.
 Let me say this. If you create a game that has a very high skill cap, fast paced adrenaline play, with competitive spirit. You will probably have more players streaming the game on twitch, bringing more attention to the game. The more players that watch pro&#39;s (when i say pro, i just mean a really good player) on twitch etc, will be inspired, and want to get as good as they are, creating a game that can become very competitive and popular.
 
 Someone made a point that only 5% of HL&#39;s userbase still play, due to the fact that great players can rape. In my eyes 5% of the user base play HL1 now, because well, the game is ancient. As fun as it is, its a very old game with outdated graphics, and the general population of people move to the newer , better graphic games out there.
 
 Even though HL has a high skill cap, its not what you guys think it is. You don&#39;t have to study the game , and get a degree in it to become good. You can become pretty good at the game in a fairly short amount of time, BUT to become masterful at the game it does take a while. ( Most masterful players, don&#39;t spend ALL their time in public servers &quot;raping noobs&quot; because it gets boring to them, just like its boring to the noob who keeps dying.)
 One of the great parts of Hl1, is that noob players can still have fun in public servers, lots of noob players till play hl1 and have fun, great players can have fun as well, and masterful players can have great fun, especially in organizing private matches vs each other (Which can be streamed on twitch or other sites and bring traffic to the game)
 
 The feeling the game gives you is so rewarding , when your flying around the map with speed, killing enemies, picking up weapons etc. Just saying. Getting a few kills in black mesa currently doesn&#39;t feel near as rewarding, because play styles are limited to much slower, straight forward styles.
 
 
 If and when you reply to this , please don&#39;t tell me that spamming LJ is not skillfull. There are so many skillful ways to long jump around in HL1, and you just generalize it all and say its spam. If you can&#39;t hit someone who is long jumping around, (even though you have rocket launchers, grenades, shotguns, machine guns) Then thats your own fault. It&#39;s not really that hard, you just shoot a nade or two near them, and they die....
 
 Final thought
 
 Please don&#39;t slow this game down, let it be fast, and free, and exciting.
 Also, crouch climbing was so key to Hl1, I hope you can find a way to put that into the source engine.
 I know crouch climbing isn&#39;t something that is realistic , in terms of what a human can do, but, it was just another tool in your movement kit to help develop your style, and get around the map more easily. HL1, had a real flow to the game, with the movement. Currently, black mesa has a clunky, slow, feel to it. (No offence, the game is still pretty awesome and will improve)
 
 I just hope you guys will watch the video&#39;s and look at the beauty and technique that is involved when you become great at the game. It doesn&#39;t take a college degree, or a million hours to be able to do it. Once you get the hang of long jumping and bunny hopping, the learning curve becomes much easier to master the movement.
 
 I know some of the &quot;top players&quot; might be coming off as arrogant or whatever. But keep in mind, these players are very passionate about the game, hence the reason they have played for so many years and got good at it. We understand how the game works, and feels in multiplayer, and to be honest, I think we have a good understanding of what&#39;s important to keep, and bring over from HL1.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 10 Oct 2015 20:43:24 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>The Cafeteria</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/my-thoughts-on-the-movement-and-where-bm-dm-should-go-with-it/14026.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>My thoughts on the MOVEMENT and where BM:DM should go with it.</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[fury]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Hey guys,</p>
<p>it’s me again… I have some more things that I’d like to point out:</p>
<ol>
<li>
<p>Devs should reduce longjump range. HL1 Longjumps are ~64 units shorter.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Devs should change crouch to be more HL1-like. When you perform a crouchjump in HL2 or HL1, your playermodel pulls his legs up --&gt; You can reach higher platforms while in the air.<br>
While in other games (Quake Live for example), the playermodel pulls it’s head down when performing a crouchjump. The difference between HL1 and HL2 is the distance in which the playermodel pulls his legs up.<br>
In HL2 you seem to crouch lower than in HL1. Atleast you reach higher platforms in BM than in HL when using crouchjumps. Autocrouchjump should only be available in singleplayer mode.</p>
</li>
</ol>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/my-thoughts-on-the-movement-and-where-bm-dm-should-go-with-it/14026/62">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/my-thoughts-on-the-movement-and-where-bm-dm-should-go-with-it/14026/62</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 10 Oct 2015 20:43:24 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14026-62</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/my-thoughts-on-the-movement-and-where-bm-dm-should-go-with-it/14026.rss">My thoughts on the MOVEMENT and where BM:DM should go with it.</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My thoughts on the MOVEMENT and where BM:DM should go with it.</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[fury]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><span class="bbcode-s"></span>Just played some AG and I think I now know what seems to be still quite a bit different about the base movement when comparing BM to HL1. It’s the acceleration. In BM you have slightly lower acceleration than in HL1. That’s why the movement feels CS-like. In HL1 you get maxspeed faster (320 ups is max on most servers… but you have the command sv_maxspeed which is 300 by default)… I recommend to have 320 as default for competetive or make it votable. Does somebody know the acceleration-values for HL1DM and AG?<span class="bbcode-s"></span></p>
<p>Edit: I think the game may just feel slower because of the big viewmodels… When you play HL1 with a field of view of 110 or more (I think I even use 120 in HL1) you get a fisheye effect and your view and your viewmodel look different, because the fov gets applied to everything. In BM the fov_desired command only affects your view, but not your viewmodel… Maybe that’s why it feels slower… Does BM have a command to change viewmodel-fov? If not I’d suggest to add one, because it really affects the feel of the game by a lot.<br>
I would also like to see the r_drawviewmodel 0 possible without sv_cheats 1 and different crosshairs (I really don’t like the gauss- and the shotgun-crosshair atm)… I hope there will be some easy way to make own crosshairs for BM. In HL1 it was only simple sprites which you were able to edit in paint and put them back into the game again. In HL2 the crosshairs are saved in some font-filetype which rather sucks (well ok the font scales with resolution which is an advantage, but it’s harder to edit and create custom ones).</p>
<p>Edit 2: In multiplayer BM is still slower and more CS-like because you can’t gain speed by running curves or circles ( for example: in HL1 you can hold forward + left and continiously move your mouse to the left to gain more speed than normal, in BM there is a speedcap). In HL1DM this technique was often used to gain speed for a next jump (to jump further… called circle-jump). Another thing I noticed that you can’t slide up ramps in most cases (atm I rebuild ag_crossfire from HL1 for BM:TDM and in HL1 you can slide up the ramps near bunker when gaussjumping into them… In BM you can’t do this… When you try, you instantly stop and lose all your speed.)</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/my-thoughts-on-the-movement-and-where-bm-dm-should-go-with-it/14026/61">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/my-thoughts-on-the-movement-and-where-bm-dm-should-go-with-it/14026/61</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 26 May 2015 19:39:18 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14026-61</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/my-thoughts-on-the-movement-and-where-bm-dm-should-go-with-it/14026.rss">My thoughts on the MOVEMENT and where BM:DM should go with it.</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My thoughts on the MOVEMENT and where BM:DM should go with it.</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[eriksonis6]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>was faster ladder climbing while pressing a+w pr d+w added today or it was there since the beginning?  i feel like it works good now and i remember it didn’t work few days ago.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/my-thoughts-on-the-movement-and-where-bm-dm-should-go-with-it/14026/60">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/my-thoughts-on-the-movement-and-where-bm-dm-should-go-with-it/14026/60</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 May 2015 20:54:24 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14026-60</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/my-thoughts-on-the-movement-and-where-bm-dm-should-go-with-it/14026.rss">My thoughts on the MOVEMENT and where BM:DM should go with it.</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My thoughts on the MOVEMENT and where BM:DM should go with it.</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[N1ghtM]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="jadebenn">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/j/aeb1de/40.png" class="avatar"> jadebenn:</div>
<blockquote>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="N1ghtM@re">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 N1ghtM@re:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>It is, for the sake of legitimacy, imperative to design and produce a fundamentally accurate and genuine remake of HL1. Furthermore, it is neccessary and appropriate to implement movements which are exclusive and true to the mechanics of HLDM. As a result, a foundation is established in validity, and is therefore acceptable with credence as it is in accordance to this principle.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I disagree, a remake or sequel does not have to preserve every aspect of it’s predecessor, especially if such aspects were unintended. In every successive version of source, more and more movement tactics (propjump, bhop, strafehop) have been removed from the code. Half-Life had use key slowdown, but Half-Life 2 does not. Implementing aspects of Half-Life into Black Mesa shouldn’t be done on just the basis  of “did Half-Life have it?”, things from Half-Life should be implemented if they result in a <span class="bbcode-b"><span class="bbcode-u">more fun game</span></span>.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I respect your opinion in regards to this matter, however; adding, removing, and changing features that could result in a “more fun game” (apart from HL1/AG) is subjective and controversial.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/my-thoughts-on-the-movement-and-where-bm-dm-should-go-with-it/14026/59">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/my-thoughts-on-the-movement-and-where-bm-dm-should-go-with-it/14026/59</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 May 2015 14:57:37 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14026-59</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/my-thoughts-on-the-movement-and-where-bm-dm-should-go-with-it/14026.rss">My thoughts on the MOVEMENT and where BM:DM should go with it.</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My thoughts on the MOVEMENT and where BM:DM should go with it.</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Alles_Ratten]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="jadebenn">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/j/aeb1de/40.png" class="avatar"> jadebenn:</div>
<blockquote>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="N1ghtM@re">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 N1ghtM@re:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>It is, for the sake of legitimacy, imperative to design and produce a fundamentally accurate and genuine remake of HL1. Furthermore, it is neccessary and appropriate to implement movements which are exclusive and true to the mechanics of HLDM. As a result, a foundation is established in validity, and is therefore acceptable with credence as it is in accordance to this principle.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I disagree, a remake or sequel does not have to preserve every aspect of it’s predecessor, especially if such aspects were unintended. In every successive version of source, more and more movement tactics (propjump, bhop, strafehop) have been removed from the code. Half-Life had use key slowdown, but Half-Life 2 does not. Implementing aspects of Half-Life into Black Mesa shouldn’t be done on just the basis  of “did Half-Life have it?”, things from Half-Life should be implemented if they result in a <span class="bbcode-b"><span class="bbcode-u">more fun game</span></span>.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>implementing 98% of half lifes gameplay will result in a “more fun game” GG</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/my-thoughts-on-the-movement-and-where-bm-dm-should-go-with-it/14026/58">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/my-thoughts-on-the-movement-and-where-bm-dm-should-go-with-it/14026/58</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 17 May 2015 23:52:24 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14026-58</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/my-thoughts-on-the-movement-and-where-bm-dm-should-go-with-it/14026.rss">My thoughts on the MOVEMENT and where BM:DM should go with it.</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My thoughts on the MOVEMENT and where BM:DM should go with it.</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Alles_Ratten]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>all this clueless talk  about bow…<br>
this is a fragmovie by me: <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=J0xQVnDULNs" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">tonsOfBowActionWithoutScript</a><br>
you will see fast shots without using a script. and i swear this is bringing tons of fun.<br>
cuz well placed, fast bow shots in hl require a lot of skill and are very satisfying when succeeding.</p>
<p>So John Snow stop talking about a game that you don’t even understand a bit.<br>
Crossbow gameplay in hl is unique and awesome in all it’s ways.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/my-thoughts-on-the-movement-and-where-bm-dm-should-go-with-it/14026/57">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/my-thoughts-on-the-movement-and-where-bm-dm-should-go-with-it/14026/57</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 17 May 2015 23:46:40 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14026-57</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/my-thoughts-on-the-movement-and-where-bm-dm-should-go-with-it/14026.rss">My thoughts on the MOVEMENT and where BM:DM should go with it.</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My thoughts on the MOVEMENT and where BM:DM should go with it.</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[eriksonis6]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="jadebenn">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/j/aeb1de/40.png" class="avatar"> jadebenn:</div>
<blockquote>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="N1ghtM@re">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 N1ghtM@re:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>It is, for the sake of legitimacy, imperative to design and produce a fundamentally accurate and genuine remake of HL1. Furthermore, it is neccessary and appropriate to implement movements which are exclusive and true to the mechanics of HLDM. As a result, a foundation is established in validity, and is therefore acceptable with credence as it is in accordance to this principle.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I disagree, a remake or sequel does not have to preserve every aspect of it’s predecessor, especially if such aspects were unintended. In every successive version of source, more and more movement tactics (propjump, bhop, strafehop) have been removed from the code. Half-Life had use key slowdown, but Half-Life 2 does not. Implementing aspects of Half-Life into Black Mesa shouldn’t be done on just the basis  of “did Half-Life have it?”, things from Half-Life should be implemented if they result in a <span class="bbcode-b"><span class="bbcode-u">more fun game</span></span>.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Some unintentional things like faster ladder climbing when holding " a+d " were in hl1 and still was ported to counter strike go. Bhop was removed because it doesn’t fit in CS GO type of game witch aims for realism. HL does not aim for realism its fast paced game where you can hold more than 10 weapons at once. This game definitely needs features like Bhop.</p>
<p>Use key insta stop was good for standing still while shooting gauss and for kz maps, but its not that essential to me.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/my-thoughts-on-the-movement-and-where-bm-dm-should-go-with-it/14026/56">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/my-thoughts-on-the-movement-and-where-bm-dm-should-go-with-it/14026/56</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 17 May 2015 10:29:59 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14026-56</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/my-thoughts-on-the-movement-and-where-bm-dm-should-go-with-it/14026.rss">My thoughts on the MOVEMENT and where BM:DM should go with it.</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My thoughts on the MOVEMENT and where BM:DM should go with it.</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[fury]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="jadebenn">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/j/aeb1de/40.png" class="avatar"> jadebenn:</div>
<blockquote>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="N1ghtM@re">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 N1ghtM@re:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>It is, for the sake of legitimacy, imperative to design and produce a fundamentally accurate and genuine remake of HL1. Furthermore, it is neccessary and appropriate to implement movements which are exclusive and true to the mechanics of HLDM. As a result, a foundation is established in validity, and is therefore acceptable with credence as it is in accordance to this principle.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I disagree, a remake or sequel does not have to preserve every aspect of it’s predecessor, especially if such aspects were unintended. In every successive version of source, more and more movement tactics (propjump, bhop, strafehop) have been removed from the code. Half-Life had use key slowdown, but Half-Life 2 does not. Implementing aspects of Half-Life into Black Mesa shouldn’t be done on just the basis  of “did Half-Life have it?”, things from Half-Life should be implemented if they result in a <span class="bbcode-b"><span class="bbcode-u">more fun game</span></span>.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>bhop makes the game more fun and more dynamic, use key slowdown makes sense so these things should get added. I would even like to see a climb-key or bigger stepsize. In HL1 people used quick crouch-doubletaps to climb up 32 unit-crates on stalkyard and other maps. I liked it because it made movement less choppy. It would be cool to have something like that. A key to step up a 32 unit high obstacle to get up faster whithout losing control over your movement. But I agree that this would be a lower priority feature.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/my-thoughts-on-the-movement-and-where-bm-dm-should-go-with-it/14026/55">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/my-thoughts-on-the-movement-and-where-bm-dm-should-go-with-it/14026/55</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 17 May 2015 00:38:54 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14026-55</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/my-thoughts-on-the-movement-and-where-bm-dm-should-go-with-it/14026.rss">My thoughts on the MOVEMENT and where BM:DM should go with it.</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My thoughts on the MOVEMENT and where BM:DM should go with it.</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[jadebenn]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="N1ghtM@re">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 N1ghtM@re:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>It is, for the sake of legitimacy, imperative to design and produce a fundamentally accurate and genuine remake of HL1. Furthermore, it is neccessary and appropriate to implement movements which are exclusive and true to the mechanics of HLDM. As a result, a foundation is established in validity, and is therefore acceptable with credence as it is in accordance to this principle.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I disagree, a remake or sequel does not have to preserve every aspect of it’s predecessor, especially if such aspects were unintended. In every successive version of source, more and more movement tactics (propjump, bhop, strafehop) have been removed from the code. Half-Life had use key slowdown, but Half-Life 2 does not. Implementing aspects of Half-Life into Black Mesa shouldn’t be done on just the basis  of “did Half-Life have it?”, things from Half-Life should be implemented if they result in a <span class="bbcode-b"><span class="bbcode-u">more fun game</span></span>.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/my-thoughts-on-the-movement-and-where-bm-dm-should-go-with-it/14026/54">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/my-thoughts-on-the-movement-and-where-bm-dm-should-go-with-it/14026/54</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 16 May 2015 23:37:57 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14026-54</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/my-thoughts-on-the-movement-and-where-bm-dm-should-go-with-it/14026.rss">My thoughts on the MOVEMENT and where BM:DM should go with it.</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My thoughts on the MOVEMENT and where BM:DM should go with it.</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[N1ghtM]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>It is, for the sake of legitimacy, imperative to design and produce a fundamentally accurate and genuine remake of HL1. Furthermore, it is neccessary and appropriate to implement movements which are exclusive and true to the mechanics of HLDM. As a result, a foundation is established in validity, and is therefore acceptable with credence as it is in accordance to this principle.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/my-thoughts-on-the-movement-and-where-bm-dm-should-go-with-it/14026/53">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/my-thoughts-on-the-movement-and-where-bm-dm-should-go-with-it/14026/53</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 16 May 2015 18:10:49 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14026-53</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/my-thoughts-on-the-movement-and-where-bm-dm-should-go-with-it/14026.rss">My thoughts on the MOVEMENT and where BM:DM should go with it.</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My thoughts on the MOVEMENT and where BM:DM should go with it.</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[fury]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I wanted to mention the Use-slowdown before but forgot it. I definately want to see this in future BM  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=9" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/my-thoughts-on-the-movement-and-where-bm-dm-should-go-with-it/14026/52">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/my-thoughts-on-the-movement-and-where-bm-dm-should-go-with-it/14026/52</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 16 May 2015 11:07:57 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14026-52</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/my-thoughts-on-the-movement-and-where-bm-dm-should-go-with-it/14026.rss">My thoughts on the MOVEMENT and where BM:DM should go with it.</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My thoughts on the MOVEMENT and where BM:DM should go with it.</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[waLLLLLsh]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I like the power of the Mag. With the bow, maybe its just the animation of the bolt travelling that is throwing me off.  Though it seems like I really have to lead a player in order to hit them<br>
Maybe Im just not used to it yet or something.</p>
<p>In regards with the movement, there was also another technique that you could do in Half life 1.  I don’t necessarily think its a super important part of the game or anything, but, When your pressed your “Use Key” , it would actually stop your movement on the spot.  Players would use this to make it easier to land on smaller platforms when gauss jumping.  You could gauss jump somewhere with speed, and hit E soon as you hit the ground and it would bring you to a halt.  This move was also nice in battle, when your gauss jumping around quick , you could stop suddenly , sometimes throwing off the enemy’s aim.  Also, correct me if I’m wrong guys, but wasn’t this also for slowing down your ability to move around while charging on a Hev or health machine?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/my-thoughts-on-the-movement-and-where-bm-dm-should-go-with-it/14026/51">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/my-thoughts-on-the-movement-and-where-bm-dm-should-go-with-it/14026/51</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 16 May 2015 03:47:57 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14026-51</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/my-thoughts-on-the-movement-and-where-bm-dm-should-go-with-it/14026.rss">My thoughts on the MOVEMENT and where BM:DM should go with it.</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My thoughts on the MOVEMENT and where BM:DM should go with it.</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[vamp]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Alright</p>
<p>Longjump</p>
<hr>
<p>Is near perfect.<br>
Are you able to hear the sound from someone else longjumping or is that just for yourself?<br>
If the latter players are likely to remove it so they have clearer sound understanding of their surroundings.<br>
If the first Im just glad it isn’t as loud as opposing force but enough players likely want it removed for silent long jump reasons.</p>
<p>Besides its realistic blast sound it would already make a sound for players to hear as they land step.<br>
What pro players ultimately would want is to be able to silent longjump.<br>
This is preformed by doing the longjump combination and then stopping mid air(air control) pressing backwards to cut off jump lenght trading off for no land sound.<br>
Making ninja style possible.<br>
There probably are some lingers or downsides about having silent longjump in the game but it is a style amongst others that formed competitive play.<br>
some consider it lame yet it is important in role reverse of control and agressive attack styles.</p>
<p>For all i care it can be excluded.</p>
<p>The biggest issue to date is that you cant jump a few units higher while preforming a longjump so you can get onto higher grounds and boxes.<br>
Thus Getting to entities faster like ammo, armor and weapons, others wouldn’t be able too without the module.<br>
Shifting control of a particular area.<br>
That is something that has got to be addressed.</p>
<p>also the way it is now you have to wait a little bit before you can preform your 2nd longjump.<br>
now this has already been addressed and I think the 2-3 jumps in a row would be more then enough to prevent mindless spamming and include mind when to use it in combat.<br>
That is only good if it wont be annoying in combat so players got to give it a good try, it could help for a skillfull play.<br>
While at the same time finding a sweet spot between pro players and average players looking for a good time.<br>
Pro players likely tend to use it before a gauss jump or bunnyhop anyway.</p>
<p>Bunnyhop</p>
<hr>
<p>I’d recommend implanting the Adrenaline Gamer 2 bunnyhop.<br>
That is the best bunnyhop I have experienced under the source engine.<br>
If you’d like I might be able to get that code for you.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/my-thoughts-on-the-movement-and-where-bm-dm-should-go-with-it/14026/50">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/my-thoughts-on-the-movement-and-where-bm-dm-should-go-with-it/14026/50</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 16 May 2015 01:54:25 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14026-50</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/my-thoughts-on-the-movement-and-where-bm-dm-should-go-with-it/14026.rss">My thoughts on the MOVEMENT and where BM:DM should go with it.</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My thoughts on the MOVEMENT and where BM:DM should go with it.</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Fr0z3n]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>This topic, much like the last big MP feedback thread has drifted off topic to something completely different.</p>
<p>Please keep this thread to talking about the player movement mechanics of MP.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/my-thoughts-on-the-movement-and-where-bm-dm-should-go-with-it/14026/49">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/my-thoughts-on-the-movement-and-where-bm-dm-should-go-with-it/14026/49</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 16 May 2015 01:30:56 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14026-49</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/my-thoughts-on-the-movement-and-where-bm-dm-should-go-with-it/14026.rss">My thoughts on the MOVEMENT and where BM:DM should go with it.</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My thoughts on the MOVEMENT and where BM:DM should go with it.</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[fsdajkl]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="biggy">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/b/dc4da7/40.png" class="avatar"> biggy:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>PS: Why do you guys believe that all opinions have the same value or legitimacy? I mean, wouldn’t Einstein be more placed to speak about general relativity than most of you guys?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>This topic needs to stick to the game, and I’m peeking in a can of worms after what happened to last to your thread, but I’m saying this so you might last on this board longer.</p>
<p>All opinions don’t have the same value and legitimacy, but everyone has a place to speak here. Your credentials make your claims more trustworthy, but you should always explain your wisdom and refrain from personal attacks.</p>
<p>And more importantly, your credentials reside in the game. That expertise does nothing to bolster your ideology or what you think this product should be, because aspirations are not knowledge. Feel free to attempt to share your aspirations with others, but it’s going to require a separate line of reasoning - should Einstein cite his credentials when telling people what they should want?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/my-thoughts-on-the-movement-and-where-bm-dm-should-go-with-it/14026/48">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/my-thoughts-on-the-movement-and-where-bm-dm-should-go-with-it/14026/48</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 16 May 2015 01:16:34 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14026-48</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/my-thoughts-on-the-movement-and-where-bm-dm-should-go-with-it/14026.rss">My thoughts on the MOVEMENT and where BM:DM should go with it.</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My thoughts on the MOVEMENT and where BM:DM should go with it.</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Taceo]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="John Snow">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 John Snow:</div>
<blockquote></blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I know I must sound like a doofus for not saying why myself (busybusybusy), but we need to say why we disagree with something or think it is a bad idea instead of just voting up or down. It is not informative to the person who has been voted down and if their post contains many points it can be misinterpreted.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/my-thoughts-on-the-movement-and-where-bm-dm-should-go-with-it/14026/47">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/my-thoughts-on-the-movement-and-where-bm-dm-should-go-with-it/14026/47</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 16 May 2015 00:10:26 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14026-47</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/my-thoughts-on-the-movement-and-where-bm-dm-should-go-with-it/14026.rss">My thoughts on the MOVEMENT and where BM:DM should go with it.</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My thoughts on the MOVEMENT and where BM:DM should go with it.</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[fury]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="John Snow">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 John Snow:</div>
<blockquote>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="biggy">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/b/dc4da7/40.png" class="avatar"> biggy:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Why is that bad, and why are you using the word to fix? Please, explain. HLDM is an aggressive game, and what makes this game interesting is precisely the fact that even when you’re 100/100, a guy with 1hp can kill you in basically one shot or less than 500 ms. How is that a problem? Develop.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Because there is almost no weapon choice for a player under control. Yes, you can always kill a player with xbow headshot, but there is practically no chance to kill a dominating player with mp5 for example, even if your aim is really good. Gluon can be nice for retaking control, but:1. It has recoil and splash.<br>
2. It is too powerful against unarmored players. For example, if you are waiting for a player respawn on crossfire with gauss, you have a chance to miss and if you did, spawned player will have a chance to run/damage you a bit. A player can also delay a respawn, so you will have to lose 11 ammo and charge again or you will take damage. Considering recoil gluon makes its user almost invulnerable against a player with no significant weapons, however sometimes it’s possible to kill a gauss player with glock. That’s why (I think) gluon should be fixed somehow.<br>
First, we can remove recoil and splash, so it will be not just more fair, but more skilled too.<br>
Second, we can change it’s armor penetration, so it will be harder to use it to rape 100/0 players (the damage should be slighly higher than mp5s) without making it useless against 100/100 players.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Isn’t this topic about movement?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/my-thoughts-on-the-movement-and-where-bm-dm-should-go-with-it/14026/46">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/my-thoughts-on-the-movement-and-where-bm-dm-should-go-with-it/14026/46</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 16 May 2015 00:07:19 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14026-46</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/my-thoughts-on-the-movement-and-where-bm-dm-should-go-with-it/14026.rss">My thoughts on the MOVEMENT and where BM:DM should go with it.</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My thoughts on the MOVEMENT and where BM:DM should go with it.</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[KyuuGryphon]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I’m inclined to agree on the Gluon Gun needing rebalancing (fight me), but I don’t understand what you mean with regards to armour penetration. If a player has 0 suit charge, then armour penetration wouldn’t make a difference, right? Do you mean something like lowering the base damage it does and upping the armour penetration it has?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/my-thoughts-on-the-movement-and-where-bm-dm-should-go-with-it/14026/45">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/my-thoughts-on-the-movement-and-where-bm-dm-should-go-with-it/14026/45</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 16 May 2015 00:01:52 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14026-45</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/my-thoughts-on-the-movement-and-where-bm-dm-should-go-with-it/14026.rss">My thoughts on the MOVEMENT and where BM:DM should go with it.</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My thoughts on the MOVEMENT and where BM:DM should go with it.</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[John_Snow]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="biggy">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/b/dc4da7/40.png" class="avatar"> biggy:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Why is that bad, and why are you using the word to fix? Please, explain. HLDM is an aggressive game, and what makes this game interesting is precisely the fact that even when you’re 100/100, a guy with 1hp can kill you in basically one shot or less than 500 ms. How is that a problem? Develop.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Because there is almost no weapon choice for a player under control. Yes, you can always kill a player with xbow headshot, but there is practically no chance to kill a dominating player with mp5 for example, even if your aim is really good. Gluon can be nice for retaking control, but:</p>
<ol>
<li>It has recoil and splash.</li>
<li>It is too powerful against unarmored players. For example, if you are waiting for a player respawn on crossfire with gauss, you have a chance to miss and if you did, spawned player will have a chance to run/damage you a bit. A player can also delay a respawn, so you will have to lose 11 ammo and charge again or you will take damage. Considering recoil gluon makes its user almost invulnerable against a player with no significant weapons, however sometimes it’s possible to kill a gauss player with glock. That’s why (I think) gluon should be fixed somehow.<br>
First, we can remove recoil and splash, so it will be not just more fair, but more skilled too.<br>
Second, we can change it’s armor penetration, so it will be harder to use it to rape 100/0 players (the damage should be slighly higher than mp5s) without making it useless against 100/100 players.</li>
</ol>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/my-thoughts-on-the-movement-and-where-bm-dm-should-go-with-it/14026/44">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/my-thoughts-on-the-movement-and-where-bm-dm-should-go-with-it/14026/44</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 May 2015 23:56:23 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14026-44</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/my-thoughts-on-the-movement-and-where-bm-dm-should-go-with-it/14026.rss">My thoughts on the MOVEMENT and where BM:DM should go with it.</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My thoughts on the MOVEMENT and where BM:DM should go with it.</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[N1ghtM]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Here’s a few issues regarding movement which I would like to mention.</p>
<ul>
<li>
<p>Ladder Climbing feels slower and unnatural compared HL1. The screen bobbing caused by strafing left and right while climbing up a ladder is disorienting and annoying.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Ducking is slow and unresponsive and doesn’t allow the player to dodge attacks very effectively. Also, you can’t duck while in the air (which could make the difference of making a jump to a ledge or not.)</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>There isn’t a way to perform a maneuver known as a “duckslide”. This allows a player to skim the ground by quickly and repeatedly pressing duck (which can be performed manually, however, it’s most commonly used with special alias) using the momentum they have gained to collect weapons on the ground and roam the map more efficiently.</p>
</li>
</ul>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/my-thoughts-on-the-movement-and-where-bm-dm-should-go-with-it/14026/43">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/my-thoughts-on-the-movement-and-where-bm-dm-should-go-with-it/14026/43</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 May 2015 23:30:14 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14026-43</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/my-thoughts-on-the-movement-and-where-bm-dm-should-go-with-it/14026.rss">My thoughts on the MOVEMENT and where BM:DM should go with it.</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My thoughts on the MOVEMENT and where BM:DM should go with it.</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[D3lta]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>This thread is hilarious.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/my-thoughts-on-the-movement-and-where-bm-dm-should-go-with-it/14026/42">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/my-thoughts-on-the-movement-and-where-bm-dm-should-go-with-it/14026/42</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 May 2015 23:05:30 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14026-42</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/my-thoughts-on-the-movement-and-where-bm-dm-should-go-with-it/14026.rss">My thoughts on the MOVEMENT and where BM:DM should go with it.</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My thoughts on the MOVEMENT and where BM:DM should go with it.</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[vamp]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>biggy I really mean it man.</p>
<p>On the surface my comment is snappy and something one could take offence too.<br>
but the fact that I care that much is the only reason I am replying.</p>
<p>Work it around!</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/my-thoughts-on-the-movement-and-where-bm-dm-should-go-with-it/14026/41">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/my-thoughts-on-the-movement-and-where-bm-dm-should-go-with-it/14026/41</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 May 2015 22:59:35 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14026-41</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/my-thoughts-on-the-movement-and-where-bm-dm-should-go-with-it/14026.rss">My thoughts on the MOVEMENT and where BM:DM should go with it.</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My thoughts on the MOVEMENT and where BM:DM should go with it.</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[vamp]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="biggy">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/b/dc4da7/40.png" class="avatar"> biggy:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>The image you gives of AG community is really faithful to what it really is vamp. Maybe it’ll eventually make people understand that I’m the only guy one can trust or listen to. :}</p>
<p>EDIT: you’re right, I’d rather like it in order to encourage you to show what AG players are. A bunch of alcoholic losers who believe they are or were some kind of “pro”, while they couldn’t even do a simple lateral move or score more than 30% accuracy with gluon.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>haha who cares what people are like, we play a game.<br>
rather be anything like that then to be someone who pursuits his own ego godlike miss-function.</p>
<p>OOPS I just gave you a bite and food to reply back with.<br>
Id admit you got some points here and there but goddamn would you be able to set this aside and be of actual use people would listen too.<br>
If only.</p>
<p>That has always been your problem.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/my-thoughts-on-the-movement-and-where-bm-dm-should-go-with-it/14026/40">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/my-thoughts-on-the-movement-and-where-bm-dm-should-go-with-it/14026/40</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 May 2015 22:50:01 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14026-40</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/my-thoughts-on-the-movement-and-where-bm-dm-should-go-with-it/14026.rss">My thoughts on the MOVEMENT and where BM:DM should go with it.</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My thoughts on the MOVEMENT and where BM:DM should go with it.</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[biggy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Is there a lag compensation <a href="https://forums.blackmesasource.com/index.php/User/45746-Fr0z3n/" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">@Fr0z3n</a>? If yes, how did you implement it?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/my-thoughts-on-the-movement-and-where-bm-dm-should-go-with-it/14026/39">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/my-thoughts-on-the-movement-and-where-bm-dm-should-go-with-it/14026/39</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 May 2015 22:44:20 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14026-39</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/my-thoughts-on-the-movement-and-where-bm-dm-should-go-with-it/14026.rss">My thoughts on the MOVEMENT and where BM:DM should go with it.</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My thoughts on the MOVEMENT and where BM:DM should go with it.</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Fr0z3n]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="KyuuGryphon">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/k/2bfe46/40.png" class="avatar"> KyuuGryphon:</div>
<blockquote>
<aside class="quote group-black-mesa-devs" data-username="TextFAMGUY1">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/user_avatar/leakfree.org/textfamguy1/40/4294_2.png" class="avatar"> TextFAMGUY1:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Just a note - the current Crossbow IS instant hit when you’re zoomed in, the same as HL1. When zoomed, it becomes hitscan.</p>
<p>It’s possible there’s some funkiness with the hitreg which is making it feel weird and not instant (I’ve been complaining to our MP programmer about this for a while), but it is definitely hitscan when zoomed in. We’ll look into it.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Are you sure it’s hitscan? I turned host_timescale down out of boredom, and while it’s extremely short, it definitely looks like there’s a delay between firing the crossbow and the bolt hitting something.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Visually, it may appear not-hitscan, but backend it should definitely be. I haven’t noticed it not being hitscan.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/my-thoughts-on-the-movement-and-where-bm-dm-should-go-with-it/14026/38">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/my-thoughts-on-the-movement-and-where-bm-dm-should-go-with-it/14026/38</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 May 2015 22:38:09 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14026-38</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/my-thoughts-on-the-movement-and-where-bm-dm-should-go-with-it/14026.rss">My thoughts on the MOVEMENT and where BM:DM should go with it.</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
