<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Bugs i have come across Ingame</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/bugs-i-have-come-across-ingame/9837</link>
    <description>Hello,

I just finished it and  , well FK its better than the original ,

only things i did not like is the removal of the Klaxon at the resonance cascade in the test chamber,Glock has no secondry fire mode.

As for bugs

1. The model of the huge wooden reel of cable like the stuff you see when they make powerlines.  the problem is the model needs cutting down , as i can see enemeys through the side of it, for example if it was a full reel of wire the wire would be out at the outside diameter but the reel is half empty and i can &quot;shoot&quot; the invisible other half of wire, for devs its like theres a noclip there. you should know what i mean 

2. Tank, once tank is destroyed , destroyed model will &quot;float&quot; about 1/4 meter off ground, im guessing its something to do with its sequence or it had driven on something higher.

3. in the Lambda reactor when the platforms are circling the main reactor if the player moves to the outer diameter and gets &quot;caught&quot; on anouther model attached to the reactor walls the platform will stop and the inner &quot;support  pipes&quot; keep rotating., once player disloges platform appears to be out of since wih inner race



Thank you so much love the game</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 15 Sep 2012 12:45:16 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>In-game Issues (Mod)</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/bugs-i-have-come-across-ingame/9837.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Bugs i have come across Ingame</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[shifteh]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Hello,</p>
<p>I just finished it and  , well FK its better than the original ,</p>
<p>only things i did not like is the removal of the Klaxon at the resonance cascade in the test chamber,Glock has no secondry fire mode.</p>
<p>As for bugs</p>
<ol>
<li>
<p>The model of the huge wooden reel of cable like the stuff you see when they make powerlines.  the problem is the model needs cutting down , as i can see enemeys through the side of it, for example if it was a full reel of wire the wire would be out at the outside diameter but the reel is half empty and i can “shoot” the invisible other half of wire, for devs its like theres a noclip there. you should know what i mean</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Tank, once tank is destroyed , destroyed model will “float” about 1/4 meter off ground, im guessing its something to do with its sequence or it had driven on something higher.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>in the Lambda reactor when the platforms are circling the main reactor if the player moves to the outer diameter and gets “caught” on anouther model attached to the reactor walls the platform will stop and the inner “support  pipes” keep rotating., once player disloges platform appears to be out of since wih inner race</p>
</li>
</ol>
<p>Thank you so much love the game</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/bugs-i-have-come-across-ingame/9837/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/bugs-i-have-come-across-ingame/9837/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 15 Sep 2012 12:45:16 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9837-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/bugs-i-have-come-across-ingame/9837.rss">Bugs i have come across Ingame</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
