<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Give MP5 it&#39;s own damage values in the skill.cfg?</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/give-mp5-its-own-damage-values-in-the-skill-cfg/13367</link>
    <description>I would like to change the damages of the mp5 and pistol separately. Currently the &quot;sk_plr_dmg_9mm&quot; value is the only way to change the damage of the mp5... but it also changes the damage of the pistol.

Is there anyway to change the mp5&#39;s damage alone or add a new damage value to the skill.cfg?

My idea is to increase the damage of the MP5 because currently the pistol outshines it :|.

EDIT: I understand what is going on between mp5 vs pistol.
Pistol has better accuracy and rate of fire(I think).
Mp5 has better magazine capacity and is only slightly better than the pistol if the mp5 is tap fired(a mechanic which I don&#39;t personally like).

I need to find a way to disable that tap fire mechanic, then give it better damage.

Also, I need to see if there is a way to give the pistol a max rate of fire (if it doesn&#39;t have one already).</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2014 05:31:02 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Help!</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/give-mp5-its-own-damage-values-in-the-skill-cfg/13367.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Give MP5 it&#39;s own damage values in the skill.cfg?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Kil3r]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I would like to change the damages of the mp5 and pistol separately. Currently the “sk_plr_dmg_9mm” value is the only way to change the damage of the mp5… but it also changes the damage of the pistol.</p>
<p>Is there anyway to change the mp5’s damage alone or add a new damage value to the skill.cfg?</p>
<p>My idea is to increase the damage of the MP5 because currently the pistol outshines it :|.</p>
<p>EDIT: I understand what is going on between mp5 vs pistol.<br>
Pistol has better accuracy and rate of fire(I think).<br>
Mp5 has better magazine capacity and is only slightly better than the pistol if the mp5 is tap fired(a mechanic which I don’t personally like).</p>
<p>I need to find a way to disable that tap fire mechanic, then give it better damage.</p>
<p>Also, I need to see if there is a way to give the pistol a max rate of fire (if it doesn’t have one already).</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/give-mp5-its-own-damage-values-in-the-skill-cfg/13367/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/give-mp5-its-own-damage-values-in-the-skill-cfg/13367/1</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2014 05:31:02 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13367-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/give-mp5-its-own-damage-values-in-the-skill-cfg/13367.rss">Give MP5 it&#39;s own damage values in the skill.cfg?</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
