<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>How to edit the BM outrocredits?</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/how-to-edit-the-bm-outrocredits/13669</link>
    <description>So I&#39;ve tried multiple things - I directly edited the credits.txt file, multiple parts of ClientScheme.res, but I can&#39;t add anything into the end credits sequence. 

What I&#39;m personally trying to do is two things. First, I&#39;m trying to modify - where after it says &#39;BLACK MESA&#39;, then when it fades out, I want another thing to fade in and then fade out - I want to put &quot;The BLACK MESA team is...&quot; just like the original HL credits. Then after that start rolling &quot;Senior Developers&quot;

Then at the end of the developers section of the credits BM credits (but before the the special thanks, and in memory of). I want it to fade out again, then fade in and say &quot;Valve is...&quot; and put the devs of the original HL in the credits as well. I&#39;ve tried all of this within the two files above - but now I&#39;m starting to think that I might have to edit the actual credits.bsp in hammer...

Any advice?</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2015 23:55:31 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>The Cafeteria</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/how-to-edit-the-bm-outrocredits/13669.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>How to edit the BM outrocredits?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[BuzzKillington]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>So I’ve tried multiple things - I directly edited the credits.txt file, multiple parts of ClientScheme.res, but I can’t add anything into the end credits sequence.</p>
<p>What I’m personally trying to do is two things. First, I’m trying to modify - where after it says ‘BLACK MESA’, then when it fades out, I want another thing to fade in and then fade out - I want to put “The BLACK MESA team is…” just like the original HL credits. Then after that start rolling “Senior Developers”</p>
<p>Then at the end of the developers section of the credits BM credits (but before the the special thanks, and in memory of). I want it to fade out again, then fade in and say “Valve is…” and put the devs of the original HL in the credits as well. I’ve tried all of this within the two files above - but now I’m starting to think that I might have to edit the actual credits.bsp in hammer…</p>
<p>Any advice?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/how-to-edit-the-bm-outrocredits/13669/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/how-to-edit-the-bm-outrocredits/13669/1</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2015 23:55:31 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13669-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/how-to-edit-the-bm-outrocredits/13669.rss">How to edit the BM outrocredits?</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
