<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Black Mesa doesn&#39;t appear at the Steam library!</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/black-mesa-doesnt-appear-at-the-steam-library/10517</link>
    <description>Hey guys, I looked up on a guide on how to install Black Mesa (a guide that someone from this forum directed me to), and I think I followed every step correctly, I installed the game, installed Source SDK Base, and I restarted Steam, but for some reason the mod doesn&#39;t appear at the library. I tried this multiple time, and it never does. I can only play the game after I install it, so I have to always reinstall it to play the game.
Any ideas on how to solve this, please? :slight_smile: 

EDIT: Never mind guys, I solved the problem myself, the problem was that I didn&#39;t install the game at the Steam Mod folder, so it didn&#39;t appear at the library.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 17 Sep 2012 09:11:41 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Help!</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/black-mesa-doesnt-appear-at-the-steam-library/10517.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Black Mesa doesn&#39;t appear at the Steam library!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[TheDonk]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Hey guys, I looked up on a guide on how to install Black Mesa (a guide that someone from this forum directed me to), and I think I followed every step correctly, I installed the game, installed Source SDK Base, and I restarted Steam, but for some reason the mod doesn’t appear at the library. I tried this multiple time, and it never does. I can only play the game after I install it, so I have to always reinstall it to play the game.<br>
Any ideas on how to solve this, please? <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=9" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
<p>EDIT: Never mind guys, I solved the problem myself, the problem was that I didn’t install the game at the Steam Mod folder, so it didn’t appear at the library.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/black-mesa-doesnt-appear-at-the-steam-library/10517/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/black-mesa-doesnt-appear-at-the-steam-library/10517/1</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 17 Sep 2012 09:11:41 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-10517-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/black-mesa-doesnt-appear-at-the-steam-library/10517.rss">Black Mesa doesn&#39;t appear at the Steam library!</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
