<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>de_abbottabad</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/de-abbottabad/12300</link>
    <description>This is going to be as accurate as possible recreation of Osama&#39;s Compound in Abbottabad. I came up with this idea only to find out that it&#39;s already been done before, however the version already out there isn&#39;t very good, so I&#39;m aiming for my own more accurate version. I started this project yesterday so there&#39;s not too much to it yet.

The first floor is just started. I&#39;m basing everything off blueprints and diagrams I&#39;ve found online. The first floor should be accurate even to the width of the walls if I&#39;ve done everything properly. The fence around the compound is relatively accurate. The wall heights are mostly accurate and some of the distances are exact, but a lot of the other angles and lengths are guesstimated.
[img]https://puu.sh/2QblZ[/img]
[img]https://puu.sh/2QbDH.jpg[/img]

Not expecting anyone to want to join me but, I want to try and remake the stealth chopper that crashed in the compound. I can sort of do the modeling myself if anyone else wants to skin and texture it (or just do the whole thing because my model might end up a little messy). I&#39;ve found a really good diagram of the chopper so the modeling itself shouldn&#39;t be bad. Also at some point general custom props would be helpful such as beds. I can make do with the stock props but they won&#39;t look as nice.

I also need to find a good night skybox as this is going to be a night map and none of the stock skies are night. I might just see if I can steal a L4D2 skybox and dump it in CS:GO.
[img]https://cloud-2.steampowered.com/ugc/541834056677520842/1E0C3E4475554258BD6208581A766B9D2538EEA5/[/img]</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 09 May 2013 22:03:10 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Show Off</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/de-abbottabad/12300.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>de_abbottabad</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[garrthbarrttinn]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>This is going to be as accurate as possible recreation of Osama’s Compound in Abbottabad. I came up with this idea only to find out that it’s already been done before, however the version already out there isn’t very good, so I’m aiming for my own more accurate version. I started this project yesterday so there’s not too much to it yet.</p>
<p>The first floor is just started. I’m basing everything off blueprints and diagrams I’ve found online. The first floor should be accurate even to the width of the walls if I’ve done everything properly. The fence around the compound is relatively accurate. The wall heights are mostly accurate and some of the distances are exact, but a lot of the other angles and lengths are guesstimated.<br>
<span alt="" class="broken-image" title="This image is broken"><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-unlink svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#unlink"></use></svg></span><br>
<span alt="" class="broken-image" title="This image is broken"><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-unlink svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#unlink"></use></svg></span></p>
<p>Not expecting anyone to want to join me but, I want to try and remake the stealth chopper that crashed in the compound. I can sort of do the modeling myself if anyone else wants to skin and texture it (or just do the whole thing because my model might end up a little messy). I’ve found a really good diagram of the chopper so the modeling itself shouldn’t be bad. Also at some point general custom props would be helpful such as beds. I can make do with the stock props but they won’t look as nice.</p>
<p>I also need to find a good night skybox as this is going to be a night map and none of the stock skies are night. I might just see if I can steal a L4D2 skybox and dump it in CS:GO.<br>
<span alt="" class="broken-image" title="This image is broken"><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-unlink svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#unlink"></use></svg></span></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/de-abbottabad/12300/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/de-abbottabad/12300/1</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2013 22:03:10 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12300-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/de-abbottabad/12300.rss">de_abbottabad</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
