<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Certain enemies becoming passive?</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/certain-enemies-becoming-passive/8984</link>
    <description>So while playing Half-Life I encoutered two parts where some Vortigaunt(s) did not attack. This was due to a bug, I&#39;m sure, but it gave a false sense of freedom that I really liked. The ability to spare certian hostiles (depending on context) is a wonderful ability in games. 

This ability is great and is fun to do when I&#39;m killing a ton of enemies and I start to wonder why they keep trying to kill me. So I disarm one and leave him amongst an area I won&#39;t be returning to, as a sign of peace. 

Let me describe how it happened in Half-Life (goldrc): I was in the hallway right before the lift to the first encounter of those Black Spec-Ops Ninjas. I get to the part where I&#39;m being ambushed by two Vortigaunts spawning on both ends of the hallway. I kill the one back where I came, get into cover, shoot the one down the hallway, get into cover, and reload.  I pause, knowing it&#39;s not dead. I go around the corner aiming for the head but I pause again as it hasn&#39;t attacked. No more Vortigaunts are appearing and I decide to go up the lift. The Vortigaunt folows me up the lift and still does not attack. The security guard dies and I decide to sent the Vortigaunt back down the elevator, thus sparing it. 

The other instance was much later in the game, durring Xen. There comes a part where you walk into an open-ish area that contains something that somewhat resembles a ski lift. I crouch walk into the area and a Vortigaunt walks right next to me but doesn&#39;t react. I soon discover that as long as I don&#39;t bump into these Vortigaunts they will not do their usual attack routine. I can go about my buisness and watch them make hand gestures as some run around the place. 


Both of these experiences greatly added to the feel of the game and both make sense when Half-Life 2 is factored in. These were great parts and were enjoyable.

This sort of thing has been built into other games too! Take Halo 3 for example. On the level Crow&#39;s Nest there is a scene with Thel &#39;Vadam where he attacks two hostile Drones and yells to them about how their leader (the &quot;prophet&quot; Truth) is lying to them (which he is). Normaly Thel &#39;Vadam kills the drones, but if the player interferes and stops him from killing the drones it will cause certian drones throughout the level to be friendly. 

(I also recall a part in Dues Ex where if you spare some certian random people it causes a truce or something.) 


What I&#39;m trying to get across is that this is a great feature that should be possible somewhere in the game. Now I&#39;m not suggesting that more than a handful of NPC&#39;s be capable of this, but when a certian NPC encounters a certian pre-set situation it could cease attacking. The ability to spare the life of someone, wether to be a lone survivor or as a sign of peace, is a great thing to be able to do in a videogame.

(The Marines or non-sentient Xen wildlife should not be considered for this.)</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 10 Sep 2012 13:58:14 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Suggestion Box</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/certain-enemies-becoming-passive/8984.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Certain enemies becoming passive?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[danielsangeo]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I think this thread has accomplished what it needed to accomplish.  We know where people stand on certain enemies becoming passive through the game.</p>
<p>danielsangeo, we’re done here.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/certain-enemies-becoming-passive/8984/113">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/certain-enemies-becoming-passive/8984/113</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 10 Sep 2012 13:58:14 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8984-113</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/certain-enemies-becoming-passive/8984.rss">Certain enemies becoming passive?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Certain enemies becoming passive?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[xalener]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Dias">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/d/4491bb/40.png" class="avatar"> Dias:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>There were only 2 shackled Vorts in HL2. That one at the start of the game &amp; a dead guy in  Nova Prospekt. There’s no proof that the collars do anything at all.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>AND THIS MEANS THEY DON’T. IT’S JUST A COINCIDENCE THAT EVERY ENSLAVED VORT CHARACTER HAS HAD A COLLAR AND EVERY FREE VORT HASN’T.<br>
/thread</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/certain-enemies-becoming-passive/8984/112">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/certain-enemies-becoming-passive/8984/112</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 10 Sep 2012 13:49:31 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8984-112</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/certain-enemies-becoming-passive/8984.rss">Certain enemies becoming passive?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Certain enemies becoming passive?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Pettifogg]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>It’d make sense for them to somewhat limit their powers to stop them revolting, though, considering what they’re capable of in Episode 2.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/certain-enemies-becoming-passive/8984/111">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/certain-enemies-becoming-passive/8984/111</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 06 Sep 2012 14:18:23 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8984-111</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/certain-enemies-becoming-passive/8984.rss">Certain enemies becoming passive?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Certain enemies becoming passive?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Dias]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>There were only 2 shackled Vorts in HL2. That one at the start of the game &amp; a dead guy in  Nova Prospekt. There’s no proof that the collars do anything at all.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/certain-enemies-becoming-passive/8984/110">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/certain-enemies-becoming-passive/8984/110</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 06 Sep 2012 04:52:12 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8984-110</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/certain-enemies-becoming-passive/8984.rss">Certain enemies becoming passive?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Certain enemies becoming passive?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Eion_Kilant_739]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Gah, why’d you bump this thread? [COLOR=‘Black’]I’m just going to post so this thread doesn’t get even more posts.</p>
<p>Anyways the collars have been confirmed to be Ninilanth-related. The Vortigauns were originaly going to revolt with you in Xen but they ran out of time. I’m also sure that the Combine use other means to control them in Half-Life 2. Recall that Vortigaunt in a diaper being watched by a metrocop?</p>
<p>The Vortigaunts in the room without controllers on Xen also don’t attack Gordon.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/certain-enemies-becoming-passive/8984/109">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/certain-enemies-becoming-passive/8984/109</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 05 Sep 2012 23:42:30 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8984-109</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/certain-enemies-becoming-passive/8984.rss">Certain enemies becoming passive?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Certain enemies becoming passive?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Lemonz_amp_amp_orang]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Llewen Ebag">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Llewen Ebag:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>^^^<br>
That.</p>
<p>Remember also that the vorts had green reflective shackles in HL. This was probably how the Nihilanth controlled them, not to mention how the Combine control them in HL2.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>the shackles could actually be defective chains left from the time the xenians were under combine control; even nihilanth has the shackles (and a stomach surgery, judging by the stitches)</p>
<p>the vorts at the Agrunt factory were probally distanced from the nihilanth’s range so the Acontrollers were responsibe for supervising them (or, the nihilanth assisgned the factory vorts to a certain platoon of Acontrollers)</p>
<p>think of it, the 2 vorts in “xen attacks” (from half life decay) are probally a small band of “spec ops” equivilents in the xenian forces</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/certain-enemies-becoming-passive/8984/108">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/certain-enemies-becoming-passive/8984/108</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 05 Sep 2012 22:01:40 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8984-108</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/certain-enemies-becoming-passive/8984.rss">Certain enemies becoming passive?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Certain enemies becoming passive?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Llewen_Ebag]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>^^^<br>
That.</p>
<p>Remember also that the vorts had green reflective shackles in HL. This was probably how the Nihilanth controlled them, not to mention how the Combine control them in HL2.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/certain-enemies-becoming-passive/8984/107">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/certain-enemies-becoming-passive/8984/107</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 05 Sep 2012 21:38:33 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8984-107</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/certain-enemies-becoming-passive/8984.rss">Certain enemies becoming passive?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Certain enemies becoming passive?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Lemonz_amp_amp_orang]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>the vorts were controlled by nihilanth; and the agurnt factory vorts probally have never been to earth, therfore they dont know if gordon is hostile until the aliencontroller comes, it “informs” the vort slaves that gordon is a enemy</p>
<p>lets not forget that vorts, nihilanth and the Acontrollers use telepathic communication</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/certain-enemies-becoming-passive/8984/106">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/certain-enemies-becoming-passive/8984/106</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 05 Sep 2012 21:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8984-106</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/certain-enemies-becoming-passive/8984.rss">Certain enemies becoming passive?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Certain enemies becoming passive?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Mangled]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Just don’t forget that Bullsquids are also peaceful in Xen so long as they are in a healing pool.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/certain-enemies-becoming-passive/8984/105">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/certain-enemies-becoming-passive/8984/105</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 05 Sep 2012 20:45:09 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8984-105</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/certain-enemies-becoming-passive/8984.rss">Certain enemies becoming passive?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Certain enemies becoming passive?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[mechaelite]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="ojcoolj">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/o/ecb155/40.png" class="avatar"> ojcoolj:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>In Black Mesa they were dazed and confused, and thought they were the ones under attack. And notice how they’re more likely to attack when they’re in large numbers. One or two would probably spend more time staring.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>That makes some sense but if they were just scared, why did they help the Agrunts to attack us without mercy? Why not just run and hide and let the other “xenians” attack us? I still remember that one of them broke a metal door to attack you the first time you encounter houndeyes. And another time that a group of vorts prepared ambushes for humans.</p>
<p>They were obviusly being controlled, they weren’t confused, they were doing what their “master” ordered them: Invade us.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/certain-enemies-becoming-passive/8984/104">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/certain-enemies-becoming-passive/8984/104</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 13 Aug 2012 16:23:09 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8984-104</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/certain-enemies-becoming-passive/8984.rss">Certain enemies becoming passive?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Certain enemies becoming passive?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[BahamutBBob]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Pepe">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/p/4da419/40.png" class="avatar"> Pepe:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>trash squeezer (is this correct name? )</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Trash compactor.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/certain-enemies-becoming-passive/8984/103">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/certain-enemies-becoming-passive/8984/103</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 11 Aug 2012 18:55:59 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8984-103</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/certain-enemies-becoming-passive/8984.rss">Certain enemies becoming passive?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Certain enemies becoming passive?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[ojcoolj]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I’m not sure if anyone mentioned this, but Vorts are naturally passive creatures who don’t hurt a fly.</p>
<p>In Black Mesa they were dazed and confused, and thought they were the ones under attack. And notice how they’re more likely to attack when they’re in large numbers. One or two would probably spend more time staring.</p>
<p>The reason they didn’t attack you on Xen was an act of passive rebellion against the Controllers and the Nihilanth. When the controllers showed up, they had to attack.<br>
Poor Vorts  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/frowning.png?v=9" title=":frowning:" class="emoji" alt=":frowning:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/certain-enemies-becoming-passive/8984/102">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/certain-enemies-becoming-passive/8984/102</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 11 Aug 2012 16:00:50 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8984-102</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/certain-enemies-becoming-passive/8984.rss">Certain enemies becoming passive?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Certain enemies becoming passive?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Pepe]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>A little bump but I wanted to add few words from myself:</p>
<ul>
<li>I guess that there is out of our concern how the things with Vortigaunts will look on Xen because: a) it might’ve been done already b) even if it’s not devs will (most probably) keep it secret to suprise players</li>
<li>about earlier parts of the game, there are 2 very easy solutions if we really wanna do (well, if we really wanna that developers will do  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=9" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:">  ) something about it:</li>
</ul>
<p>solution 1: consider Vortigaunts in Black Mesa facility as “slave soldiers” which for whatever reason (being electrocuted with collar while on “battlefield” covers it pretty well) will attack you always. consider Vortigaunts on Xen as “slave workers” which wears the collar to work faster (normal assumption why they are keep working, it doesn’t have to occur in the game), eventually they can be electrified at parts when Controller is nearby and player is spotted, than attack. Im sure devs will/already did make it right.<br>
solution 2 (which is not excluding solution 1): in part when freeman is pulled to trash squeezer (is this correct name? ) he can notice single Vortigaunt which is passing by in a distance, stops for a short while, looks at soldiers and freeman (soldiers draging freeman are looking in the opposite direction), and than knowing that he wasn’t spotted (stunned guy doesn’t count  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=9" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:">  ), moves forward. Just a little, subtle hint for player: “Hmm, what did that meant?”</p>
<p>Guess that’s quick and easy solution if we really want to bother with this particular issue.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/certain-enemies-becoming-passive/8984/101">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/certain-enemies-becoming-passive/8984/101</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 11 Aug 2012 13:10:23 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8984-101</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/certain-enemies-becoming-passive/8984.rss">Certain enemies becoming passive?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Certain enemies becoming passive?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[JerseyRyan]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Raminator">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/r/6bbea6/40.png" class="avatar"> Raminator:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I don’t know why everyone’s mixing the two up.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>It’s not that everyone’s mixing it up. It’s just that people who got the idea don’t post about it.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/certain-enemies-becoming-passive/8984/100">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/certain-enemies-becoming-passive/8984/100</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jul 2012 11:56:17 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8984-100</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/certain-enemies-becoming-passive/8984.rss">Certain enemies becoming passive?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Certain enemies becoming passive?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[mechaelite]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Eion Kilant 739">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Eion Kilant 739:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>A controller enters the room that Vortigaunts are passive in. It does something, and the Vortigaunts shudder and quiver. Then, if the player shoots the Controler (before the scene is complete) and none of the Vortigaunts die, the Controler stops the animation and looks at/attacks you. Then a Vortigaunt attacks. Then another one and then multiple attack at once. They then turn to you and are passive. (Possibly an animation now? They could just look at you…)</p>
<p>It works right?</p>
<p>It shows the player in and of itself that the Vortigaunts are not at peace with the Controlers.</p>
<p>It shows that the Controlers have control over the Vortigaunts.</p>
<p>It shows that the Vortigaunts <span class="bbcode-i">want</span> to rebel.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>That’s like the original Xen idea VALVe had. Gordon had to “create” a rebellion with the vorts against the Nihilanth and his controllers. The only problem was that 80% of the players would shoot the vorts at the very moment they saw them. That’s why Valve often used…</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Comrade Tiki">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Comrade Tiki:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>… Letting monsters be busy with things other than attacking the player. The player was oftentimes an observer instead of the focus of the game… it made the world feel more alive, these “scripted sequences”. It’s what made Half-Life better than Doom and such, where every sprite is shooting at you.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>If we simply want that 80% players group see that the vorts ain’t hostile before they waste all their precious MP5 Ammo, we need scripted sequences. If we don’t use them, well at least the 20% will know what’s really going on.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Comrade Tiki">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Comrade Tiki:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Let an eating bullsquid lie.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>[COLOR=‘Black’]<span class="bbcode-i"><span class="bbcode-u"><span class="bbcode-b">Never</span></span></span> <em>evil grinn</em></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/certain-enemies-becoming-passive/8984/99">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/certain-enemies-becoming-passive/8984/99</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jul 2012 10:09:54 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8984-99</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/certain-enemies-becoming-passive/8984.rss">Certain enemies becoming passive?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Certain enemies becoming passive?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Nightblade]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="bur">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/b/87869e/40.png" class="avatar"> bur:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>+1</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>You bastard you beat me to it!</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/certain-enemies-becoming-passive/8984/98">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/certain-enemies-becoming-passive/8984/98</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jul 2012 21:04:05 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8984-98</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/certain-enemies-becoming-passive/8984.rss">Certain enemies becoming passive?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Certain enemies becoming passive?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[bur]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Comrade Tiki">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Comrade Tiki:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Well… when you think about it, this is what Half-Life was always about.</p>
<p>You see some aliens, they’re too shocked to see you to have any reaction.<br>
You see a headcrab, it’s busy digesting some smart schmuck’s head.<br>
You see a barnacle, it’s busy being a barnacle.<br>
You see a bullsquid, it’s busy falling to its death.<br>
You see a houndeye, it’s either scampering around or sleeping.<br>
You see a couple of zombies, they’re busy munching.<br>
You see another bullsquid, it’s chasing around some cold schmuck.<br>
You see a soldier, he’s busy murdering a scientist.<br>
You see an automated gun, it’s busy shooting headcrabs.<br>
You see an ichthyosaur eating a scientist before you fall in the water.<br>
You see a huge alien, it’s burning some soldiers.<br>
You see an alien grunt, it’s stuck behind some glass.<br>
You see an apache, it’s clearing the dam of organic invaders.<br>
You see a jet. (I guess it didn’t see you.)<br>
You see some mantas, they’re dropping off some alien grunts.<br>
You see some jets, they’re blowing up some alien grunts.<br>
You see a whole bunch of soldiers, they’re fighting a bunch of aliens.</p>
<p>A lot of Half-Life was letting monsters be busy with things other than attacking the player. The player was oftentimes an observer instead of the focus of the game… it made the world feel more alive, these “scripted sequences”. It’s what made Half-Life better than Doom and such, where every sprite is shooting at you.</p>
<p>…</p>
<p>I don’t understand why a few alien slaves aren’t allowed to tinker with their devices despite the player’s presence. The drones in question were meant to seem unaware of the conflict outside the hive.</p>
<p>Is it hard to communicate motive to the player? Sure… but the possibility of being disengaged is what helps keep Half-Life so darn interesting.</p>
<p>Let an eating bullsquid lie.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>+1</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/certain-enemies-becoming-passive/8984/97">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/certain-enemies-becoming-passive/8984/97</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jul 2012 19:03:45 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8984-97</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/certain-enemies-becoming-passive/8984.rss">Certain enemies becoming passive?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Certain enemies becoming passive?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Zen609]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="trunk_slamchest">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/t/278dde/40.png" class="avatar"> trunk_slamchest:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>but in a technical sense, there was a golden period between about 1997 and 2003 where graphics and game play met at a golden ratio. one was not favored over the other because both graphics and gameplay at the time had equal faults and advantages that contrasted each other.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>There were also plenty of shitty games and games that wouldn’t have qualified as having that ‘golden ratio’, however you may define it (probably not as Φ), and likewise there are plenty games released since 2003 that surely would qualify as that. You’re a HL fan, did you enjoy HL2?  The L4D games? The Portal games? Come on, man, you couldn’t possibly think the gameplay mechanics of the Portal games are shitty.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="trunk_slamchest">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/t/278dde/40.png" class="avatar"> trunk_slamchest:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>valve knows the value of wabi sabi. so do i. idk if raminator does.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Wabi sabi!  That’s a good use of that term. But you haven’t even played the game yet, you can’t know anything about the gameplay. (other than the vort issue being discussed).</p>
<p>And, yeah, sorry, I know my comment was completely off-topic - that old school/new school thing just caught my eye, and i just wanted to toss in a quick aside.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/certain-enemies-becoming-passive/8984/96">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/certain-enemies-becoming-passive/8984/96</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jul 2012 17:33:48 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8984-96</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/certain-enemies-becoming-passive/8984.rss">Certain enemies becoming passive?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Certain enemies becoming passive?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Maxey]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Besides, is a small detail like that going to ruin the game for you? I bet most people just straight up shot the Vorts when they reached that part, because that’s what they did for the whole game.</p>
<p>BTW, I made up that quote, Ram never said that.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/certain-enemies-becoming-passive/8984/95">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/certain-enemies-becoming-passive/8984/95</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jul 2012 16:57:57 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8984-95</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/certain-enemies-becoming-passive/8984.rss">Certain enemies becoming passive?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Certain enemies becoming passive?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[trunk_slamchest]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Maxey">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/user_avatar/leakfree.org/maxey/40/4358_2.png" class="avatar"> Maxey:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>You’re giving Raminator too much credit. He’s not the only one calling the shots.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>“I used to make remakes of Half-Life but then I took 7 years doing it and still haven’t released it yet.” - Raminator</p>
<p>i hope for bms’s sake youre right.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/certain-enemies-becoming-passive/8984/94">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/certain-enemies-becoming-passive/8984/94</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jul 2012 16:41:35 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8984-94</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/certain-enemies-becoming-passive/8984.rss">Certain enemies becoming passive?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Certain enemies becoming passive?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Maxey]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>You’re giving Raminator too much credit. He’s not the only one calling the shots.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/certain-enemies-becoming-passive/8984/93">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/certain-enemies-becoming-passive/8984/93</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jul 2012 16:30:56 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8984-93</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/certain-enemies-becoming-passive/8984.rss">Certain enemies becoming passive?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Certain enemies becoming passive?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[trunk_slamchest]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Zen609">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/z/71e660/40.png" class="avatar"> Zen609:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>When Half Life was released,  no one thought the graphics were shitty - in fact, everyone thought they were awesome.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>i 100% agree</p>
<p>but in a technical sense, there was a golden period between about 1997 and 2003 where graphics and game play met at a golden ratio. one was not favored over the other because both graphics and gameplay at the time had equal faults and advantages that contrasted each other.</p>
<p>valve knows the value of wabi sabi. so do i. idk if raminator does.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/certain-enemies-becoming-passive/8984/92">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/certain-enemies-becoming-passive/8984/92</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jul 2012 16:27:17 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8984-92</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/certain-enemies-becoming-passive/8984.rss">Certain enemies becoming passive?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Certain enemies becoming passive?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[trunk_slamchest]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Raminator">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/r/6bbea6/40.png" class="avatar"> Raminator:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>So what’re you doing here, champ?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>im waiting to see if you fucked up bms or not. half life is what got me into gaming, so its an inherited interest, champ.</p>
<p>shiny new graphics are great. gameplay is essential.</p>
<p>fact of the matter is if you fuck up the game play, everyone will just go back to playing half life.</p>
<p>all the HD screen shots in the world wont make up for a game that plays like gunman chronicles.</p>
<p>bms is more or less Raminator’s Half Life. just like when old movies are remade and reinvisioned by talentless directors who dont understand why the movie he is recreating was so great in the first place.</p>
<p>EDIT: the choice given between either killing scientists or not and not having any direct consequences was the game changer. not the graphics that were awesome at the time.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/certain-enemies-becoming-passive/8984/91">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/certain-enemies-becoming-passive/8984/91</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jul 2012 16:15:32 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8984-91</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/certain-enemies-becoming-passive/8984.rss">Certain enemies becoming passive?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Certain enemies becoming passive?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Comrade_Tiki]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Raminator">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/r/6bbea6/40.png" class="avatar"> Raminator:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Having enemies that <span class="bbcode-i">sometimes</span> don’t attack you isn’t a workable idea…</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Well… when you think about it, this is what Half-Life was always about.</p>
<p>You see some aliens, they’re too shocked to see you to have any reaction.<br>
You see a headcrab, it’s busy digesting some smart schmuck’s head.<br>
You see a barnacle, it’s busy being a barnacle.<br>
You see a bullsquid, it’s busy falling to its death.<br>
You see a houndeye, it’s either scampering around or sleeping.<br>
You see a couple of zombies, they’re busy munching.<br>
You see another bullsquid, it’s chasing around some cold schmuck.<br>
You see a soldier, he’s busy murdering a scientist.<br>
You see an automated gun, it’s busy shooting headcrabs.<br>
You see an ichthyosaur eating a scientist before you fall in the water.<br>
You see a huge alien, it’s burning some soldiers.<br>
You see an alien grunt, it’s stuck behind some glass.<br>
You see an apache, it’s clearing the dam of organic invaders.<br>
You see a jet. (I guess it didn’t see you.)<br>
You see some mantas, they’re dropping off some alien grunts.<br>
You see some jets, they’re blowing up some alien grunts.<br>
You see a whole bunch of soldiers, they’re fighting a bunch of aliens.</p>
<p>A lot of Half-Life was letting monsters be busy with things other than attacking the player. The player was oftentimes an observer instead of the focus of the game… it made the world feel more alive, these “scripted sequences”. It’s what made Half-Life better than Doom and such, where every sprite is shooting at you.</p>
<p>…</p>
<p>I don’t understand why a few alien slaves aren’t allowed to tinker with their devices despite the player’s presence. The drones in question were meant to seem unaware of the conflict outside the hive.</p>
<p>Is it hard to communicate motive to the player? Sure… but the possibility of being disengaged is what helps keep Half-Life so darn interesting.</p>
<p>Let an eating bullsquid lie.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/certain-enemies-becoming-passive/8984/90">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/certain-enemies-becoming-passive/8984/90</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jul 2012 12:30:12 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8984-90</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/certain-enemies-becoming-passive/8984.rss">Certain enemies becoming passive?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Certain enemies becoming passive?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[yrr]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>^no.  Because you <span class="bbcode-i">know</span>  Half-Life. You know what’s going on, how the Vortigaunts behave and why. Everybody who hasn’t played Black Mesa (or Half Life for that Matter) will become irritated. I think Raminator explained it pretty reasonable and they won’t change it. It would be perceived in a false way.  Besides - even the original Half Life didn’t do a great job in imaging the Vorts as peaceful. Sure, there was the Scene in Interloper where they didn’t attack you, but on my first playthrough i was used to them as hostile aliens and so I shot them when I saw them. I realized their passive behaviour only when they had a tactical advantage (in the next room where you drop in the “water”), standing above me so I wouldn’t be able to attack them before they shoot me and they didn’t shoot unless there was a controller in this room. After browsing the Half Life Wiki and studying their Behaviour i was like  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/bulb.png?v=9" title=":bulb:" class="emoji" alt=":bulb:"><br>
But this was occasional empirical knowledge.  I also could’ve thought: “Hell, fucking glitch” or presumed that the Vortigaunts didn’t see/recognized you.</p>
<p>See the problems ?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/certain-enemies-becoming-passive/8984/89">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/certain-enemies-becoming-passive/8984/89</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jul 2012 07:59:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8984-89</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/certain-enemies-becoming-passive/8984.rss">Certain enemies becoming passive?</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
