<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>POLAND PLANE CRASH!!!!</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/poland-plane-crash/3726</link>
    <description>Source: [url]https://www.google.com/hostednews/ap/article/ALeqM5iVF6779laLoQqf-UdYjLw7H5Bw-AD9F06GL01[/url]


MOSCOW — Polish President Lech Kaczynski and some of the country&#39;s highest military and civilian leaders died on Saturday when the presidential plane crashed as it came in for a landing in thick fog in western Russia, killing 96, officials said.

Russian and Polish officials said there were no survivors on the 26-year-old Tupolev, which was taking the president, his wife and staff to events marking the 70th anniversary of the massacre of thousands of Polish officers by Soviet secret police.

The crash devastated the upper echelons of Poland&#39;s political and military establishments. On board were the army chief of staff, national bank president, deputy foreign minister, army chaplain, head of the National Security Office, deputy parliament speaker, civil rights commissioner and at least two presidential aides and three lawmakers, the Polish foreign ministry said.

It was not expected to directly affect the functioning of Polish government, however: Poland&#39;s president is commander in chief of its armed forces but the position&#39;s domestic duties are chiefly symbolic. The prime minister and other top government ministers were not aboard the plane.

Poland has long discussed replacing the planes that carry the country&#39;s leaders but said they lacked the funds. The presidential Tu-154 had been overhauled in December in Russia, officials said.

Russia&#39;s Emergency Ministry said there were 96 dead, 88 part of a Polish state delegation. Poland&#39;s Foreign Ministry spokesman, Piotr Paszkowski, said there were 89 people on the passenger list but one person had not shown up for the roughly 1 1/2-hour flight from Warsaw&#39;s main airport.

Poland&#39;s parliament speaker, the acting president, declared a week of national mourning.

&quot;We still cannot fully understand the scope of this tragedy and what it means for us in the future. Nothing like this has ever happened in Poland,&quot; Paszkowski said. &quot;We can assume with great certainty that all persons on board have been killed.&quot;

The plane tilted to the left before crashing, eyewitness Slawomir Sliwinski told Rossiya-24. He said there were two loud explosions when the aircraft hit the ground.

State news channel Rossiya-24 showed footage from the crash site, with pieces of the plane scattered widely amid leafless trees and small fires burning in woods shrouded with fog. A tail fin with the red and white national colors of Poland stuck up from the debris.

&quot;The Polish presidential plane did not make it to the runway while landing. Tentative findings indicate that it hit the treetops and fell apart,&quot; regional governor Sergei Anufriev said on Rossiya-24. &quot;Nobody has survived the disaster.&quot;

According to the Aviation Safety Network, there have been 66 crashes involving Tu-154s, including six in the past five years. The Russian carrier Aeroflot recently withdrew its Tu-154 fleet from service.

The presidential plane was fully overhauled in December, the general director of the Aviakor aviation maintenance plant in Samara, Russia told Rossiya-24. The plant repaired the plane&#39;s three engines, retrofitted electronic and navigation equipment and updated the interior, Alexei Gusev said. He said there could be no doubts that the plane was flightworthy.

Russian Prime Minister Vladimir Putin and President Dmitry Medvedev both called Polish Prime Minister Donald Tusk to express their condolences and they promised to work closely with Poland in investigating the crash.

&quot;On this difficult day the people of Russia stand with the Polish people,&quot; Medvedev told Tusk, the Kremlin press service said.

Putin, who has been put in charge of the commission investigating the crash, told Tusk that he would keep him fully briefed, his spokesman said.

Polish-Russian relations had been improving of late after being poisoned for decades over the Katyn massacre of some 22,000 Polish officers.

Russia never has formally apologized for the murders but Putin&#39;s decision to attend a memorial ceremony earlier this week in the forest near Katyn was seen as a gesture of goodwill toward reconciliation. Rossiya-24 showed hundreds of people around the Katyn monument, many holding Polish flags, some weeping.

In Warsaw, Tusk called an extraordinary meeting of his Cabinet and the national flag was lowered to half-staff at the presidential palace, where people gathered to lay flowers and light candles.

Black ribbons appeared in some windows in the Polish capital.

Kaczynski, 60, became president in December 2005 after defeating Tusk in that year&#39;s presidential vote.

The nationalist conservative was the twin brother of Poland&#39;s opposition leader, former Prime Minister Jaroslaw Kaczynski. Kaczynski&#39;s wife, Maria, was an economist. They had a daughter, Marta, and two granddaughters.

Kaczynski had said he would seek a second term in presidential elections this fall. He was expected to face an uphill struggle against Parliament speaker Bronislaw Komorowski, the candidate of Tusk&#39;s governing Civic Platform party.

Poland was due to hold elections in the fall, though no date had been set.

However, the constitution says the parliament speaker, who takes on the duties of president, must announce early elections within 14 days of the president&#39;s death.

The vote must be held within another 60 days. This means Poland will be holding early presidential elections before June 20.

In the village of Gorzno, in northern Poland, the streets were largely empty as people stayed home to watch television.

&quot;It is very symbolic that they were flying to pay homage to so many murdered Poles,&quot; said resident Waleria Gess, 73.

&quot;I worry because so many clever and decent people were killed,&quot; said high school student Pawel Kwas, 17. &quot;I am afraid we may have problems in the future to find equally talented politicians.&quot;

Klaus Bachmann, a professor of politics at Wroclaw University, said the president &quot;wasn&#39;t very popular and it was quite obvious that he would lose the upcoming elections.&quot;

&quot;The open question is what will Kaczynski&#39;s party and his brother do; he might decide to run for president himself, he might also consider to withdraw from politics at all because he had a very very close link to his brother and I can&#39;t imagine how much shocked he must be.&quot;

Poland, a nation of 38 million people, is by far the largest of the 10 formerly communist countries that have joined the European Union in recent years.

Last year, Poland was the only EU nation to avoid recession and posted economic growth of 1.7 percent.

It has become a firm U.S. ally in the region since the fall of communism — a stance that crosses party lines.

The country sent troops to the U.S.-led war in Iraq and recently boosted its contingent in Afghanistan to some 2,600 soldiers.

U.S. Patriot missiles are expected to be deployed in Poland this year. That was a Polish condition for a 2008 deal — backed by both Kaczynski and Tusk — to host long-range missile defense interceptors.

The deal, which was struck by the Bush administration, angered Russia and was later reconfigured under President Barack Obama&#39;s administration.

Under the Obama plan, Poland would host a different type of missile defense interceptors as part of a more mobile system and at a later date, probably not until 2018.

Kaczynski is the first serving Polish leader to die since exiled World War II-era leader Gen. Wladyslaw Sikorski in a plane crash off Gibraltar in 1943.

Associated Press writers Mansur Mirovalev in Moscow, Monika Scislowska in Warsaw, Geir Moulson in Berlin, Deborah Seward in Paris and Naomi Koppel in London contributed to this report.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 11 Apr 2010 08:18:09 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Off Topic</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/poland-plane-crash/3726.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>POLAND PLANE CRASH!!!!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[baconeggs]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>See, we can make Communism work, why can’t you?</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="X_Mastershot_X">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/x/c5a1d2/40.png" class="avatar"> X_Mastershot_X:</div>
<blockquote>
<p><span alt="" class="broken-image" title="This image is broken"><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-unlink svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#unlink"></use></svg></span></p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Man, this is going to be one boring flight…</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/poland-plane-crash/3726/53">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/poland-plane-crash/3726/53</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 11 Apr 2010 08:18:09 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3726-53</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/poland-plane-crash/3726.rss">POLAND PLANE CRASH!!!!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>POLAND PLANE CRASH!!!!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Comrade_Tiki]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Acristoff">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/a/ea666f/40.png" class="avatar"> Acristoff:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>It was China.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Actually, I too deemed that the most likely candidate. The Chinese-Russian rivalry runs deep.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/poland-plane-crash/3726/52">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/poland-plane-crash/3726/52</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 11 Apr 2010 03:03:22 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3726-52</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/poland-plane-crash/3726.rss">POLAND PLANE CRASH!!!!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>POLAND PLANE CRASH!!!!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Kairouseki]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Nah…<br>
<span alt="" class="broken-image" title="This image is broken"><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-unlink svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#unlink"></use></svg></span></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/poland-plane-crash/3726/51">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/poland-plane-crash/3726/51</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 11 Apr 2010 01:39:12 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3726-51</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/poland-plane-crash/3726.rss">POLAND PLANE CRASH!!!!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>POLAND PLANE CRASH!!!!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Acristoff]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>It was China.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/poland-plane-crash/3726/50">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/poland-plane-crash/3726/50</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 11 Apr 2010 01:33:14 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3726-50</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/poland-plane-crash/3726.rss">POLAND PLANE CRASH!!!!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>POLAND PLANE CRASH!!!!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Winged_One]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>inwithconspiracythee-roys</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/poland-plane-crash/3726/49">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/poland-plane-crash/3726/49</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 11 Apr 2010 01:32:45 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3726-49</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/poland-plane-crash/3726.rss">POLAND PLANE CRASH!!!!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>POLAND PLANE CRASH!!!!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[shifty]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>inb4conspiracythee-roys!!!</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/poland-plane-crash/3726/48">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/poland-plane-crash/3726/48</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 11 Apr 2010 01:30:08 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3726-48</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/poland-plane-crash/3726.rss">POLAND PLANE CRASH!!!!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>POLAND PLANE CRASH!!!!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Omega_Absolute]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>story = highlight of my day.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/poland-plane-crash/3726/47">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/poland-plane-crash/3726/47</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 11 Apr 2010 00:22:50 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3726-47</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/poland-plane-crash/3726.rss">POLAND PLANE CRASH!!!!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>POLAND PLANE CRASH!!!!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Jorma_Kay]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Omega_Absolute">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/o/8e8cbc/40.png" class="avatar"> Omega_Absolute:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>welcome back to page 1</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I use that line all the time in the chat, so uhh, yeah, whatever. :tired:</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/poland-plane-crash/3726/46">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/poland-plane-crash/3726/46</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 11 Apr 2010 00:21:54 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3726-46</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/poland-plane-crash/3726.rss">POLAND PLANE CRASH!!!!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>POLAND PLANE CRASH!!!!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Omega_Absolute]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Jorma Kay">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Jorma Kay:</div>
<blockquote>
<p><img src="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/original/2X/0/00d6228f38377538ae77dd951b34c8a4096d5085.jpeg" alt="" data-base62-sha1="7oMuso1cnUJ17c5ZLhsj1f26Vv" width="480" height="360"></p>
<p>REMEMBER, NO RUSSIAN.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>welcome back to page 1</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/poland-plane-crash/3726/45">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/poland-plane-crash/3726/45</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 11 Apr 2010 00:19:16 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3726-45</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/poland-plane-crash/3726.rss">POLAND PLANE CRASH!!!!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>POLAND PLANE CRASH!!!!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Jorma_Kay]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Winged One">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Winged One:</div>
<blockquote>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">The Russians</span> are at it again!</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p><img src="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/original/2X/0/00d6228f38377538ae77dd951b34c8a4096d5085.jpeg" alt="" data-base62-sha1="7oMuso1cnUJ17c5ZLhsj1f26Vv" width="480" height="360"></p>
<p><span class="bbcode-i">REMEMBER, NO RUSSIAN.</span></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/poland-plane-crash/3726/44">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/poland-plane-crash/3726/44</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 11 Apr 2010 00:18:07 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3726-44</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/poland-plane-crash/3726.rss">POLAND PLANE CRASH!!!!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>POLAND PLANE CRASH!!!!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Comrade_Tiki]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>whoah, that’s, like, metaphotoshopping</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/poland-plane-crash/3726/43">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/poland-plane-crash/3726/43</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 10 Apr 2010 22:26:23 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3726-43</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/poland-plane-crash/3726.rss">POLAND PLANE CRASH!!!!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>POLAND PLANE CRASH!!!!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Omega_Absolute]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Acristoff">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/a/ea666f/40.png" class="avatar"> Acristoff:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>That looks shopped.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="geekofalltrades">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/g/c2a13f/40.png" class="avatar"> geekofalltrades:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>As an American, I can say with one hundred percent conviction that Al Qaeda is responsible.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p><img src="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/original/2X/2/2f0984456f8dd47c5beb0a68b72c3d6cf62ef2aa.jpeg" alt="" data-base62-sha1="6I6PuuEmauXO02up6hgyYXrei26" width="300" height="300"></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/poland-plane-crash/3726/42">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/poland-plane-crash/3726/42</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 10 Apr 2010 22:18:06 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3726-42</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/poland-plane-crash/3726.rss">POLAND PLANE CRASH!!!!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>POLAND PLANE CRASH!!!!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Winged_One]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>The Russians are at it again!</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/poland-plane-crash/3726/41">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/poland-plane-crash/3726/41</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 10 Apr 2010 22:03:48 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3726-41</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/poland-plane-crash/3726.rss">POLAND PLANE CRASH!!!!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>POLAND PLANE CRASH!!!!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Ond_kaja]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="sebbie10">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/s/e5b9ba/40.png" class="avatar"> sebbie10:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I smell a spy…</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>“That pilot is not one of ours!”</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/poland-plane-crash/3726/40">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/poland-plane-crash/3726/40</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 10 Apr 2010 22:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3726-40</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/poland-plane-crash/3726.rss">POLAND PLANE CRASH!!!!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>POLAND PLANE CRASH!!!!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[geekofalltrades]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>As an American, I can say with one hundred percent conviction that Al Qaeda is responsible.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/poland-plane-crash/3726/39">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/poland-plane-crash/3726/39</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 10 Apr 2010 21:39:48 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3726-39</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/poland-plane-crash/3726.rss">POLAND PLANE CRASH!!!!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>POLAND PLANE CRASH!!!!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[papernick]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I can tell from some of the pixels.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/poland-plane-crash/3726/38">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/poland-plane-crash/3726/38</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 10 Apr 2010 20:52:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3726-38</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/poland-plane-crash/3726.rss">POLAND PLANE CRASH!!!!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>POLAND PLANE CRASH!!!!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Acristoff]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>That looks shopped.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/poland-plane-crash/3726/37">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/poland-plane-crash/3726/37</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 10 Apr 2010 20:32:59 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3726-37</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/poland-plane-crash/3726.rss">POLAND PLANE CRASH!!!!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>POLAND PLANE CRASH!!!!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[X_Mastershot_X]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Please stop i am laughing my ass off <span class="mention">@this</span> tragedy :S</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/poland-plane-crash/3726/36">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/poland-plane-crash/3726/36</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 10 Apr 2010 19:34:21 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3726-36</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/poland-plane-crash/3726.rss">POLAND PLANE CRASH!!!!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>POLAND PLANE CRASH!!!!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Shadi]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="acade365">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 acade365:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I feel bad for laughing.  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/frowning.png?v=9" title=":frowning:" class="emoji" alt=":frowning:"></p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/poland-plane-crash/3726/35">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/poland-plane-crash/3726/35</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 10 Apr 2010 19:32:06 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3726-35</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/poland-plane-crash/3726.rss">POLAND PLANE CRASH!!!!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>POLAND PLANE CRASH!!!!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[papernick]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I feel bad for laughing.  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/frowning.png?v=9" title=":frowning:" class="emoji" alt=":frowning:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/poland-plane-crash/3726/34">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/poland-plane-crash/3726/34</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 10 Apr 2010 19:28:56 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3726-34</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/poland-plane-crash/3726.rss">POLAND PLANE CRASH!!!!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>POLAND PLANE CRASH!!!!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Ramirezoid]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><span alt="" class="broken-image" title="This image is broken"><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-unlink svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#unlink"></use></svg></span></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/poland-plane-crash/3726/33">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/poland-plane-crash/3726/33</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 10 Apr 2010 19:24:02 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3726-33</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/poland-plane-crash/3726.rss">POLAND PLANE CRASH!!!!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>POLAND PLANE CRASH!!!!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Shadi]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>not funny =/</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/poland-plane-crash/3726/32">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/poland-plane-crash/3726/32</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 10 Apr 2010 18:45:02 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3726-32</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/poland-plane-crash/3726.rss">POLAND PLANE CRASH!!!!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>POLAND PLANE CRASH!!!!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[X_Mastershot_X]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I already bought the tickets!</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/poland-plane-crash/3726/31">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/poland-plane-crash/3726/31</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 10 Apr 2010 18:24:33 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3726-31</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/poland-plane-crash/3726.rss">POLAND PLANE CRASH!!!!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>POLAND PLANE CRASH!!!!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Jorma_Kay]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Now that the country has fell into total anarchy, can we go loot the place?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/poland-plane-crash/3726/30">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/poland-plane-crash/3726/30</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 10 Apr 2010 18:12:56 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3726-30</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/poland-plane-crash/3726.rss">POLAND PLANE CRASH!!!!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>POLAND PLANE CRASH!!!!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Mr.Shadow]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>wutdidhedothar?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/poland-plane-crash/3726/29">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/poland-plane-crash/3726/29</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 10 Apr 2010 17:46:41 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3726-29</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/poland-plane-crash/3726.rss">POLAND PLANE CRASH!!!!</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
