<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Government to suspend Tuition Assistance for Army</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/government-to-suspend-tuition-assistance-for-army/12182</link>
    <description>[url=&#39;https://www.armytimes.com/news/2013/03/army-army-to-suspend-tuition-assistance-030813&#39;]Because giving Egypt tanks is more important than funding the education of our soldiers.[/url] Fucks.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2013 15:34:42 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Off Topic</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/government-to-suspend-tuition-assistance-for-army/12182.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Government to suspend Tuition Assistance for Army</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Idi]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>the military should unionize</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/government-to-suspend-tuition-assistance-for-army/12182/49">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/government-to-suspend-tuition-assistance-for-army/12182/49</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2013 15:34:42 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12182-49</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/government-to-suspend-tuition-assistance-for-army/12182.rss">Government to suspend Tuition Assistance for Army</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Government to suspend Tuition Assistance for Army</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[bur]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>/thread</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/government-to-suspend-tuition-assistance-for-army/12182/48">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/government-to-suspend-tuition-assistance-for-army/12182/48</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2013 15:18:44 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12182-48</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/government-to-suspend-tuition-assistance-for-army/12182.rss">Government to suspend Tuition Assistance for Army</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Government to suspend Tuition Assistance for Army</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[k3nny1550]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="CPU">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/user_avatar/leakfree.org/cpu/40/4349_2.png" class="avatar"> CPU:</div>
<blockquote>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">[align=center]DON"T JUMP TO CONCLUSIONS:[/align]</span><br>
-Snip-</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>As I said, <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Realpolitik" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">realpolitik.</a></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/government-to-suspend-tuition-assistance-for-army/12182/47">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/government-to-suspend-tuition-assistance-for-army/12182/47</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2013 15:16:36 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12182-47</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/government-to-suspend-tuition-assistance-for-army/12182.rss">Government to suspend Tuition Assistance for Army</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Government to suspend Tuition Assistance for Army</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Idi]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>the us provides israel with 8.5 million dollars of military aid every day</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/government-to-suspend-tuition-assistance-for-army/12182/46">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/government-to-suspend-tuition-assistance-for-army/12182/46</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2013 14:24:06 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12182-46</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/government-to-suspend-tuition-assistance-for-army/12182.rss">Government to suspend Tuition Assistance for Army</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Government to suspend Tuition Assistance for Army</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[CPU]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><span class="bbcode-b">[align=center]DON"T JUMP TO CONCLUSIONS:[/align]</span></p>
<p>STATEMENT:</p>
<p>Lt. Col. Tom Alexander, spokesman for the Army’s personnel chief speaking of the announcement, said “This suspension is necessary given the significant budget execution challenges caused by the combined effects of a possible year-long continuing resolution and sequestration.”<br>
SOURCE: ArmyTimes</p>
<p>WHAT HE REALLY MEANS:</p>
<p>We are suspending, not eliminating, tuition assistance. Why? Because by us doing that it will grab the public’s attention and will lead them to begin calling their congressmen to NOT CUT OUR BUDGET! Rather than simply eliminate other OBVIOUS cuts that actually need to be done we’re announcing this in order to manipulate the people to jump on our side!</p>
<p>FINANCIAL EXAMPLE:</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-u">Not only does the Army not need new tanks, it doesn’t need to upgrade the ones it has for another few years</span>, Gen. Ray Odierno, chief of staff of the Army, told lawmakers during a March 7 hearing of the House Appropriations defense subcommittee. <a href="https://www.defensenews.com/article/20120307/DEFREG02/303070011/U-S-Army-Congress-No-New-Tanks-Please" data-bbcode="true">https://www.defensenews.com/article/20120307/DEFREG02/303070011/U-S-Army-Congress-No-New-Tanks-Please</a><br>
SOURCE: DefenseNews</p>
<p>So, rather than cut this HUGE unnecessary expense we’re going to announce that we’re suspending education expenses which will piss off the general public and lead them to make calls to their representatives thereby protecting our budget. (The tuition expense last year was only $373 million.)</p>
<p>ANOTHER CUT MADE TO PISS YOU OFF::</p>
<p>White House tours have been suspended because of budget concerns:</p>
<p>WHY DO THAT?</p>
<p>So we can piss off the public enough that they will call their congressman in order to end the sequestration.</p>
<p>FINANCIAL EXAMPLE:</p>
<p>The Marine One fleet is the Presidential helicopter fleet. Currently it is composed of 19 helicopters and 24 replacement helicopters are scheduled for replacing them. At $400 million dollars apiece, each new helicopter costs more than the President’s Air Force One Boeing 747. The development contract for replacements has ballooned from an original cost of $6.2 billion to more than $11 billion.</p>
<p>Cutting the White House tours is a yearly savings of less than $4 million and suspending the tuition cost is a yearly savings of just $373 million. That’s equal to less than ONE new Marine One helicopter. Rather than make one less Marine One helicopter they hit the public with the tours announcement because they, like the army, know it will piss the public off.</p>
<p>In each and every case the general public is being manipulated by these announcements simply to piss you off and to convince you to write in forums about it and to jump on their side. It’s not about tours or about tuitions it’s about manipulating you to call your representatives and side with them. Unfortunately, the vast majority of people react to these announcements the same way you did.</p>
<p>Simply put…You reacted to these announcements just the way that they wanted you to. You have been had.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/government-to-suspend-tuition-assistance-for-army/12182/45">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/government-to-suspend-tuition-assistance-for-army/12182/45</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2013 14:15:25 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12182-45</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/government-to-suspend-tuition-assistance-for-army/12182.rss">Government to suspend Tuition Assistance for Army</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Government to suspend Tuition Assistance for Army</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[k3nny1550]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Horse_trading" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Horse trading = political vote trading.</a></p>
<p><a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Pork_barrel" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Pork = sweetening a deal for a political figure by benefiting a state or municipality with special benefits.</a></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/government-to-suspend-tuition-assistance-for-army/12182/44">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/government-to-suspend-tuition-assistance-for-army/12182/44</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 10 Mar 2013 19:09:23 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12182-44</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/government-to-suspend-tuition-assistance-for-army/12182.rss">Government to suspend Tuition Assistance for Army</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Government to suspend Tuition Assistance for Army</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Pyroclase]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="k3nny1550">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/user_avatar/leakfree.org/k3nny1550/40/4952_2.png" class="avatar"> k3nny1550:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Horse trading creates pork, which merely exacerbates the problem.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>What the fuck does that even mean?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/government-to-suspend-tuition-assistance-for-army/12182/43">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/government-to-suspend-tuition-assistance-for-army/12182/43</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 10 Mar 2013 18:13:50 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12182-43</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/government-to-suspend-tuition-assistance-for-army/12182.rss">Government to suspend Tuition Assistance for Army</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Government to suspend Tuition Assistance for Army</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[k3nny1550]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>To be fair, Obama himself was making the sequester’s consequences out to be far worse then they have been so far. But the old guard Republicans like John McCain are just buggering this up by trying to horse-trade. Horse trading creates pork, which merely exacerbates the problem.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/government-to-suspend-tuition-assistance-for-army/12182/42">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/government-to-suspend-tuition-assistance-for-army/12182/42</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 10 Mar 2013 06:57:25 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12182-42</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/government-to-suspend-tuition-assistance-for-army/12182.rss">Government to suspend Tuition Assistance for Army</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Government to suspend Tuition Assistance for Army</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[THRRRPT]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="k3nny1550">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/user_avatar/leakfree.org/k3nny1550/40/4952_2.png" class="avatar"> k3nny1550:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>There are plenty of places to cut spending, it’s just that no one will for fear of antagonizing one or both parties. Let’s have a look!</p>
<ul>
<li>Foreign aid. In some cases this might be justified, but we really should cut or eliminate this aspect of the budget. Particularly in the case of Egypt, because we’re basically giving them millions of dollars to pay for the tanks and aircraft they’re buying from us.</li>
</ul>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Agreed.  You know how much military and financial aid we gave to Israel and Pakistan last year? Around $3 Billion for the one, and 2.5 Billion for the other.  Not a bad haul what with one being an international pariah, and the other actively harboring and abetting OBL.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<ul>
<li>PMC contracts. There are lots of private contractors supplementing our soldiers in the sandbox. Aside from the public’s reservations about the morality of contractors, we’re already spending billions on an inflated military apparatus, and we can’t field our own fucking helicopters?</li>
</ul>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Again, agreed.  Right now we’ve got warehouses and lots full of tanks, vehicles, helicopters, weaponry, that we’re never going to use.  The brass has been calling time and time again to cut the contracts we don’t need, because it’s all going to waste, but Congress isn’t going to do that.  They get too much kickback money from contractors like Lockheed-Martin and General Dynamics.  How’s that $40 Billion sinkhole that is the F35 program working out again?</p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<ul>
<li>Education. The states with the highest funding in schools (such as California, where I live) actually wind up with the lowest grades on average. Perhaps it’s because of awful tenure laws that keep bad teachers in the classroom, and the ridiculous benefits offered to administrators? (My college was trying to get a new administrator, and they were offering some hotshot from LA a friggin 2 story house, paid for by the school, to live in, in addition to exorbitant pay.) Or perhaps it’s because of many schools constantly having to spend every dime they get to get raises in allotted money for the next year?</li>
</ul>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Eh…I think you’re wrong on this one.  More a matter of what the money goes too than cutting the entire education budget.  Teaching has always been an insultingly low-paying job, and in recent years it’s only gotten worse.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<ul>
<li>Welfare (Corporate and citizen). Paying huge bonuses to the captains of sinking ships makes no sense. Nor does letting people sit on unemployment for two years before being cut off.</li>
</ul>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Corporate, yes.  Citizen, probably not.   I don’t want my taxes going towards some bankster’s golden parachute.  Bailouts are a bad idea, ‘Too Big to Fail’ is a damn lie, yadda yadda yadda…  Social aid, though?  Of all the people I’ve worked with in this city, I haven’t found a single one that comes off as lazy, or a wellfare queen, or whatever the libertarian put-down du jour is.  Rather they’re people working three jobs just to keep their heads over the poverty line.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<ul>
<li>Salaries and benefits of Congress. Those fuckers can vote themselves raises, and all of the new legislation introduced in Obamacare doesn’t actually affect their health plans. This should give you a pretty good idea of why they didn’t bother reading the bill before passing it. The people elected to Congress should do so because they wish to serve our nation, not because they want a fat check and special interest funding.</li>
</ul>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Fuck Congress.  Seriously.  You know for years they’ve had a loophole in the law that makes insider trading legal if a Congressman does it?  Right now, it’s corrupt, hopelessly divided, and irrevocably tainted by corporate money.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>More as I think of it, but honestly, we should launch a full audit into every dollar this government spends. That way we can figure out exactly where to cut, and what to cut, and hopefully get rid of some of this waste. Also, the Fed should be disallowed from inflating the currency any farther, until such a time as the government actually formulates a solid plan to pay back it’s $16 trillion debt.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Doubt that would get anywhere with this gridlock.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>But yeah, this should probably make it’s way back to topic soon, otherwise we’ll have to move these posts to a “Forumites Solve the U.S. Deficit” thread.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>On topic…</p>
<p>Well, the Republicans voted for the sequester twice, rejected every compromise that was put on the table, including those they had suggested prior, and now they’re up in arms because the President actually called their bluff?  Fuck 'em.  They’re like five-year-olds whining that their mothers won’t buy them a new toy.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/government-to-suspend-tuition-assistance-for-army/12182/41">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/government-to-suspend-tuition-assistance-for-army/12182/41</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 10 Mar 2013 00:04:11 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12182-41</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/government-to-suspend-tuition-assistance-for-army/12182.rss">Government to suspend Tuition Assistance for Army</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Government to suspend Tuition Assistance for Army</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Pyroclase]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="k3nny1550">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/user_avatar/leakfree.org/k3nny1550/40/4952_2.png" class="avatar"> k3nny1550:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>There are plenty of places to cut spending, it’s just that no one will for fear of antagonizing one or both parties. Let’s have a look!</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I really don’t see why they can’t just make a few less tanks and helicopters. Maybe sell one or two of our carrier battlegroups to Europe; we have, what, ten times the carrier strength of the next largest navy?</p>
<p>I mean, I definitely don’t mind having overwhelming military superiority, but at a certain point you’re just getting silly.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/government-to-suspend-tuition-assistance-for-army/12182/40">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/government-to-suspend-tuition-assistance-for-army/12182/40</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 09 Mar 2013 23:35:03 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12182-40</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/government-to-suspend-tuition-assistance-for-army/12182.rss">Government to suspend Tuition Assistance for Army</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Government to suspend Tuition Assistance for Army</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Bolteh]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="darkone">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/user_avatar/leakfree.org/darkone/40/4296_2.png" class="avatar"> darkone:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>this topic is why people should never talk politics.</p>
<p>also the last reason I had to join the military just went out the window (I can’t pay for collage) looks like I am stuck working in a grocery store.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>You need a lot of money for a collage in the US? Over here we simply cut out pictures from magazines etc. Though I guess you need to buy glue…</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/government-to-suspend-tuition-assistance-for-army/12182/39">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/government-to-suspend-tuition-assistance-for-army/12182/39</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 09 Mar 2013 22:22:40 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12182-39</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/government-to-suspend-tuition-assistance-for-army/12182.rss">Government to suspend Tuition Assistance for Army</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Government to suspend Tuition Assistance for Army</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[darkone]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>this topic is why people should never talk politics.</p>
<p>also the last reason I had to join the military just went out the window (I can’t pay for collage) looks like I am stuck working in a grocery store.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/government-to-suspend-tuition-assistance-for-army/12182/38">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/government-to-suspend-tuition-assistance-for-army/12182/38</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 09 Mar 2013 20:53:15 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12182-38</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/government-to-suspend-tuition-assistance-for-army/12182.rss">Government to suspend Tuition Assistance for Army</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Government to suspend Tuition Assistance for Army</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[k3nny1550]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>There are plenty of places to cut spending, it’s just that no one will for fear of antagonizing one or both parties. Let’s have a look!</p>
<ul>
<li>
<p>Foreign aid. In some cases this might be justified, but we really should cut or eliminate this aspect of the budget. Particularly in the case of Egypt, because we’re basically giving them millions of dollars to pay for the tanks and aircraft they’re buying from us.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>PMC contracts. There are lots of private contractors supplementing our soldiers in the sandbox. Aside from the public’s reservations about the morality of contractors, we’re already spending billions on an inflated military apparatus, and we can’t field our own fucking helicopters?</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Education. The states with the highest funding in schools (such as California, where I live) actually wind up with the lowest grades on average. Perhaps it’s because of awful tenure laws that keep bad teachers in the classroom, and the ridiculous benefits offered to administrators? (My college was trying to get a new administrator, and they were offering some hotshot from LA a friggin 2 story house, paid for by the school, to live in, in addition to exorbitant pay.) Or perhaps it’s because of many schools constantly having to spend every dime they get to get raises in allotted money for the next year? Or how about the constant state of construction on tons of campuses across the state? For example, my high school just finished a remodel of the administrator office, which separates the existing building into two pieces connected by a <span class="bbcode-i">glass tunnel.</span> Aside from the obvious concerns with security should another mass shooting incident occur, what exactly was the point of THAT? Or two gymnasiums, or two gigantic fields, one for track and football, and one for baseball? The middle school RIGHT ACROSS THE STREET has a baseball diamond, couldn’t we just use that? Oh wait, they added solar panels to the parking lot, too. And while I was actually attending, they replaced our two story library building with a one story library building with higher ceilings. Dafaq?</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Welfare (Corporate and citizen). Paying huge bonuses to the captains of sinking ships makes no sense. Nor does letting people sit on unemployment for two years before being cut off.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Salaries and benefits of Congress. Those fuckers can vote themselves raises, and all of the new legislation introduced in Obamacare doesn’t actually affect their health plans. This should give you a pretty good idea of why they didn’t bother reading the bill before passing it. The people elected to Congress should do so because they wish to serve our nation, not because they want a fat check and special interest funding.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<p>More as I think of it, but honestly, we should launch a full audit into every dollar this government spends. That way we can figure out exactly where to cut, and what to cut, and hopefully get rid of some of this waste. Also, the Fed should be disallowed from inflating the currency any farther, until such a time as the government actually formulates a solid plan to pay back it’s $16 trillion debt.</p>
<p>But yeah, this should probably make it’s way back to topic soon, otherwise we’ll have to move these posts to a “Forumites Solve the U.S. Deficit” thread.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/government-to-suspend-tuition-assistance-for-army/12182/37">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/government-to-suspend-tuition-assistance-for-army/12182/37</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 09 Mar 2013 20:42:13 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12182-37</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/government-to-suspend-tuition-assistance-for-army/12182.rss">Government to suspend Tuition Assistance for Army</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Government to suspend Tuition Assistance for Army</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[danielsangeo]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Well, “cutting spending” is always good, right?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/government-to-suspend-tuition-assistance-for-army/12182/36">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/government-to-suspend-tuition-assistance-for-army/12182/36</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 09 Mar 2013 20:15:22 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12182-36</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/government-to-suspend-tuition-assistance-for-army/12182.rss">Government to suspend Tuition Assistance for Army</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Government to suspend Tuition Assistance for Army</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[CatzEyes93]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I work in a government office myself, so being a republican I keep my opinions strongly to myself. But when even the most die hard democrat co-workers start to bitch about the prez and his inept leading skills, you KNOW there is something wrong. The student fee cuts is just a small part you guys are hearing about.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/government-to-suspend-tuition-assistance-for-army/12182/35">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/government-to-suspend-tuition-assistance-for-army/12182/35</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 09 Mar 2013 19:22:58 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12182-35</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/government-to-suspend-tuition-assistance-for-army/12182.rss">Government to suspend Tuition Assistance for Army</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Government to suspend Tuition Assistance for Army</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Idi]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>ok well basically on topic i dont think the state has a special responsibility to take care of its veterans any more. Back in the day it was different because you were conscripted into the military. The draft was essentially slavery and the GI bill was your 40 acres and a mule - the least that could reasonably allow you to rebuild and get your life back on track.</p>
<p>A volunteer army is different though, its basically a mercenary force and the state buys its soldiers labour at whatever price they are willing to sell it for. Shitty and exploitive but that’s capitalism huh. The whole kid rock fighting a dragon with a sword hero narrative is essentially propaganda designed to keep this price as low as possible.</p>
<p>All education should be free for everyone whether you’re some weird looking kid or you’re serving 25 for life for murder or your’e a war criminal A-10 warthog pilot happily firing poisonous depleted uranium rounds all day long and giving babies cancer and enormous heads. (dont google image depleted uranium)</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/government-to-suspend-tuition-assistance-for-army/12182/34">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/government-to-suspend-tuition-assistance-for-army/12182/34</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 09 Mar 2013 04:55:31 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12182-34</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/government-to-suspend-tuition-assistance-for-army/12182.rss">Government to suspend Tuition Assistance for Army</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Government to suspend Tuition Assistance for Army</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[danielsangeo]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>[COLOR=‘Red’]Okay, folks, let’s stay on topic.  Trashing the military and/or servicemembers is not the topic of discussion.  Thanks.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/government-to-suspend-tuition-assistance-for-army/12182/33">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/government-to-suspend-tuition-assistance-for-army/12182/33</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 09 Mar 2013 04:19:07 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12182-33</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/government-to-suspend-tuition-assistance-for-army/12182.rss">Government to suspend Tuition Assistance for Army</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Government to suspend Tuition Assistance for Army</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Idi]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><img src="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/original/2X/2/2f0984456f8dd47c5beb0a68b72c3d6cf62ef2aa.jpeg" alt="" data-base62-sha1="6I6PuuEmauXO02up6hgyYXrei26" width="300" height="300"></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/government-to-suspend-tuition-assistance-for-army/12182/32">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/government-to-suspend-tuition-assistance-for-army/12182/32</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 09 Mar 2013 03:58:28 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12182-32</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/government-to-suspend-tuition-assistance-for-army/12182.rss">Government to suspend Tuition Assistance for Army</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Government to suspend Tuition Assistance for Army</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Chickenprotector]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>“Gibberish” coming from you… yeah… that’s rich. Read it instead of skimming you idgit. I bring up some valid points, if you want the TL;DR version: your people are also serving over there too. <span class="bbcode-i">No</span> self-righteous human being with a heart would kill someone unless it was a last resort. Period. You’re insulting yourself and your own country when you say that. Not just the military.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/government-to-suspend-tuition-assistance-for-army/12182/31">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/government-to-suspend-tuition-assistance-for-army/12182/31</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 09 Mar 2013 03:52:01 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12182-31</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/government-to-suspend-tuition-assistance-for-army/12182.rss">Government to suspend Tuition Assistance for Army</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Government to suspend Tuition Assistance for Army</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Idi]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>thats a cool couple of paragraphs of sorta racist gibberish good job + god bless</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/government-to-suspend-tuition-assistance-for-army/12182/30">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/government-to-suspend-tuition-assistance-for-army/12182/30</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 09 Mar 2013 03:47:40 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12182-30</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/government-to-suspend-tuition-assistance-for-army/12182.rss">Government to suspend Tuition Assistance for Army</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Government to suspend Tuition Assistance for Army</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Chickenprotector]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I don’t know whether to pity your ignorance or call you stupid Idi.</p>
<p>Most of those surveys are skewered half the time and are worthless when it comes to giving concrete facts. I, on the other hand, know plenty of people who have or are serving as we argue over this forum. You don’t have to take my word for it, but Elevenbravo would know what I’m talking about when I say: they’re all are good men and women and I very highly doubt they would’ve willingly killed an innocent if given the chance. If they did, it would haunt them for all eternity, as it would any average person who has a heart, let alone an American. That’s not to say that there isn’t cases of some heartless asshole taking an unwarranted shot at an innocent, but in reality, there’s no way in hell the average Joe/Jane would take the shot unless it didn’t put the Civ at risk.</p>
<p>A majority of the kills you’re listing is because of the Jihadists laying around in the Middle East. They were bad people to begin with, and continue to be. If you want to blame anyone for the inhumane acts, blame them. Watch a show on Discovery/Nat Geo called “Hell’s Highway” and you’ll see what I mean. You’ll witness some of them plant an IDE next to a busy highway, and in some cases I wouldn’t be surprised if they indiscriminately set off the charge with their own country folk near it. There’s also another show who’s name escapes me, but they’re willing to risk life and limb, even though in some cases the regs forbid them to do so, to help some Afghans who’re injured out in the field, whether by US allied forces or not. So when you say the US Military’s full of thugs, you’re not just insulting yourself by making yourself look stupid. You’re insulting the good men and women of this proud country and likely your own kin who’re fighting the same war over seas.</p>
<p>I think my government’s run by idiots (this is just a prime case), but I despise ignorance more than moronism.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/government-to-suspend-tuition-assistance-for-army/12182/29">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/government-to-suspend-tuition-assistance-for-army/12182/29</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 09 Mar 2013 03:40:48 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12182-29</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/government-to-suspend-tuition-assistance-for-army/12182.rss">Government to suspend Tuition Assistance for Army</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Government to suspend Tuition Assistance for Army</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Idi]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>when you stop delivering it on people you dont know  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=9" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/government-to-suspend-tuition-assistance-for-army/12182/28">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/government-to-suspend-tuition-assistance-for-army/12182/28</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 09 Mar 2013 02:35:40 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12182-28</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/government-to-suspend-tuition-assistance-for-army/12182.rss">Government to suspend Tuition Assistance for Army</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Government to suspend Tuition Assistance for Army</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[elevenbravo]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Always found it funny that the only people that claim that soldiers commit all these inhumane acts are the ones that have never even been in the same country.</p>
<p>The only civilian deaths that my WHOLE unit experienced was by the insurgents because a family accepted water and food from us.</p>
<p>I have no need to continue I mean, this is basically going to resort to " we’ll see this article from <a href="http://fightheman.com" rel="nofollow noopener">fightheman.com</a> says blabla.</p>
<p>So continue to wish death upon people you don’t know and all that idi.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/government-to-suspend-tuition-assistance-for-army/12182/27">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/government-to-suspend-tuition-assistance-for-army/12182/27</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 09 Mar 2013 02:27:54 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12182-27</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/government-to-suspend-tuition-assistance-for-army/12182.rss">Government to suspend Tuition Assistance for Army</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Government to suspend Tuition Assistance for Army</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Idi]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>the wiki leaks numbers came from the us military which makes them hardly impartial so not very trustworthy imo but they did include 15,000 deaths that the third party organisations diddnt know about before.<br>
drop weapons are used and there have been plenty or reports indicating its pretty widespread.<br>
Even deaths from car bombs and shit are directly because of the leadership who went in half cocked into a place they knew shit all about and lit off a powder keg. The soldiers on the ground are not directly responsible for that but every time you follow an order you are complicit in it and every kill is a murder and when you die or your friends die its not a brave heroic sacrifice for freedom its pointless and stupid.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/government-to-suspend-tuition-assistance-for-army/12182/26">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/government-to-suspend-tuition-assistance-for-army/12182/26</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 09 Mar 2013 02:24:19 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12182-26</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/government-to-suspend-tuition-assistance-for-army/12182.rss">Government to suspend Tuition Assistance for Army</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Government to suspend Tuition Assistance for Army</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Surplus]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="JeffMOD">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/user_avatar/leakfree.org/jeffmod/40/4333_2.png" class="avatar"> JeffMOD:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>If it’s the conflicts you’re pissed about, Idi, blame the governments responsible, not their soldiers.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Yes, do not blame the people who of their own free will sign up to support something. Only blame the system not the names and faces behind the system.  If the United States military is committing inhumane and unjust acts the soldiers are every bit as responsible as the suit and tie men giving the go ahead.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/government-to-suspend-tuition-assistance-for-army/12182/25">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/government-to-suspend-tuition-assistance-for-army/12182/25</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 09 Mar 2013 02:14:53 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12182-25</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/government-to-suspend-tuition-assistance-for-army/12182.rss">Government to suspend Tuition Assistance for Army</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
