<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>My opinion about the MP weapon balance</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/my-opinion-about-the-mp-weapon-balance/14252</link>
    <description>Hello,
i want to write my opinions about the weapons in Multiplayer, and my opinions what needs to be fixed.

[u]Gauss[/u]
Well since the fix the weapon is too easy too handle. Thats of 2 reasons:
1: Aiming is too easy: I am with my crosshair beside the player but hit him full. I know this was fixed but now it seems to easy.
2: Charging: The time until the Gauss is full charged is too short. I can kill easy people with just a milisecond charged gauss.

[u]Shotgun[/u]
I think the secondary shot of the shotgun makes too many damage. I get easily killed by people with one shot and i have some armor. This need some fixes by damage reduction and maybe add more spread to the bullets.


[u]MP5[/u]
The MP5 seems very balanced for me.

[u]9mm Pistol[/u]
Well sometimes i get easily killed by the secondary shots of the Pistol. The fire rate in HL1 seems slower, i would like to the a slower rate too in BM :smiley: M.

[u]Grenades[/u]
Well i learned to hate these little fuckers. I can understand why new spawned People have them: To defend themself easiler, but on a full MP server you get soo easy killed by a grenade. I think they make too much damage.


[u]Revolver[/u]
I like the Revolver. It makes good damage if you have aim.

I hope some dev reads this and we can talk about it  :slight_smile:</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 03 Jul 2015 20:37:44 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>The Cafeteria</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/my-opinion-about-the-mp-weapon-balance/14252.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>My opinion about the MP weapon balance</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[fury]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>some more suggestions:</p>
<ul>
<li>change RPG and Crossbow (zoomed and unzoomed) so you can shoot them under water</li>
<li>increase RPG reload time slightly</li>
<li>decrease shotgun-reload time slightly</li>
<li>make shotgun secondary fire animation more spectacular (atm there is a very long break between the actual shot and the pump)</li>
<li>nerf hornetgun damage slightly or increase it’s reload time because sometimes it seems extremely powerful</li>
<li>remove or drastically decrease the amount of flinch when getting hit… imo you should only flinch while zoomed in with crossbow or 357</li>
<li>when you are up in the air and get shot by shotgun, it kicks you far up in the air (huge amount of knockback)… Knockback was a lot less in HLDM and I think it should be adapted in BMDM</li>
<li>sometimes when I move around I hear somebody shooting egon even though nobody seems to be near (sometimes i thought it was played global… but I think that’s not true… it must be some kind of bug with the 3D sound)… Same for the sound that gets played when somebody has armor and takes damage…</li>
<li>when you pick up longjump module you hear this “piishhhhhhtttt”-sound. Can you change the official sound and replace it with a remake of the old suit voice sound? (“power assist movement activated”)</li>
</ul>
<p>Edit: - maybe remove tinitus-effect when getting hit by explosives (I think it’s cool for singleplayer, but rather bad to have this in multiplayer aswell)</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/my-opinion-about-the-mp-weapon-balance/14252/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/my-opinion-about-the-mp-weapon-balance/14252/7</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jul 2015 20:37:44 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14252-7</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/my-opinion-about-the-mp-weapon-balance/14252.rss">My opinion about the MP weapon balance</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My opinion about the MP weapon balance</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[fury]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>another suggestion: can you please remove suit-zoom in multiplayer?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/my-opinion-about-the-mp-weapon-balance/14252/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/my-opinion-about-the-mp-weapon-balance/14252/6</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 27 Jun 2015 16:45:25 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14252-6</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/my-opinion-about-the-mp-weapon-balance/14252.rss">My opinion about the MP weapon balance</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My opinion about the MP weapon balance</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[fury]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Also make gauss carriers with charged gauss more hearable… in hl1 you can spot them so nice from far distance… atm on bounce it happens really often that i get sniped silently by gaussers… remove tracer from zoomed crossbow and review it’s netcode to make it a useful sniper. faster weaponswitch (shorter drawanimations) will make crossbow and shotgun more useful, too.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/my-opinion-about-the-mp-weapon-balance/14252/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/my-opinion-about-the-mp-weapon-balance/14252/5</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 26 Jun 2015 15:45:01 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14252-5</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/my-opinion-about-the-mp-weapon-balance/14252.rss">My opinion about the MP weapon balance</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My opinion about the MP weapon balance</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[fury]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Please nerf the 357 to 35 or 40 damage. Originally it was meant to be a low tier weapon, that was barely better than the normal pistol. In current bm it’s better than smg, shotgun and crossbow… That shouldn’t be the case. I understand it was stronger in HL2DM, but in HL2DM there was no gauss and the crossbow worked totally different… So that’s why I think it filled the role of HL1’s gauss and crossbow in HL2DM… but in BM it should be  more weak. Since hitreg and precision is very good for magnum, I think 35 or 40 damage (+ headshot chance --&gt; 3 body shots or 1 headshot) is good enaugh. I think you should first balance the low and mid tier weapons before you nerf the high tier weapons (if you might nerf them at all)</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/my-opinion-about-the-mp-weapon-balance/14252/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/my-opinion-about-the-mp-weapon-balance/14252/4</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 26 Jun 2015 15:03:43 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14252-4</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/my-opinion-about-the-mp-weapon-balance/14252.rss">My opinion about the MP weapon balance</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My opinion about the MP weapon balance</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[eriksonis6]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>All changes that were made in recent patch are steps in right direction. But few things still needs to be fixed.</p>
<p>Crossbows zoomed reg still seems bad and overall that tracer effect feels broken (my opinion)</p>
<p>Mp5 shouldn’t have recoil like that.</p>
<p>Grenades are much more powerful than in original HLDM. They are really hard to spot so you can often die without even noticing grenade, that’t the problem is you play ffa on pub server, in regular clanwars it shouldn’t be a problem.</p>
<p>Gauss seems really powerful now, don’t know if its too strong or not - time will tell. I think we should leave it as it is for now.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/my-opinion-about-the-mp-weapon-balance/14252/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/my-opinion-about-the-mp-weapon-balance/14252/3</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 26 Jun 2015 12:18:18 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14252-3</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/my-opinion-about-the-mp-weapon-balance/14252.rss">My opinion about the MP weapon balance</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My opinion about the MP weapon balance</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[fury]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Dmx6">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/d/c37758/40.png" class="avatar"> Dmx6:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Hello,<br>
i want to write my opinions about the weapons in Multiplayer, and my opinions what needs to be fixed.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-u">Gauss</span><br>
Well since the fix the weapon is too easy too handle. Thats of 2 reasons:<br>
1: Aiming is too easy: I am with my crosshair beside the player but hit him full. I know this was fixed but now it seems to easy.<br>
2: Charging: The time until the Gauss is full charged is too short. I can kill easy people with just a milisecond charged gauss.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I don’t understand why people think hitting is too easy…  Maybe I have bad aim  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/smiley.png?v=9" title=":smiley:" class="emoji" alt=":smiley:">  but I think it’s fine… If you think about it: It’s a beam, it should have some radius… also in real life you get wounded even if you don’t get fully hit but also when a bullet passes by very very closely (you get hurt by the blast wave)… I think the new hitreg is wonderful, but gauss deals slightly too much damage after very short chargetimes --&gt; just try to remake it as close to HL1 as possible</p>
<p>Edit:<br>
You should make the beam-effect slightly thinner, fix the particle effect on the frontside of the barrel and play the beam effect in shorter time to make it look more powerful and less glowy.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Dmx6">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/d/c37758/40.png" class="avatar"> Dmx6:</div>
<blockquote>
<p><span class="bbcode-u">Shotgun</span><br>
I think the secondary shot of the shotgun makes too many damage. I get easily killed by people with one shot and i have some armor. This need some fixes by damage reduction and maybe add more spread to the bullets.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Shotgun damage seems alright to me. I just think that it’s feels very random to hit the enemies head. But yea… Sometimes I think primary fire could deal slightly less damage but be more precise (primary fire should be good for headshotting, secondary fire should be good for closer ranges bursts to the chest / head --&gt; insta-kill).</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Dmx6">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/d/c37758/40.png" class="avatar"> Dmx6:</div>
<blockquote>
<p><span class="bbcode-u">MP5</span><br>
The MP5 seems very balanced for me.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-u">9mm Pistol</span><br>
Well sometimes i get easily killed by the secondary shots of the Pistol. The fire rate in HL1 seems slower, i would like to the a slower rate too in BM <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/smiley.png?v=9" title=":smiley:" class="emoji" alt=":smiley:"> M.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Pistol and MP5 deal more damage than in HL1… I think you should remove recoil from the MP5 and change damagevalues back to how they were in HL1. In HL1 you had only screenshake and spray on the MP5, you did not need to compensate recoil and I think it was very good. Right now it seems to be a lot of luck involved in hitting headshots… In my opinion it’s because of the recoil (if you shoot, the recoil pulls up your view) and because you have so many different playeranimations. In HL1 playermodels moved around in a more upright stance and it was easier to aim and track the enemies head. I also never seem to hit any headshots with shotgun (maybe I just can’t see it)… So yea… In my opinion headshots feel more random in BM and more skilled / more consistent in HL1…</p>
<p>Edit: I think the recoil is cool for singleplayer, but I’d rather liked it to get removed from multiplayer.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Dmx6">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/d/c37758/40.png" class="avatar"> Dmx6:</div>
<blockquote>
<p><span class="bbcode-u">Grenades</span><br>
Well i learned to hate these little fuckers. I can understand why new spawned People have them: To defend themself easiler, but on a full MP server you get soo easy killed by a grenade. I think they make too much damage.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Damage seems ok to me… maybe just nerf it very very slightly… But I think they should NOT be a spawn-weapon. There are enaugh weapons (and handgrenades/satchels/tripmines) on all maps so really these aren’t needed as a spawnweapon. Also when you throw handgrenades, they seem to have a strange spawn-origin and don’t spawn close to your crosshair (same for crossbow-bolts and MP5-grenades…) In my opinion all these “projectiles” should all spawn right on your crosshair (except RPG rockets) and fly their arch (if they have any) from there…</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Dmx6">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/d/c37758/40.png" class="avatar"> Dmx6:</div>
<blockquote>
<p><span class="bbcode-u">Revolver</span><br>
I like the Revolver. It makes good damage if you have aim.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I think it’s too strong… Normally it should be just a low-tier weapon. Now it’s very strong just like a high tier weapon, which should not be the case imo. This is not HL2DM. There are enaugh very strong hitscan weapons in BMDM (shotgun, crossbow, tau-cannon)</p>
<p>About the weaponswitch:<br>
When I play shotgun and bow combo in HL1 it’s way more powerful, because you can shoot / zoom in earlier right after a weaponswitch… Like I said… In HL1 you don’t need to watch the whole drawanimation till the end… you can skip it by using primary or secondary attack after a certain weapon-switch delay… from what I know all weapons in HL1 have the same switch time… Not sure but I hope it’s on your “to fix”-list… I mean… In BMDM combo-shots like these for example arent possible:</p>
<p><a href="https://youtu.be/P_4nP3DVAWo?t=22s" rel="nofollow noopener">youtu.be/P_4nP3DVAWo?t=22s</a></p>
<p>examples in the video: 00:22 , 02:05 , 02:15</p>
<p>(shots very very short time after weaponswitch)</p>
<p>About crossbow:<br>
I think hitreg sure is better than before, but I’d recommend to use the same shoot-sound for zoomed and unzoomed shots (primary fire sound is a lot better and more faithful than current sound for zoomed shots)… Also the shootingline-effect is distracting and also a big nerf for the crossbow… In HL1 the crossbow used to be a stealth weapon (In HL1 you weren’t able to spot the direction from where you get shot from if your enemy was far away uses the crossbow… also there was no tracer-effect and you didn’t lose your position immediately…)</p>
<p>About RPG reload:<br>
For this update you implemented HL1-style RPG-reload mechanics I explained in the other thread. It still can be improved a bit more: In the current version you still have to wait until your shoot-animation is completely done before you can reload your RPG --&gt; Most of the time it doesn’t make any difference if you wait or if you use the “no laserdot fast-reload” trick. --&gt; After you shot, you should be able to cancel the shoot animation by pressing reload…</p>
<p>Edit: Also don’t forget to make rocket and ARgrenades speed slightly slower (more dodgeable) and increase ammolimit for ARgrenades to 5.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/my-opinion-about-the-mp-weapon-balance/14252/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/my-opinion-about-the-mp-weapon-balance/14252/2</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jun 2015 21:06:03 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14252-2</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/my-opinion-about-the-mp-weapon-balance/14252.rss">My opinion about the MP weapon balance</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My opinion about the MP weapon balance</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Dmx6]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Hello,<br>
i want to write my opinions about the weapons in Multiplayer, and my opinions what needs to be fixed.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-u">Gauss</span><br>
Well since the fix the weapon is too easy too handle. Thats of 2 reasons:<br>
1: Aiming is too easy: I am with my crosshair beside the player but hit him full. I know this was fixed but now it seems to easy.<br>
2: Charging: The time until the Gauss is full charged is too short. I can kill easy people with just a milisecond charged gauss.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-u">Shotgun</span><br>
I think the secondary shot of the shotgun makes too many damage. I get easily killed by people with one shot and i have some armor. This need some fixes by damage reduction and maybe add more spread to the bullets.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-u">MP5</span><br>
The MP5 seems very balanced for me.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-u">9mm Pistol</span><br>
Well sometimes i get easily killed by the secondary shots of the Pistol. The fire rate in HL1 seems slower, i would like to the a slower rate too in BM <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/smiley.png?v=9" title=":smiley:" class="emoji" alt=":smiley:"> M.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-u">Grenades</span><br>
Well i learned to hate these little fuckers. I can understand why new spawned People have them: To defend themself easiler, but on a full MP server you get soo easy killed by a grenade. I think they make too much damage.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-u">Revolver</span><br>
I like the Revolver. It makes good damage if you have aim.</p>
<p>I hope some dev reads this and we can talk about it  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=9" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/my-opinion-about-the-mp-weapon-balance/14252/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/my-opinion-about-the-mp-weapon-balance/14252/1</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jun 2015 19:08:30 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14252-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/my-opinion-about-the-mp-weapon-balance/14252.rss">My opinion about the MP weapon balance</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
