<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Embryonic stem cell research</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/embryonic-stem-cell-research/2146</link>
    <description>I&#39;m continuing a converation here so that the mininova thread doesn&#39;t get derailed any more than it is.
[quote=&quot;JohnKiller118&quot;]
(piracy) Never has an argument had such a simple and easily discoverable conclusion! Even the anti-religion argument in the &quot;French Court Convicts Scientology&quot; thread was more complicated! (Apparently, making you feel &quot;warm and fuzzy inside&quot; justifies genocide, homophobia, and stopping scientific advancements because it&#39;s &quot;immoral!&quot; (ie stem cell research), as well as indoctrinating children into cults.)
[/quote]

[quote=&quot;Cup o Joe&quot;]
Adult stem cell research has done a lot and I agree with it because it&#39;s natural and very useful (and someone has cloned her own lung to heal herself from cancer using her own stem cells). it&#39;s embryonic that has done nothing because as it kills the human embryo in the process, if you think murder of a human zygote is justifiable for scientific means then you&#39;re discriminatory against the age of that human. What if one of those frozen zygotes could have been someone who would change the world for the better like an other Tesla, or an other Edison or a Thomas Aquinas? We&#39;ll never know because some of those kinds of people might be created under IVF and are under the microscope not allowed to grow as a result of this so called &quot;scientific research&quot; called &quot;embryonic stem cell research&quot; which is essentially selective breeding.

Adult Stem cell research on the other hand is the best, it&#39;s natural and has done very well. I mean with the proper nutrition given to the stem cells which are produced in the small intestine people can clone their own organs in a lab, it doesn&#39;t get much better than that. Adult stem cells can turn into any one of the 200 types of cells your body needs.
[/quote]

[quote=&quot;loony636&quot;]
Stem cell research has nothing to do with the killing of human zygotes that were destined for anything else other than the trashcan. 

Adult stem cells may be adequate for some purposes, but I think its a bit naive to say that one is a complete replacement for the other; depriving scientists the opportunity to fully explore the field means that any potential gains are automatically lost, and your theory becomes self-serving (since embryonic stem cells never get to do anything because nobody is allowed to research them, whereas adult stem cells are developed far beyond what embryonic stem cells can achieve).
[/quote]

[QUOTE=Cup o Joe]
&quot;embryonic stem cell research&quot; and IVF is selective breeding.
[/QUOTE]
Every human zygote that is produced are human lives, it&#39;s a very basic universal and scientific truth.
Think about this in IVF about 20 eggs are fertilized, that means 20 human beings are given life and at the exact moment of conception they are starting to grow. Doctors decide out of those twenty who is &quot;fit to live&quot;. you know what that is? it&#39;s eugenics. 

Prenatal eugenics is going and deciding who is fit to live before a human being has a chance to even think for himself or herself. Embryonic stem cell research is intrinsically anti life, IVF the way it is done right now is immoral but if the method is changed it can become moral and always productive if it is done like this: Only one egg should be fertilized at a time and without cutting through the membrane. Think about this, doctors cut the egg open to make it easier for the one sperm to get through. That&#39;s not the way it&#39;s supposed to be, the sperm are supposed to be allowed to do their part. For the sperm it&#39;s supposed to be the survival of the fittest to get through to the egg. If it&#39;s not survival of the fittest for the sperm, the person can be born with many disabilities because of a damaged sperm that got through to the egg to create him or her. The only way that IVF will be universally accepted is if it&#39;s one egg that is fertilized at a time without cutting it open; the sperm MUST be allowed to do their part in the creative process that is life.

Now for Embryonic stem cell research. The egg is fertilized specifically to be destroyed by doctors to collect cells that everyone produces in their own bodies everyday. There is no reason to kill a new human life. Stem cells can and do turn into any cell that the body needs. It can also be instructed to change into Neurons. It&#39;s only a matter of time before doctors find a way to tweak an adult stem cell that is produced in the small intestine to instruct them to turn into which ever cell the body needs. If a woman can clone her own lung using a few stem cells and a piece of her clean lung, it&#39;s only a matter if time before they can figure out a way to instruct the stem cells to reattach the spinal cord. There&#39;s no need to kill humans for stem cells. They can be found in the umbilical cord of every new born child, they are produced in the small intestines from the 6th week of pregnancy until death and it flows in the blood to change into which ever cell the body needs.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 06 Jan 2010 19:15:53 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Off Topic</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/embryonic-stem-cell-research/2146.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Embryonic stem cell research</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Madcat1030]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>It’s really okay, really!  The rest of the world has gotten so far ahead with Embryonic Stem Cell research, that as soon as certain groups get off their high-horses, we’ll be up to speed with nary a missed step.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/embryonic-stem-cell-research/2146/325">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/embryonic-stem-cell-research/2146/325</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 06 Jan 2010 19:15:53 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2146-325</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/embryonic-stem-cell-research/2146.rss">Embryonic stem cell research</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Embryonic stem cell research</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[mattemuse]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>No idea about the cost/quality etc, that too can be found by googling. <span class="bbcode-i">I’m</span> not arguing against the use of embryonic stem cells if necessary. But alternatives are obviously a good thing, considering the controversy.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/embryonic-stem-cell-research/2146/324">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/embryonic-stem-cell-research/2146/324</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 04 Jan 2010 23:36:10 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2146-324</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/embryonic-stem-cell-research/2146.rss">Embryonic stem cell research</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Embryonic stem cell research</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Soup]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="mattemuse">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/m/dc4da7/40.png" class="avatar"> mattemuse:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Soup, you can stop asking for “source” any time now. Google ‘induced pluripotency.’ It’s a fact.<br>
Would this discovery have been possible without embryonic stem cell research? Doubtful.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Fair enough, but, in relation to embryonic research: what are the costs, what’s the success rate and what’s the quality of the resultant cells?</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="mattemuse">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/m/dc4da7/40.png" class="avatar"> mattemuse:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Religion is an inherent aspect of human nature. It isn’t going anywhere. And a good thing too, considering the massive amount of charity/aid distributed to the world’s poorest populations through religious organizations. But thats a discussion more suited for the Eucharistic Shenanigans thread.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>See my answer in the Eucharistic Shenanigans thread.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/embryonic-stem-cell-research/2146/323">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/embryonic-stem-cell-research/2146/323</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 04 Jan 2010 23:34:32 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2146-323</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/embryonic-stem-cell-research/2146.rss">Embryonic stem cell research</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Embryonic stem cell research</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[mattemuse]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Soup, you can stop asking for “source” any time now. Google ‘induced pluripotency.’ It’s a fact.<br>
Would this discovery have been possible without embryonic stem cell research? Doubtful.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="intooblivion">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/i/8491ac/40.png" class="avatar"> intooblivion:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Religion doesn’t really have a place in human culture anymore whatsoever.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Religion is an inherent aspect of human nature. It isn’t going anywhere. And a good thing too, considering the massive amount of charity/aid distributed to the world’s poorest populations through religious organizations. But thats a discussion more suited for the Eucharistic Shenanigans thread.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/embryonic-stem-cell-research/2146/322">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/embryonic-stem-cell-research/2146/322</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 04 Jan 2010 22:16:01 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2146-322</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/embryonic-stem-cell-research/2146.rss">Embryonic stem cell research</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Embryonic stem cell research</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Acristoff]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="intooblivion">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/i/8491ac/40.png" class="avatar"> intooblivion:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Umbilical cords also have stem cells in them as well, and since that’s also classified under embryonic stem cell research everybody’s against that too.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Some of you seem to think that if it’s called a stem cell it’s like any other stem cell, if you can get stem cells from another source it’s probably not as free in whatever those cells can become.</p>
<p>Let me put it into simple terms for you:</p>
<p>Embryonic stem cells - Good</p>
<p>Umbilical cord stem cells (forgot the actual term) - Okay</p>
<p>Artificial stem cells - bad</p>
<p>All in terms of quality of course.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/embryonic-stem-cell-research/2146/321">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/embryonic-stem-cell-research/2146/321</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 04 Jan 2010 21:48:41 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2146-321</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/embryonic-stem-cell-research/2146.rss">Embryonic stem cell research</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Embryonic stem cell research</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[intooblivion]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Cup o Joe">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Cup o Joe:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Doctors decide out of those twenty who is “fit to live”.</p>
<p>“it’s supposed to be the survival of the fittest”</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Well I’m glad that you agree with yourself.</p>
<p>Anyway doctors shouldn’t be allowed to make any advances in science, because morals are what make humans the superior species.</p>
<p>Oh wait.</p>
<p>First off there’s way too many people on the earth to begin with, so if some good can come out of what would eventually be another foster kid (if they’re lucky) that can’t get a decent education because money is split across so many people already then that is the most wonderful thing that scientists could do.</p>
<p>Umbilical cords also have stem cells in them as well, and since that’s also classified under embryonic stem cell research everybody’s against that too.</p>
<p>There will probably never be another Einstein or Bell or other great inventors, because people nowadays are becoming stupider thanks to apathy, and human kind has basically resorted to trying to make existing inventions somewhat better or different. Not to mention trying to get our failed inventions to work even though they never will work, IE religion or only will with humongous changes, IE government and social systems.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>does (religion) really have a place out in the real world and actual issues?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Religion doesn’t really have a place in human culture anymore whatsoever. But there it stays.</p>
<p><em>shrugs</em></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/embryonic-stem-cell-research/2146/320">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/embryonic-stem-cell-research/2146/320</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 04 Jan 2010 21:37:11 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2146-320</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/embryonic-stem-cell-research/2146.rss">Embryonic stem cell research</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Embryonic stem cell research</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Soup]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Bramblepath">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Bramblepath:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I had to sit through a whole lecture on this shit. D:</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>…</p>
<p>Source?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/embryonic-stem-cell-research/2146/319">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/embryonic-stem-cell-research/2146/319</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 04 Jan 2010 20:59:19 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2146-319</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/embryonic-stem-cell-research/2146.rss">Embryonic stem cell research</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Embryonic stem cell research</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Acristoff]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Then you probably didn’t pay too much attention.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/embryonic-stem-cell-research/2146/318">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/embryonic-stem-cell-research/2146/318</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 04 Jan 2010 19:57:26 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2146-318</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/embryonic-stem-cell-research/2146.rss">Embryonic stem cell research</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Embryonic stem cell research</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Acristoff]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Bramblepath">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Bramblepath:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Researchers can now in-fact produce stem cells from almost any cell and make it pluripotent, meaning that there’s no need to use embryonic stem cells  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=9" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"></p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>That’s true but those have a higher rate of failure, and are generally worse.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/embryonic-stem-cell-research/2146/317">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/embryonic-stem-cell-research/2146/317</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 04 Jan 2010 18:45:16 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2146-317</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/embryonic-stem-cell-research/2146.rss">Embryonic stem cell research</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Embryonic stem cell research</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Soup]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Source?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/embryonic-stem-cell-research/2146/316">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/embryonic-stem-cell-research/2146/316</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 04 Jan 2010 16:50:45 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2146-316</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/embryonic-stem-cell-research/2146.rss">Embryonic stem cell research</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Embryonic stem cell research</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[DansonDelta40]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>As much as any fanfiction does.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/embryonic-stem-cell-research/2146/315">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/embryonic-stem-cell-research/2146/315</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 04 Jan 2010 11:35:57 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2146-315</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/embryonic-stem-cell-research/2146.rss">Embryonic stem cell research</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Embryonic stem cell research</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Acristoff]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Why is the bible even in this topic, I realize religion is a thing that is close to many people but does it really have a place out in the real world and actual issues?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/embryonic-stem-cell-research/2146/314">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/embryonic-stem-cell-research/2146/314</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 04 Jan 2010 04:42:41 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2146-314</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/embryonic-stem-cell-research/2146.rss">Embryonic stem cell research</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Embryonic stem cell research</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[geekofalltrades]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Seems to me that “knit together” implies raw materials, like… undifferentiated stem cells?  Which, per the passage, are not themselves human if they are being used as raw materials.  Otherwise the passage would read, “you miraculously and improbably poofed me into existence in my mother’s womb.”</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/embryonic-stem-cell-research/2146/313">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/embryonic-stem-cell-research/2146/313</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 03 Jan 2010 07:52:42 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2146-313</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/embryonic-stem-cell-research/2146.rss">Embryonic stem cell research</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Embryonic stem cell research</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[bur]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Only if the knitter is wearing its mother.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/embryonic-stem-cell-research/2146/312">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/embryonic-stem-cell-research/2146/312</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 02 Jan 2010 05:32:54 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2146-312</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/embryonic-stem-cell-research/2146.rss">Embryonic stem cell research</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Embryonic stem cell research</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[mattemuse]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><span class="bbcode-b">Psalm 139:13<br>
For you created my inmost being; you knit me together in my mother’s womb.<br>
</span></p>
<p>I take this to mean that at the moment a needle touches a piece of thread, it is this exact moment in which a sweater is Created.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/embryonic-stem-cell-research/2146/311">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/embryonic-stem-cell-research/2146/311</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 02 Jan 2010 03:54:48 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2146-311</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/embryonic-stem-cell-research/2146.rss">Embryonic stem cell research</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Embryonic stem cell research</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[CatzEyes93]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>And this one too…</p>
<p>btw, yes it IS in the bible.  Here is one of many.<br>
Psalm 139:13<br>
For you created my inmost being; you knit me together in my mother’s womb.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/embryonic-stem-cell-research/2146/310">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/embryonic-stem-cell-research/2146/310</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Dec 2009 19:46:39 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2146-310</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/embryonic-stem-cell-research/2146.rss">Embryonic stem cell research</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Embryonic stem cell research</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Brother_Shrike]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="JohnKiller118">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 JohnKiller118:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Where in the Bible does it say that anyway?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>It doesn’t. :meh: [color=’<span class="hashtag">#212121</span>’]i hope that wasn’t a rhetorical question…</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/embryonic-stem-cell-research/2146/309">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/embryonic-stem-cell-research/2146/309</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Dec 2009 19:37:50 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2146-309</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/embryonic-stem-cell-research/2146.rss">Embryonic stem cell research</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Embryonic stem cell research</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[garrthbarrttinn]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="JamestheDoc">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/j/5daacb/40.png" class="avatar"> JamestheDoc:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>People wonder why we can’t cure cancer, people ask why so many have to suffer with Parkinson’s Disease, diabetes, breast cancer, and autism.  They do because people are so quick to take “Embryo,” as a word, and being completely ignorant of the biology and technicality of the term’s use, make embryonic stem cells out to be a life wasted.  When these cells are just a lump of nothing.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>We already have the cure for cancer; organic food. You see, pharmacuetical companies don’t make money off organic food, so they pay farmers to poison their food so it’s unhealthy for us and gives us asthma, diabetes, cancer, atheism, and many more chronic diseases. My friend was Asian and doctors suggested an intense regiment of chemo for 3 years, instead he started the Gerson’s cure and 5 months later he was cured!!!</p>
<p>(for anybody who hasn’t stumbled upon cup o joe’s ignorance yet this post is imitating him)[/SIZE]</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/embryonic-stem-cell-research/2146/308">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/embryonic-stem-cell-research/2146/308</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Dec 2009 17:18:12 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2146-308</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/embryonic-stem-cell-research/2146.rss">Embryonic stem cell research</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Embryonic stem cell research</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[JohnKiller118]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Where in the Bible does it say that anyway?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/embryonic-stem-cell-research/2146/307">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/embryonic-stem-cell-research/2146/307</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Dec 2009 14:45:46 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2146-307</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/embryonic-stem-cell-research/2146.rss">Embryonic stem cell research</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Embryonic stem cell research</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[bur]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>inb4 Cup o Joe saying “a human life is started at conception, this is a universal truth and cannot be denied.”</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/embryonic-stem-cell-research/2146/306">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/embryonic-stem-cell-research/2146/306</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Dec 2009 14:23:59 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2146-306</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/embryonic-stem-cell-research/2146.rss">Embryonic stem cell research</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Embryonic stem cell research</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[JohnKiller118]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Wait, I thought there was no God?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/embryonic-stem-cell-research/2146/305">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/embryonic-stem-cell-research/2146/305</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Dec 2009 14:09:41 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2146-305</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/embryonic-stem-cell-research/2146.rss">Embryonic stem cell research</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Embryonic stem cell research</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[nietzschesaurus]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>/thread. please for the love of fucking GOD /THREAD.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/embryonic-stem-cell-research/2146/304">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/embryonic-stem-cell-research/2146/304</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Dec 2009 12:02:19 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2146-304</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/embryonic-stem-cell-research/2146.rss">Embryonic stem cell research</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Embryonic stem cell research</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[JamestheDoc]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I was lurking, curiosity got the better of me, and my career path/education made it too tempting not to post.</p>
<p>Embryonic stem cells come from an embryo that’s between 50 and 200 cells large.  It’s a tiny, tiny dot of little cells that COULD give rise to a human life if they were to begin dividing and building specific cellular systems based on encoded genetic data, but they are harvested before they can.</p>
<p><a href="https://stemcells.nih.gov/info/basics/basics3.asp" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://stemcells.nih.gov/info/basics/basics3.asp</a></p>
<p>(This is from the National Institute of Health, a government organization of the United States that researches and experiments with medicine and human health sciences, as well as directing public health facilities and groups in the treatment of persons both here in the states and abroad.   They also back their data with research and information already culminated from both American and International research.  In short, it’s not Wikipedia.)</p>
<p>It’s not a human life, it’s a microscopic handful of cells that, when they work together, can create human life.  You might as well imprison yourself for the murder of trillions of billions of innocent sperm cells, or the loss of hundreds of thousands of unfertilized ovum.  They have the ability to create human life as much as embryonic stem cells.  It’s just a matter of having them triggered properly to do so.</p>
<p>Stem cells do not correlate into a living organism, they’re just a mesh of unspecified cells that can rapidly replicate and grow into bigger cellular forms when they’re engaged by natural triggers within their genetic code.  They have the POTENTIAL to form life, but they in themselves ARE NOT life.</p>
<p>Stem cells are so important to medicine because of how they act, they can  mimic cells to develop tissues and systems on their own.  So, if applied correctly, a woman suffering from debilitating heart disease or lung cancer can have new, healthy lung or heart tissue grown from embryonic stem cells.  (Much like this rat)</p>
<p><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ruZvo9zH8Bc" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ruZvo9zH8Bc</a></p>
<p>(And yeah, the stem cells were taken from newborn rats, but they’re lab rats used for research dammit.)</p>
<p>Hell, this shouldn’t even be such a big deal anymore, we know how to synthesize these stem cells from a healthy adult, without the whole embryonic thing.</p>
<p><a href="https://stemcells.nih.gov/info/basics/basics4.asp" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://stemcells.nih.gov/info/basics/basics4.asp</a></p>
<p>(and that’s the National Institute of friggin’ health, again.)</p>
<p>Both types of stem cells have their pros and cons, embryonic stem cells generally being a little more complicated to grow and harvest than ones found already within human beings, and both having issues with cell compatibility upon introduction to the body.</p>
<p>People wonder why we can’t cure cancer, people ask why so many have to suffer with Parkinson’s Disease, diabetes, breast cancer, and autism.  They do because people are so quick to take “Embryo,” as a word, and being completely ignorant of the biology and technicality of the term’s use, make embryonic stem cells out to be a life wasted.  When these cells are just a lump of nothing.</p>
<p>It’s so blindingly obvious, so many people just can’t grasp that embryonic stem cells are cells that haven’t formed into any kind of organism yet, not the ones harvested for human research like we’re talking about.  Now if these were older embryos in which the stem cells have began pooling into sections to form organs and limbs, then it’d be debatable.  But they’re not, they’re a lump of unused cells.  No different from the countless sperm that have died on balled-up tissues or unused eggs in the ovaries.</p>
<p>Honestly, if public schools did a little better to educate with biology and human anatomy and physiology there wouldn’t be such a shitstorm over this issue.  If you wanna bitch and moan about lives wasted, why not bitch and moan about abortion?  Those are stem cells that HAVE formed living organisms with distinct biological systems.  That could be debated.  Embryonic stem cells on the other hand… well, seriously?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/embryonic-stem-cell-research/2146/303">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/embryonic-stem-cell-research/2146/303</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Dec 2009 09:57:45 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2146-303</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/embryonic-stem-cell-research/2146.rss">Embryonic stem cell research</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Embryonic stem cell research</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[DONT_CALL_ME_A_VORT]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="mattemuse">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/m/dc4da7/40.png" class="avatar"> mattemuse:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>The immediately pre-birth baby is biologically identical to the post-birth baby</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>It is still dependent on the mother, though.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/embryonic-stem-cell-research/2146/302">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/embryonic-stem-cell-research/2146/302</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Dec 2009 06:03:37 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2146-302</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/embryonic-stem-cell-research/2146.rss">Embryonic stem cell research</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Embryonic stem cell research</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[garrthbarrttinn]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Cup o Joe">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Cup o Joe:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>No, I said that anyone who does not believe that an individual human life starts conception is in denial.</p>
<p>Baconeggs, that photo is irrelevant, a human is still a human regardless of how young he or she is. What else could it be? a giraffe? seriously it doesn’t matter if we look similar for the first 3 weeks, all creatures were created by the same God. <a href="https://www.scborromeo.org/ccc/para/159.htm" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Science cannot contradict Faith</a> as I’ve said before.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I told my dad (who is a doctor) about your Gerson’s cure and bleeding statue bullshit and he suggested you take Haldol.</p>
<p>On a more serious note, qoutes from the bible are not valid arguments. When qouting a source you should check the sources credibility and the credibility of the author, see if other sources confirm your original source, see if the source is up-to-date, and finally see if professionals in the field support your source.  The bible epically fails all of the above tests. BTW the above is almost directly taken from my English text book.</p>
<p>And the above link is based off the fact that religion is true. Here is that link simplified. Science cannot contradict faith because faith is right.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/embryonic-stem-cell-research/2146/301">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/embryonic-stem-cell-research/2146/301</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 24 Dec 2009 18:55:14 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2146-301</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/embryonic-stem-cell-research/2146.rss">Embryonic stem cell research</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
