<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Game-Halting Screwdriver Glitch in Unforeseen Consequences</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/game-halting-screwdriver-glitch-in-unforeseen-consequences/14140</link>
    <description>map : bm_c1a1a at: 3558 x, 1206 y, -31 z
setpos 3558.791504 1206.118652 -31.968750;setang 7.523964 87.991035 0.000000

As you&#39;re moving through Unforeseen Consequences, you come to a point where a group of scientists fall to their death in an elevator (on a tangential note, I really enjoyed how well that scene was mimicked from the original).

As you&#39;re approaching the door that the elevator is behind, however, there is a screwdriver on the floor to your left (I haven&#39;t tried this with other props yet). Picking up this screwdriver will allow you to shatter the glass on the door an access the elevator shaft early. If you hold the screwdriver out into the shaft at the right angle, you can get it caught between the elevator roof and the floor, preventing the elevator from crashing to the floor. Once you&#39;ve released the screwdriver, there&#39;s no way to get it out again and you&#39;re stuck looking at the frozen scientists inside, given that there appears to be an invisible wall at the top of the ladder until the elevator has crashed).

I&#39;d attach a screenshot, but my computer hasn&#39;t been fond of taking them lately, so unfortunately I can&#39;t get an image of this.

EDIT: You can also do it with the wrench laying to the left of the door as well.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 28 May 2015 11:59:01 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>In-game Issues</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/game-halting-screwdriver-glitch-in-unforeseen-consequences/14140.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Game-Halting Screwdriver Glitch in Unforeseen Consequences</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[MrNameisme]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>map : bm_c1a1a at: 3558 x, 1206 y, -31 z<br>
setpos 3558.791504 1206.118652 -31.968750;setang 7.523964 87.991035 0.000000</p>
<p>As you’re moving through Unforeseen Consequences, you come to a point where a group of scientists fall to their death in an elevator (on a tangential note, I really enjoyed how well that scene was mimicked from the original).</p>
<p>As you’re approaching the door that the elevator is behind, however, there is a screwdriver on the floor to your left (I haven’t tried this with other props yet). Picking up this screwdriver will allow you to shatter the glass on the door an access the elevator shaft early. If you hold the screwdriver out into the shaft at the right angle, you can get it caught between the elevator roof and the floor, preventing the elevator from crashing to the floor. Once you’ve released the screwdriver, there’s no way to get it out again and you’re stuck looking at the frozen scientists inside, given that there appears to be an invisible wall at the top of the ladder until the elevator has crashed).</p>
<p>I’d attach a screenshot, but my computer hasn’t been fond of taking them lately, so unfortunately I can’t get an image of this.</p>
<p>EDIT: You can also do it with the wrench laying to the left of the door as well.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/game-halting-screwdriver-glitch-in-unforeseen-consequences/14140/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/game-halting-screwdriver-glitch-in-unforeseen-consequences/14140/1</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 28 May 2015 11:59:01 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14140-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/game-halting-screwdriver-glitch-in-unforeseen-consequences/14140.rss">Game-Halting Screwdriver Glitch in Unforeseen Consequences</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
