<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>need a save file.</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/need-a-save-file/13417</link>
    <description>hello. my name is jason. i am a small gamer on YouTube. i try to record a variety of games and played through black mesa but didn&#39;t complete it. there was a point where i started doing modded minecraft and skyblock and i ended up setting the game aside. since then i have felt the urge to continue where i left off but between the time i paused black mesa and now i got a new gaming pc. and i don&#39;t have the save file anymore. so i was wandering if anyone had a save file or a tool i could use to skip to the level i left off at? the last part i recorded was the beginning of the level after burning the giant crab squid thing. sorry not so good with names XD. anyway thanks in advance.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2014 07:30:17 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Help!</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/need-a-save-file/13417.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>need a save file.</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypt]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Open the console, type “sv_unlockedchapters 99” then you can select whatever chapter you were on from the New Game menu.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/need-a-save-file/13417/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/need-a-save-file/13417/2</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2014 07:30:17 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13417-2</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/need-a-save-file/13417.rss">need a save file.</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>need a save file.</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Mrabagaming]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>hello. my name is jason. i am a small gamer on YouTube. i try to record a variety of games and played through black mesa but didn’t complete it. there was a point where i started doing modded minecraft and skyblock and i ended up setting the game aside. since then i have felt the urge to continue where i left off but between the time i paused black mesa and now i got a new gaming pc. and i don’t have the save file anymore. so i was wandering if anyone had a save file or a tool i could use to skip to the level i left off at? the last part i recorded was the beginning of the level after burning the giant crab squid thing. sorry not so good with names XD. anyway thanks in advance.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/need-a-save-file/13417/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/need-a-save-file/13417/1</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2014 06:40:13 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13417-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/need-a-save-file/13417.rss">need a save file.</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
