<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>HLDM Fanfic? (Odd concept)</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/hldm-fanfic-odd-concept/3115</link>
    <description>Dr. Simmons awoke, his eyes adjusting to the dim red lighting that surrounded him. He was upright, on his feet. Had he fallen asleep standing up? He checked himself over, to make sure he wasn&#39;t dreaming. Lab coat, bright blue trousers, ludicrously purple shirt, striped tie. It was him, no doubt about it. Then to his astonishment, he realised he was brandishing a 9mm pistol, standard Black Mesa security issue. He felt a weight in the back of his lab coat.

“What in the the name of...” he reached around and found a crowbar, stored in the back of his trousers. He was utterly perplexed as he glanced around the tunnel he was in. He could see daylight up ahead, just beyond the opening of the tunnel, as well as a rocky cliff face. It was definitely Black Mesa, but not a part that Simmons had ever entered. Suddenly, a figure came into view. It was Gina Cross. “Oh thank goodness.” Simmons was relieved to see a familiar and friendly face.

Something wasn&#39;t right though. Gina was running straight for him, her arms out in front, cradling what looked like an experimental weapon from the QE labs. Her HEV was different too, rather than the uniform orange and black, this one was bright green and pink.

“Dr. Cross!” Simmons called out. Just as he did she opened up on him with the Gauss Gun. Simmons screamed and darted in the opposite direction, towards a pool of water which contained chunks of concrete and the entrance to a pipe. Another figure appeared from the mouth of the pipe, with an equally bizarre variation of the HEV in yellow and red. “Gordon Freeman? Thank heavens! Dr. Cross has stolen an experimental weapon and gone totally loopy!”

Freeman stood, motionless, with rage and hate burning in his eyes. He too opened fire, Mp5 rounds pelting into the rocks and water. Simmons let out another yelp and fired his pistol towards the frenzied physicist. A round struck him in the chest and he grunted, a second smashed into his forehead and he slumped to the ground. Simmons dashed for the sub machine gun as Gina strafed from around the corner in the tunnel. Simmons leapt across the water and scooped up the Mp5, turning on his heel and pulling the trigger. The gun emitted a loud click and nothing more. Simmons glanced at the empty weapon and then back to Gina. White hot depleted Uranium burst out of the Gauss gun and ripped through Simmons&#39; chest. He screamed out loud as he was knocked back, another 3 rounds tearing through his body which flopped into the water and bobbed on the surface lifeless.

Simmons gasped as his eyes whipped open. He was sweating excessively, unable to hear anything over the sound of his heavy breathing and his panic stricken heart rate. Was it a dream?

He looked around. He was upright again, on his feet, his hand clutching a 9mm Glock pistol and the weight of a crowbar against his back. He was in a concrete bunker, set into a cliff, overlooking a large space of land. On the opposite side he could see an opening to a tunnel, and Gordon Freeman was running into it, donning a yellow and red HEV suit, grasping a hand grenade. Simmons could see a ladder leading up to a ledge set high above the arena, a crossbow in plain sight. He smirked and dove out of the window, an alien launch pad below sending him sailing upward towards his destination.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 21 Feb 2010 22:46:23 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Show Off</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/hldm-fanfic-odd-concept/3115.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>HLDM Fanfic? (Odd concept)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[King_Max]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>very cool I like it  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=9" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/hldm-fanfic-odd-concept/3115/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/hldm-fanfic-odd-concept/3115/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 21 Feb 2010 22:46:23 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3115-2</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/hldm-fanfic-odd-concept/3115.rss">HLDM Fanfic? (Odd concept)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>HLDM Fanfic? (Odd concept)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[UrBY]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Dr. Simmons awoke, his eyes adjusting to the dim red lighting that surrounded him. He was upright, on his feet. Had he fallen asleep standing up? He checked himself over, to make sure he wasn’t dreaming. Lab coat, bright blue trousers, ludicrously purple shirt, striped tie. It was him, no doubt about it. Then to his astonishment, he realised he was brandishing a 9mm pistol, standard Black Mesa security issue. He felt a weight in the back of his lab coat.</p>
<p>“What in the the name of…” he reached around and found a crowbar, stored in the back of his trousers. He was utterly perplexed as he glanced around the tunnel he was in. He could see daylight up ahead, just beyond the opening of the tunnel, as well as a rocky cliff face. It was definitely Black Mesa, but not a part that Simmons had ever entered. Suddenly, a figure came into view. It was Gina Cross. “Oh thank goodness.” Simmons was relieved to see a familiar and friendly face.</p>
<p>Something wasn’t right though. Gina was running straight for him, her arms out in front, cradling what looked like an experimental weapon from the QE labs. Her HEV was different too, rather than the uniform orange and black, this one was bright green and pink.</p>
<p>“Dr. Cross!” Simmons called out. Just as he did she opened up on him with the Gauss Gun. Simmons screamed and darted in the opposite direction, towards a pool of water which contained chunks of concrete and the entrance to a pipe. Another figure appeared from the mouth of the pipe, with an equally bizarre variation of the HEV in yellow and red. “Gordon Freeman? Thank heavens! Dr. Cross has stolen an experimental weapon and gone totally loopy!”</p>
<p>Freeman stood, motionless, with rage and hate burning in his eyes. He too opened fire, Mp5 rounds pelting into the rocks and water. Simmons let out another yelp and fired his pistol towards the frenzied physicist. A round struck him in the chest and he grunted, a second smashed into his forehead and he slumped to the ground. Simmons dashed for the sub machine gun as Gina strafed from around the corner in the tunnel. Simmons leapt across the water and scooped up the Mp5, turning on his heel and pulling the trigger. The gun emitted a loud click and nothing more. Simmons glanced at the empty weapon and then back to Gina. White hot depleted Uranium burst out of the Gauss gun and ripped through Simmons’ chest. He screamed out loud as he was knocked back, another 3 rounds tearing through his body which flopped into the water and bobbed on the surface lifeless.</p>
<p>Simmons gasped as his eyes whipped open. He was sweating excessively, unable to hear anything over the sound of his heavy breathing and his panic stricken heart rate. Was it a dream?</p>
<p>He looked around. He was upright again, on his feet, his hand clutching a 9mm Glock pistol and the weight of a crowbar against his back. He was in a concrete bunker, set into a cliff, overlooking a large space of land. On the opposite side he could see an opening to a tunnel, and Gordon Freeman was running into it, donning a yellow and red HEV suit, grasping a hand grenade. Simmons could see a ladder leading up to a ledge set high above the arena, a crossbow in plain sight. He smirked and dove out of the window, an alien launch pad below sending him sailing upward towards his destination.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/hldm-fanfic-odd-concept/3115/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/hldm-fanfic-odd-concept/3115/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 21 Feb 2010 22:35:11 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3115-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/hldm-fanfic-odd-concept/3115.rss">HLDM Fanfic? (Odd concept)</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
