<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Mayan exhibit on Kickstarter</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/mayan-exhibit-on-kickstarter/9094</link>
    <description>One of my friends is hosting a Mayan exhibit this winter, and has started a Kickstarter to get the funds to print out all the posters and etc.  If any of you guys are interested, here is the email he sent me.
[quote]
[img]https://dl.dropbox.com/u/27262125/mayan.jpg[/img]

Dear all,
I am getting ready to present this year&#39;s pre-columbian photographic exhibit. I am planning to present it the week after Thanksgiving. As I promised before, this time I will talk about the Mayans, since everyone seems to be talking about them lately and the whole mythology behind 2012. I have posted this project on Kickstarter, which means that if I don&#39;t reach the goal by the designated date, the project won&#39;t be possible and no donations will be collected.
Please help me to spread the word and support my project. For those who have attended my previous Aztec exhibits this time it&#39;s going to be bigger and improved, so you will be dazzled by what I will present.
I hope to see you all at the exhibit as well!

This is the link to my Kickstarter page:

[url]https://www.kickstarter.com/projects/641259295/the-mayans-and-the-end-of-time[/url]

Thanks again,

George Zamora
[/quote]</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 27 Jul 2012 15:25:19 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Off Topic</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/mayan-exhibit-on-kickstarter/9094.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Mayan exhibit on Kickstarter</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[BahamutBBob]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>One of my friends is hosting a Mayan exhibit this winter, and has started a Kickstarter to get the funds to print out all the posters and etc.  If any of you guys are interested, here is the email he sent me.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p><span alt="" class="broken-image" title="This image is broken"><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-unlink svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#unlink"></use></svg></span></p>
<p>Dear all,<br>
I am getting ready to present this year’s pre-columbian photographic exhibit. I am planning to present it the week after Thanksgiving. As I promised before, this time I will talk about the Mayans, since everyone seems to be talking about them lately and the whole mythology behind 2012. I have posted this project on Kickstarter, which means that if I don’t reach the goal by the designated date, the project won’t be possible and no donations will be collected.<br>
Please help me to spread the word and support my project. For those who have attended my previous Aztec exhibits this time it’s going to be bigger and improved, so you will be dazzled by what I will present.<br>
I hope to see you all at the exhibit as well!</p>
<p>This is the link to my Kickstarter page:</p>
<p><a href="https://www.kickstarter.com/projects/641259295/the-mayans-and-the-end-of-time" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://www.kickstarter.com/projects/641259295/the-mayans-and-the-end-of-time</a></p>
<p>Thanks again,</p>
<p>George Zamora</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/mayan-exhibit-on-kickstarter/9094/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/mayan-exhibit-on-kickstarter/9094/1</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jul 2012 15:25:19 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9094-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/mayan-exhibit-on-kickstarter/9094.rss">Mayan exhibit on Kickstarter</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
