<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>What&#39;s the point of this remake (BM, BMDM)?</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/whats-the-point-of-this-remake-bm-bmdm/13967</link>
    <description>Hi,

in the past days,  some people came to me in order to have my opinion about this game* (and especially BMDM). This caught my attention, and I have to admit that I don&#39;t understand the motivations of its developers. What&#39;s the point to rebuild a 16 years old game in a 10 years old one? If the goal was to revive the unique spirit of half-life (deathmatch) and its unique gameplay, I think that what you guys are doing is not on a good road, but will rather lead to failure in a sense I&#39;ll try to make clear in what follows.

First, half-life is a 16 years old game, mostly (if not totally) dead, with an already split community (people playing valve and people playing adrenaline gamer, both steam and won2).  Being an original game and not just a(nother) copy, it inherits some form of authority you guys will have hard time dethroning. Surely, this previous virtue is not something one should focus on too much, there is room for improvement and continuation of half-life style. Yet, can BMDM unify half-life communities and bring to it new (non casual) ones? If yes, how? Can it do it without any big drawbacks on what the original game is?  Isn&#39;t source an already out dated engine to realize such a project? Let us recall what happened with quake 3 and quakelive (no change of engine). The game is now totally dead and is fictively alive thanks to some sponsors and marketing made by its developers.
  
Second, by looking at the team members of this project, the lack of good players is not left unnoticed.  Where are the members who understand the game for what it really is, for its potential, and for what has to be improved?  The little &quot;history&quot; of video gaming has shown that projects like that always led to a simplification, not to say a noobification (skillwise speaking), of games mechanics. You know, video games are like school systems. You don&#39;t make a good game by decreasing the amount of skill  and exigency it requires to be well played. On the contrary, a good game is a game that discriminates players with respect to their skill and investment, and that is not friendly to casual and unskilled players.  What makes half-life (deathmatch) unique is both its long learning curve in order to be able to express yourself decently, and  its aggressiveness (being anti-casual gamers). In this game, you can perfect and rape a supposedly good player in a 1o1 if you&#39;re much better and aggressive enough. In this game, you have to time weapon and ammo, not armors. You can kill someone who is 100/100 with 1 HP thanks to head shot and the total unbalance of weapons, making hitscan aim (gluon, bow, gauss and especially wallgauss and nukes) a much more efficient tool to rape your opponent than projectiles. You have to develop a whole gameplay around spawn cycle (the latter being not so random at all), and can&#39;t possibly be called a good player if you don&#39;t know how to move at least decently.

Third, it looks like the game you guys released is still full of bugs, and lack most half-life features (wallgauss, etc etc). How is that a good strategy to release an unfinished game? You know, most people are trying a game when it is released and then forget it. Maybe you guys should consider being less  hasty. Let me give you a criterion in this respect: take a look at this channel [url]https://www.youtube.com/user/1212testmicro[/url] and these movies [youtube.com/watch?v=3NXnGuS2Jvk](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=3NXnGuS2Jvk) .
Now, consider that the game shouldn&#39;t be released until it becomes possible to redo all these things in a way that is more or less as hard as in the original game.

Regards.
* because I&#39;m more or less the authority of half-life deathmatch.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 13 May 2015 20:17:24 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>The Cafeteria</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/whats-the-point-of-this-remake-bm-bmdm/13967.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>What&#39;s the point of this remake (BM, BMDM)?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[TextFAMGUY1]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I’m closing this thread now, because it’s been nothing more than a shit slinging whine fest from the outset.</p>
<p>Competitive players are welcomed and encouraged to voice their opinions on what can be done to add depth to the game and make it more fun. If they do so in a civil and reasonable manner. That has not been done here. There have been plenty of other competitive players voicing concerns in reasonable and civil ways elsewhere, and we are certainly listening and looking to further improve the game in whatever way we can, for all skill levels.</p>
<p>I hope you will eventually realise that this incredibly adversarial tone you guys have adopted is detrimental to your cause. Threads and posts like these are what give the competitive community a bad name. This is the exact reason I was hesitant to engage with you guys in the first place, and you proved me right. It’s a game, guys. If these kinds of posts continue to be repeated in other threads, I will be handing out permabans.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/whats-the-point-of-this-remake-bm-bmdm/13967/72">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/whats-the-point-of-this-remake-bm-bmdm/13967/72</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 13 May 2015 20:17:24 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13967-72</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/whats-the-point-of-this-remake-bm-bmdm/13967.rss">What&#39;s the point of this remake (BM, BMDM)?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>What&#39;s the point of this remake (BM, BMDM)?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Rezaltas]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="biggy">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/b/dc4da7/40.png" class="avatar"> biggy:</div>
<blockquote>
<ul>
<li>because I’m more or less the authority of half-life deathmatch.</li>
</ul>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p><img src="https://i.gyazo.com/af6f2a37ca5c72ee378994e4e9450167.png" alt="" width="640" height="360"></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/whats-the-point-of-this-remake-bm-bmdm/13967/71">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/whats-the-point-of-this-remake-bm-bmdm/13967/71</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 13 May 2015 20:15:06 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13967-71</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/whats-the-point-of-this-remake-bm-bmdm/13967.rss">What&#39;s the point of this remake (BM, BMDM)?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>What&#39;s the point of this remake (BM, BMDM)?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Juniez]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>fuckin lol. no wonder the original hldm community is dead</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/whats-the-point-of-this-remake-bm-bmdm/13967/70">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/whats-the-point-of-this-remake-bm-bmdm/13967/70</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 13 May 2015 20:14:21 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13967-70</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/whats-the-point-of-this-remake-bm-bmdm/13967.rss">What&#39;s the point of this remake (BM, BMDM)?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>What&#39;s the point of this remake (BM, BMDM)?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[BIAPOS]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="JeffMOD">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/user_avatar/leakfree.org/jeffmod/40/4333_2.png" class="avatar"> JeffMOD:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Obviously you haven’t experienced this in over a decade, but it’s not fun to join a server and not be able to play because every time you spawn you die instantly.<br>
Answer me this: How does one get more skilled at a game when they have no opportunity to play and learn it? If you, as the the popular term among pro players seems to be, “get raped” when you play, you’re not enjoying yourself, and you’re more likely to quit.<br>
People who quit, don’t get better. It’s not noobification of the game, it’s making it more accessible - and, unlike most modern games, BMDM is doing it without being hand-holdy about it; If you lack skill, you’re still going to die a lot - but not so much that you feel like you can never win no matter how hard you try.</p>
<p>You say skill means nothing if it’s ‘pointless’ to get skilled. I say skill means nothing if you’re not given an opportunity to gain any.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>You can start by reading the whole thread instead of some bits, and more specifically:</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="biggy">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/b/dc4da7/40.png" class="avatar"> biggy:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>If what you guys’ fear is to get raped by experienced players, then it’s a false problem (also because there are really few of them). There are ways to avoid that, for example one could</p>
<ol>
<li>
<p>built a skill quantifier as quakelive has, and make an option (that could be turned on/off) on servers to restrict the access to some skill range,</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>train hard in order to compete and have even more satisfaction playing the game,</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>create its own mode if its easy to do and allowed.</p>
</li>
</ol>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>You seem to be under the impression losing does not help you improve. Allow me to share my story: I started off as a newbie player just like everyone else, getting stomped by good players, sometimes even without scoring a single frag. This however showed me that I am far from becoming the player I wanted which in return forced me to think about new ways to improve myself, to find new routes, to reevaluate the way I react to certain situations,ect… all of which gradually made me a player who managed to foil more and more often his opponents plan to dominate him and express their skill while doing the same himself. The beauty I found in the performance of skilled players was always what motivated me to try and become one myself, or even surpass them, even if that meant I had to suffer losing so badly in those 1v1s. It was not fun, but with time I started learning what works better and what is bad, and I understood better and better what I have to do to achieve my goal and that in order to truly become good it is necessary to suffer, fail and work hard. After all this failing, the understanding , skill  and mentality that I have now allow me to enter a server in HLDM full of people like you - guys who never invested in becoming good and chose fun instead of skill, guys who I was once like -  and make everyone quit.</p>
<p>In the end, is it the player who is too strong for you that you do not improve? or perhaps it is your lack of will to suffer and work hard to become the ideal player with beautiful aim, movement and gameplay? I’ll let you conclude.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="JeffMOD">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/user_avatar/leakfree.org/jeffmod/40/4333_2.png" class="avatar"> JeffMOD:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Well, that’s kind of my point. You’ve spent more time developing your skills, so you’re better at the game than I am. I have no doubt that you could kick my ass.So why do you need them to add new mechanics to make it more like AG? With your skills you can already dominate me and most of the rest of the playerbase without those mechanics, right? You don’t need Bhop or wallstrafing to beat me. So now it’s down to pure skill in playing the game, with no exploits to artificially boost them. If anything, it adds to the challenge in playing, because there aren’t those exploits to rely on - think of it as having the thrill of a new challenge the likes of which you haven’t had in years.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>We don’t need or care about challenge, please re-read.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/whats-the-point-of-this-remake-bm-bmdm/13967/69">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/whats-the-point-of-this-remake-bm-bmdm/13967/69</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 13 May 2015 20:10:05 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13967-69</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/whats-the-point-of-this-remake-bm-bmdm/13967.rss">What&#39;s the point of this remake (BM, BMDM)?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>What&#39;s the point of this remake (BM, BMDM)?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[biggy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><a href="https://forums.blackmesasource.com/index.php/User/941-xalener/" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">@xalener</a>: why are you implying I’m crazy, or that I only have video games in my life? The views I hold above are consistent with the ones I have in life, and they allowed me to become a mathematical physicist* working on interesting stuff as a living. Thanks to care about my sanity.</p>
<p><a href="https://forums.blackmesasource.com/index.php/User/36331-TextFAMGUY1/" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">@TextFAMGUY1</a>: you eventually revealed your intentions (or the ones of BM devs) after 4 pages. Congratulation, it is now clear that you don’t want to make BMDM a skilled game, and it is therefore no need for me to argue any longer.</p>
<p>PS: if you believe that the questions you ask are not led by any ideology you’re not even aware of, it’s sad. This is what disappoints me. You guys think that there’s only one way playing video games, and that there’s nothing more meaningful or absolute to find there. That’s just plain false, but its useless arguing in any case, because you eventually chose a side.</p>
<ul>
<li>and no, this is not at all related to half-life, freeman character or whatever.</li>
</ul>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/whats-the-point-of-this-remake-bm-bmdm/13967/68">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/whats-the-point-of-this-remake-bm-bmdm/13967/68</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 13 May 2015 20:04:39 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13967-68</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/whats-the-point-of-this-remake-bm-bmdm/13967.rss">What&#39;s the point of this remake (BM, BMDM)?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>What&#39;s the point of this remake (BM, BMDM)?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[xalener]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>It doesn’t matter if we tell him that his opinion is subjective, he won’t believe us. It wouldn’t have mattered if you were the damn project leader or even a veteran Valve employee whose fuck-ups directly resulted in these old exploits. He’s really good at a 17 year old game, therefore he knows better than you.</p>
<p>That’s about the gist I’m getting, and I think nothing short of a life changing epiphany, like an honest to god near death situation, is gonna show him how warped his POV is.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/whats-the-point-of-this-remake-bm-bmdm/13967/67">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/whats-the-point-of-this-remake-bm-bmdm/13967/67</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 13 May 2015 20:03:56 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13967-67</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/whats-the-point-of-this-remake-bm-bmdm/13967.rss">What&#39;s the point of this remake (BM, BMDM)?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>What&#39;s the point of this remake (BM, BMDM)?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[TextFAMGUY1]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Enough of this. I’m not interested in this high level discussion. Constantly harping on about what the “spirit of Half-Life” and what it means to have skill is a pointless discussion here. It’s pretty much the only topic in this entire MP discussion which is <span class="bbcode-b">purely subjective</span>. The “spirit of Half-Life” and HLDM means totally different things to different people, and there’s no objective definition for it. In my opinion, our game’s MP preserves the spirit of Half-Life’s multiplayer, while revitalising and modernising it. You cannot convince me that this opinion is wrong, because it’s purely an opinion, even if it’s totally at odds with what you guys think. And I know that it is, and that you competitive guys vehemently disagree with me. And that’s cool. We like that.</p>
<p>But here’s the thing - the things we care about in this game, with regards to gameplay mechanics, really boil down to 2 very basic points. 1) Does it add depth to the gameplay? 2) Is it fun for players? That’s literally all you need to answer to convince me that a change is good or not. I don’t care about what you guys think of the overall competitive landscape, or how good your understanding of the game is. Put those 2 points across, convince me, and I will look into adding it in. We care about things from a <span class="bbcode-b">practical</span>, not an <span class="bbcode-b">ideological</span> perspective.</p>
<p>Here’s an example. Bunny hopping. Does it add depth to the gameplay? Yes. A fair bit, from everything I’ve heard, so much so that competitive players think it’s a core part of the gameplay. Is it fun for players? Well…that’s a tougher one. A very small percentage of the community will care about or attempt to master it, because it’s a difficult skill. They will use it to destroy those who don’t (the vast majority). Not particularly fun, but still worth considering. We put it on the list.</p>
<p>Compare that, to Tau Wallshotting, for example. Adds depth to the gameplay? Absolutely. Unquestionably. Is it fun for players? Well, despite the nuances to it, at its surface, it is a simple mechanic. You can shoot through walls. It can be used in a variety of circumstances that most, if not all players, will find themselves in. It can create awesome moments where you get a fantastic shot on someone through a wall / thin cover, no matter what your skill level. Skilled players and newer players alike can take advantage of it and enjoy it.</p>
<p>So, we know which out of those two mechanics goes up on the priorities list, above the other. It’s really as simple and practical as that. This is how you should approach issues when talking to us. With a practical eye. Enough with all this higher ideological nonsense. Let’s keep it simple, logical, and pleasant.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/whats-the-point-of-this-remake-bm-bmdm/13967/66">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/whats-the-point-of-this-remake-bm-bmdm/13967/66</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 13 May 2015 19:52:07 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13967-66</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/whats-the-point-of-this-remake-bm-bmdm/13967.rss">What&#39;s the point of this remake (BM, BMDM)?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>What&#39;s the point of this remake (BM, BMDM)?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[xalener]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Biggy, I’m starting to think that skill in twitch arena shooters is the only skill you’ve developed. No one with any power is going to agree with your (excessively) extreme point of view. Not a damn soul.</p>
<p>Personally, I think you feel <span class="bbcode-i">too </span>strongly about this.</p>
<p>Fun is ugly? Jesus christ, go wallstrafe to a shrink’s office.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/whats-the-point-of-this-remake-bm-bmdm/13967/65">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/whats-the-point-of-this-remake-bm-bmdm/13967/65</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 13 May 2015 19:50:50 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13967-65</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/whats-the-point-of-this-remake-bm-bmdm/13967.rss">What&#39;s the point of this remake (BM, BMDM)?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>What&#39;s the point of this remake (BM, BMDM)?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[_WC_Stabsley]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>You make me really, really sad. How do you not get that the overwhelming majority of players are just looking to have some fun? If you want to turn games into some sort of chore, you do that, but don’t force the rest of us to play in your sad, depressing sandbox with you. It’s a game, lighten up dude.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/whats-the-point-of-this-remake-bm-bmdm/13967/64">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/whats-the-point-of-this-remake-bm-bmdm/13967/64</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 13 May 2015 19:18:02 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13967-64</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/whats-the-point-of-this-remake-bm-bmdm/13967.rss">What&#39;s the point of this remake (BM, BMDM)?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>What&#39;s the point of this remake (BM, BMDM)?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[JeffMOD]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="biggy">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/b/dc4da7/40.png" class="avatar"> biggy:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Because I trained hard for it and invested my time to develop these skills, whereas you never did.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Well, that’s kind of my point. You’ve spent more time developing your skills, so you’re better at the game than I am. I have no doubt that you could kick my ass.<br>
So why do you need them to add new mechanics to make it more like AG? With your skills you can already dominate me and most of the rest of the playerbase without those mechanics, right? You don’t need Bhop or wallstrafing to beat me. So now it’s down to pure skill in playing the game, with no exploits to artificially boost them. If anything, it adds to the challenge in playing, because there aren’t those exploits to rely on - think of it as having the thrill of a new challenge the likes of which you haven’t had in years.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/whats-the-point-of-this-remake-bm-bmdm/13967/63">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/whats-the-point-of-this-remake-bm-bmdm/13967/63</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 13 May 2015 19:13:08 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13967-63</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/whats-the-point-of-this-remake-bm-bmdm/13967.rss">What&#39;s the point of this remake (BM, BMDM)?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>What&#39;s the point of this remake (BM, BMDM)?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[MichaelTannock]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>In real life you develop skills to gain an advantage over other potential recruits, because you want the job.<br>
In games you develop skills to gain an advantage over other players, because why?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/whats-the-point-of-this-remake-bm-bmdm/13967/62">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/whats-the-point-of-this-remake-bm-bmdm/13967/62</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 13 May 2015 19:08:27 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13967-62</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/whats-the-point-of-this-remake-bm-bmdm/13967.rss">What&#39;s the point of this remake (BM, BMDM)?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>What&#39;s the point of this remake (BM, BMDM)?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[biggy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="JeffMOD">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/user_avatar/leakfree.org/jeffmod/40/4333_2.png" class="avatar"> JeffMOD:</div>
<blockquote>
<p><a href="https://forums.blackmesasource.com/index.php/User/57533-biggy/" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">@biggy</a><br>
I’d like to use an example from GO. The number of pieces you have in GO is inversely proportional to your skill - if you’re a pro at the game, you start with much fewer pieces than a first-time player. Obviously, this isn’t sustainable for a DM game, but you should really be asking yourself - you’re skilled. Why do you need to have more tools than unskilled players, when the tools you both share, you’re better with?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Because I trained hard for it and invested my time to develop these skills, whereas you never did. Video games are no different than real life. You can’t ask people to recruit you for an interesting job or a well paid one if you didn’t develop the skills needed to hold such positions. The problem is that you think that everyone is playing video games for fun: there’s more to video games than fun. Like sports, (or any job) one can do an activity for performances, intellectual pursuit, or for the very sake of doing the activity for what it is (without being obsessed or even caring about the fun it might gives you). Do you think that it is fun to train hard? It’s not. Do you think that it’s fun to “rape” a casual player? It’s not either, but it’s a nice challenge trying to score as much as you can. I’ve personally never played video games for fun itself, but for skill and the freedom it gives me. Yes, skill gives freedom, allowing the skilled player to express its creativity and taking new paths an unskilled one wouldn’t be able to even know of their very existence. Moreover, in a skilled game, there exists some intuitive notion of an ideal player, giving a goal to aim at. Skill allows to reach such ideals, and the latter are beautiful. Fun, on the contrary, is ugly.</p>
<p>Now, it is easy to satisfy people who wants to play video games for the above ugliness: just do what quakelive did with a skill quantifier and a restrictive access to servers. What’s the problem here?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/whats-the-point-of-this-remake-bm-bmdm/13967/61">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/whats-the-point-of-this-remake-bm-bmdm/13967/61</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 13 May 2015 18:53:50 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13967-61</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/whats-the-point-of-this-remake-bm-bmdm/13967.rss">What&#39;s the point of this remake (BM, BMDM)?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>What&#39;s the point of this remake (BM, BMDM)?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[eriksonis6]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I would like to know if developers are interested in making matchmaking system? If yes, then all problems with good players destroying bad players would be over.  If not, then you cant do anything about it, in every game there always will be way better players than beginners.  and beginners when playing against way better players will always be raped. And it doesn’t matter if game is noob friendly or not.</p>
<p>But will good players on purpose join server full of bad players?  Personally i have never joined hldm server to rape lower skilled player, and my clan mates didn’t too, we always are trying to find players who knows what they are doing. And majority players feels the same. like 95% of AG players don’t even play hl.</p>
<p>In conclusion i don’t think that skill difference in pub servers is big problem.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/whats-the-point-of-this-remake-bm-bmdm/13967/60">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/whats-the-point-of-this-remake-bm-bmdm/13967/60</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 13 May 2015 18:50:52 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13967-60</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/whats-the-point-of-this-remake-bm-bmdm/13967.rss">What&#39;s the point of this remake (BM, BMDM)?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>What&#39;s the point of this remake (BM, BMDM)?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[fury]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="JeffMOD">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/user_avatar/leakfree.org/jeffmod/40/4333_2.png" class="avatar"> JeffMOD:</div>
<blockquote>
<p><a href="https://forums.blackmesasource.com/index.php/User/1005-fury/" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">@fury</a>At the current time, though, there aren’t any private servers to the game. This will be changed, I’m sure, but even then, there will be lots of public servers that people will play on, and there’s nothing stopping a group of competitive players from hopping on it too and “pubstomping” everyone.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Yea right. Just wait until the game is more polished and motivate more people to try the game. explain how it works, have fun etc.<br>
If you really like this game, get your own server for the game. then you can put a password on it and play with your friends… or make it completely public and kick/ban people who are too good or annoying. I am good in HL so I don’t have problems with this.<br>
I also may get a server for BM <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/smiley.png?v=9" title=":smiley:" class="emoji" alt=":smiley:"> M but I’m not sure if it’s worth it at this point. Atm I still play more HL1:AG than this… So I might rather rent a server for AG. If this game gets better… I will get a server for this.</p>
<p>Edit: In the end you have this problem of “getting stomped” in almost every game. In CoD you get spawnraped by choppergunner or AC130, in Quake you don’t get any armor or weapons and you die a lot, in starcraft you get zergrushed, in Battlefield you don’t win a single jet-fight because there is some freak on the server who plays jet 24/7… It happens in every game that has atleast a bit of depth. So please just deal with it. It doesn’t make sense to dumb everything down just to maybe make some casual players a bit more happy. There has to be some motivation for getting better at multiplayer-games… Without any motivation to play the game… Why play it? You can rather play singleplayer games then… These games (ideally) have some story atleast.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/whats-the-point-of-this-remake-bm-bmdm/13967/59">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/whats-the-point-of-this-remake-bm-bmdm/13967/59</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 13 May 2015 18:46:36 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13967-59</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/whats-the-point-of-this-remake-bm-bmdm/13967.rss">What&#39;s the point of this remake (BM, BMDM)?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>What&#39;s the point of this remake (BM, BMDM)?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[JeffMOD]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><a href="https://forums.blackmesasource.com/index.php/User/57533-biggy/" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">@biggy</a><br>
The problem with that argument is that, much like the actual act of sexual assault, getting “raped” in a game is the exact opposite of enjoyable. It’s one thing to be bested - it’s another to be “raped”<br>
You seem be under the impression that the opposite is true, and that indicates that you don’t genuinely care if other players have a good time, so long as you’re at the top of the leaderboards, or at the very least that you’ve never given any thought to it.</p>
<p>I’d like to use an example from GO. The number of pieces you have in GO is inversely proportional to your skill - if you’re a pro at the game, you start with much fewer pieces than a first-time player. Obviously, this isn’t sustainable for a DM game, but you should really be asking yourself - you’re skilled. Why do you need to have more tools than unskilled players, when the tools you both share, you’re better with?</p>
<p><a href="https://forums.blackmesasource.com/index.php/User/1005-fury/" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">@fury</a><br>
At the current time, though, there aren’t any private servers to the game. This will be changed, I’m sure, but even then, there will be lots of public servers that people will play on, and there’s nothing stopping a group of competitive players from hopping on it too and “pubstomping” everyone.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/whats-the-point-of-this-remake-bm-bmdm/13967/58">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/whats-the-point-of-this-remake-bm-bmdm/13967/58</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 13 May 2015 18:36:50 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13967-58</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/whats-the-point-of-this-remake-bm-bmdm/13967.rss">What&#39;s the point of this remake (BM, BMDM)?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>What&#39;s the point of this remake (BM, BMDM)?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[fury]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="JeffMOD">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/user_avatar/leakfree.org/jeffmod/40/4333_2.png" class="avatar"> JeffMOD:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Obviously you haven’t experienced this in over a decade, but it’s not fun to join a server and not be able to play because every time you spawn you die instantly.<br>
Answer me this: How does one get more skilled at a game when they have no opportunity to play and learn it? If you, as the the popular term among pro players seems to be, “get raped” when you play, you’re not enjoying yourself, and you’re more likely to quit.<br>
People who quit, don’t get better. It’s not noobification of the game, it’s making it more accessible - and, unlike most modern games, BMDM is doing it without being hand-holdy about it; If you lack skill, you’re still going to die a lot - but not so much that you feel like you can never win no matter how hard you try.</p>
<p>You say skill means nothing if it’s ‘pointless’ to get skilled. I say skill means nothing if you’re not given an opportunity to gain any.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>again… then you play on the wrong server. if you get annoyed, feel free to change the server or ask your friends to play some matches on equal skill levels. most pro players don’t even play public.<br>
if i experience cheaters in other games i votekick or instantly leave the server. that’s how it works.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/whats-the-point-of-this-remake-bm-bmdm/13967/57">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/whats-the-point-of-this-remake-bm-bmdm/13967/57</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 13 May 2015 18:35:50 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13967-57</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/whats-the-point-of-this-remake-bm-bmdm/13967.rss">What&#39;s the point of this remake (BM, BMDM)?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>What&#39;s the point of this remake (BM, BMDM)?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[biggy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>BIAPOS just made a pretty good point. The very possibility that a strong player comes in some server and rapes everyone is exactly in the spirit of half-life deathmatch: it sells dream, it gives the feeling that the player is invincible, much more free than you are, and it makes you want to do the same. That’s exactly what attracted me here, and I’m certain that it is the same for many people. Don’t fear that, on the contrary, you should try to produce it if you really want to make half-life spirit lives.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/whats-the-point-of-this-remake-bm-bmdm/13967/56">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/whats-the-point-of-this-remake-bm-bmdm/13967/56</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 13 May 2015 18:25:58 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13967-56</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/whats-the-point-of-this-remake-bm-bmdm/13967.rss">What&#39;s the point of this remake (BM, BMDM)?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>What&#39;s the point of this remake (BM, BMDM)?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[JeffMOD]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Obviously you haven’t experienced this in over a decade, but it’s not fun to join a server and not be able to play because every time you spawn you die instantly.<br>
Answer me this: How does one get more skilled at a game when they have no opportunity to play and learn it? If you, as the the popular term among pro players seems to be, “get raped” when you play, you’re not enjoying yourself, and you’re more likely to quit.<br>
People who quit, don’t get better. It’s not noobification of the game, it’s making it more accessible - and, unlike most modern games, BMDM is doing it without being hand-holdy about it; If you lack skill, you’re still going to die a lot - but not so much that you feel like you can never win no matter how hard you try.</p>
<p>You say skill means nothing if it’s ‘pointless’ to get skilled. I say skill means nothing if you’re not given an opportunity to gain any.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/whats-the-point-of-this-remake-bm-bmdm/13967/55">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/whats-the-point-of-this-remake-bm-bmdm/13967/55</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 13 May 2015 18:23:23 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13967-55</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/whats-the-point-of-this-remake-bm-bmdm/13967.rss">What&#39;s the point of this remake (BM, BMDM)?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>What&#39;s the point of this remake (BM, BMDM)?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[fury]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="BIAPOS">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/b/9de0a6/40.png" class="avatar"> BIAPOS:</div>
<blockquote>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="biggy">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/b/dc4da7/40.png" class="avatar"> biggy:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>EDIT for JeffMOD below this post: No, it is not possible to make a game that is vertical enough and allows casual gamers not to get crushed by good ones. If it were, then it would mean that the contribution of skill (aim, moves, gameplay) to kill your opponent is not high, that is, it is not effective to be skilled in order to win. This means that the gap in skill, as high as it can be, is actually useless to win the game or express yourself. Thus, such a game can’t be said to be a skilled game, because it is pointless to get skilled.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Mr. JeffMOD, how can you honestly claim that you can do both when clearly if in BM you’re capable of killing a strong player while in HLDM you get raped 100-0 then there is some noobification ocuring. Clearly then  BM has killed the expressive potential high skill gives you which means BM deviates from the true spirit of HLDM. Can you truly not see this?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>The game just got released. it’s early access. changes will be made. which of these satemens don’t you understand? omg.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/whats-the-point-of-this-remake-bm-bmdm/13967/54">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/whats-the-point-of-this-remake-bm-bmdm/13967/54</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 13 May 2015 18:18:47 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13967-54</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/whats-the-point-of-this-remake-bm-bmdm/13967.rss">What&#39;s the point of this remake (BM, BMDM)?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>What&#39;s the point of this remake (BM, BMDM)?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[BIAPOS]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="biggy">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/b/dc4da7/40.png" class="avatar"> biggy:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>EDIT for JeffMOD below this post: No, it is not possible to make a game that is vertical enough and allows casual gamers not to get crushed by good ones. If it were, then it would mean that the contribution of skill (aim, moves, gameplay) to kill your opponent is not high, that is, it is not effective to be skilled in order to win. This means that the gap in skill, as high as it can be, is actually useless to win the game or express yourself. Thus, such a game can’t be said to be a skilled game, because it is pointless to get skilled.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Mr. JeffMOD, how can you honestly claim that you can do both when clearly if in BM you’re capable of killing a strong player while in HLDM you get raped 100-0 then there is some noobification ocuring? Clearly then  BM has killed the expressive potential high skill gives you which means BM deviates from the true spirit of HLDM. Can you truly not see this?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/whats-the-point-of-this-remake-bm-bmdm/13967/53">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/whats-the-point-of-this-remake-bm-bmdm/13967/53</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 13 May 2015 18:16:29 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13967-53</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/whats-the-point-of-this-remake-bm-bmdm/13967.rss">What&#39;s the point of this remake (BM, BMDM)?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>What&#39;s the point of this remake (BM, BMDM)?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[TextFAMGUY1]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>It’s not about taking sides. It’s about not being a jerk to other peoples’ opinions, even if you disagree with them. We don’t need or want elitism here. This is a forum for open discussion about how to improve the game; something that we all want. You are free to disagree with each other or even me. But there’s nothing inherently superior about anyone here - it is a level playing field. It’s about the merits in what you are saying (which I have not debated whatsoever).</p>
<p>“I understand the game so much deeper than you” is not an argument. That’s pretty much all that you’ve argued in this thread. I haven’t argued anything back because I don’t think it’s worth the time. I’ve taken the points from what you competitive guys have been saying and have worked it into our plans for the next major update. We are listening to what you have to say, weighing it up against what we want to do and what we can do. We want BMS to be a high skill cap and enjoyable shooter. It is very possible to create an experience which is welcoming and fun for new players and also has a high skill ceiling, and that is our goal.</p>
<p>I’m just asking you to stop being elitist jerks about what you want for the game, and to stop with the “us vs them” mentality which is running rampant in this thread. Shortly, I’m going to stop asking nicely.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/whats-the-point-of-this-remake-bm-bmdm/13967/52">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/whats-the-point-of-this-remake-bm-bmdm/13967/52</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 13 May 2015 17:54:19 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13967-52</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/whats-the-point-of-this-remake-bm-bmdm/13967.rss">What&#39;s the point of this remake (BM, BMDM)?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>What&#39;s the point of this remake (BM, BMDM)?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[JeffMOD]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Not everything has to be about sides. It <span class="bbcode-i">is</span> possible to make a game that’s deep enough to take time to master, but easy to jump into and hold your own without having people destroy you without end when you jump on a server, and (though I can’t speak for them) I believe that’s what CC is going for - something with the fast-paced, skill-based gameplay of Half-Life, but balanced enough that everyone has more or less a fair shake.<br>
I hop on to a server with some friends, I get wrecked because they’re better at the game than I am. But I can still score the occasional kill, and feel like I have a chance, so I don’t quit the game outright.</p>
<p>Since I don’t quit the game outright, because it doesn’t feel unfair, I can get better at the game as I develop my skills.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/whats-the-point-of-this-remake-bm-bmdm/13967/51">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/whats-the-point-of-this-remake-bm-bmdm/13967/51</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 13 May 2015 17:36:28 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13967-51</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/whats-the-point-of-this-remake-bm-bmdm/13967.rss">What&#39;s the point of this remake (BM, BMDM)?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>What&#39;s the point of this remake (BM, BMDM)?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[biggy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote group-black-mesa-devs" data-username="TextFAMGUY1">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/user_avatar/leakfree.org/textfamguy1/40/4294_2.png" class="avatar"> TextFAMGUY1:</div>
<blockquote>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="BIAPOS">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/b/9de0a6/40.png" class="avatar"> BIAPOS:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Dear community manager, you must understand that the people you request feedback from have different idea as to what path this project should follow. However the motivation behind this project will give different paths a different value, meaning that some people have to be disregarded if you wish to stay true to your goal. If the developers are motivated for this project to be a remake of our beloved half-life 1, both in the spirit at its core and its unique details, then it is natural for them to turn to the most skilled players - those who hold the deepest understanding of this game - for criticism of the current stage of the project as well as guidance on the direction the developers should take. Taking this as a motivation will mean people without skill should be disregarded as their picture of the game is muddy and faint. Now, if the developers goal is to have this project become popular, then you will try to satisfy as many people as possible, which as seen frequently in gaming, would be the casual players. This will lead to a big noobification of the game which will kill its spirit in the hopes that its noob-friendly enough to attract lots of people.<br>
After all of this is said it’s clear that there are some people in this thread who are under the impression that the developers care about the first goal, hence this discrimination by skill that you see. So tell us, Mr. community manager, what is the goal of this project? Clear it out for us so we can know whose feedback is wanted and whose isn’t.</p>
<p>peace and love,<br>
BIAPOS S2</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>We look at the merit of what people are saying. It’s as simple as that. Your opinion of the game is not inherently correct 100% of the time because you have a deeper understanding of it than someone else. I’m not going to take every word you guys say as golden just because you have skill. I’m going to look at the reasoning and what you’re saying and draw my own conclusions from it. Attempting to argue otherwise boils down to a proclamation of self-superiority.</p>
<p>We care about making an awesome tribute to Half-Life that is fun, enduring, and balanced at all levels. We want input from everyone.</p>
<p>If you have a deep and complex understanding of the game, you will be able to provide me with feedback and reasoning that goes far deeper than “because I’m a skilled player and thus my opinion is more valid than others.” You will be able to explain to us logically why X, Y and Z change is important for the game and has a big impact, and benefits everyone. Thus far though, except from a few select posters, we haven’t been given feedback that goes beyond that. That’s the source of my frustrations here, and shouting down other peoples’ opinions is not okay, no matter how right you think you are. If you want to prove you are right, then you make a solid argument which can’t be beaten. That’s how it works.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Everything I claimed is logical and well developed. The problem is that  it really looks like my understanding of the game is too deep for people to really understands what I mean. You know, understanding is like a stair: you need to climb to the 10th steps if you want to ever understand the 11th and 12th ones.  Does this sound arrogant? Clearly, but isn’t it true? Who else here, can claim to understand the game as I do? Moreover, does it look like I really argue for my own interests like other people have clearly shown to do so?</p>
<p>Also, if you believe that it is possible to make a game that is everything at once (balanced at all levels, you claim), then I invite you to take more than five seconds thinking about what I said (both here, and above). Feel free to ask for precisions.</p>
<p>PS: if you believe that my arguments are not solids and can be beaten, then feel free to do it. However, you shouldn’t forget that all I do is arguing in favor of a skilled oriented game. If you want BMDM not to be a skilled game, then it’s no need asking for solid arguments in this respect. What about being honest about the intention you guys want to do with this BMDM? It would simplify all this talk, you know. Choose a side, we are all listening to you.</p>
<p>EDIT for JeffMOD below this post: No, it is not possible to make a game that is vertical enough and allows casual gamers not to get crushed by good ones. If it were, then it would mean that the contribution of skill (aim, moves, gameplay) to kill your opponent is not high, that is, it is not effective to be skilled in order to win. This means that the gap in skill, as high as it can be, is actually useless to win the game or express yourself. Thus, such a game can’t be said to be a skilled game, because it is pointless to get skilled.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/whats-the-point-of-this-remake-bm-bmdm/13967/50">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/whats-the-point-of-this-remake-bm-bmdm/13967/50</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 13 May 2015 17:26:43 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13967-50</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/whats-the-point-of-this-remake-bm-bmdm/13967.rss">What&#39;s the point of this remake (BM, BMDM)?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>What&#39;s the point of this remake (BM, BMDM)?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[TextFAMGUY1]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="BIAPOS">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/b/9de0a6/40.png" class="avatar"> BIAPOS:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Dear community manager, you must understand that the people you request feedback from have different idea as to what path this project should follow. However the motivation behind this project will give different paths a different value, meaning that some people have to be disregarded if you wish to stay true to your goal. If the developers are motivated for this project to be a remake of our beloved half-life 1, both in the spirit at its core and its unique details, then it is natural for them to turn to the most skilled players - those who hold the deepest understanding of this game - for criticism of the current stage of the project as well as guidance on the direction the developers should take. Taking this as a motivation will mean people without skill should be disregarded as their picture of the game is muddy and faint. Now, if the developers goal is to have this project become popular, then you will try to satisfy as many people as possible, which as seen frequently in gaming, would be the casual players. This will lead to a big noobification of the game which will kill its spirit in the hopes that its noob-friendly enough to attract lots of people.<br>
After all of this is said it’s clear that there are some people in this thread who are under the impression that the developers care about the first goal, hence this discrimination by skill that you see. So tell us, Mr. community manager, what is the goal of this project? Clear it out for us so we can know whose feedback is wanted and whose isn’t.</p>
<p>peace and love,<br>
BIAPOS S2</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>We look at the merit of what people are saying. It’s as simple as that. Your opinion of the game is not inherently correct 100% of the time because you have a deeper understanding of it than someone else. I’m not going to take every word you guys say as golden just because you have skill. I’m going to look at the reasoning and what you’re saying and draw my own conclusions from it. Attempting to argue otherwise boils down to a proclamation of self-superiority.</p>
<p>We care about making an awesome tribute to Half-Life that is fun, enduring, and balanced at all levels. We want input from everyone.</p>
<p>If you have a deep and complex understanding of the game, you will be able to provide me with feedback and reasoning that goes far deeper than “because I’m a skilled player and thus my opinion is more valid than others.” You will be able to explain to us logically why X, Y and Z change is important for the game and has a big impact, and benefits everyone. Thus far though, except from a few select posters, we haven’t been given feedback that goes beyond that. That’s the source of my frustrations here, and shouting down other peoples’ opinions is not okay, no matter how right you think you are. If you want to prove you are right, then you make a solid argument which can’t be beaten. That’s how it works.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/whats-the-point-of-this-remake-bm-bmdm/13967/49">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/whats-the-point-of-this-remake-bm-bmdm/13967/49</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 13 May 2015 15:29:31 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13967-49</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/whats-the-point-of-this-remake-bm-bmdm/13967.rss">What&#39;s the point of this remake (BM, BMDM)?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>What&#39;s the point of this remake (BM, BMDM)?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[BIAPOS]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote group-black-mesa-devs" data-username="TextFAMGUY1">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/user_avatar/leakfree.org/textfamguy1/40/4294_2.png" class="avatar"> TextFAMGUY1:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>This overall tone of this discussion is getting very adversarial and it’s getting out of hand. Tone it back please or I’m going to start banning people. You are free to discuss the merits of implementing/changing mechanics, and what you think works best. But, there’s no need to attack people because they have a different opinion on how the game should be, or a different skill level to you. It’s about the points they make, and nothing more. Seeing as you guys have chosen to “represent” the competitive HLDM community on here, remember that the tone of the discussion impacts whether people listen to and agree with your suggestions or not. You’re not doing any favours for yourselves by being like this.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Dear community manager, you must understand that the people you request feedback from have different idea as to what path this project should follow. However the motivation behind this project will give different paths a different value, meaning that some people have to be disregarded if you wish to stay true to your goal. If the developers are motivated for this project to be a remake of our beloved half-life 1, both in the spirit at its core and its unique details, then it is natural for them to turn to the most skilled players - those who hold the deepest understanding of this game - for criticism of the current stage of the project as well as guidance on the direction the developers should take. Taking this as a motivation will mean people without skill should be disregarded as their picture of the game is muddy and faint. Now, if the developers goal is to have this project become popular, then you will try to satisfy as many people as possible, which as seen frequently in gaming, would be the casual players. This will lead to a big noobification of the game which will kill its spirit in the hopes that its noob-friendly enough to attract lots of people.</p>
<p>After all of this is said it’s clear that there are some people in this thread who are under the impression that the developers care about the first goal, hence this discrimination by skill that you see. So tell us, Mr. community manager, what is the goal of this project? Clear it out for us so we can know whose feedback is wanted and whose isn’t.</p>
<p>peace and love,<br>
BIAPOS S2<br>
[/size]</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/whats-the-point-of-this-remake-bm-bmdm/13967/48">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/whats-the-point-of-this-remake-bm-bmdm/13967/48</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 13 May 2015 14:37:28 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13967-48</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/whats-the-point-of-this-remake-bm-bmdm/13967.rss">What&#39;s the point of this remake (BM, BMDM)?</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
