<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Cannot pick up ammo / Zombie issues / Cannot kill barnacle</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/cannot-pick-up-ammo-zombie-issues-cannot-kill-barnacle/10788</link>
    <description>I&#39;ve been having trouble with the game since the first time you could pick up trip mines. When I encountered the first trip mines to be picked up, the HUD said I picked some up but they did not appear in my inventory.

From this point on I have been able to collect very little ammo. I think there&#39;s only been SOME shotgun ammo I&#39;ve been able to pick up. I have encountered every other ammo (pistol, magnum, submachine, grenade launcher, grenades). At this point I have very little of each ammo, well below the max amount.

Also I have not been tracked/attacked by any headcrab zombies. They just die.

Also if I happen to get snagged by a Barnacle, no matter how much I shoot them they will not die. They eventually kill me, every time.

And finally, if I encounter a friendly NPC they will also die shortly after I see them.

The game was working fine up until this part. Nothing to my knowledge has changed.

What&#39;s going on, and how can this be fixed on my end?

Let me know if there&#39;s any further information I can provide.

Brian</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 19 Sep 2012 04:36:02 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>In-game Issues (Mod)</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/cannot-pick-up-ammo-zombie-issues-cannot-kill-barnacle/10788.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Cannot pick up ammo / Zombie issues / Cannot kill barnacle</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[volt]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I’ve been having trouble with the game since the first time you could pick up trip mines. When I encountered the first trip mines to be picked up, the HUD said I picked some up but they did not appear in my inventory.</p>
<p>From this point on I have been able to collect very little ammo. I think there’s only been SOME shotgun ammo I’ve been able to pick up. I have encountered every other ammo (pistol, magnum, submachine, grenade launcher, grenades). At this point I have very little of each ammo, well below the max amount.</p>
<p>Also I have not been tracked/attacked by any headcrab zombies. They just die.</p>
<p>Also if I happen to get snagged by a Barnacle, no matter how much I shoot them they will not die. They eventually kill me, every time.</p>
<p>And finally, if I encounter a friendly NPC they will also die shortly after I see them.</p>
<p>The game was working fine up until this part. Nothing to my knowledge has changed.</p>
<p>What’s going on, and how can this be fixed on my end?</p>
<p>Let me know if there’s any further information I can provide.</p>
<p>Brian</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/cannot-pick-up-ammo-zombie-issues-cannot-kill-barnacle/10788/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/cannot-pick-up-ammo-zombie-issues-cannot-kill-barnacle/10788/1</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 19 Sep 2012 04:36:02 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-10788-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/cannot-pick-up-ammo-zombie-issues-cannot-kill-barnacle/10788.rss">Cannot pick up ammo / Zombie issues / Cannot kill barnacle</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
