<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>How to use the bug tracker</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/how-to-use-the-bug-tracker/11053</link>
    <description>I&#39;ve set up a bug tracker at [url=&#39;https://bitbucket.org/bmscd/black-mesa-source/issues/&#39;]this address[/url] in order to help developpers to solve bugs.

A BUG TRACKER IS NOT A FORUM.[/SIZE]

This is the main reason that I (and some other people too) think that this is NOT the right place to do bug reporting. There are, at the moment I&#39;m writing this, almost 3000 different issues reported, and an important part of them are duplicates.

Worse, it&#39;s almost impossible to mark these items as solved, or to assign them to some developer.

This is why I try to help BMS developers by using the appropriate tool.

You can help them too, by using this very same tool. NO ACCOUNT creation is required.[/SIZE] (you can use one of your already existing accounts)

And for those who are still in doubt, a [url=&#39;https://forums.blackmesasource.com/showpost.php?p=500449&amp;postcount=22&#39;]developer has already agreed[/url] that [url=&#39;https://forums.blackmesasource.com/showpost.php?p=500367&amp;postcount=21&#39;]it[/url] would be a better solution.

Oh and the guidelines for reporting bugs ([url=&#39;https://forums.blackmesasource.com/showthread.php?t=14063&#39;]#1[/url], [url=&#39;https://forums.blackmesasource.com/showthread.php?t=13000&#39;]#2[/url], [url=&#39;https://forums.blackmesasource.com/showthread.php?t=12513&#39;]#3[/url]) still apply to the bug tracker of course.



[align=center]• • •[/align]



So, now, how does the bug tracker really works ?[/SIZE]
Well, that&#39;s simple :

What&#39;s like the forum :

1. [url=&#39;https://bitbucket.org/account/signin/&#39;]Log In[/url] (using any provider you want, google, yahoo, AOL, etc. [url=&#39;https://forums.blackmesasource.com/showthread.php?p=504623#post504623&#39;]See here to know why[/url]).
1. [url=&#39;https://bitbucket.org/bmscd/black-mesa-source/issues/new&#39;]Create a new issue[/url].
1. Set a name for it.
1. Fill its content (description of the bug and related informations).
1. Attach files related to the said bug (select them ALL in one time in your browser dialog, or you won&#39;t be able to attach them more than one at a time).


What&#39;s NOT like the forum :

1. Set its TYPE. That means : tell if it&#39;s a bug, an enhancement, a proposal (these two are really similar; to help you choose, I&#39;d say : a proposal is a change that is not necessarily an enhancement), or a task. The latter is won&#39;t be used for the moment. 
1. Set the priority of the bug ACCORDING TO FACTS (and not to your liking. If everyone sets bugs to critical, it will take WAY more time to solve them, since the developers will have to sort them out first). That means :
[list=1]
[*]Blocker if you have to uninstall/reinstall the game to solve it.
1. Critical if it affects the whole game, like severe crashes that corrupt savegames, for example.
1. Major if it prevents you from continue playing (not PROGRESSING, that&#39;s a minor one if no crash happens), like a crash return-to-desktop (segmentation fault for example).
1. Minor if it is annoying (even really annoying) but doesn&#39;t crash the game.
1. Trivial if it&#39;s some cosmetic issue (like a weapon wrongly displayed or so)

Indeed these instructions are GUIDELINES and you&#39;re allowed to choose the severity of the bug according to your judgement.[/*:m]
[*]Set the affected component. If you don&#39;t know, let it as default.[/*:m]
[*]Set the version, which is, for now, 1.0.[/*:m][/list:o]

And in the end, validate the issue, of course.

[align=center]• • •[/align]

Let&#39;s help them making an even better mod!  :slight_smile: 

EDIT: Since mirroring all these bugs take a LOT of my time, I will NOT mirror additions made to these threads after my post saying to &quot;continue discussion on the bug tracker&quot;. Thank you very much.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2013 20:51:37 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>In-game Issues (Mod)</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/how-to-use-the-bug-tracker/11053.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>How to use the bug tracker</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[zorrinek]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Well, I’d shape the guidelines slightly differently:</p>
<p>trivial - issue is hardly noticeable<br>
minor - issue is noticeable, but does not have a serious impact on gameplay<br>
major - issue prevents the player from progressing or seriously affects his/her gameplay after progressing or is very noticeable and annoying<br>
critical - issue causes the game to crash or causes serious performance problems<br>
blocker - issue prevents the game from starting at all</p>
<p>Also issue status guide:</p>
<p>INVALID - described issue does not actually exist or affects only modded or otherwise altered game<br>
WONTFIX - developers decided not to fix this issue<br>
DUPLICATE - description covers an issue that was already posted earlier<br>
ON HOLD - issue is confirmed to exist, but it will not be fixed until additional information is provided<br>
RESOLVED - issue has been fixed<br>
OPEN - issue has been confirmed to exist and is awaiting an examination</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/how-to-use-the-bug-tracker/11053/52">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/how-to-use-the-bug-tracker/11053/52</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2013 20:51:37 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11053-52</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/how-to-use-the-bug-tracker/11053.rss">How to use the bug tracker</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How to use the bug tracker</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Flatline]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Dadster">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/d/e495f1/40.png" class="avatar"> Dadster:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I don’t think you’re grasping the overall long-term big picture.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>If anyone is not grasping the bigger picture (rather than focussing on the minutiae), its you. I would have thought that the last few posts would have made things clear to you, evidently not.</p>
<p>Have a free holiday on me, enjoy!</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/how-to-use-the-bug-tracker/11053/51">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/how-to-use-the-bug-tracker/11053/51</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2013 11:06:51 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11053-51</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/how-to-use-the-bug-tracker/11053.rss">How to use the bug tracker</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How to use the bug tracker</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Dadster]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Crypt19">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Crypt19:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Why is this a court case?<br>
They want to fix important bugs, not minor aesthetic blemishes. Why is this so difficult for you to grasp?</p>
<p><a href="https://i.imgur.com/XaEHTrc.jpg" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">This</a> is an aesthetic worth fixing ASAP. <a href="https://i.imgur.com/Gj3h0A1.jpg" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">This</a> however, can wait until the important stuff is fixed.</p>
<p>Labeling these minor bugs as WONTFIX for the time being keeps them from having to sift through your dozens of “bugs” in order to find actual issues that need solving.</p>
<p>Say you’ve got 30 errors causing users to crash, and you’ve got 70 gaps in railings. Which ones should be fixed <span class="bbcode-i">now</span>?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I don’t think you’re grasping the overall long-term big picture.</p>
<p>In response to your question, the 30 errors causing users to crash.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/how-to-use-the-bug-tracker/11053/50">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/how-to-use-the-bug-tracker/11053/50</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2013 10:49:50 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11053-50</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/how-to-use-the-bug-tracker/11053.rss">How to use the bug tracker</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How to use the bug tracker</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypt]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Why is this a court case?<br>
They want to fix important bugs, not minor aesthetic blemishes. Why is this so difficult for you to grasp?</p>
<p><a href="https://i.imgur.com/XaEHTrc.jpg" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">This</a> is an aesthetic worth fixing ASAP. <a href="https://i.imgur.com/Gj3h0A1.jpg" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">This</a> however, can wait until the important stuff is fixed.</p>
<p>Labeling these minor bugs as WONTFIX for the time being keeps them from having to sift through your dozens of “bugs” in order to find actual issues that need solving.</p>
<p>Say you’ve got 30 errors causing users to crash, and you’ve got 70 gaps in railings. Which ones should be fixed <span class="bbcode-i">now</span>?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/how-to-use-the-bug-tracker/11053/49">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/how-to-use-the-bug-tracker/11053/49</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2013 01:51:52 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11053-49</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/how-to-use-the-bug-tracker/11053.rss">How to use the bug tracker</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How to use the bug tracker</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Dadster]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Let me reply to some of the comments posted by your-name-here, in post <span class="hashtag">#49</span>, and JamesKane , in post <span class="hashtag">#50</span>, both situated on page 3 (which is partially clipping into page 4).</p>
<p>I’m not going to adopt an adversarial stance, concerning this discussion, as I think the two of you have.</p>
<p>In response to this excerpt from your-name-here, “185 of your bugs will not be fixed unless BMS is completely polished”. Contrary to other comments made by you and other BM Devs, are you stating that BMS will never be completely polished or polished to some noticeable visually improved state, that incorporates fixes pertaining to the bug reports that you have/will receive? That’s interesting.</p>
<p>In contrast to your observations, although I did use noclip early on in searching for bugs, as I’ve repeatedly stated recently, I’ve refrained from doing so, at your request, for sometime now. I’m using normal player movement and suit zoom to search out bugs. You keep overlooking this point.</p>
<p>You keep bringing up and hanging on to my now famous “a switch being in an unsafe place” issue. That was reported almost two months ago, early on in my bug reporting. At the time, I accepted your feedback, hence the reason why I haven’t reported anything similar since.</p>
<p>You keep stating that my bugs reports are taxing and causing you a serious loss of resources. That really is a load of bullcrap. My bug reports are detailed with carefully crafted screenshots, in order to assist you in easily comprehending and determining the nature of the bug. For the most part, no sooner had I submitted my bug report, your team almost immediately categorized it as WONTFIX, which was evident when I refreshed the bug-reporter page, after the submission of each bug report. You could not have gone into the game editor, or whatever you use to confirm the bug issue reported. As quickly as I was submitting them, you were identifying them as WONTFIX. This was happening right before my eyes, in real time, with minimal delay. Actually, it took less time for you to do this than it did for me to submit the bugs. You weren’t investing any appreciable amount of time in accomplishing this, contrary to your statements.</p>
<p>I guess this all boils down to what someone considers as game-breaking bugs. Your viewpoint is geared towards issues that crash the game or inhibit the player from progressing or using the assets that are available to him/her. On top of this, my viewpoint includes aesthetic and visual details that breaks the player’s game immersion factor, such as:</p>
<ul>
<li>textures that blink in and out of view.</li>
<li>similar assets/models that display different lighting characteristics.</li>
<li>handrails with gaps.</li>
<li>handrails that don’t contact walls.</li>
<li>pipe mounting brackets not adhered to surfaces (what’s the point of your pipe assets/models having mounting brackets if they’re not attached to anything?).</li>
<li>objects clipping into/through other objects (including the player).</li>
<li>objects floating in mid air.</li>
<li>inconsistencies in object placement, either within a map or other level(s).</li>
</ul>
<p>Going forward, I get your drift. I’ll endeavor to post bugs that don’t involve issues related to clipping, z-fighting or lighting issues, unless they are extreme/obvious in nature.</p>
<p>In reply to an excerpt from JamesKane, “The average player is not going to give two shits about a monitor prop floating… when he is shooting bees out of an aliens ass and having fun doing it”. I think all living species, whether human or not, expect a certain amount of decorum, decency and respect, when it comes to impacting pain onto ones private parts. Consider the discomfort if it was imparted onto you!</p>
<p>Maybe you Devs experienced this as a result of my numerous bug reports? If so, I sincerely apologize for not recognizing it sooner and causing you such discomfort, to your private parts.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/how-to-use-the-bug-tracker/11053/48">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/how-to-use-the-bug-tracker/11053/48</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2013 00:51:39 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11053-48</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/how-to-use-the-bug-tracker/11053.rss">How to use the bug tracker</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How to use the bug tracker</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[JamesKane]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Let me make this clear. We want bugs. We want crash reports. We want to help the community.<br>
However, wasting our time on bugs which do not improve the user experience is pointless.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>So, regarding bug-reports, because I care more about BMS than any other community member, I get singled out, discredited and ridiculed?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Dadster while I appreciate your enthusiasm. We will NOT and I repeat NOT spend our limited time fixing non-critical aesthetics “problems” which tickle your inner autism.</p>
<p>Instead of fixing potential real bugs we are faced with spending time closing ridiculous reports like a switch “being in a unsafe place” or a clipping brush no player would ever see because you have to no-clip to an area a player can never get to.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>You have a bug-tracker, however inadequate. I report what I deem or see as bugs. I get scolded, reprimanded, asked to refrain from reporting further bugs and to turn my focus/attentions onto other mods and locked out of gaining access to your bug-tracker on several occasions, even though, in the end, I was following your community published instructions. This whole scenario has left me shaking my head.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>We have a bug tracker to find and fix game breaking bugs, game-play nuisance, crash, warranted atheistic problems ( which are obvious when playing the game normally and not because you no-clipped or used artificially abilities ).</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Ask yourself before posting, would this bug hinder me or any other player from playing the game? If so, why? What does it do to prevent you from playing normally? </span></p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>Maybe you should post an updated status or outline for the whole community to see and understand and confirming the present state of affairs concerning the bug-tracker and reporting bugs, so that we’re ALL on the same page.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I agree. We are a small team whom are not working on this game full-time but rather during our “free” time. We are working on ways to provide updates and support through and for our community and should have something in the future.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>And why is it that a lowly community member needs to tell you that this action is necessary and would most likely be beneficial to everyone concerned?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>The average player is not going to give two shits about a monitor prop  floating two inches from its base when he is shooting bees out of an aliens ass and having fun doing it.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/how-to-use-the-bug-tracker/11053/47">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/how-to-use-the-bug-tracker/11053/47</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2013 21:59:55 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11053-47</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/how-to-use-the-bug-tracker/11053.rss">How to use the bug tracker</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How to use the bug tracker</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[your-name-here]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Dadster">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/d/e495f1/40.png" class="avatar"> Dadster:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>So, regarding bug-reports, because I care more about BMS than any other community member, I get singled out, discredited and ridiculed? With all due respect, that’s not great logic. It really doesn’t provide me with any comfort. You have a bug-tracker, however inadequate. I report what I deem or see as bugs. I get scolded, reprimanded, asked to refrain from reporting further bugs and to turn my focus/attentions onto other mods and locked out of gaining access to your bug-tracker on several occasions, even though, in the end, I was following your community published instructions. This whole scenario has left me shaking my head.</p>
<p>I guess I should take it as some sort of odd and twisted compliment and move on, as it seems that you’ve just relented and are now accepting ALL bug-reports, or am I misinterpreting this as well? If I start submitting bug reports in my usual manner, should I expect to be locked out of your bug-tracker again?</p>
<p>Maybe you should post an updated status or outline for the whole community to see and understand and confirming the present state of affairs concerning the bug-tracker and reporting bugs, so that we’re ALL on the same page.</p>
<p>And why is it that a lowly community member needs to tell you that this action is necessary and would most likely be beneficial to everyone concerned?</p>
<p>It’s really funny, here I am still looking out for your best interests, even after the way I’ve been treated. Take it as a sign that I’m still in your corner and an avid supporter of BMS, whether you like it or not.</p>
<p>To err is human, but forgiveness is a golden trait.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>You know what, I’m sorry; I should’ve worded my post differently. It was not a matter of singling you out, you just happened to be the only case in which a user had submitted 200+ bugs. You’re right, stormseeker did state “continue posting these bugs.” I’ll be honest with you though, I doubt we’ll have time to be fixing them (they’re extremely minor issues). My guess is he said this not to hurt your fragile feelings. I’m more of a fan of being direct. You’re a useful bug reporter and community member, but I think your efforts would be put to better use reporting <span class="bbcode-b">gameplay</span> bugs. If you still have questions on what that means, send me a private message.</p>
<p>And now, onto the good stuff:</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Dadster">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/d/e495f1/40.png" class="avatar"> Dadster:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>So, regarding bug-reports, because I care more about BMS than any other community member,</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I don’t think that’s a fair statement. # of bug reports != you being the most caring BMS community member.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Dadster">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/d/e495f1/40.png" class="avatar"> Dadster:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I get singled out, discredited and ridiculed? With all due respect, that’s not great logic.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Like I said (three times now), <span class="bbcode-b">nobody else</span> has 200+ bugs registered. You’re right, I could’ve worded it differently, but I can’t take that back now; What I want to draw your attention to are the statistics (facts) I posted previously. 185 of your bugs will not be fixed unless BMS is completely polished.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Dadster">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/d/e495f1/40.png" class="avatar"> Dadster:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I get scolded, reprimanded, asked to refrain from reporting further bugs and to turn my focus/attentions onto other mods and locked out of gaining access to your bug-tracker on several occasions</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I’ve sent you MULTIPLE private messages asking both nicely and bluntly to refrain from posting bugs that are related to clipping. I’ve made two MASSIVE posts about what we’d love to see (which you completely ignored). I have not had to do this for anyone else using our tracker. <span class="bbcode-b">Just you</span>.</p>
<p>I shut the tracker down (for everyone, not just you) because we had to triage the ton of bug reports you made. Your metric fuckton of bug reports crowds out everyone elses, which means more time spent WONTFIX’ing your stuff rather than actually resolving some crash reports.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Dadster">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/d/e495f1/40.png" class="avatar"> Dadster:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I guess I should take it as some sort of odd and twisted compliment and move on, as it seems that you’ve just relented and are now accepting ALL bug-reports, or am I misinterpreting this as well? If I start submitting bug reports in my usual manner, should I expect to be locked out of your bug-tracker again?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Believe me, this wasn’t intended to be a compliment, more of a “hey, stop it!” Let me be clear Dadster, please refrain from posting issues related to clipping, z-fighting, or prop placement. That clear enough for you? You pulled the same thing with TexFAMGUY1 and he also replied in a similar (albeit more polite) fashion.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Dadster">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/d/e495f1/40.png" class="avatar"> Dadster:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Maybe you should post an updated status or outline for the whole community to see and understand and confirming the present state of affairs concerning the bug-tracker and reporting bugs, so that we’re ALL on the same page.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>No no, I think everyone here is on the same page except you (which is why you have 185 clipping issues on the bug tracker and nobody else does).</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Dadster">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/d/e495f1/40.png" class="avatar"> Dadster:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>And why is it that a lowly community member needs to tell you that this action is necessary and would most likely be beneficial to everyone concerned?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>There is no such thing as a “lowly” community member. I consider everyone my equal which is why I won’t sugar coat bullshit  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=9" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Dadster">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/d/e495f1/40.png" class="avatar"> Dadster:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>It’s really funny, here I am still looking out for your best interests, even after the way I’ve been treated. Take it as a sign that I’m still in your corner and an avid supporter of BMS, whether you like it or not.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>As TexFAMGUY1 said, we owe you nothing and you owe us nothing. If I’ve offended you to the point where you don’t want to post bugs, feel free to stop. I’m not going to hold your hand and kiss your cuts and scrapes.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/how-to-use-the-bug-tracker/11053/46">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/how-to-use-the-bug-tracker/11053/46</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2013 21:22:35 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11053-46</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/how-to-use-the-bug-tracker/11053.rss">How to use the bug tracker</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How to use the bug tracker</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Dadster]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="your-name-here">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/y/e480ec/40.png" class="avatar"> your-name-here:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>OK. You win.</p>
<p>I should add, you’re the only person who has posted 200+ bugs which is why your name was dropped. If someone else had done the same thing, I would’ve used their name instead.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>So, regarding bug-reports, because I care more about BMS than any other community member, I get singled out, discredited and ridiculed? With all due respect, that’s not great logic. It really doesn’t provide me with any comfort. You have a bug-tracker, however inadequate. I report what I deem or see as bugs. I get scolded, reprimanded, asked to refrain from reporting further bugs and to turn my focus/attentions onto other mods and locked out of gaining access to your bug-tracker on several occasions, even though, in the end, I was following your community published instructions. This whole scenario has left me shaking my head.</p>
<p>I guess I should take it as some sort of odd and twisted compliment and move on, as it seems that you’ve just relented and are now accepting ALL bug-reports, or am I misinterpreting this as well? If I start submitting bug reports in my usual manner, should I expect to be locked out of your bug-tracker again?</p>
<p>Maybe you should post an updated status or outline for the whole community to see and understand and confirming the present state of affairs concerning the bug-tracker and reporting bugs, so that we’re ALL on the same page.</p>
<p>And why is it that a lowly community member needs to tell you that this action is necessary and would most likely be beneficial to everyone concerned?</p>
<p>It’s really funny, here I am still looking out for your best interests, even after the way I’ve been treated. Take it as a sign that I’m still in your corner and an avid supporter of BMS, whether you like it or not.</p>
<p>To err is human, but forgiveness is a golden trait.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/how-to-use-the-bug-tracker/11053/45">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/how-to-use-the-bug-tracker/11053/45</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2013 18:45:27 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11053-45</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/how-to-use-the-bug-tracker/11053.rss">How to use the bug tracker</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How to use the bug tracker</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[D3lta]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>^^Out of curiosity why don’t you start becoming a tester for companys?<br>
I’ve seen you litterally pointing out the smallest flaws.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/how-to-use-the-bug-tracker/11053/44">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/how-to-use-the-bug-tracker/11053/44</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2013 15:19:54 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11053-44</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/how-to-use-the-bug-tracker/11053.rss">How to use the bug tracker</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How to use the bug tracker</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[your-name-here]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Dadster">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/d/e495f1/40.png" class="avatar"> Dadster:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I harken back to an excerpt from post <span class="hashtag">#33</span> on page 2, by stormseeker, to the community.</p>
<p>“The tag “wontfix” is perhaps misleading, but consider it a temporary position that those lower priority issues will be placed in for reassessment later. The issues are still archived on the tracker and can be reopened when priorities are shifted”.</p>
<p>“Until then, please do continue to report these areas for enhancement, if I or John assign “wontfix” to it, don’t be offended, we’re simply streamlining trivials in preference to criticals and things that are more noticeable for the patch. I’ve spent 4 hours a day looking into each and every one of these bugs, in addition to my other work, each one has been assessed correctly and placed where it needs to be”.</p>
<p>Based on his comments/instructions, specifically “please do continue to report these areas for enhancement”, I resumed my normal bug report submissions, knowing full well that the majority of them would likely be tagged as WONTFIX. However, they would be cataloged/registered within the bug-tracker for your future reference and possible solution in subsequent future patches.</p>
<p>What is frustrating and unfair is that I am being discredited and singled out, as a result of following stormseeker’s recent instructions.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>OK. You win.</p>
<p>I should add, you’re the only person who has posted 200+ bugs which is why your name was dropped. If someone else had done the same thing, I would’ve used their name instead.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/how-to-use-the-bug-tracker/11053/43">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/how-to-use-the-bug-tracker/11053/43</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2013 15:18:43 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11053-43</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/how-to-use-the-bug-tracker/11053.rss">How to use the bug tracker</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How to use the bug tracker</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Dadster]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I harken back to an excerpt from post <span class="hashtag">#33</span> on page 2, by stormseeker, to the community.</p>
<p>“The tag “wontfix” is perhaps misleading, but consider it a temporary position that those lower priority issues will be placed in for reassessment later. The issues are still archived on the tracker and can be reopened when priorities are shifted”.</p>
<p>“Until then, please do continue to report these areas for enhancement, if I or John assign “wontfix” to it, don’t be offended, we’re simply streamlining trivials in preference to criticals and things that are more noticeable for the patch. I’ve spent 4 hours a day looking into each and every one of these bugs, in addition to my other work, each one has been assessed correctly and placed where it needs to be”.</p>
<p>Based on his comments/instructions, specifically “please do continue to report these areas for enhancement”, I resumed my normal bug report submissions, knowing full well that the majority of them would likely be tagged as WONTFIX. However, they would be cataloged/registered within the bug-tracker for your future reference and possible solution in subsequent future patches.</p>
<p>What is frustrating and unfair is that I am being discredited and singled out, as a result of following stormseeker’s recent instructions.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/how-to-use-the-bug-tracker/11053/42">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/how-to-use-the-bug-tracker/11053/42</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2013 15:00:27 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11053-42</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/how-to-use-the-bug-tracker/11053.rss">How to use the bug tracker</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How to use the bug tracker</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[your-name-here]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Dadster">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/d/e495f1/40.png" class="avatar"> Dadster:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>So much for your concerns about not being rude. Any particular reason why you’re singling out and ripping me apart, in a post originally submitted by TurboTsunami, concerning revamping/updating/redesigning the bug-tracker?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Yeah, because my original post was about how we’re dealing with a sheer number of bug reports that aren’t useful to which TurboTsunami’s reply was ‘Make a new tracker!’ You’re the one who submitted them so I made mention of that.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Dadster">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/d/e495f1/40.png" class="avatar"> Dadster:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Respectfully, I take issue with your comment that “Everyone else has been reporting awesome issues that are definitely problems. Dadster’s reports on the other hand, consist of objects being off by three units, or safety problems such as switches being too close to a ledge”. These two examples are by far, far in the minority and were put forth more as proposals, rather than bug-fixes.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Doing a cursory search for ‘clip into’ on the bug tracker yields <a href="https://bitbucket.org/bmscd/black-mesa-source/issue/728/electrical-cables-clip-into-face-of-data" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">24 results</a>. Go do a search for all of your bugs. A huge portion of them are minor issues that aren’t reasonable to fix.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Dadster">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/d/e495f1/40.png" class="avatar"> Dadster:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Obviously, I’d like to think that I’ve also “reported awesome issues that are definitely problems”, just like the rest of the community, as is evidenced by the fact that dozens of bugs-issues that I have reported were actually accepted and have been “RESOLVED” by your team. Let’s not lose sight of this fact, and make it appear or suggest that ALL of my bug submissions are nonsensical. That would be an inaccurate statement or conclusion on your part.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Out of the <a href="https://bitbucket.org/bmscd/black-mesa-source/issues?reported_by=~BM-Eye" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">263</a> bugs you have reported:</p>
<ul>
<li>
<a href="https://bitbucket.org/bmscd/black-mesa-source/issues?reported_by=~BM-Eye&amp;status=resolved" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">47</a> were marked RESOLVED.</li>
<li>
<a href="https://bitbucket.org/bmscd/black-mesa-source/issues?reported_by=~BM-Eye&amp;status=wontfix" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">185</a> are marked WONTFIX, virtually all of which are minor visual problems.</li>
<li>
<a href="https://bitbucket.org/bmscd/black-mesa-source/issues?reported_by=~BM-Eye&amp;status=new" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">9</a> are marked as new.</li>
<li>
<a href="https://bitbucket.org/bmscd/black-mesa-source/issues?reported_by=~BM-Eye&amp;status=duplicate" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">11</a> are duplicates.</li>
</ul>
<p>Note: None of those 263 issues are gameplay or crash issues.</p>
<p>As you can see, the RESOLVED vs WONTFIX count is vastly different. Why are 185 of your issues marked WONTFIX? We clearly marked issues we fixed with RESOLVED. The only conclusion left is that 185 of your bug reports are things we don’t feel we want to / can fix. We triaged every single one of your 263 bug reports. That takes a lot of time which was my gripe in the original post I made to which TurboTsunami replied (Well make a new bug tracker, duh!).  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=9" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
<p>There is a reason why both TexFAMGUY1 and I reacted the same way to your reports Dadster. Both he, myself, and even stormseeker to an extent spent a time attempting to tell you why we’re ignoring visual issues.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Dadster">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/d/e495f1/40.png" class="avatar"> Dadster:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I think I should be afforded some amount of appreciation and/or credit, and not made out to be the bad guy, in my efforts to improve BMS.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I’m not trying to make you out to be the bad guy. I griped about the bug tracker and you happened to be the reason why. No harm no foul.</p>
<p>I guess the final word on the tracker is, we are working through bug tracker issues at a steady pace. If we deem that its necessary to install a new tracker, we’ll let everyone know. Right now, it is easier (and cheaper) to use a free service like bitbucket.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/how-to-use-the-bug-tracker/11053/41">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/how-to-use-the-bug-tracker/11053/41</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2013 14:03:15 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11053-41</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/how-to-use-the-bug-tracker/11053.rss">How to use the bug tracker</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How to use the bug tracker</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Dadster]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="your-name-here">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/y/e480ec/40.png" class="avatar"> your-name-here:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Look bro, I think there has been a miscommunication here. My problem is not with the volume of bug reports. It’s with the volume of bug reports <span class="bbcode-b">from Dadster</span>. Everyone else has been reporting awesome issues that are definitely problems. Dadster’s reports on the other hand, consist of objects being off by three units, or safety problems such as switches being too close to a ledge. I’ll open the bug tracker and he’ll literally post 50/60 bugs within 5-6 hours about stuff that we honestly can’t easily fix.</p>
<p>I don’t have a 4-5 hour chunk of free time to setup an entirely new bug tracker, configure it, and test it. We’re not getting paid to work on this project. Doing stuff like this takes away time from my real job and my family.</p>
<p>Quite frankly, this really isn’t your problem, so no need to worry about it  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=9" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>So much for your concerns about not being rude. Any particular reason why you’re singling out and ripping me apart, in a post originally submitted by TurboTsunami, concerning revamping/updating/redesigning the bug-tracker?</p>
<p>Respectfully, I take issue with your comment that “Everyone else has been reporting awesome issues that are definitely problems. Dadster’s reports on the other hand, consist of objects being off by three units, or safety problems such as switches being too close to a ledge”. These two examples are by far, far in the minority and were put forth more as proposals, rather than bug-fixes.</p>
<p>Obviously, I’d like to think that I’ve also “reported awesome issues that are definitely problems”, just like the rest of the community, as is evidenced by the fact that dozens of bugs-issues that I have reported were actually accepted and have been “RESOLVED” by your team. Let’s not lose sight of this fact, and make it appear or suggest that ALL of my bug submissions are nonsensical, as you have done. That would be an inaccurate statement or conclusion on your part.</p>
<p>I think I should be afforded some amount of appreciation or credit in my efforts to improve BMS, and not made out to be the bad guy.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/how-to-use-the-bug-tracker/11053/40">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/how-to-use-the-bug-tracker/11053/40</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2013 13:24:26 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11053-40</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/how-to-use-the-bug-tracker/11053.rss">How to use the bug tracker</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How to use the bug tracker</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[your-name-here]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="TurboTsunami">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 TurboTsunami:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>But you had the time to read through all of these forum topics? I doubt that this took you less time than setting up a bugtracker when i was asking about it back in september.</p>
<p>You should be prepared for another huge wave of bugreports after the release of the first patch. I still don’t get the point in waiting?<br>
You guys will have a lot more work with reading topics on the forums and bug reports on the “unofficial” bugtracker. Also there will be much more identical reports to sort out again.</p>
<p>It’s better to invest the time now, before you release any patch, isn’t it?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Look bro, I think there has been a miscommunication here. My problem is not with the volume of bug reports. It’s with the volume of bug reports <span class="bbcode-b">from Dadster</span>. Everyone else has been reporting awesome issues that are definitely problems. Dadster’s reports on the other hand, consist of objects being off by three units, or safety problems such as switches being too close to a ledge. I’ll open the bug tracker and he’ll literally post 50/60 bugs within 5-6 hours about stuff that we honestly can’t easily fix.</p>
<p>I don’t have a 4-5 hour chunk of free time to setup an entirely new bug tracker, configure it, and test it. We’re not getting paid to work on this project. Doing stuff like this takes away time from my real job and my family.</p>
<p>Quite frankly, this really isn’t your problem, so no need to worry about it  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=9" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/how-to-use-the-bug-tracker/11053/39">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/how-to-use-the-bug-tracker/11053/39</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2013 11:48:52 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11053-39</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/how-to-use-the-bug-tracker/11053.rss">How to use the bug tracker</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How to use the bug tracker</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Quetejodan]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="your-name-here">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/y/e480ec/40.png" class="avatar"> your-name-here:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>and setting one up on our own webspace takes <span class="bbcode-b">time</span>. We don’t have that right now.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>But you had the time to read through all of these forum topics? I doubt that this took you less time than setting up a bugtracker when i was asking about it back in september.</p>
<p>You should be prepared for another huge wave of bugreports after the release of the first patch. I still don’t get the point in waiting?<br>
You guys will have a lot more work with reading topics on the forums and bug reports on the “unofficial” bugtracker. Also there will be much more identical reports to sort out again.</p>
<p>It’s better to invest the time now, before you release any patch, isn’t it?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/how-to-use-the-bug-tracker/11053/38">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/how-to-use-the-bug-tracker/11053/38</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2013 21:30:54 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11053-38</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/how-to-use-the-bug-tracker/11053.rss">How to use the bug tracker</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How to use the bug tracker</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[your-name-here]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="TurboTsunami">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 TurboTsunami:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>As i <a href="https://forums.blackmesasource.com/showpost.php?p=492378&amp;postcount=2" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">said</a> many month ago, only two days after you opened the Bug Reporting Forums, i would recommend to install your own bugtracker on your webspace.<br>
That would give you much more control over the tracker and the bug-reporting.</p>
<p>I simply dont get the point with the forums at all. Many month have passed and the forums are still open for submissions. Why?<br>
It’s not a good idea to have two places for something like bug reporting, and a forum isn’t suitable for this at all.</p>
<p>What you should do: close the bug reporting forums, install your own bugtracker, integrate it to your website and benefit from something, that is designed for your needs.<br>
This way you will also get your &gt;&gt;&gt;official&lt;&lt;&lt; solution.</p>
<p>You should have done this long ago, but better now than never? Your choice.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>First off, there’s no reason to be so curt. Secondly, I wasn’t even on the team when this bug tracker was setup, and setting one up on our own webspace takes <span class="bbcode-b">time</span>. We don’t have that right now. I will agree that having two places to report bugs might get confusing, but I think we’re managing just fine.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/how-to-use-the-bug-tracker/11053/37">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/how-to-use-the-bug-tracker/11053/37</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2013 16:05:06 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11053-37</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/how-to-use-the-bug-tracker/11053.rss">How to use the bug tracker</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How to use the bug tracker</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Quetejodan]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="your-name-here">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/y/e480ec/40.png" class="avatar"> your-name-here:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Considering the fact that I can’t mass change bug status which is a core feature to any other bug tracker, I’m going to discuss moving to another online solution to deal with bugs.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>As i <a href="https://forums.blackmesasource.com/showpost.php?p=492378&amp;postcount=2" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">said</a> many month ago, only two days after you opened the Bug Reporting Forums, i would recommend to install your own bugtracker on your webspace.<br>
That would give you much more control over the tracker and the bug-reporting.</p>
<p>I simply dont get the point with the forums at all. Many month have passed and the forums are still open for submissions. Why?<br>
It’s not a good idea to have two places for something like bug reporting, and a forum isn’t suitable for this at all.</p>
<p>What you should do: close the bug reporting forums, install your own bugtracker, integrate it to your website and benefit from something, that is designed for your needs.<br>
This way you will also get your &gt;&gt;&gt;official&lt;&lt;&lt; solution.</p>
<p>You should have done this long ago, but better now than never? Your choice.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/how-to-use-the-bug-tracker/11053/36">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/how-to-use-the-bug-tracker/11053/36</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2013 13:07:48 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11053-36</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/how-to-use-the-bug-tracker/11053.rss">How to use the bug tracker</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How to use the bug tracker</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[your-name-here]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Dadster">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/d/e495f1/40.png" class="avatar"> Dadster:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>It’s poor foresight and community education on your part that an explanation as to the change in categorizing most of the issues reported through the bug tracker to a “WONTFIX” status, was prompted only after an inquiry by imadoofus, questioning you as to why this was the case.</p>
<p>Although your detailed explanation is certainly welcomed, it should have been posted 6 days ago, when this change in the manner in which you handle bug reports was initially instigated.</p>
<p>It would have saved the BM community the potential angst, demoralization and frustration that our efforts were not being appreciated, availed of, and hopefully and eventually acted upon, working in tandem with you towards the overall betterment of the BMS mod.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="stormseeker">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/user_avatar/leakfree.org/stormseeker/40/4396_2.png" class="avatar"> stormseeker:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>This issue has been discussed well in advance before by other team members, specifically with you regarding these trivial enhancement reports as seen earlier in this thread, and in private communications with you.</p>
<p>The vast majority of those bugs temporarily placed in “wontfix” status are in fact related to your reports, and not the community as a whole. Despite having had several lengthy pieces of advice from other members of the team on what to report and what not to report. I was requested to remedy the situation and come up with a solution, this is the most efficient solution I can think of currently within the limitations of this particular bugtracker, and I make no apology for that.</p>
<p>The vast majority of bugs reported by the rest of the community have in fact been relevant, I refer you to the initial post on “how to report an issue”</p>
<p><a href="https://forums.blackmesasource.com/showpost.php?p=488838&amp;postcount=1" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://forums.blackmesasource.com/showpost.php?p=488838&amp;postcount=1</a></p>
<p>Crashes:</p>
<pre><code>Every time the game crashes, it will create an MDMP (minidump) file in your SteamApps\username\source sdk base 2007 folder. Your crash will be the newest entry in that folder. If you attach the file to your report, it will help us track down and solve the issue.
</code></pre>
<p>Performance Issues:</p>
<pre><code>If you have generally low performance, try decreasing your graphical settings. If your computer is lower-end, you should be lowering the display resolution, dropping the texture detail and disabling settings such as anti-aliasing. If you're getting noticeably worse performance than usual in one particular area, grab a screenshot of the problematic area with the showbudget panel enabled so we know where to start.
</code></pre>
<p>Glitches:</p>
<pre><code>If you find something that doesn't behave as intended or you would expect, grab a screenshot and getpos information.
Type 'status' into your console and get the map name.
Type 'getpos' into your console, and copy-paste the co-ordinates it spits out.
Explain in your post what you were doing, what you thought should happen, and what did happen.
</code></pre>
<p>Exploits:</p>
<pre><code>If you find that a weapon or NPC can be exploited, write down what you did and how you did it. If you find a portion of a map that can be exploited, grab a screenshot and getpos information (as above) and explain what you did and how you did it.
</code></pre>
<p>Whilst I appreciate that enhancements would be ideally included in patch 1.0, and I personally welcome them all being highlighted for future review in later patches, I considered the advice above to be pretty clear, and for the most part everyone has followed it, placed as it was in order to attempt to avoid overly trivial bugs being reported, bulking the bug tracker and making critical and major issues that need direct attention hard to find. I wasn’t aware however that the community needed additional “education” on this issue after Raminators official post.</p>
<p>I regret that you have been caused personal angst by this situation, and assure you that your efforts are in fact appreciated and considered useful by the level design team. However it is neccesary at the current time to concentrate on critical bugs and things that are plainly obvious, hence the setup of Raminators post. It does in fact take a considerable amount of time to test each bug report to verify the bug is reproducable and/or noticeable enough to qualify as a patch candidate.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>To sum this all up, please refrain from posting clipping, lighting, or z-fighting issues. I doubt we’ll ever address half of those (strictly because we have so much more work to do). They’re incredibly minor, don’t affect gameplay, and distract us from major issues like weapon bugs / crashes.  We hold those in much higher priority than clipping / z-fighting / lighting problems.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/how-to-use-the-bug-tracker/11053/35">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/how-to-use-the-bug-tracker/11053/35</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2013 16:54:41 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11053-35</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/how-to-use-the-bug-tracker/11053.rss">How to use the bug tracker</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How to use the bug tracker</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Dadster]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>It’s poor foresight and community education on your part that an explanation as to the change in categorizing most of the issues reported through the bug tracker to a “WONTFIX” status, was prompted only after an inquiry by imadoofus, questioning you as to why this was the case.</p>
<p>Although your detailed explanation is certainly welcomed, it should have been posted 6 days ago, when this change in the manner in which you handle bug reports was initially instigated.</p>
<p>It would have saved the BM community the potential angst, demoralization and frustration that our efforts were not being appreciated, availed of, and hopefully and eventually acted upon, working in tandem with you towards the overall betterment of the BMS mod.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/how-to-use-the-bug-tracker/11053/34">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/how-to-use-the-bug-tracker/11053/34</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2013 17:41:55 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11053-34</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/how-to-use-the-bug-tracker/11053.rss">How to use the bug tracker</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How to use the bug tracker</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[imadoofus]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Oh, I see. Sorry for the mixup.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/how-to-use-the-bug-tracker/11053/33">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/how-to-use-the-bug-tracker/11053/33</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2013 19:52:13 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11053-33</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/how-to-use-the-bug-tracker/11053.rss">How to use the bug tracker</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How to use the bug tracker</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[imadoofus]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>It’s amazing how many “very minor” wontfixes there are lately. Not to dis the developers, but if I spent six years on a mod, I wouldn’t care how minor something was. I’d still fix it.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/how-to-use-the-bug-tracker/11053/32">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/how-to-use-the-bug-tracker/11053/32</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2013 15:18:39 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11053-32</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/how-to-use-the-bug-tracker/11053.rss">How to use the bug tracker</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How to use the bug tracker</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[your-name-here]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Dadster">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/d/e495f1/40.png" class="avatar"> Dadster:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>@ your-name-here</p>
<p>Within your bug reporting outline post to me, “Stuff We Care About”, you used issue <span class="hashtag">#368</span> as an example of a desirable “fixable” bug, as follows:</p>
<p><a href="https://bitbucket.org/bmscd/black-mesa-source/issue/368/plants-grasses-clipping-through-sidewalks" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://bitbucket.org/bmscd/black-mesa-source/issue/368/plants-grasses-clipping-through-sidewalks</a><br>
“Same deal here. Ask yourself, are the curb and plant affected by in-game physics? No they’re not so that’s yet another issue we’ll need to fix”.</p>
<p>In fact, issue <span class="hashtag">#368</span> has been categorized as “WONTFIX”. As you can imagine, I’m a bit confused. Can you please give me your definitive comments/position concerning grass/plant clipping issues. There are far more noticeable and worse occurrences than issue <span class="hashtag">#368</span>, especially with plants, that exist in the outdoor areas.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Read the bug report again. John Welsh has given you the answer. Just because I said you should report a bug doesn’t mean it will be fixed. For example, I was not aware that the grass was procedurally generated. I would have figured that out after you have posted the bug as I would need to look into the cause of the issue.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/how-to-use-the-bug-tracker/11053/31">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/how-to-use-the-bug-tracker/11053/31</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2013 10:19:05 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11053-31</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/how-to-use-the-bug-tracker/11053.rss">How to use the bug tracker</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How to use the bug tracker</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Dadster]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>@ your-name-here</p>
<p>Within your bug reporting outline post to me, “Stuff We Care About”, you used issue <span class="hashtag">#368</span> as an example of a desirable “fixable” bug, as follows:</p>
<p><a href="https://bitbucket.org/bmscd/black-mesa-source/issue/368/plants-grasses-clipping-through-sidewalks" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://bitbucket.org/bmscd/black-mesa-source/issue/368/plants-grasses-clipping-through-sidewalks</a><br>
“Same deal here. Ask yourself, are the curb and plant affected by in-game physics? No they’re not so that’s yet another issue we’ll need to fix”.</p>
<p>In fact, issue <span class="hashtag">#368</span> has been categorized as “WONTFIX”. As you can imagine, I’m a bit confused. Can you please give me your definitive comments/position concerning grass/plant clipping issues. There are far more noticeable and worse occurrences than issue <span class="hashtag">#368</span>, especially with plants, that exist in the outdoor areas.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/how-to-use-the-bug-tracker/11053/30">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/how-to-use-the-bug-tracker/11053/30</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2013 19:06:11 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11053-30</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/how-to-use-the-bug-tracker/11053.rss">How to use the bug tracker</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How to use the bug tracker</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Chickenprotector]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="your-name-here">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/y/e480ec/40.png" class="avatar"> your-name-here:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>What can I do? This unfortunately is one of the annoyances that comes with a bug tracker. I don’t think there is any bug tracker that allows me to ‘describe’ a category. And even if I did, it requires that the submitter actually click more buttons to go and read the descriptions. We can’t even get people to read the stickies on the forum haha. If you have a suggestion, post it here.  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=9" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Poke <a href="https://forums.blackmesasource.com/member.php?u=1" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Hubicorn</a> or another site admin until he or they give you a sub forum for exactly this. It worked with the mapping sub-forum but that was with lobbying from the Moderators. It would make life easier for most of us to merge it to the forum anyway.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/how-to-use-the-bug-tracker/11053/29">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/how-to-use-the-bug-tracker/11053/29</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 09 Mar 2013 03:46:34 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11053-29</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/how-to-use-the-bug-tracker/11053.rss">How to use the bug tracker</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How to use the bug tracker</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Dadster]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="your-name-here">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/y/e480ec/40.png" class="avatar"> your-name-here:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>What can I do? This unfortunately is one of the annoyances that comes with a bug tracker. I don’t think there is any bug tracker that allows me to ‘describe’ a category. And even if I did, it requires that the submitter actually click more buttons to go and read the descriptions. We can’t even get people to read the stickies on the forum haha. If you have a suggestion, post it here.  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=9" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Only thing I can think of is not to have the bug submitter select a category at all, and have your moderators correctly categorize the bug after it’s been submitted. Don’t know if that’s workable and it does mean a little more work for your moderators, but this is something that they’re already doing, to some extent. Or maybe have an “Unknown” or “Uncertain” category? A moderator can then open up that category and select the proper category for each reported bug.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/how-to-use-the-bug-tracker/11053/28">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/how-to-use-the-bug-tracker/11053/28</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2013 02:00:19 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11053-28</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/how-to-use-the-bug-tracker/11053.rss">How to use the bug tracker</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
