<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Remix Competition Entry</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/remix-competition-entry/7059</link>
    <description>So, I found out there&#39;s an official Daft Punk/Tron Lecacy remix contest on Indaba Music and made my own remix of Derezzed.

Now, you all will probably think I&#39;m just whoring for votes and expecting everybody to blindly vote for me. In that case, you&#39;re wrong. I ask you to just listen to my track and some other tracks submitted and THEN, if you like it or think it deserves better ranking (91st of 890), vote for it. Most of you probably didn&#39;t know about this contest anyway.

So here&#39;s the track. It&#39;s something between dubstep and electro house but I suck at genres so don&#39;t get all mad about it. Just listen and tell me how it makes you feel.

[url]https://www.indabamusic.com/opportunities/tron/submissions/54648[/url]


Here&#39;s also my youtube channel, most of my other music is available there.

[url]https://www.youtube.com/user/DpbProductionz?feature=mhum[/url]</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 03 May 2011 21:17:09 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Show Off</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/remix-competition-entry/7059.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Remix Competition Entry</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Wombat]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>So, I found out there’s an official Daft Punk/Tron Lecacy remix contest on Indaba Music and made my own remix of Derezzed.</p>
<p>Now, you all will probably think I’m just whoring for votes and expecting everybody to blindly vote for me. In that case, you’re wrong. I ask you to just listen to my track and some other tracks submitted and THEN, if you like it or think it deserves better ranking (91st of 890), vote for it. Most of you probably didn’t know about this contest anyway.</p>
<p>So here’s the track. It’s something between dubstep and electro house but I suck at genres so don’t get all mad about it. Just listen and tell me how it makes you feel.</p>
<p><a href="https://www.indabamusic.com/opportunities/tron/submissions/54648" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://www.indabamusic.com/opportunities/tron/submissions/54648</a></p>
<p>Here’s also my youtube channel, most of my other music is available there.</p>
<p><a href="https://www.youtube.com/user/DpbProductionz?feature=mhum" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://www.youtube.com/user/DpbProductionz?feature=mhum</a></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/remix-competition-entry/7059/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/remix-competition-entry/7059/1</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 03 May 2011 21:17:09 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7059-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/remix-competition-entry/7059.rss">Remix Competition Entry</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
