<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Suggestions for Game Improvement/Tweaks</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/suggestions-for-game-improvement-tweaks/10349</link>
    <description>I have made this thread so that I and others can report different problems that we think make the game worse, and post suggestions for how we think it can be made better.

My list is gathered from things I have encountered in-game and some things that the community has reported on these forums.   I will update this in the future as I continue to replay and examine the game.

I have generally organized my list with the problem followed by the suggested fix in parenthesis. 
General suggestion withought specific problems are preceded and finished with {}.   
Problems preceded by -- are generally related to the previous line.
Many of the things on this list are minor, I have tried to keep the suggested fixes as realistically plausible/achievable as possible.

Feel free to post your suggestions for things that can improve the game.  Also feel free to criticize my list.


My list:


General:

- Jumping height is too short, leads to frustration in general and for certain jumping puzzles. (Raise jumping height, could use hl2&#39;s settins for jumping)

- Animation for crowbar is unnatural/swings too fast. (Replace with hl2&#39;s animation)

- Glock fires too fast. (Add short delay between each shot/perhaps make a tiny bit more powerful?)

- Crosshair for grenades is very difficult to see. (Enlarge crosshair)

	--Grenades also are thrown too high. (Make thrown grenades fly straighter, like in hl2)

- In general, hecu grunts will single you out even if other enemies are present (I don&#39;t know what causes this)

- {Not necessarily a problem, but perhaps there could be more instances of the military troops fighting xen on the ground, also hecu grunts dont throw grenades.  [At least I havent seen it]}



In Residue Processing:

	- Some members of the forum report confusion in the room with many conveyor belts.  I will take a closer look at this area later.


In Surface Tenstion:


	- The helicopter encuonter in the cliff section takes too many hits to take down. (Reduce # of hits required to take it down.)  

		--Side Note: There could be some possible confusion for new players with the ammo resupply crate, they may not know they can interact with it.
 		  (Consider having another instance of it earlier in the game.)

		--Animation for helicopter crash is a bit strange. (make animation look more realistic)

	- Not enough cover in area where player first meets the tank, after the cliff scaling section (adding cover that can perhaps be
	  destroyed by the tank, forcing player to move.) 

	
	- In section with the tripmined building, before reaching the room with the elevator in the middle, those single tripmines in 
	  the hall shouldn&#39;t destroy the whole building / fade to white / be instant failure. (Make those tripmines with crates cause normal
	  damage.)


	-Gargantua section:	

		-- Gargantua ingnores the marines that shot at you through the vent. (Have the gargantua dispatch the marines first
	   	   {preferably in a very brutal and cinematic nature.})

		-- In area with the artillery, it is unclear that one is supposed to shoot the radio tower, the first reaction for most
		   is to shoot the gate.  In general very little is destructible in the scene. (Create a cinematic physics 
		   destruction for the gate when hit with artillery/ or make objective of hitting the tower more obvious.)

		--{Perhaps Gargantuam could eventuall break/ topple the tower if the player fails to kill it within certain amount of time.}

In Forget About Freeman:

	- The area where player meets second tank in the level is awkward, the proxitiy of the tank and its inability to fire on close targets leads 
	  	   to xen enemies defeating soldiers in the room and then running close to the tank and attacking it, otherwise ignoring the
	 	   player. 
 
		-- Soldiers have opposite problem they will ignore xen enemies and instead attack you if they see you in this area, though this is also a problem throughout the game, soldiers will generally single player out.

		--(Perhaps this specific area/room is in need of re-structuring)</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 16 Sep 2012 19:05:46 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>The Cafeteria</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/suggestions-for-game-improvement-tweaks/10349.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Suggestions for Game Improvement/Tweaks</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[arizzi]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I have made this thread so that I and others can report different problems that we think make the game worse, and post suggestions for how we think it can be made better.</p>
<p>My list is gathered from things I have encountered in-game and some things that the community has reported on these forums.   I will update this in the future as I continue to replay and examine the game.</p>
<p>I have generally organized my list with the problem followed by the suggested fix in parenthesis.<br>
General suggestion withought specific problems are preceded and finished with {}.<br>
Problems preceded by – are generally related to the previous line.<br>
Many of the things on this list are minor, I have tried to keep the suggested fixes as realistically plausible/achievable as possible.</p>
<p>Feel free to post your suggestions for things that can improve the game.  Also feel free to criticize my list.</p>
<p>My list:</p>
<p>General:</p>
<ul>
<li>
<p>Jumping height is too short, leads to frustration in general and for certain jumping puzzles. (Raise jumping height, could use hl2’s settins for jumping)</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Animation for crowbar is unnatural/swings too fast. (Replace with hl2’s animation)</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Glock fires too fast. (Add short delay between each shot/perhaps make a tiny bit more powerful?)</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Crosshair for grenades is very difficult to see. (Enlarge crosshair)</p>
<p>–Grenades also are thrown too high. (Make thrown grenades fly straighter, like in hl2)</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>In general, hecu grunts will single you out even if other enemies are present (I don’t know what causes this)</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>{Not necessarily a problem, but perhaps there could be more instances of the military troops fighting xen on the ground, also hecu grunts dont throw grenades.  [At least I havent seen it]}</p>
</li>
</ul>
<p>In Residue Processing:</p>
<pre><code>- Some members of the forum report confusion in the room with many conveyor belts.  I will take a closer look at this area later.
</code></pre>
<p>In Surface Tenstion:</p>
<pre><code>- The helicopter encuonter in the cliff section takes too many hits to take down. (Reduce # of hits required to take it down.)  

	--Side Note: There could be some possible confusion for new players with the ammo resupply crate, they may not know they can interact with it.
	  (Consider having another instance of it earlier in the game.)

	--Animation for helicopter crash is a bit strange. (make animation look more realistic)

- Not enough cover in area where player first meets the tank, after the cliff scaling section (adding cover that can perhaps be
  destroyed by the tank, forcing player to move.) 


- In section with the tripmined building, before reaching the room with the elevator in the middle, those single tripmines in 
  the hall shouldn't destroy the whole building / fade to white / be instant failure. (Make those tripmines with crates cause normal
  damage.)


-Gargantua section:	

	-- Gargantua ingnores the marines that shot at you through the vent. (Have the gargantua dispatch the marines first
   	   {preferably in a very brutal and cinematic nature.})

	-- In area with the artillery, it is unclear that one is supposed to shoot the radio tower, the first reaction for most
	   is to shoot the gate.  In general very little is destructible in the scene. (Create a cinematic physics 
	   destruction for the gate when hit with artillery/ or make objective of hitting the tower more obvious.)

	--{Perhaps Gargantuam could eventuall break/ topple the tower if the player fails to kill it within certain amount of time.}
</code></pre>
<p>In Forget About Freeman:</p>
<pre><code>- The area where player meets second tank in the level is awkward, the proxitiy of the tank and its inability to fire on close targets leads 
  	   to xen enemies defeating soldiers in the room and then running close to the tank and attacking it, otherwise ignoring the
 	   player. 

	-- Soldiers have opposite problem they will ignore xen enemies and instead attack you if they see you in this area, though this is also a problem throughout the game, soldiers will generally single player out.

	--(Perhaps this specific area/room is in need of re-structuring)</code></pre>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/suggestions-for-game-improvement-tweaks/10349/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/suggestions-for-game-improvement-tweaks/10349/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 16 Sep 2012 19:05:46 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-10349-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/suggestions-for-game-improvement-tweaks/10349.rss">Suggestions for Game Improvement/Tweaks</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
