<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>A question to devs regarding modifying particle effects.</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/a-question-to-devs-regarding-modifying-particle-effects/14600</link>
    <description>Hey folks, i&#39;ve been asking few questions in store page discussions, but seems like noone reads them or something, so i&#39;ll ask here.

I am not sure what you did, but i can&#39;t replace particle effects, no matter how i try. I made new explosion particle ( grenade_explosion_01 ), i made an addon for it, and put few sounds to test. Sounds work fine, but not particle effect, it&#39;s default. I tried to replace .pcf file with mine in bms particles folder, but still no luck, even if i remove bms particles folder it doesn&#39;t matter. It&#39;s like game is told to use only particles from bms_misc, which is really lame for me, because i can&#39;t do anything with particles, and i planned so much. I am currently working on a HL1 explosion recreation on BM, here&#39;s work in progress video of it :

[youtu.be/4w71d5gVreE](https://youtu.be/4w71d5gVreE)

Do you have any solution or will this be &quot;fixed&quot; in the next patch? It would be also great if you could control which particle to spawn via script file, so i could randomize explosions too, if you can add that that&#39;ll be great. Also if you could delete the leftovers of old explosion from the particle explosion - that will be great.

Another question is, in-game tools are not available, i treid to launch the game with -tool -nop4, but nothing happens.

Thanks.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 17 Jan 2016 22:57:40 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Black Mesa</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/a-question-to-devs-regarding-modifying-particle-effects/14600.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>A question to devs regarding modifying particle effects.</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[subatomic]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Expecting an instant reply when it’s the weekend and these guys have regular jobs and families and stuff is unfair. Patience works wonders.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/a-question-to-devs-regarding-modifying-particle-effects/14600/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/a-question-to-devs-regarding-modifying-particle-effects/14600/7</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 17 Jan 2016 22:57:40 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14600-7</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/a-question-to-devs-regarding-modifying-particle-effects/14600.rss">A question to devs regarding modifying particle effects.</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>A question to devs regarding modifying particle effects.</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Gunship_Mark_II]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>At this point i do question myself if i really want to make something for this game, i’ve planned a huge particle effects overhaul, not just 1 Classic HL1 explosion recreation, but the tools for making content have been broken since the latest update including the one of the most important features and aspects of the game - steam workshop, if that is not one of the prioritization points for them, then i don’t know what it is besides Xen. I’ve been asking devs on the store page, for at least telling me that they are aware of the issue, but i got no answer. I came here with even more info, and the story repeats. At least you replied, so that can be considered as a plus, half broken plus. If i sound “entitled” to you, because i might know what’s the reason behind the problem is, i had my fair share of source related coding before. If i had a source code i could’ve tested that myself, at least i said to them where to dig for the solution. Guess i ask for too much then. If you consider what i ask as a “bitching” then i hope my “bitching” will be at least heard by developers.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/a-question-to-devs-regarding-modifying-particle-effects/14600/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/a-question-to-devs-regarding-modifying-particle-effects/14600/6</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 17 Jan 2016 21:34:45 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14600-6</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/a-question-to-devs-regarding-modifying-particle-effects/14600.rss">A question to devs regarding modifying particle effects.</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>A question to devs regarding modifying particle effects.</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypt]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>You’re coming across as kinda bitchy and entitled, to be honest. A bit unnecessary.</p>
<p>The game is still Early Access, the developers have far more important things to prioritize ahead of making the tools work. Chances are this is something they’ll address later. For now, just be a bit patient.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/a-question-to-devs-regarding-modifying-particle-effects/14600/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/a-question-to-devs-regarding-modifying-particle-effects/14600/5</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 17 Jan 2016 20:19:43 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14600-5</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/a-question-to-devs-regarding-modifying-particle-effects/14600.rss">A question to devs regarding modifying particle effects.</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>A question to devs regarding modifying particle effects.</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Gunship_Mark_II]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Come on, guys, do i really ask a lot by making free content for your game? Just add a few lines into code to whitelist particles folder to be read by custom folder and message me back, that’s all i really want.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/a-question-to-devs-regarding-modifying-particle-effects/14600/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/a-question-to-devs-regarding-modifying-particle-effects/14600/4</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 17 Jan 2016 20:12:36 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14600-4</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/a-question-to-devs-regarding-modifying-particle-effects/14600.rss">A question to devs regarding modifying particle effects.</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>A question to devs regarding modifying particle effects.</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Gunship_Mark_II]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Yep, did that, i even replaced .pcf file with correct names in it. It still uses stuff from bms_misc archive no matter what.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/a-question-to-devs-regarding-modifying-particle-effects/14600/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/a-question-to-devs-regarding-modifying-particle-effects/14600/3</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Jan 2016 20:20:48 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14600-3</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/a-question-to-devs-regarding-modifying-particle-effects/14600.rss">A question to devs regarding modifying particle effects.</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>A question to devs regarding modifying particle effects.</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypt]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Did you add it to the particle manifest file?<br>
Also yes, I think BM’s particle editor is broken right now.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/a-question-to-devs-regarding-modifying-particle-effects/14600/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/a-question-to-devs-regarding-modifying-particle-effects/14600/2</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Jan 2016 20:10:34 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14600-2</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/a-question-to-devs-regarding-modifying-particle-effects/14600.rss">A question to devs regarding modifying particle effects.</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>A question to devs regarding modifying particle effects.</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Gunship_Mark_II]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Hey folks, i’ve been asking few questions in store page discussions, but seems like noone reads them or something, so i’ll ask here.</p>
<p>I am not sure what you did, but i can’t replace particle effects, no matter how i try. I made new explosion particle ( grenade_explosion_01 ), i made an addon for it, and put few sounds to test. Sounds work fine, but not particle effect, it’s default. I tried to replace .pcf file with mine in bms particles folder, but still no luck, even if i remove bms particles folder it doesn’t matter. It’s like game is told to use only particles from bms_misc, which is really lame for me, because i can’t do anything with particles, and i planned so much. I am currently working on a HL1 explosion recreation on BM, here’s work in progress video of it :</p>
<p><a href="https://youtu.be/4w71d5gVreE" rel="nofollow noopener">youtu.be/4w71d5gVreE</a></p>
<p>Do you have any solution or will this be “fixed” in the next patch? It would be also great if you could control which particle to spawn via script file, so i could randomize explosions too, if you can add that that’ll be great. Also if you could delete the leftovers of old explosion from the particle explosion - that will be great.</p>
<p>Another question is, in-game tools are not available, i treid to launch the game with -tool -nop4, but nothing happens.</p>
<p>Thanks.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/a-question-to-devs-regarding-modifying-particle-effects/14600/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/a-question-to-devs-regarding-modifying-particle-effects/14600/1</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Jan 2016 19:59:33 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14600-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/a-question-to-devs-regarding-modifying-particle-effects/14600.rss">A question to devs regarding modifying particle effects.</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
