<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Game Ratings</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/game-ratings/1146</link>
    <description>Choose a few games you have played recently and say whether you like them or not, why, and if you&#39;d recommend them. I&#39;ll start.


Far Cry 2
Fail African fps iron sight free roamer. Many minor irritations such as mortars that are extremely hard to find, gun jams that take around 5 minutes to unjam, laggy multiplayer, and more. It does have great graphics, but not as good as Crysis Warhead which was released before it. Gets a :meh: Do not recommend. 

Dead Space
Pretty good third person space horror. Had an intense horror effect, interesting storyline and really good graphics, but it is very lacking in action and I always felt starved for ammo, something that drives me insane in video games. gets a  :slight_smile: . I do recommend if you really like horror, but I suggest buying a few of the games listed below first.

Call of Juarez Bound in Blood
Amazing wild west style iron sights fps. Wonderful game mechanics, stunning graphics, very fun storyline (a spectacular climax) and wonderful setting. The one downside is a slightly short campaign, it took me 6 hours and I usually take my time with video games. Lots of clever little things packed into this game, such as when using the bow you get a short period of slo mo when zooming and door breaking scenes in which you and your brother break into a building filled with enemies through giant doubles doors and mow them down in classic wild west style. there is some nice periods of free roam, but they were a little short. Gets a ^_^.

F.E.A.R. Project Origin
Best game ever. (fps iron sights horror) Wonderful horror effect that isn&#39;t over the top, has bits of comic relief, intense firefights, great game mechanics, great storyline, nice slo mo feature and reaply value with its awards system. I really have nothing bad to say about this game. Gets :jizz:. 

Prototype
Spectacular third person &quot;power fantasy&quot; free roamer. Whether your tearing through Manhatten trashing citizens, or completing a mission Prototype is very fun.   Nice upgrades feature, fun game mechanics, very long fun storyline, and great boss fights. Great rewards for exploration with collectible landmarks and hints. Nothing more satisfying than sneaking up on a soldier and snapping his neck only to become him, smashing through crowds of citizens with a massive shield protruding from your arm or drop kicking fucking helicopters. (there&#39;s a comic somewhere on that) Nothing bad to say. Get&#39;s ^_^. Do buy, but get F.E.A.R. Project Origin first.


EDIT:
Forgot one
Tomb Raider Underworld
Epic fail third person puzzle oriented shooter. Played this game for about and hour before getting completely sick of it. No combat whatsover, just jumping puzzle after jumping puzzle. Horrible game, really really boring. Does have nice graphics and laura has huge tits  :stuck_out_tongue:  but that is all it has going for it. gets a :fffuuu:. Do not buy even if you have played and gotten bored of every single video game from today all the way back to 1998. Go online and find some flash games instead.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 20 Aug 2009 17:53:08 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Technology and Gaming</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/game-ratings/1146.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Game Ratings</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Level]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Hmm, sounds good, I’ll give it a try.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/game-ratings/1146/22">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/game-ratings/1146/22</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 20 Aug 2009 17:53:08 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-1146-22</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/game-ratings/1146.rss">Game Ratings</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Game Ratings</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Dust]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>All things that can break and affect your driving, all have a sort of life bar. Except it’s not a bar it’s an icon.</p>
<p>Basically it can go from a transparent grey colour to yellow, to red, etc.  How far damaged it is, is how much it affects your driving.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/game-ratings/1146/21">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/game-ratings/1146/21</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 20 Aug 2009 08:12:27 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-1146-21</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/game-ratings/1146.rss">Game Ratings</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Game Ratings</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Level]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Imonfire">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/i/e47c2d/40.png" class="avatar"> Imonfire:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>It affects performance and handling. It even does it a bit too much IMO. For example if you hit a wall at too high speed you can fuck up a wheel and not be able to turn right or left, or always have to steer a bit to the right to go straight. I guess (I only played it a bit) you can also destroy your turbo, radiator, gearbox, everything as in DiRT.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>How about minor bumps and such, like driving along, and you hit another cars side going around a corner.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/game-ratings/1146/20">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/game-ratings/1146/20</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 20 Aug 2009 05:31:39 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-1146-20</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/game-ratings/1146.rss">Game Ratings</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Game Ratings</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Guf]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>…if only I could get it to go…   Tried the thing for tweaking settings first, and when it finished loading one of the maps it got stuck just as things were supposed to go 3d.  Killed the process and tried again and it did that on the first one, that had worked fine before.<br>
Oddly thereafter Lego Batman started occasionally doing the same thing, which I found I could fix by alt-tabbing out and back in, but doing that when FC2 is stuck takes about 5mins…  Haven’t tried it in ages tho - maybe a recent driver update will have fixed that…</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/game-ratings/1146/19">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/game-ratings/1146/19</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 20 Aug 2009 02:43:07 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-1146-19</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/game-ratings/1146.rss">Game Ratings</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Game Ratings</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Fungus]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>(Again) Far Cry 2: While there are some really annoying details,  (cars breaking down WAY too much), it is a pretty cool game. Weapons feel nice, <span class="bbcode-b"><span class="bbcode-u">old worn down</span></span> weapons jam, and eventually break, a night day cycle, fire (literally) fights everywhere. And while the overall objective of some missions is the same, what you are actualy doing varies quite a bit. And lots of cool little anims, like the health stabilizing things, and the gun jamming. Could have been much better, but its still fun to play.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/game-ratings/1146/18">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/game-ratings/1146/18</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 20 Aug 2009 02:31:52 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-1146-18</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/game-ratings/1146.rss">Game Ratings</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Game Ratings</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Imonfire]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>It affects performance and handling. It even does it a bit too much IMO. For example if you hit a wall at too high speed you can fuck up a wheel and not be able to turn right or left, or always have to steer a bit to the right to go straight. I guess (I only played it a bit) you can also destroy your turbo, radiator, gearbox, everything as in DiRT.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/game-ratings/1146/17">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/game-ratings/1146/17</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 20 Aug 2009 01:44:36 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-1146-17</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/game-ratings/1146.rss">Game Ratings</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Game Ratings</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Level]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="OldDirtyBastard">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/o/dec6dc/40.png" class="avatar"> OldDirtyBastard:</div>
<blockquote>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">GRID</span> - got into Le Mans GT1 with Lamborgini Murcielago R-GT.<br>
Puny Corvettes, heck, even Aston Martins can’t keep with me and my teammate up on second to the max difficulty level.</p>
<p>Lambo is fucking awesome, as is the game, especially after GT2 hell.<br>
The game itself is pure fucking fun.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Can you clear something up about grid. I like some racing games, but I’m not very good at them, which explains why I’m good at flatout 2, because hitting cars and other objects is a plus for the most part. How does taking damage in grid effect your cars performance and such, is it one crash and you’re gone, or a lot more forgiving?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/game-ratings/1146/16">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/game-ratings/1146/16</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 19 Aug 2009 19:51:56 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-1146-16</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/game-ratings/1146.rss">Game Ratings</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Game Ratings</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Lolipopman]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Fable 2: Fun at first, but gets a bit repetative, and theres nothing to do after you’ve killed Lucien. 6/10.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/game-ratings/1146/15">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/game-ratings/1146/15</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 19 Aug 2009 18:40:51 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-1146-15</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/game-ratings/1146.rss">Game Ratings</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Game Ratings</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Hamst3r]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Cryostasis: Sleep of Reason</p>
<p>Finished this last night and I found it to be quite brilliant. The gameplay mechanics and situations were very unique. The story is crazy. It eventually makes sense though, even though it makes sense by just getting more outlandish.</p>
<p>It’s a tough one to explain, you just need to play it.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/game-ratings/1146/14">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/game-ratings/1146/14</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 19 Aug 2009 15:35:05 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-1146-14</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/game-ratings/1146.rss">Game Ratings</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Game Ratings</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[CTID]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I’m pretty sure they canceled Episode 2 because One was a financial failure, or something like that.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/game-ratings/1146/13">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/game-ratings/1146/13</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 19 Aug 2009 05:04:34 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-1146-13</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/game-ratings/1146.rss">Game Ratings</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Game Ratings</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Guf]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I liked it, tho it’s been ages and still no Ep2 so it’s more like SiN Episode.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/game-ratings/1146/12">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/game-ratings/1146/12</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 19 Aug 2009 04:45:27 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-1146-12</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/game-ratings/1146.rss">Game Ratings</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Game Ratings</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Master_Chef]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Has anyone here played SiN: Episodes? I’m thinking about purchasing it, based off of it’s cheap price and that it seems kinda fun, but I haven’t seen any reviews of it.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/game-ratings/1146/11">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/game-ratings/1146/11</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 19 Aug 2009 04:36:48 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-1146-11</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/game-ratings/1146.rss">Game Ratings</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Game Ratings</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Neon_Impulse]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><span class="bbcode-b">Half-life</span><br>
an awesome game with amazing technology for 1998 and fantastic gameplay with many immersing environments. but has a few little glitches and annoyances, and gets a :awesome: (4/5) from me.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Half-life 2</span><br>
an okay game with great story-telling and deep plot, but I found it boring and repetitive, and I found a huge lack of enemies and weapons. however, the gravity gun was just awesome and raises my rating of it from 2/5 to 3/5! gets a  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=9" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Portal</span><br>
A very fun game which combines puzzle solving with occasional combat, which I like. I don’t know how to describe it- it’s just awesome! gets a :awesome: (4/5)</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/game-ratings/1146/10">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/game-ratings/1146/10</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 14 Aug 2009 23:28:27 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-1146-10</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/game-ratings/1146.rss">Game Ratings</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Game Ratings</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[OldDirtyBastard]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><span class="bbcode-b">GRID</span> - got into Le Mans GT1 with Lamborgini Murcielago R-GT.<br>
Puny Corvettes, heck, even Aston Martins can’t keep with me and my teammate up on second to the max difficulty level.</p>
<p>Lambo is fucking awesome, as is the game, especially after GT2 hell.<br>
The game itself is pure fucking fun.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/game-ratings/1146/9">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/game-ratings/1146/9</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 13 Aug 2009 18:11:19 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-1146-9</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/game-ratings/1146.rss">Game Ratings</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Game Ratings</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Dust]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>InFamous - The first few hours can be intresting ones. Learning the powes and climbing mechanics can be fun, and the first set of Story missions are enjoyable and well presented. It is later in the game you relise you are starting to get extremely bored, and relise the game lacks emotional impact. I wouldn’t be surprised if it was forgotten by all in a couple of months. Saying that, if you are looking for a superhuman experiance, this has a slight edge over Prototype in my opinion.</p>
<p>Elder Scrolls 4: Oblivion - A massive, beautiful and atmospheric game. From the first few hours struggling through minor enemies, to the extreme fun of blasting massive demons, this game keeps attention throughout. Despite the many glitches and repetitive missions, this is one of my favourite games of all time.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/game-ratings/1146/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/game-ratings/1146/8</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 13 Aug 2009 17:43:42 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-1146-8</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/game-ratings/1146.rss">Game Ratings</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Game Ratings</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[JohnKiller118]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Dr. Perky">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Dr. Perky:</div>
<blockquote>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Psychonauts</span> - I’m not even done with this one and I love it I’ve loved every second of it its amazing I wish I had played all those years ago when I keep telling myself I’ll get it next time I have the money. So far the best level has been the milkman level its just so out there and the way the level is set up is awesome.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Secret of Monkey Island</span> - This game definitely got me thinking a lot something many games don’t do anymore of course if your one of those people who demands action be prepared to be disappointed as fighting is done with swords sure but all the actual interaction you make is delivering insults and comebacks which was brilliant the game is filled with humor and is a greatly amusing game.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Brutal Legend better be financial success or else I’ll be pissed!</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/game-ratings/1146/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/game-ratings/1146/7</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 13 Aug 2009 17:30:46 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-1146-7</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/game-ratings/1146.rss">Game Ratings</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Game Ratings</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Dr_Perky]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><span class="bbcode-b">Psychonauts</span> - I’m not even done with this one and I love it I’ve loved every second of it its amazing I wish I had played all those years ago when I keep telling myself I’ll get it next time I have the money. So far the best level has been the milkman level its just so out there and the way the level is set up is awesome.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Secret of Monkey Island</span> - This game definitely got me thinking a lot something many games don’t do anymore of course if your one of those people who demands action be prepared to be disappointed as fighting is done with swords sure but all the actual interaction you make is delivering insults and comebacks which was brilliant the game is filled with humor and is a greatly amusing game.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/game-ratings/1146/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/game-ratings/1146/6</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 13 Aug 2009 16:50:01 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-1146-6</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/game-ratings/1146.rss">Game Ratings</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Game Ratings</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[garrthbarrttinn]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Raminator">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/r/6bbea6/40.png" class="avatar"> Raminator:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>HOLY FUCKING HELL THERE IS A "TECHNOLOGY AND “<span class="bbcode-b">GAMING</span>” FORUM THAT YOU MISS EVERY SINGLE TIME YOU START ANOTHER CRAPPY THREAD</p>
<p>GODDAMN IF YOU DO IT ONE MORE TIME I’M TAKING YOUR THREAD CREATING PRIVILEGES AWAY</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Really? I’ve put a few in off-topic that got moved to show off, but I don’t remember mis-posting any that belonged in technology and gaming before. Anyway, oops my bad.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/game-ratings/1146/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/game-ratings/1146/5</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 10 Aug 2009 18:41:08 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-1146-5</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/game-ratings/1146.rss">Game Ratings</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Game Ratings</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Level]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Rollercoaster tycoon<br>
Really fun, better then the 3d version, except my computer died and I lost my save games, so I never beat it. Got pretty far though, I usually ended up beating my objected pretty quick, and waiting around for an hour or so.</p>
<p>GTA 4<br>
My computer isn’t quite good enough to play this one (CPU is lacking), and so it stutters quite a bit, but still fun. Lots of the missions are go find this thing, and kill everyone in your way, which is okay because the cover aspect works pretty well, but gets kind of tedious.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/game-ratings/1146/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/game-ratings/1146/4</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 10 Aug 2009 15:18:35 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-1146-4</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/game-ratings/1146.rss">Game Ratings</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Game Ratings</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Dr_Perky]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Audiosurf<br>
quite possibly the greatest rhythm game I have ever played. Its more fun than guitar hero or rock band IMHO, if you haven’t tried it out steam has a demo.</p>
<p>Garry’s Mod<br>
enough has been said…</p>
<p>Theme Hospital<br>
the greatest sim game ever because of its simplicity, charm and delightful sense of humor.</p>
<p>Mass Effect<br>
this game is incredible its very long has almost no set path to the finsh and can kill hours upon hours of time but it can also suck them away.</p>
<p>those are my favorites at the moment.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/game-ratings/1146/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/game-ratings/1146/3</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 10 Aug 2009 09:23:21 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-1146-3</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/game-ratings/1146.rss">Game Ratings</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Game Ratings</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Hamst3r]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>This is just copy and pasted off my site:</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">May</span></p>
<p><span alt="" class="broken-image" title="This image is broken"><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-unlink svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#unlink"></use></svg></span><br>
<span class="bbcode-b">Zeno Clash</span> <span class="bbcode-i">[ 5/29/2009 ]</span><br>
<span class="bbcode-i">(What? I don’t get it, but I like it. An exceedingly well done first-person brawler!)</span></p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">June</span></p>
<p><span alt="" class="broken-image" title="This image is broken"><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-unlink svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#unlink"></use></svg></span><br>
<span class="bbcode-b">Quake 2: Ground Zero</span> <span class="bbcode-i">[ 6/05/2009 ]</span><br>
<span class="bbcode-i">(You have defeated the Strogg invasion! Yes, I only just got around to this.)</span></p>
<pre><code>[img]https://www.hamst3r.com/images/201.jpg[/img]
</code></pre>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Mirror’s Edge</span> <span class="bbcode-i">[ 6/25/2009 ]</span></p>
<p><span class="bbcode-i">(Running is enjoyable. Fighting is frustrating. Still, a beautiful game.)</span></p>
<pre><code>[b]July[/b]

[img]https://www.hamst3r.com/images/203.jpg[/img]
</code></pre>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">F.E.A.R. 2: Project Origin</span> <span class="bbcode-i">[ 7/11/2009 ]</span><br>
<span class="bbcode-i">(Remove some of the new gameplay mechanics and it would be perfect.)</span></p>
<pre><code>[img]https://www.hamst3r.com/images/204.jpg[/img]
</code></pre>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Trine</span> <span class="bbcode-i">[ 7/12/2009 ]</span><br>
<span class="bbcode-i">(Frozenbyte has blossomed into a truly great developer and Trine shows it.)</span></p>
<pre><code>[img]https://www.hamst3r.com/images/205.jpg[/img]
</code></pre>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">S.T.A.L.K.E.R.: Clear Sky</span> <span class="bbcode-i">[ 7/19/2009 ]</span><br>
<span class="bbcode-i">(A great game with a poor ending. Not as great as the original, but plenty good!)</span></p>
<ul>
<li>
</li></ul>
<p>Right now I’m playing Cryostasis and Bookworm Adventures 2.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/game-ratings/1146/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/game-ratings/1146/2</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 10 Aug 2009 08:48:45 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-1146-2</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/game-ratings/1146.rss">Game Ratings</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Game Ratings</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[garrthbarrttinn]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Choose a few games you have played recently and say whether you like them or not, why, and if you’d recommend them. I’ll start.</p>
<p>Far Cry 2<br>
Fail African fps iron sight free roamer. Many minor irritations such as mortars that are extremely hard to find, gun jams that take around 5 minutes to unjam, laggy multiplayer, and more. It does have great graphics, but not as good as Crysis Warhead which was released before it. Gets a :meh: Do not recommend.</p>
<p>Dead Space<br>
Pretty good third person space horror. Had an intense horror effect, interesting storyline and really good graphics, but it is very lacking in action and I always felt starved for ammo, something that drives me insane in video games. gets a  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=9" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"> . I do recommend if you really like horror, but I suggest buying a few of the games listed below first.</p>
<p>Call of Juarez Bound in Blood<br>
Amazing wild west style iron sights fps. Wonderful game mechanics, stunning graphics, very fun storyline (a spectacular climax) and wonderful setting. The one downside is a slightly short campaign, it took me 6 hours and I usually take my time with video games. Lots of clever little things packed into this game, such as when using the bow you get a short period of slo mo when zooming and door breaking scenes in which you and your brother break into a building filled with enemies through giant doubles doors and mow them down in classic wild west style. there is some nice periods of free roam, but they were a little short. Gets a ^_^.</p>
<p>F.E.A.R. Project Origin<br>
Best game ever. (fps iron sights horror) Wonderful horror effect that isn’t over the top, has bits of comic relief, intense firefights, great game mechanics, great storyline, nice slo mo feature and reaply value with its awards system. I really have nothing bad to say about this game. Gets :jizz:.</p>
<p>Prototype<br>
Spectacular third person “power fantasy” free roamer. Whether your tearing through Manhatten trashing citizens, or completing a mission Prototype is very fun.   Nice upgrades feature, fun game mechanics, very long fun storyline, and great boss fights. Great rewards for exploration with collectible landmarks and hints. Nothing more satisfying than sneaking up on a soldier and snapping his neck only to become him, smashing through crowds of citizens with a massive shield protruding from your arm or drop kicking fucking helicopters. (there’s a comic somewhere on that) Nothing bad to say. Get’s ^_^. Do buy, but get F.E.A.R. Project Origin first.</p>
<p>EDIT:<br>
Forgot one<br>
Tomb Raider Underworld<br>
Epic fail third person puzzle oriented shooter. Played this game for about and hour before getting completely sick of it. No combat whatsover, just jumping puzzle after jumping puzzle. Horrible game, really really boring. Does have nice graphics and laura has huge tits  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=9" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:">  but that is all it has going for it. gets a :fffuuu:. Do not buy even if you have played and gotten bored of every single video game from today all the way back to 1998. Go online and find some flash games instead.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/game-ratings/1146/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/game-ratings/1146/1</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 10 Aug 2009 04:30:07 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-1146-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/game-ratings/1146.rss">Game Ratings</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
