<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Ask an Atheist!!!</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/ask-an-atheist/2542</link>
    <description>Seems like we&#39;re on an &quot;ask a ____&quot; thread spree I&#39;d make an ask an atheist thread.

To summarize my beliefs, I believe strictly in a scientific world. I think nothing is outside of science; if something is true then it can be explained by science. I do not believe in and feel there is no valid scientific evidence supporting things such as religion, Big Foot, alien abductions, ghosts, and just about anything &quot;supernatural&quot; or &quot;paranormal&quot;.

If you have a question for me or another atheist, post it here. Also, as my sig says, a large portion of my beliefs can be explained by a Biology textbook.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 15 Jan 2011 06:58:22 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Off Topic</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/ask-an-atheist/2542.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Ask an Atheist!!!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[intooblivion]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>God can be refuted by this fact: God is perfect - God needs worhsip</p>
<p>Needs = Imperfections</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/ask-an-atheist/2542/1334">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/ask-an-atheist/2542/1334</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 15 Jan 2011 06:58:22 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2542-1334</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/ask-an-atheist/2542.rss">Ask an Atheist!!!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Ask an Atheist!!!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[gugamilare]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="King_Kaddo">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/k/bcef8e/40.png" class="avatar"> King_Kaddo:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>What is your strongest argument against god? I won’t answer to anything so you can keep it short if you want.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>There are actually numerous of evidences against the existence of God. At least, the existence of God as portrayed in the bible or any religion derived from Judaism.</p>
<p>First, when someone says something about God (what he likes, what he wants, etc), it uses the same part of the brain that is used someone talks about other people, whether imaginary, real or dead. A wider explanation about it is in <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=1iMmvu9eMrg" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">this video</a>.</p>
<p>Second, monotheism only appeared in Israel around 600 BC. Iahweh was a “modification” of a god of war among many other gods. Watch <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=MlnnWbkMlbg&amp;feature=recentf" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">this video</a> or <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Yahweh#Early_history_of_Yahweh_worship" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">read this in Wikipedia</a>.</p>
<p>Third, the hell. It contradicts omnibenevolence. I have a reasoning similar to the <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Problem_of_evil#Logical_problem_of_evil" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">problem of evil</a>, but slightly different. I don’t see evil in the world as a bad thing if we can get something back from the suffering, like if we gradually learn a lot of stuff (as Spiritism believes) or if that eventually gets us to heaven. But I can’t see how hell is a good thing for the people that end up there. It is like pulling the trigger of a gun while it is pointed at someone: you didn’t kill the victim, the bullet did, but you are guilt because you knew the pulling the trigger would make the bullet to be projected and kill the person.</p>
<p>Fourth, God, in the old testament, is an angry, vengeful, selfish superhuman. He even literally struggled with one of the prophets. He also ordered many murders, wars and sacrifices in his name, while also killing and torturing lots of people himself for not complying to him. He left his own people wandering in the desert! As time and human knowledge increased, God developed to a more believable, benevolent being. That means God was invented by humans, not shown to humans, or he and his will would not mutate with time.</p>
<p>Fifth, inconsistency. Lots of people say they have “personally experienced” God and that they know him, but they have different views about what God is or wants, what he did or did not, etc. Ok, people are people, you may argue that they can make mistakes, but, then, how can I trust them when they say they “personally experienced” God? I used to be a Christian and I “personally experienced” God, but that is not much different from listening to a nice music, concentrating on your objectives in life or having hope on what is right.</p>
<p>Sixth, prayer do not work, as shown by several statistical studies.</p>
<p>Seventh, the whole concept that a completely blind belief in God will save you from eternal damnation. That looks much more like a weapon that the Roman empire used to control people and nowadays is an evil inheritance.</p>
<p>Anyway, I only said the main reasons. All that the above is saying is, in one sentence, that there is no evidence that God exists. All alleged evidences or proofs cannot be trusted.</p>
<p>I honestly believe that a God <span class="bbcode-i">might</span> exist. I <span class="bbcode-i">like</span> to think about God as a being that</p>
<ol>
<li>have complete free will, as in “he is able to prevent himself from doing anything that he does not want to”</li>
<li>is omnipotent, as in “he can do anything that doe not contradict logic”</li>
<li>is omniscient, as in “he can know anything that is knowable”</li>
<li>is omnibenevolent, as in “each suffering that happens to each subject as a direct of indirect consequence of one of his choices has a benevolent consequence for the subject that is greater than the suffering caused”</li>
<li>created everything else that exists</li>
<li>created the laws of Physics</li>
</ol>
<p>I say the most generic definition of God is a being who satisfies at least (1) and (5). If you want to define multiple Gods, than all of them should satisfy (1) while (5) should be substituted by “the set of all Gods created everything else that exists”.</p>
<p>Let’s stick to one God. Since he created everything else (5) and chose to do so (1), all suffering is ultimately chosen by him, so (4) is equivalent to:</p>
<p>“Each suffering that happens to each subject has a benevolent consequence for the subject that is greater than the suffering caused”.</p>
<p>This means hell isn’t possible. And that is because my definition of omnibenevolence is more relaxed than the usual one! With the usual one, an absurd is created because of the existence of evil, creating, therefore, an absurd. One thing I am sure about: God might or not exist but, if God exists, he is not even nearly like <span class="bbcode-i"><span class="bbcode-b">any</span></span> religion have depicted him.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/ask-an-atheist/2542/1333">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/ask-an-atheist/2542/1333</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 15 Jan 2011 05:03:02 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2542-1333</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/ask-an-atheist/2542.rss">Ask an Atheist!!!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Ask an Atheist!!!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[sersoft]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="sersoft">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/user_avatar/leakfree.org/sersoft/40/5837_2.png" class="avatar"> sersoft:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>the world came into existence because nonexistent hypothetical numbers create a specific number when put into an equation</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I already answered why the universe is there, why we are here, why there is no god and even why most species are separated into 2 genders. I can’t prove it and it takes a high IQ to understand.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/ask-an-atheist/2542/1332">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/ask-an-atheist/2542/1332</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jan 2011 21:30:08 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2542-1332</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/ask-an-atheist/2542.rss">Ask an Atheist!!!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Ask an Atheist!!!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[King_Kaddo]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="MaxTheLimit">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/m/0ea827/40.png" class="avatar"> MaxTheLimit:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>A god that created EVERYTHING just for mankind, and to be the keeper of mankind? No.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Agree with that.</p>
<p>PS: Don’t think that I ignore the text I cut off from replies.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="danielsangeo">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/user_avatar/leakfree.org/danielsangeo/40/4347_2.png" class="avatar"> danielsangeo:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I mentioned that I wasn’t trying to be fatuous but the rhetorical device I used was actually a good one.  What is my strongest argument against a god?  That there’s no evidence FOR a god.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Oh, ok.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/ask-an-atheist/2542/1331">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/ask-an-atheist/2542/1331</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jan 2011 21:26:03 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2542-1331</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/ask-an-atheist/2542.rss">Ask an Atheist!!!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Ask an Atheist!!!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[danielsangeo]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I mentioned that I wasn’t trying to be fatuous but the rhetorical device I used was actually a good one.  What is my strongest argument against a god?  That there’s no evidence FOR a god.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/ask-an-atheist/2542/1330">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/ask-an-atheist/2542/1330</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jan 2011 21:24:22 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2542-1330</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/ask-an-atheist/2542.rss">Ask an Atheist!!!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Ask an Atheist!!!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[King_Kaddo]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="danielsangeo">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/user_avatar/leakfree.org/danielsangeo/40/4347_2.png" class="avatar"> danielsangeo:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>wat</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Sorry I will try again. I recommended you not to begin with that rhetorical device the next time. I liked the part I have cut off.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/ask-an-atheist/2542/1329">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/ask-an-atheist/2542/1329</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jan 2011 21:22:35 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2542-1329</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/ask-an-atheist/2542.rss">Ask an Atheist!!!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Ask an Atheist!!!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[MaxTheLimit]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>If there is a god that interacts with our universe in any significant way that actually existed, it should leave some sort of evidence behind. Since there is none to be found, one must logically conclude that until some sort of evidence is found, the more logical proposition would be that the god doesn’t exist. If this god did not exist then there would be no evidence, as we have seen thus far this is what is indicated.<br>
Since we have noticed that the concepts of unobservable beings occur naturally in children not exposed to any sort of doctrine, then we can logically say that the concept of a god occurs naturally.<br>
Since we have found no evidence, and the idea is naturally occurring that imaginary beings exist when they do not, it is more logical to go on the assumption that the being god is just another imagined being.</p>
<p>The chance of something without evidence existing simply because we imagine it does is roughly 1 chance in ∞.  The chance that we simply don’t know or understand some grander function of the universe because of our limited perception? I’d say that is far more probable. Because we already acknowledge that we don not understand everything about the uni/multiverse.</p>
<p>The idea of a personal god seems to take this concept further to suggest that all of these ideas should be ignored including what we actually CAN observe. A god that simply interacts with a universe can be something discussed. A god that created EVERYTHING just for mankind, and to be the keeper of mankind? No.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/ask-an-atheist/2542/1328">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/ask-an-atheist/2542/1328</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jan 2011 21:17:29 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2542-1328</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/ask-an-atheist/2542.rss">Ask an Atheist!!!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Ask an Atheist!!!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[danielsangeo]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>wat</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/ask-an-atheist/2542/1327">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/ask-an-atheist/2542/1327</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jan 2011 21:13:23 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2542-1327</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/ask-an-atheist/2542.rss">Ask an Atheist!!!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Ask an Atheist!!!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[King_Kaddo]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>See it from another angle. I recommended you to cut off that part I didn’t.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>Why that specific deity?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I will answer that soon.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/ask-an-atheist/2542/1326">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/ask-an-atheist/2542/1326</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jan 2011 21:11:20 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2542-1326</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/ask-an-atheist/2542.rss">Ask an Atheist!!!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Ask an Atheist!!!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[danielsangeo]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>But then, couldn’t it be ANYTHING?  Why that specific deity?  What about leprechauns?  Fairies?  The vortigaunts?  Joe Pesci?  There’s just as much evidence that these entities did these things as that deity, isn’t there?</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="King_Kaddo">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/k/bcef8e/40.png" class="avatar"> King_Kaddo:</div>
<blockquote>
<p><span class="bbcode-i">“Ask an atheist!!!”</span><br>
You shouldn’t answer any question with the question simply inverted.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I noticed that you cut off the rest of my response.  Thanks!</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/ask-an-atheist/2542/1325">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/ask-an-atheist/2542/1325</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jan 2011 21:08:17 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2542-1325</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/ask-an-atheist/2542.rss">Ask an Atheist!!!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Ask an Atheist!!!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[King_Kaddo]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="danielsangeo">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/user_avatar/leakfree.org/danielsangeo/40/4347_2.png" class="avatar"> danielsangeo:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>What’s your strongest argument FOR god?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p><span class="bbcode-i">“Ask an atheist!!!”</span><br>
You shouldn’t answer any question with the question simply inverted.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/ask-an-atheist/2542/1324">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/ask-an-atheist/2542/1324</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jan 2011 21:06:38 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2542-1324</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/ask-an-atheist/2542.rss">Ask an Atheist!!!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Ask an Atheist!!!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[sersoft]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="King_Kaddo">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/k/bcef8e/40.png" class="avatar"> King_Kaddo:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Yes.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>a predictable answer, people who believe in god usually use circumstantial evidence that can be described as pure coincidence as evidence of god’s involvement.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/ask-an-atheist/2542/1323">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/ask-an-atheist/2542/1323</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jan 2011 21:06:15 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2542-1323</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/ask-an-atheist/2542.rss">Ask an Atheist!!!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Ask an Atheist!!!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[danielsangeo]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="King_Kaddo">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/k/bcef8e/40.png" class="avatar"> King_Kaddo:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>What is your strongest argument against god?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>What’s your strongest argument FOR god?</p>
<p>I don’t mean to be fatuous, but there’s absolutely nothing to show for any deity so why should I believe in something that has no evidence?</p>
<p>If he supposedly interacts with this universe, there needs to be at least a single solitary SHRED of evidence.  Where is it?  In the thousands of years that humans have been in existence, billions of people have looked.  No one, not a single person has ever found a single piece of evidence for any deity.</p>
<p>Why?</p>
<p>And why should I believe?  Because you say so?  Because some book says so?  No dice.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/ask-an-atheist/2542/1322">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/ask-an-atheist/2542/1322</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jan 2011 21:02:21 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2542-1322</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/ask-an-atheist/2542.rss">Ask an Atheist!!!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Ask an Atheist!!!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[King_Kaddo]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Yes.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/ask-an-atheist/2542/1321">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/ask-an-atheist/2542/1321</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jan 2011 20:59:18 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2542-1321</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/ask-an-atheist/2542.rss">Ask an Atheist!!!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Ask an Atheist!!!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[MaxTheLimit]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="King_Kaddo">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/k/bcef8e/40.png" class="avatar"> King_Kaddo:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>The god I am referecing to is not bound to anything he created (Space and Time).<br>
Therefore he is not imaginable and is not restricted in any way. His thoughts are not known besides that what he told us about them.<br>
There is more but I think this is enough.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Does the god you reference interact with this universe he supposedly created?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/ask-an-atheist/2542/1320">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/ask-an-atheist/2542/1320</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jan 2011 20:53:15 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2542-1320</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/ask-an-atheist/2542.rss">Ask an Atheist!!!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Ask an Atheist!!!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[King_Kaddo]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>The god I am referecing to is not bound to anything he created (Space and Time).<br>
Therefore he is not imaginable and is not restricted in any way. His thoughts are not known besides that what he told us about them.<br>
There is more but I think this is enough.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/ask-an-atheist/2542/1319">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/ask-an-atheist/2542/1319</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jan 2011 20:48:59 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2542-1319</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/ask-an-atheist/2542.rss">Ask an Atheist!!!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Ask an Atheist!!!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[MaxTheLimit]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>There is zero evidence for any sort of god. In fact there seems to be an indication from observation that the universe isn’t designed FOR us, so any possible god wouldn’t be a theistic god, but rather a deistic god. Since there is no evidence of a deistic god, then assuming there is one amongst the infinite other possibilities would be silly. What is the definition of ‘god’ are you referencing? I would need to know that before addressing the question.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/ask-an-atheist/2542/1318">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/ask-an-atheist/2542/1318</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jan 2011 19:09:28 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2542-1318</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/ask-an-atheist/2542.rss">Ask an Atheist!!!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Ask an Atheist!!!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[King_Kaddo]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>What is your strongest argument against god? I won’t answer to anything so you can keep it short if you want.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/ask-an-atheist/2542/1317">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/ask-an-atheist/2542/1317</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jan 2011 19:04:03 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2542-1317</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/ask-an-atheist/2542.rss">Ask an Atheist!!!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Ask an Atheist!!!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[gugamilare]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Hey, everyone here must have the chance to say anything, even if that sounds stupid.</p>
<p>Going back in the discussion a little bit:</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="MaxTheLimit">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/m/0ea827/40.png" class="avatar"> MaxTheLimit:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Going back a bit to the discussion of the accuracy, and origins or religious texts I found an interesting video. I was wondering if anyone had some opinions:</p>
<p><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=MlnnWbkMlbg&amp;feature=recentf" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=MlnnWbkMlbg&amp;feature=recentf</a></p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>This theory is in Wikipedia as well, with lots of sources. It looks like it is not just some bullshit theory like Zeitgeist.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Wikipedia">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Wikipedia:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Both the archaeological evidence and the Biblical texts document tensions between groups comfortable with the worship of Yahweh alongside local deities such as Asherah and Baal and those insistent on worship of Yahweh alone during the monarchal period. The Deuteronomistic source gives evidence of a strong monotheistic party during the reign of king Josiah during the late 7th century BCE, but the strength and prevalence of earlier monotheistic worship of Yahweh is widely debated based on interpretations of how much of the Deuteronomistic history is accurately based on earlier sources, and how much has been re-worked by Deuteronomistic redactors to bolster their theological views. The archaeological record documents <span class="bbcode-b">widespread polytheism in and around Israel</span> during the period of the monarchy.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p><a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Yahweh#Early_history_of_Yahweh_worship" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Yahweh#Early_history_of_Yahweh_worship</a></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/ask-an-atheist/2542/1316">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/ask-an-atheist/2542/1316</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jan 2011 13:56:09 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2542-1316</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/ask-an-atheist/2542.rss">Ask an Atheist!!!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Ask an Atheist!!!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[sersoft]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>nobody asked you, read the thread title</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/ask-an-atheist/2542/1315">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/ask-an-atheist/2542/1315</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jan 2011 10:34:31 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2542-1315</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/ask-an-atheist/2542.rss">Ask an Atheist!!!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Ask an Atheist!!!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[King_Kaddo]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="danielsangeo">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/user_avatar/leakfree.org/danielsangeo/40/4347_2.png" class="avatar"> danielsangeo:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I’ve never been able to figure that out, to be honest.  How do they separate fantasy from reality?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>That’s a good question. Although I am not an atheist I will try to answer it in a few days.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/ask-an-atheist/2542/1314">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/ask-an-atheist/2542/1314</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jan 2011 08:55:40 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2542-1314</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/ask-an-atheist/2542.rss">Ask an Atheist!!!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Ask an Atheist!!!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[MaxTheLimit]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="gibbelin">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/g/45deac/40.png" class="avatar"> gibbelin:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>That wasn’t really my point, but if I have to defend the analogy then OK. The day I see evidence for a god, I’ll start believing in one. Until then, it’s just a blank space on the map, and all we can do is go on the evidence we have, which has been rapidly removing places for such a being to hide for the last two centuries.</p>
<p>My point was that just because we don’t know the answer to something, that doesn’t mean there is no answer, and that no answer is always preferable to a made-up answer.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I kind of like the map analogy when referencing our knowledge. We have this grand detailed map. There is some detail lacking, but it gets more detailed all the time.<br>
There is blank spots on this map as well. There are people who say there is an amazing thing in these blank spots. But as the holes become fewer and fewer, and there is nothing like what those people said, but rather more interesting map stuff, nothing you wouldn’t expect to find on the map. We will never completely get rid of the blank spots, but as we fill up more and more, create more and more detail, without evidence of anything non usual map stuff, then to me it seems more an more likely that the map is just one hell of an amazing map.</p>
<p>I’m sure someone could elucidate the metaphor better than me though.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/ask-an-atheist/2542/1313">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/ask-an-atheist/2542/1313</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jan 2011 04:32:14 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2542-1313</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/ask-an-atheist/2542.rss">Ask an Atheist!!!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Ask an Atheist!!!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[danielsangeo]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Agreed.  However, if someone insists that they have the evidence that there is something there because some guy wrote about it many years ago…but there’s absolutely no evidence of it ever existing…</p>
<p>I’m just curious as to how they can separate, in their mind, between, say, Harry Potter and the Bible.  Why is one actually “real” (God) and the other is “fictional” (magic spells) if both have exactly the same evidence:  None?</p>
<p>I’ve never been able to figure that out, to be honest.  How do they separate fantasy from reality?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/ask-an-atheist/2542/1312">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/ask-an-atheist/2542/1312</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jan 2011 02:49:36 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2542-1312</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/ask-an-atheist/2542.rss">Ask an Atheist!!!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Ask an Atheist!!!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[gibbelin]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="danielsangeo">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/user_avatar/leakfree.org/danielsangeo/40/4347_2.png" class="avatar"> danielsangeo:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>But just because there’s blank spaces on the map doesn’t mean that continents ARE there, either.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="danielsangeo">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/user_avatar/leakfree.org/danielsangeo/40/4347_2.png" class="avatar"> danielsangeo:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>But just because there’s blank spaces on the map doesn’t mean that continents ARE there, either.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>That wasn’t really my point, but if I have to defend the analogy then OK. The day I see evidence for a god, I’ll start believing in one. Until then, it’s just a blank space on the map, and all we can do is go on the evidence we have, which has been rapidly removing places for such a being to hide for the last two centuries.</p>
<p>My point was that just because we don’t know the answer to something, that doesn’t mean there is no answer, and that no answer is always preferable to a made-up answer.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/ask-an-atheist/2542/1311">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/ask-an-atheist/2542/1311</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jan 2011 02:24:26 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2542-1311</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/ask-an-atheist/2542.rss">Ask an Atheist!!!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Ask an Atheist!!!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[gugamilare]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="gibbelin">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/g/45deac/40.png" class="avatar"> gibbelin:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Surely you mean physicists? Or perhaps these are some particularly philosophical general practitioners?  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=9" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"></p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p><img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/blush.png?v=9" title=":blush:" class="emoji" alt=":blush:"> Yeah, physicists.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/ask-an-atheist/2542/1310">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/ask-an-atheist/2542/1310</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jan 2011 02:19:23 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2542-1310</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/ask-an-atheist/2542.rss">Ask an Atheist!!!</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
