<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Fan in Blast Pit causes crash upon starting it.</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/fan-in-blast-pit-causes-crash-upon-starting-it/10647</link>
    <description>In the chapter &quot;Blast Pit&quot;, when turning on that huge freaking fan to power the coolant or whatever for the rocket to launch makes my game crash. Every time.
It&#39;s like clock work. Anyways, I&#39;ve attached the latest mini dump file from the source SDK 2007 file as reference. In the meantime, i&#39;ll be tinkering with loads and saves to see if i it may simply be a corrupt file save or whatnot. Thanks.

(~P.S, Thanks so much for taking the time to create this mod. I&#39;ve been dying for this to launch.)
&lt;a class=&#39;attachment&#39; href=&#39;/uploads/default/original/2X/8/8b0a232930a10cea785be695635745cad6c87ac2.mdmp&#39;&gt;hl2_4104_crash_2012_9_15T18_32_39C0.mdmp&lt;/a&gt; (93.9 KB)</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 17 Sep 2012 23:20:52 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>In-game Issues (Mod)</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/fan-in-blast-pit-causes-crash-upon-starting-it/10647.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Fan in Blast Pit causes crash upon starting it.</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[k-dubs]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>i had this problem too.<br>
there’s two things i tried, and im not sure which one fixed it.</p>
<p>but first off, make sure that ANY wood boxes, or palettes are completely destroyed and any of the pieces that wont destroy, throw them into the bottom of the pit. also drop the two propane tank kinda looking things into the bottom of the pit too.</p>
<p>The second thing that apparently helps, is getting back to the top floor before the bug occurs (which apparently happens when the fan hits full speed/power.) so you’re gonna have to race up as soon as you have hit the button.</p>
<p>hope this helps. it was very frustrating but this worked for me and i was able to continue the game.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/fan-in-blast-pit-causes-crash-upon-starting-it/10647/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/fan-in-blast-pit-causes-crash-upon-starting-it/10647/2</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 17 Sep 2012 23:20:52 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-10647-2</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/fan-in-blast-pit-causes-crash-upon-starting-it/10647.rss">Fan in Blast Pit causes crash upon starting it.</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Fan in Blast Pit causes crash upon starting it.</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[plippernast]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>In the chapter “Blast Pit”, when turning on that huge freaking fan to power the coolant or whatever for the rocket to launch makes my game crash. Every time.<br>
It’s like clock work. Anyways, I’ve attached the latest mini dump file from the source SDK 2007 file as reference. In the meantime, i’ll be tinkering with loads and saves to see if i it may simply be a corrupt file save or whatnot. Thanks.</p>
<p>(~P.S, Thanks so much for taking the time to create this mod. I’ve been dying for this to launch.)<br>
<a class="attachment" href="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/original/2X/8/8b0a232930a10cea785be695635745cad6c87ac2.mdmp">hl2_4104_crash_2012_9_15T18_32_39C0.mdmp</a> (93.9 KB)</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/fan-in-blast-pit-causes-crash-upon-starting-it/10647/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/fan-in-blast-pit-causes-crash-upon-starting-it/10647/1</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 17 Sep 2012 23:08:12 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-10647-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/fan-in-blast-pit-causes-crash-upon-starting-it/10647.rss">Fan in Blast Pit causes crash upon starting it.</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
