<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Name of Interesting HL1 Mod</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/name-of-interesting-hl1-mod/11914</link>
    <description>I was glad to be able to discover again the archived site of one HL mod, Resurrection. It&#39;s prompted me to try to remember another ambitious mod, one of which I don&#39;t think was finished either. It was developed before HL2, which makes it even more interesting. This what I remember of it.

It&#39;s set is a crummy futuristic dystopian city (like City 17), and it&#39;s infested with better evolved Xenian aliens and populated with former Barneys and Black Mesa scientists who&#39;ve turned into bums and hoodlums. It features grunts and assassins as living in the city too, I think. The player, whose name I can&#39;t remember, discoverrs that Gordon Freeman, who was living in this city, has been murdered, and his goal is to explore the city and determine who murdered him. There barnacles and headcrabs had reinforced armor, so they&#39;re even harder to fight.

What I&#39;ve just described sounds like a pre-HL2 with elements from Xatrix&#39;s Kingpin and a noir murder mystery. The game shots looked pretty good the last time I saw them (which is years ago). It would help if I knew the name. Sounds familiar to anyone?</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 24 Jan 2013 20:57:30 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Half-Life Series</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/name-of-interesting-hl1-mod/11914.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Name of Interesting HL1 Mod</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[MSKyuuni]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Huh, I’d love to play that. I can only find the sequel though, so that’s a bummer.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/name-of-interesting-hl1-mod/11914/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/name-of-interesting-hl1-mod/11914/8</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jan 2013 20:57:30 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11914-8</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/name-of-interesting-hl1-mod/11914.rss">Name of Interesting HL1 Mod</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Name of Interesting HL1 Mod</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[jesse]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Lotta good multiplayer mods out there that would have been good. like wastelands</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/name-of-interesting-hl1-mod/11914/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/name-of-interesting-hl1-mod/11914/7</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 09 Jan 2013 00:46:41 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11914-7</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/name-of-interesting-hl1-mod/11914.rss">Name of Interesting HL1 Mod</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Name of Interesting HL1 Mod</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Boundaryman]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Poke646 is awesome looking, but it wasn’t quite what I referring to…</p>
<p>I can’t find a suitable archive of the site, but that wonderful archive of PHL still documents it:</p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>Tuesday, 30 May, 2000 – Planet Half-Life News<br>
After-Life Interview<br>
7:18 PST | | Print News | Mail News<br>
Frenzy has posted an interview with Fragmeister from our hosted mod, After-Life. Here’s a taste:</p>
<p>What’s the story behind the mod?<br>
The story starts when Gordon Freeman goes missing. Soon the player stumbles upon Gordon’s dead body. It is then a quest/murder mystery to find out who killed Gordon Freeman and to seek vengeance on the murderer. The plot twists several times throughout the game.</p>
<p>Saturday, 9 September, 2000 – Planet Half-Life News<br>
After-Life Interview<br>
12:24 PST | | Print News | Mail News<br>
Mods Outpost has put together an interview with members of our hosted mod, After-Life. Here’s a taste:</p>
<p>[tkc]destructar: What is the mod about? The basics of the mod itself.<br>
After-Life: The mod is a single player and multiplayer add-on for Half-Life. The single player game puts you in the shoes of Doug Cavent, a friend of Gordon Freeman. When Gordon Freeman goes missing, you (the player), go searching for him. You find out that Gordon Freeman has been murdered. From then on, it is up to you to find out and take revenge on Gordon’s killer.</p>
<p>[tkc]destructar: Do you have more of a problem making a mod then earlier mod makers like counter-strike because of it’s popularity and getting recognized by the game playing public?</p>
<p>After-Life: Not particularly. In fact, it is probably harder for mod makers such as the developers of Counter-Strike since they have so much competition. There are so many multiplayer mods in production and not that many major single player modifications. The only single player mods that have really made an impact are the They Hungers and Redemption. There is an incredible amount of mod makers simply copying Counter-Strike and trying to better it which just isn’t possible since Counter-Strike has had so much time spent on it and has built up an incredible community (congrats to the CS team for that).</p>
<p>I am unsure of how many of the games playing public actually know about After-Life. That is the reason for me releasing the preview to several websites in around a week. Hopefully, After-Life will get some good feedback and some publicity that way.</p>
<p>Saturday, 7 October, 2000 – Planet Half-Life News<br>
Another After-Life Preview<br>
14:49 PST | | Print News | Mail News<br>
The BSP has posted a preview of the Alpha version of the After-Life mod. Here’s a taste:</p>
<p>One of the things that most mods are lacking today (other than a stable team ) is a good story to tell. Although there are a few exceptions, it seems that most mods are either knockoffs of previously popular ideas or Doom style shooters with absolutely no point. After-Life is here to break the trend.<br>
After-Life takes place after the Black Mesa incident, but don’t worry, it’s quite different from most games that start off this way. In this mod you play Doug Cavent, a tough guy with a badass attitude, and you’re trying to solve the mystery of who killed Gordon Freeman. That’s right, Gordon is dead and you’ve got to avenge him.</p>
<p>After-Life Alpha Preview<br>
11:07 PST | | Print News | Mail News<br>
Hangar 16 has whipped up a preview of the Alpha version of the After-Life mod. Here’s a taste:</p>
<p>Well as this is only a pre Alpha there is not too much going on regarding gameplay or puzzles as such. A couple of scattered enemies were there just to keep us on your toes. The level design is great, in terms of atmosphere and the textures are interesting and used well. The beginning puzzle is nice and although the mod at the moment is incomplete, all are in balance with look and atmosphere of your surroundings. Examining the picture ‘Club Swank’ for instance, the girder work etc are nice. Also ‘Sewer’ although a bit plain maybe has a nice feel to it, a prospect of further things.</p>
<p>Tuesday, 17 October, 2000 – Planet Half-Life News<br>
Another After-Life Preview<br>
13:27 PST | | Print News | Mail News<br>
The Mushroom has posted a preview of the After-Life mod from an advance copy they received. Here’ a taste:</p>
<p>The preview we received was pretty short, but gave a good indication to the amount of work going into this project. The level design is solid, the new textures suit the game very well, and the voice acting is decent. The new weapons looked good too, although it bothered me that a .50 caliber Desert Eagle has 17 shots in the clip, but I’m just picky like that. Also new is a radar of some kind, but it didn’t quite work in this alpha version.</p>
<p>After-Life Preview<br>
9:46 PST | | Print News | Mail News<br>
The Forge has whipped up a preview of the After-Life mod from an advance copy of it. Here’s a taste:</p>
<p>The visuals look amazingly like those of King-Pin, not surprisingly, since that is where most of them are coming from. The atmosphere that has been created however suits the mod incredibly well. Fire barrels with pretty flickering lighting and that cheerful burning roaring sound litter the streets. The maps have been constructed with many lights, most using the light shading model technique (you know, where there is a translucent model pointing downward, with a sunlight texture.<br>
Heck, I don’t know what you call it, its just the solid lighting, not the sprites, O.K?), and this gives the maps the feeling of dingy, smoke-filled hell hole that every private investigator should feel. The mappers would perhaps like to think about editing the lights, since it looks rather unconvincing when the light reaches halfway down a wall and then stops abruptly. After-Life has added more sequences of character dialogue also, just for your viewing pleasure, and I like the way creator Sam Robinson created a little e-mail sequence.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I was right, it was supposed to have a Kingpin-styled look to it. If the team had succeeded it before Poke646, we would’ve had another mod with a pre-City 17 look. As I felt about the demise of Half-Life Resurrection, it sucks that this particular mod which PHL died out. Unlike Poke646, it would’ve had different looking and enhanced monsters (and anti-social hoodlum Barneys). I just wish that time and new site management didn’t screw up with the site’s infrastructure, because it makes it harder to fully explore the old links and old PHL articles.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/name-of-interesting-hl1-mod/11914/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/name-of-interesting-hl1-mod/11914/6</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 04 Jan 2013 04:11:29 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11914-6</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/name-of-interesting-hl1-mod/11914.rss">Name of Interesting HL1 Mod</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Name of Interesting HL1 Mod</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Pyroclase]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>That’s what I thought when I read ‘city’, but OP is talking about some sorta weird HL-themed detective noir murder mystery mod.</p>
<p>Poke646 is outstanding, though. Highly recommend it to anyone who hasn’t played.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/name-of-interesting-hl1-mod/11914/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/name-of-interesting-hl1-mod/11914/5</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 30 Dec 2012 02:56:49 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11914-5</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/name-of-interesting-hl1-mod/11914.rss">Name of Interesting HL1 Mod</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Name of Interesting HL1 Mod</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Problematic_A-hole]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=w7FznNccnfU" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">This mod?</a></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/name-of-interesting-hl1-mod/11914/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/name-of-interesting-hl1-mod/11914/4</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 30 Dec 2012 02:44:50 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11914-4</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/name-of-interesting-hl1-mod/11914.rss">Name of Interesting HL1 Mod</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Name of Interesting HL1 Mod</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[HollywooD]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Can’t say that I’ve heard of it either. Certainly a unique premise, would love to give it a spin if you’re able to find a link.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/name-of-interesting-hl1-mod/11914/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/name-of-interesting-hl1-mod/11914/3</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 30 Dec 2012 01:41:35 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11914-3</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/name-of-interesting-hl1-mod/11914.rss">Name of Interesting HL1 Mod</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Name of Interesting HL1 Mod</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Pyroclase]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Can’t say I’ve heard of it, unfortunately. Sounds interesting though.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/name-of-interesting-hl1-mod/11914/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/name-of-interesting-hl1-mod/11914/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 29 Dec 2012 23:41:56 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11914-2</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/name-of-interesting-hl1-mod/11914.rss">Name of Interesting HL1 Mod</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Name of Interesting HL1 Mod</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Boundaryman]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I was glad to be able to discover again the archived site of one HL mod, Resurrection. It’s prompted me to try to remember another ambitious mod, one of which I don’t think was finished either. It was developed before HL2, which makes it even more interesting. This what I remember of it.</p>
<p>It’s set is a crummy futuristic dystopian city (like City 17), and it’s infested with better evolved Xenian aliens and populated with former Barneys and Black Mesa scientists who’ve turned into bums and hoodlums. It features grunts and assassins as living in the city too, I think. The player, whose name I can’t remember, discoverrs that Gordon Freeman, who was living in this city, has been murdered, and his goal is to explore the city and determine who murdered him. There barnacles and headcrabs had reinforced armor, so they’re even harder to fight.</p>
<p>What I’ve just described sounds like a pre-HL2 with elements from Xatrix’s Kingpin and a noir murder mystery. The game shots looked pretty good the last time I saw them (which is years ago). It would help if I knew the name. Sounds familiar to anyone?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/name-of-interesting-hl1-mod/11914/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/name-of-interesting-hl1-mod/11914/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 29 Dec 2012 23:25:07 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11914-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/name-of-interesting-hl1-mod/11914.rss">Name of Interesting HL1 Mod</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
