<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Taxes?</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/taxes/3255</link>
    <description>I debated with myself for quite some time before posting this topic because of the potential for flaming.  However, I fully believe that if we can be mature about this subject, someone may learn something from someone else.  Let&#39;s hope we can be mature about this.  I&#39;ll try not to tread on anyone at least starting out.  I am approaching this from the point of view of someone living in the United States so I&#39;m going to be Americentric here.  I apologize to non-Americans.

So, there&#39;s this common belief in the United States (not sure how it is in other parts of the world) that &quot;taxes&quot; are &quot;evil&quot; and a barrier to economic growth.  This notion leads to people believing that being taxed is somehow punishment and if someone on the higher end of the income spectrum is taxed at a higher rate, they are being &quot;punished for success&quot;.

I don&#39;t believe that at all.  They aren&#39;t being punished for anything.

They will claim that, through &quot;hard work&quot; and &quot;perseverance&quot;, that they became successful by themselves with &quot;no help&quot; from anyone-- especially not those in government.

To me, everyone that is a &quot;success&quot;, at least in the United States, did it not only through their hard work, but through the hard work of others.  Bill Gates would not be the &quot;success&quot; that he is without the hard work of all the people employed at Microsoft (I use him only as an example).  I submit that NO ONE becomes a &quot;success&quot; all by themselves.  They heavily rely on government.

Because of this, I fully believe that, if you rely so much on a government system and benefit substantially, you should pay for it.

This leads me to the &quot;involuntary&quot; claim that many make:  That government is &quot;taking your money&quot; at the &quot;point of a gun&quot;. What they mean by this is, if you don&#39;t pay your taxes, the government will send people to your house with guns to force the money out of your pocket.  Not only do I find this extremely inane, its implications are sorely lacking in reality.  Yes, if you refuse to pay taxes, there will be law enforcement at your door.  That much is true.  What isn&#39;t true, however, is that they&#39;re there to &#39;steal&#39; your money (as many claim).

I use a grocery store as an analogy.  If you go into a grocery store and begin eating the produce...and refuse to pay for what you&#39;re consuming, law enforcement will be there to &quot;force the money out of your pocket&quot;.  I can already hear the response: &quot;I don&#39;t have to go into that store&quot; and this is absolutely true.  But if you ARE in the store and consume things, you must pay.

Simply living in the United States (or any other civilized nation) consumes government resources.  From Bill Gates down to the homeless vagrant on the street; they all consume government resources just for simply existing in the United States.

And there are those that don&#39;t want to pay for what they consume by continuing to benefit from a civilized society.  I never begrudge a single penny that leaves my pocket in the form of taxes.  I will, however, begrudge what that money is used for.

I&#39;d love to hear other people&#39;s take on taxes.

Thanks!   :slight_smile:</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 07 Mar 2010 05:58:52 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Off Topic</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/taxes/3255.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Taxes?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[danielsangeo]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>The way I see it, paying taxes suck in exactly the same way that paying the rest of my bills suck.  I am not happy with the idea that, as soon as I get paid, nearly 3/4 of what I earned immediately goes out to another party.</p>
<p>I would be far LESS happy, however, with the alternative.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/taxes/3255/30">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/taxes/3255/30</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 07 Mar 2010 05:58:52 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3255-30</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/taxes/3255.rss">Taxes?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Taxes?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Mr_Someguy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Taxes suck, nobody likes them. But without taxes, <a href="https://www.denverpost.com/news/ci_14303473" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">things like this start to happen</a>.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/taxes/3255/29">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/taxes/3255/29</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 07 Mar 2010 02:07:48 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3255-29</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/taxes/3255.rss">Taxes?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Taxes?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[mental2k]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>In that case I’m all for tax, lol.  Within sensible limits.  Oh yeah I hate stealth taxes, I’d rather they were just up front with what they are charging us too.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/taxes/3255/28">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/taxes/3255/28</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 06 Mar 2010 18:34:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3255-28</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/taxes/3255.rss">Taxes?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Taxes?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[danielsangeo]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>To me, the “way taxes are spent” is a separate (but related) issue.  To me, if you disagree with how your taxes are spent, then it’s related to who you put into office.  However, you have to be careful there because your hope to stop what you feel is “wasteful” might have unforeseen consequences. [color=’<span class="hashtag">#212121</span>’]c wat i did thar?</p>
<p>Taxes are spent on a LOT of good things in the countries that collect them; from roads to laws enforcement to food regulation.  Most people would not recognize their country if the government stopped operating and just shrunk down to the size where you can drown it in a bathtub<a href="https://ic2.pbase.com/v3/90/78990/1/49857062.25DrownGovernmentintheBathtub.jpg" data-bbcode="true">.</a></p>
<p>They’re also spent on a lot of bad things that many think we need.  And we disagree on what those “bad things” are.  But that discussion is inevitably lost in the “taxes are teh evul” arguments.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/taxes/3255/27">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/taxes/3255/27</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 06 Mar 2010 17:58:32 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3255-27</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/taxes/3255.rss">Taxes?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Taxes?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[mental2k]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Personally I have no problem with tax.  It pays for our health service (UK) and various other things.  What I do disagree with is some of the ways it is spent.  Creating pointless jobs is one!  Some of the jobs I have seen advertised in newspapers by local authorities are pointless and overpaid.  I’ll give an example from the times A “protected learning time facilitator” in Luton, Bedfordshire, whose task was to organise the temporary closure of all GP surgeries in the town.</p>
<p>My biggest problem with miss-spent tax money are people who fraudulently claim benefits.  They put nothing back into society and are not interested in getting a job. When they’re caught they are not even forced to pay the money back.  They get a token fine.  Makes me angry, as there are 14 year old children making more of a contribution to society than them.</p>
<p>/end rant.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/taxes/3255/26">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/taxes/3255/26</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 06 Mar 2010 17:36:12 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3255-26</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/taxes/3255.rss">Taxes?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Taxes?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[danielsangeo]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Zerego">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/z/c57346/40.png" class="avatar"> Zerego:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>So much for maturity.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Whom are you responding to, Zerego?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/taxes/3255/25">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/taxes/3255/25</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 06 Mar 2010 17:27:25 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3255-25</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/taxes/3255.rss">Taxes?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Taxes?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Zerego]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>So much for maturity.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/taxes/3255/24">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/taxes/3255/24</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 06 Mar 2010 17:25:33 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3255-24</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/taxes/3255.rss">Taxes?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Taxes?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[danielsangeo]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="cceplopu">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/c/b9e5f3/40.png" class="avatar"> cceplopu:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Enjoy being taxed on land you own and having your income taken away.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>You wouldn’t have an “income” if it weren’t for government assistance.</p>
<p>I don’t want to talk about “printing more money” (inflation) in this thread.  I want to devote this thread solely to taxes.  Can we keep on topic, please?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/taxes/3255/23">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/taxes/3255/23</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 06 Mar 2010 17:15:18 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3255-23</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/taxes/3255.rss">Taxes?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Taxes?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Mr.Shadow]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I don’t care about paying taxes as long as the taxes go to something meaningfull, like highways and airports. However, if it goes to fundraising or something like that I’d hate it. Not because I hate people n Africa but rather because our so-called “leader” (he’s actually a massive prick that made something like 4 governments fail, but still gets elected probably because there’s aot of christians here and he’s christian himself but whatever) did that for three years. The country I live in (the Netherlands) has a government (actually had because we have NO governement until May) which acts like it doesn’t care about the country, but rather wants to kill the Dutch stereotype (greedy people) by being the most generous country in the world. There are alot of problems that could’ve been solved years ago if it weren’t for that stupid idiot pumping 1/3th all our money in Africa and the like. But because we had no budget for those problems our country has, the country still has the same problems.</p>
<p>In addition, the plan they had on "fixing’ the problem with the economy here would’ve most likely worsenned the problem. It could all be solved if we got our military back home so we don’t have to pump the second 1/3th in all that.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/taxes/3255/22">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/taxes/3255/22</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 06 Mar 2010 16:22:28 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3255-22</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/taxes/3255.rss">Taxes?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Taxes?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[baconeggs]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Print extra money during economic times and don’t tell anyone about it. Result = INFLATION FREE STIMULUS!</p>
<p>Too bad that doesn’t work.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/taxes/3255/21">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/taxes/3255/21</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 06 Mar 2010 10:13:58 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3255-21</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/taxes/3255.rss">Taxes?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Taxes?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[cceplopu]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Jingles">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/j/46a35a/40.png" class="avatar"> Jingles:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>If they print more billls, then the value of each one decreases as there are more to go around. Think about it mate.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Did you know the United States is in the midst of a recession?  Did you know the government conjured up 700 billion+ last fall to hand out?  Connect the dots.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/taxes/3255/20">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/taxes/3255/20</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 06 Mar 2010 09:34:49 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3255-20</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/taxes/3255.rss">Taxes?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Taxes?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[cceplopu]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Comrade Tiki">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Comrade Tiki:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Enjoy your tattered bills and roadside muggings.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Apparently you misunderstood.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/taxes/3255/19">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/taxes/3255/19</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 06 Mar 2010 09:22:10 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3255-19</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/taxes/3255.rss">Taxes?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Taxes?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Jingles]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>If they print more billls, then the value of each one decreases as there are more to go around. Think about it mate.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/taxes/3255/18">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/taxes/3255/18</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 06 Mar 2010 09:22:05 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3255-18</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/taxes/3255.rss">Taxes?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Taxes?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Comrade_Tiki]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="cceplopu">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/c/b9e5f3/40.png" class="avatar"> cceplopu:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I don’t know why the United States needs to tax it’s citizens anymore.  They already print out billions upon billions for their own purposes, what do they need our money for anymore?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Enjoy your tattered bills and roadside muggings.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/taxes/3255/17">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/taxes/3255/17</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 06 Mar 2010 09:19:40 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3255-17</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/taxes/3255.rss">Taxes?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Taxes?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[cceplopu]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I don’t know why the United States needs to tax it’s citizens anymore.  They already print out billions upon billions for their own purposes, what do they need our money for anymore?</p>
<p>Country will fall sooner or later anyway though.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/taxes/3255/16">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/taxes/3255/16</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 06 Mar 2010 08:58:49 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3255-16</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/taxes/3255.rss">Taxes?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Taxes?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Jingles]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Especially inheritance tax, that is a load of bull.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/taxes/3255/15">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/taxes/3255/15</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 06 Mar 2010 08:56:49 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3255-15</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/taxes/3255.rss">Taxes?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Taxes?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[cceplopu]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Enjoy being taxed on land you own and having your income taken away.</p>
<p>Oh, looks like you are enjoying it.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/taxes/3255/14">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/taxes/3255/14</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 06 Mar 2010 08:53:24 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3255-14</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/taxes/3255.rss">Taxes?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Taxes?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Level]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="cceplopu">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/c/b9e5f3/40.png" class="avatar"> cceplopu:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Income and property taxes are complete bullshit.</p>
<p>That is all.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Enjoy your unpaved roads.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/taxes/3255/13">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/taxes/3255/13</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 06 Mar 2010 08:52:43 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3255-13</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/taxes/3255.rss">Taxes?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Taxes?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[cceplopu]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Income and property taxes are complete bullshit.</p>
<p>That is all.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/taxes/3255/12">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/taxes/3255/12</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 06 Mar 2010 08:51:22 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3255-12</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/taxes/3255.rss">Taxes?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Taxes?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Skizzam]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I totally agree that its necessary for people to be taxed, But that doesn’t mean i cant bitch about it. Barely scraping by as it is</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/taxes/3255/11">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/taxes/3255/11</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 06 Mar 2010 08:44:28 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3255-11</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/taxes/3255.rss">Taxes?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Taxes?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[X_Mastershot_X]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>to be serious I don’t agree with my government’s economic policy. They sold out every possible mine and factory. They didn’t build anything useful. and when the government had nothing to get money from, they started raising the tax levels. They have been very spendthrift. We have lots of problems. I wonder how this is going to end.</p>
<p>Edit: sorry for my bad english I am still trying to improve it at the college, I hope you can understand me.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/taxes/3255/10">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/taxes/3255/10</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 06 Mar 2010 08:25:29 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3255-10</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/taxes/3255.rss">Taxes?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Taxes?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[danielsangeo]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="X_Mastershot_X">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/x/c5a1d2/40.png" class="avatar"> X_Mastershot_X:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>taxes suck.</p>
<p>No need to thank me[/SIZE]</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>A government-free state (AKA ‘failed state’) would suck a whole helluva lot more.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/taxes/3255/9">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/taxes/3255/9</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 06 Mar 2010 07:27:11 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3255-9</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/taxes/3255.rss">Taxes?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Taxes?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[X_Mastershot_X]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>taxes suck.</p>
<p>No need to thank me[/SIZE]</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/taxes/3255/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/taxes/3255/8</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 05 Mar 2010 19:48:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3255-8</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/taxes/3255.rss">Taxes?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Taxes?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[mattemuse]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>These are the people you want to have a “mature discussion” with.</p>
<p><img src="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/original/2X/f/f9b6b8c3570d8f1c57dbe63c81651d393843b8bb.png" alt="" data-base62-sha1="zD4mUUzGDm7iTUnTQdP2SrRysVt" width="543" height="317"></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/taxes/3255/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/taxes/3255/7</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 05 Mar 2010 16:00:09 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3255-7</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/taxes/3255.rss">Taxes?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Taxes?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[baconeggs]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>People who complain about taxes only see the government taking their money. If I had it my way I’d make all citizens of a taxed country play SimCity 4 so they could see exactly why taxes exist. You want the government to build roads and a new police station? Then give them some damn money so they can actually do it. Not happy about where your taxes are being spent? Tough shit, the government decides what is more important to work on in society. You don’t like those decisions then VOTE against it. Don’t like that system? Then go set up your own bloody country or start a revolution.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/taxes/3255/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/taxes/3255/6</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 05 Mar 2010 07:53:17 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3255-6</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/taxes/3255.rss">Taxes?</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
