<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Vortigaunts and The Freeman</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/vortigaunts-and-the-freeman/4927</link>
    <description>We all know that Freeman is deeply connected with the Vortigaunts. They rescued Alyx and Gordon at the beginning of Episode One, screwing with G-Man in the process. The White Forest Mines Vort mentions that Freeman &quot;bears some traits [they] thought innate to Vort-kind.&quot; Even more interesting is that they haven&#39;t really forgiven Gordon for killing so many of their own, but have allied with him - and the rest of earth - for the common purpose of freedom.

This is one of the biggest mysteries in the series; it&#39;s right there behind G-man and those huge pistons at the base of the Citadel.

How are they connected? Why did this happen? Why can&#39;t Gordon shoot lightning from his hands? All are important questions.



The Vorts (most notably the &quot;All-Knowing&quot; Vort) have some [i]very[/i] interesting things to say on this subject, and others, if you +USE them. Some of the quotes even seem to be leaning on the fourth wall.

[i]&quot;Something secret steers us both. We shall not name it.&quot;

&quot;We remember the Freeman. We are coterminous.&quot;

&quot;We cannot forget those whose cords you cut. Forgiveness is not ours to bestow.&quot;

&quot;Far distant eyes look out through yours.&quot;

&quot;That sharp spur of hope has not dulled to this day. For once the lesser master lay defeated, we knew the greater must also fall in time. &quot;[/SIZE][/i]

Check the attached file to see them all, excerpted from closecaption_english.txt in source engine.gcf.



EDit: Oh, I forgot to mention that this thread is to discuss this. Obviously.
&lt;a class=&#39;attachment&#39; href=&#39;/uploads/default/original/1X/ad915ec1ca49e06d6c9a2b00e830f2f19d76bcca.txt&#39;&gt;Vort Quotes.txt&lt;/a&gt; (3.04 KB)</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 31 Jul 2010 20:53:03 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Half-Life Series</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/vortigaunts-and-the-freeman/4927.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Vortigaunts and The Freeman</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[FireTime]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I think that it’s a little farce to think that advisors arrived at that exact moment. While I do see it possible they could breach defenses without detection (kind of an insignificant/impossible talking point  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=9" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"> ). Due the events preceding the death of Eli I think that it was made fairly obvious that G-man intervened on some level to cause such events to happen. From what we know of g-man his preferred style of interaction is to nuge or setup the environments necessary for his goals to be achieved and let others accomplish them for him. (think all of HL1 and HL2) In fact EP1 is the first time your not doing g-mans bidding thanks to the Vortigaunts.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/vortigaunts-and-the-freeman/4927/72">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/vortigaunts-and-the-freeman/4927/72</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 31 Jul 2010 20:53:03 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-4927-72</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/vortigaunts-and-the-freeman/4927.rss">Vortigaunts and The Freeman</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Vortigaunts and The Freeman</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[mechaelite]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>what I think is that the advisors could pass the white forest defenses thanks to their powers, while the striders were distracting everyone they could have destroyed or manipulated some of the defenses. And the G-man already knew this and wanted to warn Eli. Or how johnyo said, he could be telling him that he would discover the borealis on the message…</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/vortigaunts-and-the-freeman/4927/71">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/vortigaunts-and-the-freeman/4927/71</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 31 Jul 2010 19:17:33 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-4927-71</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/vortigaunts-and-the-freeman/4927.rss">Vortigaunts and The Freeman</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Vortigaunts and The Freeman</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[johnyo]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Pyro">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/p/71e660/40.png" class="avatar"> Pyro:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>It was preemptive, because he “warned” Eli ahead of time.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I think that the “unforseen consequences” refer to the borealis, just like Eli himself voiced, rather than Eli’s death, but that’s just a matter of opinion since we can’t really know for sure.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Pyro">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/p/71e660/40.png" class="avatar"> Pyro:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>It’s not very likely at all that G-Man wants what’s in the Borealis, because if he wanted it, he could easily have taken it at any time. He’s quite powerful, or so we’re led to believe.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>During the cutscene in ep2 Gman admitted he is not allowed to meddle much in the happenings directly. One might, of course, argue wheather he was being truthful in that statement or not.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Pyro">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/p/71e660/40.png" class="avatar"> Pyro:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>It’s more likely that Eli died because he was trying to rebel against the G-Man.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Gman is in a position where it hardly matters wheather anyone agrees with him or not. I don’t think he would see Eli (or any human for that matter) as a threat.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/vortigaunts-and-the-freeman/4927/70">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/vortigaunts-and-the-freeman/4927/70</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 31 Jul 2010 19:02:51 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-4927-70</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/vortigaunts-and-the-freeman/4927.rss">Vortigaunts and The Freeman</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Vortigaunts and The Freeman</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Pyroclase]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>It was preemptive, because he “warned” Eli ahead of time.</p>
<p>It’s not very likely at all that G-Man wants what’s in the Borealis, because if he wanted it, he could easily have taken it at any time. He’s quite powerful, or so we’re led to believe. It’s more likely that Eli died because he was trying to rebel against the G-Man.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/vortigaunts-and-the-freeman/4927/69">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/vortigaunts-and-the-freeman/4927/69</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 31 Jul 2010 18:39:56 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-4927-69</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/vortigaunts-and-the-freeman/4927.rss">Vortigaunts and The Freeman</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Vortigaunts and The Freeman</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[FireTime]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Yah I agree that G-man had dealings with the death of Eli. (they kind of banged that into the players skull) But was the closing of the portal the reason for killing him or was Eli blowing his cover/his intention of destroying the Borealis the true meaning. I think this does provide a good cover of the true story line from the player so when the true story is revealed it can be looked back on as an ah-ha moment.</p>
<p>It could be possible that G-man (or his associates) want what is in the Borealis. Think this would give credence of my concept that G-man killed Eli because of his proposed actions of destroying the Borealis not his past actions of closing the portal. Also I think this fits better with G-man’s style of preemptive actions, not reactive ones.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/vortigaunts-and-the-freeman/4927/68">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/vortigaunts-and-the-freeman/4927/68</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 31 Jul 2010 17:24:01 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-4927-68</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/vortigaunts-and-the-freeman/4927.rss">Vortigaunts and The Freeman</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Vortigaunts and The Freeman</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Pyroclase]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I don’t think you understand the scope of what’s going on behind the scenes. It’s all too possible that Eli’s untimely death was the result of G-Man’s machinations; surely you haven’t forgotten the “unforeseen consequences?” He was probably referring to the fact that closing the portal would surely trigger some sort of backlash from the Combine.</p>
<p>It just doesn’t make sense that those two Advisors would be able to get into the base so easily, without even triggering an alarm; White Forest obviously has some sort of perimeter monitoring system. (that’s how they knew where the Striders were coming from, not to mention the ease with which MIRT was able to rig up a radar to the car) G-Man, however, could easily set up such an incident.</p>
<p>Does anybody have any idea where this discussion is going? Or, for that matter, how it got here?[/SIZE]</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Pettifogg">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/p/ebca7d/40.png" class="avatar"> Pettifogg:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>This thread is a joy to read. <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=9" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Why thank you. Glad to see it’s actually possible to spark some intelligent discussion here.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/vortigaunts-and-the-freeman/4927/67">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/vortigaunts-and-the-freeman/4927/67</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 31 Jul 2010 16:50:04 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-4927-67</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/vortigaunts-and-the-freeman/4927.rss">Vortigaunts and The Freeman</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Vortigaunts and The Freeman</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[FireTime]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Eli talked about a power that can(should) not be harnessed or controlled in the Borealis. Kleiner wanted to use it because (just guessing because of the nature of his character) it is a new power or energy source that was created or, I think more likely, recently discovered/harnessed (vortessence?). At the end of ep2 Eli tells the player (Gordon) about his knowledge of the g-man. Now that we know that he knows g-man I would have to suspect that he has a better understanding of the tech involved (due to two things, first is he’s a scientist that makes g-dam teleporters <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=9" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"> , second is that…  i’m not entirely sure how to place it into words but it’s kind of cliché but it has to do to the way I saw the ending of ep2. They build up Eli to be the all-knowing character then kill him as soon as the player would have access to this information. This concept has be used over and over in a plethora of movies. Now the main character has to learn what he was going to be told first hand. And when he learns it, it will all make sense. Due to the face we see eli working closely with vorts and his daughter also being close to them I would suspect his attempting to stop, contain the Borealis’es powers conceivable.</p>
<p>EDIT: also <a class="mention" href="/u/pettifogg">@Pettifogg</a> inorite!</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/vortigaunts-and-the-freeman/4927/66">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/vortigaunts-and-the-freeman/4927/66</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 31 Jul 2010 09:53:41 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-4927-66</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/vortigaunts-and-the-freeman/4927.rss">Vortigaunts and The Freeman</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Vortigaunts and The Freeman</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Pettifogg]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>This thread is a joy to read. <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=9" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/vortigaunts-and-the-freeman/4927/65">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/vortigaunts-and-the-freeman/4927/65</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 31 Jul 2010 03:07:02 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-4927-65</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/vortigaunts-and-the-freeman/4927.rss">Vortigaunts and The Freeman</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Vortigaunts and The Freeman</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Hazelwolf]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Pyro">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/p/71e660/40.png" class="avatar"> Pyro:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>So, we have to choose between either teleporting somewhere (probably full of Combine) or shooting lighting from your fingers? I mean, teleportation (if that’s what they’re even doing on that ship) isn’t too useful for a gameplay mechanic. The potential for sequence breaking <span class="bbcode-i">alone</span> was reason for a similar ability to be cut from <span class="bbcode-i">Bioshock</span>.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>More than likely. To be honest open choice, although an interesting concept, within Ep3 would just feel weird. Linearity has worked for them so far and so it should remain. It’s essentially interactive story telling where the only dialogue the protagonist is capable of is bullets.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Pyro">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/p/71e660/40.png" class="avatar"> Pyro:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Now, what about the Vort’s apparent unwillingness to forgive Gordon for his acts of violence (his “personal holocaust,” as G-Man puts it) at Black Mesa? It’s not like they’re gonna turn on Gordon once we win, but it’s still an interesting idea. Though, if they can see the future… :fffuuu:</p>
<p>Also, has anybody else realized that we’re bringing in string theory and quantum mechanics just to speculate about the plot? :jizz:</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I hope not, I like the Vorts, they’re awesome. I should think that a creature that sees gratitude as unnecessary to beings bonded by common cause and nature is unlikely to hold a treacherous grudge, especially as it has worked in their favour.</p>
<p>The way i interpreted the “we haven’t forgotten, forgiveness is not ours to bestow” line is simply that they will always remember their fallen kin who Gordon killed during the BM incident, linked as they are through the fourth dimension. But as those vorts died as Gordon’s enemies the surviving vorts are unable to definitively forgive Gordon on their behalf. The Victory Mine Vort’s thoughts on death: ‘an eternity’s repose. It brings peaceful thoughts, does it not?’ strike me as the thoughts of a race that isn’t given over to seek needless revenge in the name of the dead. We also need to remember that the vorts are speaking English (or whatever language the game is translated into) as a second language. Flux shifting is probably able to convey very complex concepts and emotions but as they have to speak in an auditary language using human terms it’s very difficult to tell exactly what they mean at times.</p>
<p>As for the Quantum theory: Might seem a bit overkill for an FPS plot but Mark Laidlaw is a pretty cool guy, eh writes intelligent sci-fi and doesn’t afraid of anything.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/vortigaunts-and-the-freeman/4927/64">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/vortigaunts-and-the-freeman/4927/64</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jul 2010 16:29:41 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-4927-64</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/vortigaunts-and-the-freeman/4927.rss">Vortigaunts and The Freeman</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Vortigaunts and The Freeman</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Pyroclase]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Hazelwolf">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/h/ba8739/40.png" class="avatar"> Hazelwolf:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>It would make for an interesting option: the choice between the power of Science the Borealis offers or the power of the Vortessence.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>So, we have to choose between either teleporting somewhere (probably full of Combine) or shooting lighting from your fingers? I mean, teleportation (if that’s what they’re even doing on that ship) isn’t too useful for a gameplay mechanic. The potential for sequence breaking <span class="bbcode-i">alone</span> was reason for a similar ability to be cut from <span class="bbcode-i">Bioshock</span>.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Hazelwolf">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/h/ba8739/40.png" class="avatar"> Hazelwolf:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>The Vorts do make mention of being able to perceive moments in time simultaneously, seeing gordon both in the present and in the nihilanth’s chamber. So time and space when perceived within the context of the vortessence become one in the same so it could be that the GMan uses the same principle.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Yeah, that makes sense.<br>
It’s possible that they can see the past, present, and future (the 4th dimension) all at once, in the same way that we can see all the space in front of us (the 1st, 2nd, and 3rd dimensions) (we can’t see behind us, but that’s a biological thing) at once. That is, they are to the 5th dimension what we are to the 4th dimension. I think someone posted a great <a href="https://www.darkroastedblend.com/2009/01/imagining-tenth-dimension.html" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">video</a> of the concepts earlier.</p>
<p>Now, what about the Vort’s apparent unwillingness to forgive Gordon for his acts of violence (his “personal holocaust,” as G-Man puts it) at Black Mesa? I think I already said this, but it seems like the Vorts are only fighting alongside humanity to free themselves; at least those enslaved by the Combine, or the higher power they seem to be hinting at. It’s not like they’re gonna turn on Gordon once we win, but it’s still an interesting idea. Though, if they can see the future… :fffuuu:</p>
<p>Also, has anybody else realized that we’re bringing in string theory and quantum mechanics just to speculate about the plot? :jizz:</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/vortigaunts-and-the-freeman/4927/63">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/vortigaunts-and-the-freeman/4927/63</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jul 2010 15:59:14 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-4927-63</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/vortigaunts-and-the-freeman/4927.rss">Vortigaunts and The Freeman</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Vortigaunts and The Freeman</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Hazelwolf]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="johnyo">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/j/a9a28c/40.png" class="avatar"> johnyo:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I’d assume there’s more to this ‘vortessence’ than ethical treatment.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>What I meant, but didn’t do a very good job of explaining, is not that ethics and the vortessence are the same but that it makes sense that each sentient race would approach and explain things in their own terms. Just as humans have coined the terms ‘Humane’ and ‘Human rights’ to pertain to certain standards of ethics the Vortigaunts have given their own terms ‘Vortessence’ and ‘Vortal’ to how they perceive the conditions under which they live. So the Vortessence itself could be accessed, perceived and utilised by other species other than just the Vortigaunts. Vortessence is just their term for a thing that could be universal.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="johnyo">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/j/a9a28c/40.png" class="avatar"> johnyo:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>It wouldn’t be that hard for a different being to appear and sound as a human (and it’s not like it’s very good at either of those things.)<br>
<img src="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/original/2X/2/2b8657e314e9c459135f2efc701e776c0bd32e13.gif" alt="" data-base62-sha1="6d2mlx8Sa6NaosIGNuKHUXUO1gv" width="110" height="110"></p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p><img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/smiley.png?v=9" title=":smiley:" class="emoji only-emoji" alt=":smiley:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/vortigaunts-and-the-freeman/4927/62">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/vortigaunts-and-the-freeman/4927/62</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jul 2010 14:51:40 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-4927-62</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/vortigaunts-and-the-freeman/4927.rss">Vortigaunts and The Freeman</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Vortigaunts and The Freeman</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[johnyo]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="mechaelite">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/m/c68b51/40.png" class="avatar"> mechaelite:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>You love avoid my arguments don’t you?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>huh?</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Hazelwolf">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/h/ba8739/40.png" class="avatar"> Hazelwolf:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>my sarcasm detector’s in the shop so I’m not sure if that’s what you’re being here.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I wasn’t  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/wink.png?v=9" title=":wink:" class="emoji" alt=":wink:"></p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Hazelwolf">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/h/ba8739/40.png" class="avatar"> Hazelwolf:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I suppose it comes down to what the vortessence actually is and whether it’s something specific to the Vortigaunt psychic interconnection or if it’s simply their name for the life force of the multiverse that connects all living and sentient creatures, much in the same way ‘humane’ refers to the ideal of fair and ethical treatment which is not necessarily unique to human beings. The overwiki seems to go with the latter.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>From some of the things the vorts say, like <span class="bbcode-i">“We are a tapestry woven of Vortessence. It is the same for you if only you would see it.”</span> I’d assume there’s more to this ‘vortessence’ than ethical treatment. However, since it’s not specified wheather “you” implies Gordon or human race in general, I can’t really back this up. (brb, looking at more quotes)</p>
<p>[EDIT] I’m back!<span class="bbcode-i"> “For a brief time you joined with us. You are one. Between the worlds.”</span> I believe this suggests Gordon (and Alyx) have obtained vortessenceness (:aah <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=9" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:">  at the beginning of HL2 (or end of HL). So, I guess, other humans can’t access those powers.</p>
<p>P.S. I use the term ‘vortessence’ loosely as I have no idea what it means (I guess I shouldn’t be using it at all in that case. Oh, well…  :s hrugs: ) I just assume that this ‘vortessence’ allows the vorts (and Gman?) to manage those shenanigans with the timespace.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Hazelwolf">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/h/ba8739/40.png" class="avatar"> Hazelwolf:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>In which case it’s very likely that the GMan uses the same principles to interact and control Gordon. How that has any bearing on his implied time travelling and use of portals is uncertain, but the Vorts do make mention of being able to perceive moments in time simultaneously, seeing gordon both in the present and in the nihilanth’s chamber. So time and space when perceived within the context of the vortessence become one in the same so it could be that the GMan uses the same principle.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>^this</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Hazelwolf">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/h/ba8739/40.png" class="avatar"> Hazelwolf:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>The purple? probably something specific to the Vorts or something mystical and sciencey. It’s very unlikely that the GMan’s actual appearance, whatever that may be, is in any way like the grey-toned human we are accustomed to so it’s likely it’s all a deception to allow him to appear unnoticed to humans and to keep his true nature hidden. In which case he can appear however he wants when using the vortessence if that’s what it is.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I must admit I have always thought of gman as human… well -ish. Now that I think of it, that is completely stupid. It wouldn’t be that hard for a different being to appear and sound as a human (and it’s not like it’s very good at either of those things.)</p>
<p><img src="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/original/2X/2/2b8657e314e9c459135f2efc701e776c0bd32e13.gif" alt="" data-base62-sha1="6d2mlx8Sa6NaosIGNuKHUXUO1gv" width="110" height="110"><br>
[Another edit] Hey, that explains the cockroaches in BMRF!</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/vortigaunts-and-the-freeman/4927/61">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/vortigaunts-and-the-freeman/4927/61</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jul 2010 14:25:40 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-4927-61</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/vortigaunts-and-the-freeman/4927.rss">Vortigaunts and The Freeman</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Vortigaunts and The Freeman</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Hazelwolf]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="johnyo">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/j/a9a28c/40.png" class="avatar"> johnyo:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>OOOOOOOOHHHHH! Gman uses the vortessence!!! So Gordon can do it too, he just doesn’t know how!</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>my sarcasm detector’s in the shop so I’m not sure if that’s what you’re being here. But meh, why not run with it. I suppose it comes down to what the vortessence actually is and whether it’s something specific to the Vortigaunt psychic interconnection or if it’s simply their name for the life force of the multiverse that connects all living and sentient creatures, much in the same way ‘humane’ refers to the ideal of fair and ethical treatment which is not necessarily unique to human beings. The overwiki seems to go with the latter.</p>
<p>In which case it’s very likely that the GMan uses the same principles to interact and control Gordon. How that has any bearing on his implied time travelling and use of portals is uncertain, but the Vorts do make mention of being able to perceive moments in time simultaneously, seeing gordon both in the present and in the nihilanth’s chamber. So time and space when perceived within the context of the vortessence become one in the same so it could be that the GMan uses the same principle.</p>
<p>The purple? probably something specific to the Vorts or something mystical and sciencey. It’s very unlikely that the GMan’s actual appearance, whatever that may be, is in any way like the grey-toned human we are accustomed to so it’s likely it’s all a deception to allow him to appear unnoticed to humans and to keep his true nature hidden. In which case he can appear however he wants when using the vortessence if that’s what it is. He seems to have a thing for negative shading  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=9" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/vortigaunts-and-the-freeman/4927/60">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/vortigaunts-and-the-freeman/4927/60</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jul 2010 13:40:11 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-4927-60</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/vortigaunts-and-the-freeman/4927.rss">Vortigaunts and The Freeman</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Vortigaunts and The Freeman</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[mechaelite]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="johnyo">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/j/a9a28c/40.png" class="avatar"> johnyo:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Source?</p>
<p>Source?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>No source, from playing I have not seen any vort ussing vortessence for anything wich isn’t heal OR stop G-man.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="johnyo">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/j/a9a28c/40.png" class="avatar"> johnyo:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I guess you’re right here. Since he can manipulate the time?space in that state (showing different locations from the present and past and even blending them together) and don’t see how he could avoid turning purple (which, by the way, could be exclusive to vorts, thus voiding your argument completely.)</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>You love avoid my arguments don’t you?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/vortigaunts-and-the-freeman/4927/59">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/vortigaunts-and-the-freeman/4927/59</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jul 2010 12:08:50 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-4927-59</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/vortigaunts-and-the-freeman/4927.rss">Vortigaunts and The Freeman</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Vortigaunts and The Freeman</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[johnyo]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="mechaelite">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/m/c68b51/40.png" class="avatar"> mechaelite:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>no, G-man does not use it, the vortessence is more telephatic and healing powers than teleporting and stop time ones…</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Source?</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="mechaelite">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/m/c68b51/40.png" class="avatar"> mechaelite:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>the G-man has other powers wich can be stopped for a while with the vortessence…</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Source?</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="mechaelite">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/m/c68b51/40.png" class="avatar"> mechaelite:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>When a vort uses the vortessence it turns purple/blue, I didn’t see any G-man purple/blue yet… Hell can you imagine him in those colors?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I guess you’re right here. Since he can manipulate the time?space in that state (showing different locations from the present and past and even blending them together) and don’t see how he could avoid turning purple (which, by the way, could be exclusive to vorts, thus voiding your argument completely.)</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/vortigaunts-and-the-freeman/4927/58">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/vortigaunts-and-the-freeman/4927/58</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jul 2010 11:53:33 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-4927-58</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/vortigaunts-and-the-freeman/4927.rss">Vortigaunts and The Freeman</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Vortigaunts and The Freeman</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[mechaelite]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>no, G-man does not use it, the vortessence is more telephatic and healing powers than teleporting and stop time ones… the G-man has other powers wich can be stopped for a while with the vortessence… When a vort uses the vortessence it turns purple/blue, I didn’t see any G-man purple/blue yet… Hell can you imagine him in those colors?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/vortigaunts-and-the-freeman/4927/57">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/vortigaunts-and-the-freeman/4927/57</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jul 2010 11:35:16 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-4927-57</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/vortigaunts-and-the-freeman/4927.rss">Vortigaunts and The Freeman</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Vortigaunts and The Freeman</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[johnyo]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="mechaelite">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/m/c68b51/40.png" class="avatar"> mechaelite:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I think it’s more like that of they would like to die for honor if with their deads they can save someone or something.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Protip: look up the term “interval”</p>
<p>As forthe vortessence I don’t think it has anything to do with shooting lightning. That power seems to be more of a physical (biological) ability of the vorts (not unlike spitting acid for the antlion workers). I can’t remember the vorts ever using the lightning for any kind of ritual. IMO the vortessence is about what the vorts did at the start of ep1 and healing alyx in ep2. Apparently Gordon (or any human in general?) can also access the vortessence to some extent. Or maybe the quote just implies that all living beings share something in common. (this does not fly well with the “if only you would see it” part.) OOOOOOOOHHHHH! Gman uses the vortessence!!! So Gordon can do it too, he just doesn’t know how!</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/vortigaunts-and-the-freeman/4927/56">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/vortigaunts-and-the-freeman/4927/56</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jul 2010 11:23:06 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-4927-56</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/vortigaunts-and-the-freeman/4927.rss">Vortigaunts and The Freeman</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Vortigaunts and The Freeman</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[mechaelite]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="sams ron">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 sams ron:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Denzel Washington, Samual L Jackson, and Chris Tucker to be the first person to die in it lol.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>:facepalm:<br>
If you think you are funny you are wrong. You little crockroach eeeeh… gargantua. You are not going to win fans by doing such stupid things in this forums.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Orpheon">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/o/6bbea6/40.png" class="avatar"> Orpheon:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>“What seems to you a sacrifice is merely, to us, an oscillation. We do not fear the interval of darkness.” On the wiki this quote was suggested to mean that vortigaunts might have the power to reincarnate in new bodies after death through use of the vortessence. I’m not sure that’s what was originally meant by the quote but it’s an interesting idea.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>The idea is a good possibility but I think it’s more like that of they would like to die for honor if with their deads they can save someone or something.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/vortigaunts-and-the-freeman/4927/55">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/vortigaunts-and-the-freeman/4927/55</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jul 2010 08:58:52 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-4927-55</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/vortigaunts-and-the-freeman/4927.rss">Vortigaunts and The Freeman</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Vortigaunts and The Freeman</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Hazelwolf]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Orpheon">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/o/6bbea6/40.png" class="avatar"> Orpheon:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Strictly speaking, I don’t think the vorts are quite at the level of a hive mind.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Good point. I was tired and hive mind felt like a good catch-all term, but your description sums them up much more accurately. It’s more like their society exists mostly on the telepathic level rather than the physical as humans do. They certainly seem to put greater emphasis on the community than the individual. The Bugbait Vort in HL2 refers to himself as “this one” and the concept of names, as humans understand them, seem to be a new thing. Uriah seems to have taken on a few mantels of individuality, probably to do with being in a position of honour.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Orpheon">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/o/6bbea6/40.png" class="avatar"> Orpheon:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>whatever power the vortigaunts tap into to use their abilities, such as telepathy and yes, electrical discharges, could also be used by humans if they knew how.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>It’s a possibility if the electrical abilities and Vortal manipulation stem from a higher mental state rather than anything biological, a channeling of the vortessence itself. Even so, although a portion of Ep3 spent as a Vortigordon, facing down advisors backed up with purple vorts blasting away with vortal energy, would be all kinds of win, I doubt it’ll come into play. Unless it were just a momentary thing for the game’s climax much like the super grav gun. It would make for an interesting option: the choice between the power of Science the Borealis offers or the power of the Vortessence.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/vortigaunts-and-the-freeman/4927/54">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/vortigaunts-and-the-freeman/4927/54</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jul 2010 07:10:48 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-4927-54</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/vortigaunts-and-the-freeman/4927.rss">Vortigaunts and The Freeman</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Vortigaunts and The Freeman</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Orpheon]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Hazelwolf">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/h/ba8739/40.png" class="avatar"> Hazelwolf:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>The vortigaunt view of the world is very social, probably born of being a hive mind and perceiving the world on a higher dimension than humanity. They view death as a transition to a peaceful state of being.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Strictly speaking, I don’t think the vorts are quite at the level of a hive mind. Certainly they have a strong form of telepathy among them, good enough to send images to another vortigaunt, as evidenced by Alyx’s statement that sometimes vorts get sent to Nova Propekt and send pictures back, and binding enough that affinities and mannerisms can spread between them without contact, as evidenced by the Victory Mine’s use of Magnusson’s expression “What next in the parade of constant interruptions?” However, a hive mind in science fiction usually refers to a single consciousness sharing many bodies, which is not the case with the vortigaunts, who retain a good measure of individuality. A hive mind could also refer to a superorganism, which is defined as “a collection of agents which can act in concert to produce phenomena governed by the collective”, but that sort of term is generally attributed to organisms with very little intelligence of their own but that can accomplish complex tasks in great numbers. Vortigaunts, while communal, are quite intelligent themselves and do not seem to be exhibit greater intelligence in groups any more than humans do.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Hazelwolf">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/h/ba8739/40.png" class="avatar"> Hazelwolf:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>For srs though I feel the vort was talking about transcendental matters rather than gameplay mechanics. plus, Gordon’s human. Shooting lightning is something we generally aren’t biologically adapted for. The only way Gordon’s going to be shooting lightning is if he found a shockroach.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I agree with this. However, despite his physiology the All Knowing Vortigaunt says “We are a tapestry woven of Vortessence. It is the same for you if only you would see it.” This suggests that whatever power the vortigaunts tap into to use their abilities, such as telepathy and yes, electrical discharges, could also be used by humans if they knew how.</p>
<p>“What seems to you a sacrifice is merely, to us, an oscillation. We do not fear the interval of darkness.” On the wiki this quote was suggested to mean that vortigaunts might have the power to reincarnate in new bodies after death through use of the vortessence. I’m not sure that’s what was originally meant by the quote but it’s an interesting idea.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/vortigaunts-and-the-freeman/4927/53">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/vortigaunts-and-the-freeman/4927/53</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jul 2010 03:51:32 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-4927-53</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/vortigaunts-and-the-freeman/4927.rss">Vortigaunts and The Freeman</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Vortigaunts and The Freeman</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Hazelwolf]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Pyro">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/p/71e660/40.png" class="avatar"> Pyro:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Now, the question I want answered is why Gordon can’t shoot lighting. The Vorts say something about how “you are not so different from us, if only you would see it.”</p>
<p>I really hope he realizes it in Episode 3.  :awesome:</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Because he has rubber boots.</p>
<p>For srs though I feel the vort was talking about transcendental matters rather than gameplay mechanics. plus, Gordon’s human. Shooting lightning is something we generally aren’t biologically adapted for. The only way Gordon’s going to be shooting lightning is if he found a shockroach.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/vortigaunts-and-the-freeman/4927/52">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/vortigaunts-and-the-freeman/4927/52</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jul 2010 00:20:22 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-4927-52</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/vortigaunts-and-the-freeman/4927.rss">Vortigaunts and The Freeman</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Vortigaunts and The Freeman</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Pyroclase]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Now, the question I want answered is why Gordon can’t shoot lighting. The Vorts say something about how “you are not so different from us, if only you would see it.”</p>
<p>I really hope he sees it in Episode 3.  :awesome:</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/vortigaunts-and-the-freeman/4927/51">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/vortigaunts-and-the-freeman/4927/51</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jul 2010 00:16:14 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-4927-51</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/vortigaunts-and-the-freeman/4927.rss">Vortigaunts and The Freeman</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Vortigaunts and The Freeman</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Hazelwolf]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Pyro">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/p/71e660/40.png" class="avatar"> Pyro:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Now, how about we discuss the subject matter: Freeman’s connection with the Vortigaunts.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Anything in particular you wish to discuss. I get the feeling we’ll just cover old ground.</p>
<p>The interplay between Alyx and the Victory Mine Vortigaunt is interesting to note.</p>
<p>‘Our bonds are ones of nature, they require no gratitude.’</p>
<p>The vortigaunt view of the world is very social, probably born of being a hive mind and perceiving the world on a higher dimension than humanity. They view death as a transition to a peaceful state of being.</p>
<p>Yet his reaction when Alyx gives him a thank you kiss spoke volumes in its simplicity. A blink and a shake of the head. What could that indicate? Irritation? puzzlement? maybe a reaction to sensing an unfamiliar human emotion?</p>
<p>(in b4 someone mentions something to do with the Alyx Vance stimulating his ‘vort essence’ <em>bow chicka wah-wah</em> :fffuuu <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=9" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/vortigaunts-and-the-freeman/4927/50">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/vortigaunts-and-the-freeman/4927/50</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jul 2010 00:06:50 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-4927-50</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/vortigaunts-and-the-freeman/4927.rss">Vortigaunts and The Freeman</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Vortigaunts and The Freeman</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Pyroclase]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Yeah, it more or less is agreeable. I can’t honestly say I read it thoroughly, though.</p>
<p>Now, how about we discuss the subject matter: Freeman’s connection with the Vortigaunts.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/vortigaunts-and-the-freeman/4927/49">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/vortigaunts-and-the-freeman/4927/49</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jul 2010 23:16:18 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-4927-49</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/vortigaunts-and-the-freeman/4927.rss">Vortigaunts and The Freeman</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Vortigaunts and The Freeman</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Hazelwolf]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="johnyo">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/j/a9a28c/40.png" class="avatar"> johnyo:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I must admit I share your opinion almost completely.<br>
Ok, since I can’t find a single sentence I wouldn’t agree with, you can probably drop the “almost”.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Glad I meet the johnyo seal of approval <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=9" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/vortigaunts-and-the-freeman/4927/48">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/vortigaunts-and-the-freeman/4927/48</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jul 2010 22:56:01 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-4927-48</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/vortigaunts-and-the-freeman/4927.rss">Vortigaunts and The Freeman</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
