<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Half-Life 2 weapon mods?</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/half-life-2-weapon-mods/13645</link>
    <description>So I played through Black Mesa using IIopn&#39;s weapon animations and redone weapon models. Frankly, I was very impressed with the final product, and since I&#39;m just about to transition to Half-Life 2 (going through Gordon&#39;s story), I wanted to ask if the same exists for Half-Life 2. I found a few of IIopn&#39;s stuff for HL2, but it&#39;s mostly whole model swaps and only seems to exist for a few weapons.

Are there any other weapon mods around? Preferably such that don&#39;t add a ton of extra Counter-Strike weapons or iron sights aiming, or mess with weapon stats and such? Frankly, I don&#39;t have a problem with Half-Life 2 itself. Yeah, it&#39;s a bit of an old game and the graphics are dated even with the upgraded Source engine, but it holds up fine. The only aspect I have an issue with is weapon models, since those have aged the most poorly plus Valve have never been very good at animating weapons (look at L4D2).

I know there&#39;s some kind of Cinematic mod that adds a bunch more weapons and I&#39;ve seen a few more that add real-world guns into the game, but that&#39;s really not what I&#39;m after. Half-Life 2 takes place in a sci-fi future. I like that it uses mostly fake guns. I also like the weapon balance in the game itself. Just looking for a cosmetic facelift, is all.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2015 14:20:09 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Half-Life Series</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/half-life-2-weapon-mods/13645.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Half-Life 2 weapon mods?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[BuzzKillington]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Smod.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/half-life-2-weapon-mods/13645/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/half-life-2-weapon-mods/13645/3</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2015 14:20:09 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13645-3</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/half-life-2-weapon-mods/13645.rss">Half-Life 2 weapon mods?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Half-Life 2 weapon mods?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Malidictus]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>OK, so nobody knows. Fair enough  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=9" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:">  How about a simpler question, then?</p>
<p>I found a number of really cool alternate weapon sounds for Half-Life 2. I can do without new weapon models and animations, custom sounds will do. But I can’t get the custom sounds to work, either. I figured out what folders to make and where to put the sound files, but some of them just plain don’t work. Short sounds, like the various sub-second clicks of the pistol’s reload animation, just don’t play well. Out-of-game, I can play them just fine in, say, Media Player Classic. In-game, however, reloading my gun sounds like I’m trying to connect over a dial-up modem - broken, scratchy, dilated audio. I haven’t the slightest idea what to do about this.</p>
<p>Does anyone know how I can get the custom sounds to play correctly in the actual game?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/half-life-2-weapon-mods/13645/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/half-life-2-weapon-mods/13645/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2015 19:58:31 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13645-2</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/half-life-2-weapon-mods/13645.rss">Half-Life 2 weapon mods?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Half-Life 2 weapon mods?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Malidictus]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>So I played through Black Mesa using IIopn’s weapon animations and redone weapon models. Frankly, I was very impressed with the final product, and since I’m just about to transition to Half-Life 2 (going through Gordon’s story), I wanted to ask if the same exists for Half-Life 2. I found a few of IIopn’s stuff for HL2, but it’s mostly whole model swaps and only seems to exist for a few weapons.</p>
<p>Are there any other weapon mods around? Preferably such that don’t add a ton of extra Counter-Strike weapons or iron sights aiming, or mess with weapon stats and such? Frankly, I don’t have a problem with Half-Life 2 itself. Yeah, it’s a bit of an old game and the graphics are dated even with the upgraded Source engine, but it holds up fine. The only aspect I have an issue with is weapon models, since those have aged the most poorly plus Valve have never been very good at animating weapons (look at L4D2).</p>
<p>I know there’s some kind of Cinematic mod that adds a bunch more weapons and I’ve seen a few more that add real-world guns into the game, but that’s really not what I’m after. Half-Life 2 takes place in a sci-fi future. I like that it uses mostly fake guns. I also like the weapon balance in the game itself. Just looking for a cosmetic facelift, is all.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/half-life-2-weapon-mods/13645/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/half-life-2-weapon-mods/13645/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2015 13:38:24 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13645-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/half-life-2-weapon-mods/13645.rss">Half-Life 2 weapon mods?</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
