<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Blog rules.</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/blog-rules/13475</link>
    <description>[b][u][i]BKDALE86 (Brian) WILL NOT answer questions about any other content. Including but not limited to: Xen, level changes, what&#39;s going on internally with the devs, release dates etc. The only questions that are acceptable and that I will answer are ones pertaining to the current project, I.E. the textures and models used in each individual blog. This is a development peek because I like doing it. Treat it as your right and the blogs will stop. FAILURE TO FOLLOW THESE SIMPLE RULES WILL RESULT IN THREAD CLOSURE AND POSSIBLE TERMINATION OF PUBLIC SHARING BY THE DEVELOPER AT THEIR CHOICE. THIS IS NON-NEGOTIABLE. AS INDICATED BELOW:[/SIZE][/i][/u][/b]


TL;DR:

*  [url=&#39;https://forums.blackmesasource.com/showpost.php?p=586405&amp;postcount=3&#39;]Be[/url] [url=https://forums.blackmesasource.com/showpost.php?p=586425&amp;postcount=10]respectful[/url] [url=https://forums.blackmesasource.com/showpost.php?p=586428&amp;postcount=12[/url]and[/url] [url=https://forums.blackmesasource.com/showpost.php?p=584500&amp;postcount=13]constructive with your criticisms[/url]. If you&#39;re not sure, read it to yourself and ask yourself &quot;Would I want to answer this myself?,&quot; if your answer&#39;s no, re-word it. Saying &quot;I don&#39;t like X&quot; and not elaborating will result in someone confusing you for the common troll (if you act like a jerk). 

*  Don&#39;t  be a jerk. This is straight forward, don&#39;t go on a tirade about something stupid. You can get banned or get slapped with an infarction for that in extreme cases. If it&#39;s a dumb question don&#39;t ask it.

*  If you want to ask questions that are only superficially pertaining to the topic such as [url=https://forums.blackmesasource.com/showpost.php?p=586431&amp;postcount=14]this[/url] or [url=https://forums.blackmesasource.com/showpost.php?p=584666&amp;postcount=15]this[/url] they&#39;re okay, but don&#39;t expect an answer.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 13 Sep 2014 17:24:20 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Developer Logs</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/blog-rules/13475.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Blog rules.</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[bkdale86]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><span class="bbcode-b"><span class="bbcode-u"><span class="bbcode-i">BKDALE86 (Brian) WILL NOT answer questions about any other content. Including but not limited to: Xen, level changes, what’s going on internally with the devs, release dates etc. The only questions that are acceptable and that I will answer are ones pertaining to the current project, I.E. the textures and models used in each individual blog. This is a development peek because I like doing it. Treat it as your right and the blogs will stop. FAILURE TO FOLLOW THESE SIMPLE RULES WILL RESULT IN THREAD CLOSURE AND POSSIBLE TERMINATION OF PUBLIC SHARING BY THE DEVELOPER AT THEIR CHOICE. THIS IS NON-NEGOTIABLE. AS INDICATED BELOW:[/SIZE]</span></span></span></p>
<p>TL;DR:</p>
<ul>
<li>
<p><a href="https://forums.blackmesasource.com/showpost.php?p=586405&amp;postcount=3" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Be</a> <a href="https://forums.blackmesasource.com/showpost.php?p=586425&amp;postcount=10" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">respectful</a> <a href="https://forums.blackmesasource.com/showpost.php?p=586428&amp;postcount=12%5B/url" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">and</a> <a href="https://forums.blackmesasource.com/showpost.php?p=584500&amp;postcount=13" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">constructive with your criticisms</a>. If you’re not sure, read it to yourself and ask yourself “Would I want to answer this myself?,” if your answer’s no, re-word it. Saying “I don’t like X” and not elaborating will result in someone confusing you for the common troll (if you act like a jerk).</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Don’t  be a jerk. This is straight forward, don’t go on a tirade about something stupid. You can get banned or get slapped with an infarction for that in extreme cases. If it’s a dumb question don’t ask it.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>If you want to ask questions that are only superficially pertaining to the topic such as <a href="https://forums.blackmesasource.com/showpost.php?p=586431&amp;postcount=14" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">this</a> or <a href="https://forums.blackmesasource.com/showpost.php?p=584666&amp;postcount=15" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">this</a> they’re okay, but don’t expect an answer.</p>
</li>
</ul>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/blog-rules/13475/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/blog-rules/13475/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 13 Sep 2014 17:24:20 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13475-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/blog-rules/13475.rss">Blog rules.</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
