<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Adobe CS5 Release announced</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/adobe-cs5-release-announced/3604</link>
    <description>The next Creative Suite version has been announced for April 12. I have been trying to find some kind of press release about it, but all I can find is the counter and &quot;register for the launch event&quot; and no details about the launch event. If anyone finds any news somewhere about it, post it here. Otherwise this thread can be used to discuss the new creative suite software. 

I read somewhere that some programs are going to run as 64 bit only, and that CS5 premiere and After effects are going to be 64 bit only. Do any of you think that there will be many more programs to run in 64 bit only, and does anyone think that CS5 may be all 64bit only?

Also, does anyone know, from either offical sources or past experience, if the CS5 launch will have all CS5 programs or just a few they have finished and others to be added later? 

Does anyone know if they will have student edition available shortly after launch? (I realize that no one has any official word on this yet, but individuals who were paying attention might know if it was available at the launch of CS3 or CS4, and hence whether it will be likely to be available at launch or shortly after) The reason why I am asking is because I have been holding off on getting Photoshop CS4 because I heard that it was buggy and CS5 wasn&#39;t too far off. 

If I decide that CS5 isn&#39;t right for me, is Adobe likely to continue sale of CS4 software for a short while after CS5&#39;s launch to clear out CS4 inventory? Or will they discontinue sale to force new users into CS5?

EDIT: poo... I didn&#39;t see the other thread about it at the very bottom of the thread list. I promised I looked before I posted, I just didn&#39;t look at the very bottom. Well mod&#39;s can decide to merge or close if they want to.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 31 Mar 2010 23:02:08 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Technology and Gaming</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/adobe-cs5-release-announced/3604.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Adobe CS5 Release announced</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Sitten_duck]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>The next Creative Suite version has been announced for April 12. I have been trying to find some kind of press release about it, but all I can find is the counter and “register for the launch event” and no details about the launch event. If anyone finds any news somewhere about it, post it here. Otherwise this thread can be used to discuss the new creative suite software.</p>
<p>I read somewhere that some programs are going to run as 64 bit only, and that CS5 premiere and After effects are going to be 64 bit only. Do any of you think that there will be many more programs to run in 64 bit only, and does anyone think that CS5 may be all 64bit only?</p>
<p>Also, does anyone know, from either offical sources or past experience, if the CS5 launch will have all CS5 programs or just a few they have finished and others to be added later?</p>
<p>Does anyone know if they will have student edition available shortly after launch? (I realize that no one has any official word on this yet, but individuals who were paying attention might know if it was available at the launch of CS3 or CS4, and hence whether it will be likely to be available at launch or shortly after) The reason why I am asking is because I have been holding off on getting Photoshop CS4 because I heard that it was buggy and CS5 wasn’t too far off.</p>
<p>If I decide that CS5 isn’t right for me, is Adobe likely to continue sale of CS4 software for a short while after CS5’s launch to clear out CS4 inventory? Or will they discontinue sale to force new users into CS5?</p>
<p>EDIT: poo… I didn’t see the other thread about it at the very bottom of the thread list. I promised I looked before I posted, I just didn’t look at the very bottom. Well mod’s can decide to merge or close if they want to.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/adobe-cs5-release-announced/3604/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/adobe-cs5-release-announced/3604/1</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 31 Mar 2010 23:02:08 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3604-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/adobe-cs5-release-announced/3604.rss">Adobe CS5 Release announced</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
