<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Fallout (?)</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/fallout/6726</link>
    <description>I am currently debating (internally) over whether I should play a Fallout game. I&#39;ve heard great things about it from sources I don&#39;t trust, and nothing from sources that I do. So I turn it to you at the BM Forums.

It looks like the art is good throughout, but it seems a little gimmicky to me. And not in the 50&#39;s style way that BioShock adopted (I love BioShock for mainly this reason,) it&#39;s seems like the notion of 50&#39;s style is there, but after a while it&#39;s ignored, and the game exchanges it&#39;s emphasis on a great setting for less artsy, more mainstream &#39;kickin-ass&#39; stuff.

I like the FPS/RPG genre a whole lot, and I have no reason to think the gameplay isn&#39;t fun, but some elements seem annoying to me, like feeding yourself apparently as often as a Sims character, and a &#39;karma&#39; system, seem silly. (EDIT) I also heard once that the whole game is an endless menu screen, which would be... not good.

I also have no knowledge as to what the story is like. For a sandbox game, it may well suck, but just out of my curiosity, a &#39;yay&#39; or &#39;nay&#39; would help me.

Remember, this is all what I&#39;ve gathered from a first-impression. I may be very wrong, and if so, please correct me ^^</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 13 Mar 2011 12:38:02 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Technology and Gaming</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/fallout/6726.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Fallout (?)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[k3nny1550]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I liked Fallout 3, but I could never finish it. The game world is so large, it’s almost <span class="bbcode-i">too</span> big. The main quest is apparently beatable in 45 minutes, but there is so much other stuff that will divert you from that quest yarn for sure. I myself took up a personal quest to get to the Washington Monument rather than visit 3 Dog or whatever I need to do for the main quest. I haven’t played it in a long time. Perhaps I’ll revisit it after I finish FFXIII.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/fallout/6726/28">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/fallout/6726/28</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 13 Mar 2011 12:38:02 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-6726-28</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/fallout/6726.rss">Fallout (?)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Fallout (?)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[orange_cat]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="doomyshadowsquirrels">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/d/e36b37/40.png" class="avatar"> doomyshadowsquirrels:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I’ve heard great things about it from sources I don’t trust, and nothing from sources that I do. So I turn it to you at the BM Forums.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>We’re a trusted source?</p>
<p>I have played Fallout 3 and found it similar to Oblivion, just in a post apocalyptic world with guns and robots. I did enjoy it and it does have some differences and nice features (like VATS with a mini-gun  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=9" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"> ).</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/fallout/6726/27">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/fallout/6726/27</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 13 Mar 2011 12:35:15 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-6726-27</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/fallout/6726.rss">Fallout (?)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Fallout (?)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Ry_amp_955_n]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Yeah, I’m not looking for a fight, man. I thought I praised your last paragraph, rtanger. And your writing is amazing. I was just sayin’. My post was rather more directionally detailed instead of being artistically/descriptively detailed like yours.<br>
Neither were brain dumps.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/fallout/6726/26">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/fallout/6726/26</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 13 Mar 2011 02:58:22 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-6726-26</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/fallout/6726.rss">Fallout (?)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Fallout (?)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[k3nny1550]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Can’t we all just get along and post intelligently? I don’t mind long posts if the poster has something interesting to say…</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/fallout/6726/25">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/fallout/6726/25</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 13 Mar 2011 01:11:59 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-6726-25</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/fallout/6726.rss">Fallout (?)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Fallout (?)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[rtanger]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Ryλn">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Ryλn:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Being overly descriptive is nice and all, and big words are excellently used, but what all you said could be summarized for easy reading. just sayin’  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=9" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>This coming from the guy whose previous post was a massive brain dump that could have simply read “Cheating in Fallout is fun!”</p>
<p>tl;dr: :meh:</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/fallout/6726/24">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/fallout/6726/24</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 12 Mar 2011 21:53:58 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-6726-24</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/fallout/6726.rss">Fallout (?)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Fallout (?)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Ry_amp_955_n]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Being overly descriptive is nice and all, and big words are excellently used, but what all you said could be summarized for easy reading. just sayin’  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=9" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
<p>You nailed it though on the last paragraph. i agree completely.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/fallout/6726/23">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/fallout/6726/23</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 12 Mar 2011 21:46:21 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-6726-23</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/fallout/6726.rss">Fallout (?)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Fallout (?)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[rtanger]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I love the Fallout games.</p>
<p>One thing I certainly would not do is consider the art style and the overall aesthetic as being something either arbitrarily used or ignored past a certain point throughout the games. There’s an entire underlying philosophy that ties into this retro-future-50’s thing they have going on. It’s evident in the brash, optimistic attitudes displayed throughout the artifacts of life before the bombs dropped. There’s the sense that all would be right with the world if the entire world was the USA. Everything is big and bold and loud and people get what they want by doing what they want and “let God sort the details out” in the end. The cavalier attitude towards nuclear energy is almost as strong of a counterpoint to the real-world cold-war paranoia that stigmatized nuclear energy in our society.</p>
<p>Nuclear power is to that world what the concept of “sustainable living” is becoming to ours-- the answer to everything. It shows its irony when you see all the remnants of humanities golden age losing their glitter and rotting away to the madness and desperation that overtook the land when the power of the future ended the future they sought. The entire philosophy and aesthetic is carried out unflinchingly and uncompromisingly throughout the series. How much of this you notice depends entirely on how deep you wish to dig, or how much you read and pay attention to the details beyond the main questlines.</p>
<p>The design programs for posters, autos, electronics, computers, houses, offices, sci-fi, robotics, and essentially everything else is steeped in mid-20th century Americana, almost to the point of overdoing it. The world is the best ideals of the 50’s and the shiniest of its camp married with the rotten desperation of a world gone mad with death. It makes for quite the startling juxtapositions at times, and in some random set pieces here and there, downright depressing to witness.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/fallout/6726/22">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/fallout/6726/22</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 12 Mar 2011 20:28:12 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-6726-22</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/fallout/6726.rss">Fallout (?)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Fallout (?)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Ry_amp_955_n]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>OR if you have PC (everyone here should…), Start the game with a gender you haven’t chosen before, like a female for instance. Put your intelligence at 2 or lower bc doing so I heard changes all of the dialogue choice options in the game to “caveman talk”.  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=9" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:">  haha</p>
<p>I wanted to try it sometime after i’m done with my serious character. And to make it even more replayable and fun, Max out your characters stats and skills, get all perks, and spawn best weapons and armor right from the beginning by using the console. That’s always fun. (take the Wild Wasteland perk too, if you haven’t in the beginning already)</p>
<p>Tgm (toggle god mode) in console and have infinite ammo, condition, health, and no reload. Firing a missile launcher with no reload is a blast. No pun intended.  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/wink.png?v=9" title=":wink:" class="emoji" alt=":wink:"></p>
<p>The game has a huge replay value, imo. So many different ways to play it.<br>
Currently, I have a male, do-gooder, idolized by several factions, and specializes in sniping, guns, sneak, and speech/barter.<br>
My second character will be a psychotic murdering seductive bitch, evil sexy female, with a charisma of 10 with the Black Widow perk and an intelligence of 1 for more dialogue lulz (better make her bright blonde  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/smiley.png?v=9" title=":smiley:" class="emoji" alt=":smiley:"> ), and will be hated by every faction except for Ceasar’s Legion while specializing in melee and explosives.</p>
<p>After finding the right console commands and fun shit to spawn and fuck with, you can have endless fun. I remember when i played Fallout3, i started off in Vault 101: tgm, spawned an Experimental MIRV with 20 mininukes, and shot 8 mininukes per second (no reload from god mode) at whoever i saw. My computer got pretty laggy. lol.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/fallout/6726/21">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/fallout/6726/21</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 12 Mar 2011 19:25:13 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-6726-21</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/fallout/6726.rss">Fallout (?)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Fallout (?)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Keresh]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Right, paying…</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/fallout/6726/20">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/fallout/6726/20</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 12 Mar 2011 14:46:27 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-6726-20</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/fallout/6726.rss">Fallout (?)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Fallout (?)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[doomyshadowsquirrels]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Keresh">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/k/85f322/40.png" class="avatar"> Keresh:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Protip: Try it, it’s a game. You’re not gonna fucking die if you won’t like it.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Fun fact: I’m a fourteen year old who recently collected enough change to buy Dead Space 2. Took me a damn while.<br>
I’m not paying for anything bad  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=9" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/fallout/6726/19">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/fallout/6726/19</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 Mar 2011 23:16:10 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-6726-19</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/fallout/6726.rss">Fallout (?)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Fallout (?)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Harun]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="garthbartin">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 garthbartin:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>But that was fixed with the DLC. AFAIK that has not been fixed yet in New Vegas. It is a pretty big deal. I don’t have a huge problem with paying to keep going, I do have a problem with not being able to keep going period.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>there is a mod enabling you to play after main story line is finished.<br>
<a href="https://www.newvegasnexus.com/downloads/file.php?id=40373" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://www.newvegasnexus.com/downloads/file.php?id=40373</a><br>
haven´t tested it.</p>
<p>as said above, fallout is a great game. i played fallout 3 with all dlc´s and new vegas several times through.<br>
especially fallout 3 is a game, where you(or at least i) actually WANT to take the time doing all the stuff there is to do. If you started it you don´t want to miss anything the game has to offer.<br>
of course the game´s not perfect, it´s quite buggy actually(well fallout 3 not so much anymore) and there might be some annoying stuff for some people, but the story of the game, the setting, the sidequests, the humour, everything just adds up to a big whole feeling of awesome…<br>
you, the lone wanderer of the wastes, have to struggle against the harshness of radiation, mutation and evil of a scorched land. you decide whether to work the gain of your kind or to seek only your own profit. Of course you can also handle it like Alexander The Great: be benevolent to those you like and cruel to your foes.<br>
I´m saying this not because i want to advertise or to sum up what you do but to point out what feeling you get while playing the game, because you really get into it… well i should stop writing so much here.</p>
<p>fallout 3 and new vegas are great: great story, great quests, great setting, i missed the humour of fallout 3 a little in new vegas, but both games are definitly worth trying.</p>
<p>also important: you can mod the shit outta it. i would recommend playing both games vanilla first, but then there are so great mods out there to further enhance and add to the gameplay of fallout.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/fallout/6726/18">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/fallout/6726/18</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 Mar 2011 21:48:42 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-6726-18</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/fallout/6726.rss">Fallout (?)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Fallout (?)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Shinobi]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I didn’t play New Vegas (I really want it, but I’m going to get Skyrim instead), but Fallout 3 was amazing. The story is good and all, but I really bought it for the setting. They do post-apocalypse very well, and I still play it every now and then just to be able to walk around and explore because its so pretty. I really liked the combat systems too, and while you can go all macho with miniguns and lasers and stuff, I stuck with the more conventional weapons like pistols and rifles. Its whatever you make it really.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/fallout/6726/17">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/fallout/6726/17</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 Mar 2011 21:14:12 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-6726-17</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/fallout/6726.rss">Fallout (?)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Fallout (?)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[garrthbarrttinn]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="BahamutBBob">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/b/e9bcb4/40.png" class="avatar"> BahamutBBob:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Garth.  In Fallout 3, you couldn’t continue either unless you spent $10 extra.</p>
<p>It’s not a big deal.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>But that was fixed with the DLC. AFAIK that has not been fixed yet in New Vegas. It is a pretty big deal. I don’t have a huge problem with paying to keep going, I do have a problem with not being able to keep going period.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/fallout/6726/16">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/fallout/6726/16</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 Mar 2011 21:08:50 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-6726-16</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/fallout/6726.rss">Fallout (?)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Fallout (?)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[BahamutBBob]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Garth.  In Fallout 3, you couldn’t continue either unless you spent $10 extra.</p>
<p>It’s not a big deal.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/fallout/6726/15">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/fallout/6726/15</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 Mar 2011 20:53:48 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-6726-15</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/fallout/6726.rss">Fallout (?)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Fallout (?)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[garrthbarrttinn]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Some people, including me, are very careful with what they do with their cash.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/fallout/6726/14">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/fallout/6726/14</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 Mar 2011 20:51:40 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-6726-14</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/fallout/6726.rss">Fallout (?)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Fallout (?)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Keresh]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Protip: Try it, it’s a game. You’re not gonna fucking die if you won’t like it.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/fallout/6726/13">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/fallout/6726/13</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 Mar 2011 19:54:30 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-6726-13</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/fallout/6726.rss">Fallout (?)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Fallout (?)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[garrthbarrttinn]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Thanks a lot Ryan, never noticed that. But it won’t help me now because I’ve literally gone everything in the game.</p>
<p>The two things that really annoyed me about the end of New Vegas was that [COLOR=‘Black’]you couldn’t keep playing once you beat the game and if you chose independent NV you had to betray NCR rather than allying with them.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/fallout/6726/12">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/fallout/6726/12</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 Mar 2011 19:12:19 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-6726-12</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/fallout/6726.rss">Fallout (?)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Fallout (?)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[YARO]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>If you don’t care about graphics then start with the original Fallout. There’s a LOT more story to it and it will suck you in more if you’re a RPG guy. Then again if you do then F3 would be a good choice, NV was awesome untill near the end which bored the crap out of me and it’s waiting to be finished till this day…</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/fallout/6726/11">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/fallout/6726/11</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 Mar 2011 07:49:51 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-6726-11</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/fallout/6726.rss">Fallout (?)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Fallout (?)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Ry_amp_955_n]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Amazing, genius games. Fallout was around wayyyy before Bioskock was even brainstormed, so thank the Fallout series for the innovative 50’s style resurrection in today’s modern gaming.</p>
<p>Also, <span class="bbcode-i">endless menu screen</span>? wat. Fallout has a basic HUD. (health, compass, ammo, actionpoints[stamina/fatigue bscly], and crosshair.<br>
You can also change the colors of it and the opacity(visibilty of it/ see-through, bold, etc.) of it too.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Art/characters/details of whole game:</span> excellent.<br>
<span class="bbcode-b">Story:</span> Pretty entertaining and intense. -variety of things to do and get sidetracted into as well.<br>
<span class="bbcode-b">Gameplay:</span> I don’t like the combat too much, but the exploration, interaction, atmosphere, music, and style makes up for it. Oh, plus a wide range of different weapons and a ridiculous number of ways to kill thigns and people with an assortment of riduculous ragdoll and bloody mess, gib-fun physics.  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/smiley.png?v=9" title=":smiley:" class="emoji" alt=":smiley:"></p>
<p><span alt="" class="broken-image" title="This image is broken"><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-unlink svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#unlink"></use></svg></span><br>
A pic displaying the HUD. The “Pipboy3000”(inventory) is accessed via tab key and contains yours current stats, weapons, apparel, progress, information, etc.</p>
<p><span alt="" class="broken-image" title="This image is broken"><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-unlink svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#unlink"></use></svg></span><br>
AKA: My fave thing to do -Pump Shotgun blast to innocent human’s forehead.  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=9" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"></p>
<p><span alt="" class="broken-image" title="This image is broken"><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-unlink svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#unlink"></use></svg></span><br>
<span class="bbcode-i">True Iron sights</span> setting. I like it. oh, and a limbless old town eccentirc that I shot up for a couple minutes lays before me.</p>
<p><span alt="" class="broken-image" title="This image is broken"><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-unlink svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#unlink"></use></svg></span><br>
Letting off some steam in the desert night air as my 5mm cartidges fall and ting against the other hollowed out shells that accumulate in the dry sand. &lt;3</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="garthbartin">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 garthbartin:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>“…I think the one thing it could really use is a hotkey system that would allow you to quickly use items or equip weapons; it’s really a bother to change weapons in the middle of battle…”</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>It does, bro. While using your Pipboy, hold any number down, 1-9, while in your “weapons, aparrel, or aid” items menu. A Screen with pop up in your pipboy with emtpy slots. Hold “1” and click on a rifle, grenade, hat, stimpack, radaway, whatever, and that weapon, clothing, or aid will be equiped or consumed if a drug or food whenever you press the number one key.</p>
<p>Believe me, it’s incredibly time-saving and convenient when I play:<br>
<em>Sees a Deathclaw, “1” -pulls out sniper rifle, BOOM headshot!</em><br>
<em>Deathclaw closes distance, and knocks my health down 50% in one swipe</em><br>
<em>Use 3 stimpacks by pressing “8” 3 times. Then “3” -Pulls out my shotgun</em><br>
<em>Finishes off deathclaw while health regenerates from stimpacks. Success.</em><br>
<em>Thumbs up to Hotkeys</em></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/fallout/6726/10">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/fallout/6726/10</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 Mar 2011 05:41:24 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-6726-10</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/fallout/6726.rss">Fallout (?)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Fallout (?)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[doomyshadowsquirrels]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="garthbartin">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 garthbartin:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>That’s not it at all. It does post apocalypse very well. And it’s definitely not a testosterone fest like Gears of War (see Gears of Awesome) if that’s the kind of macho you’re referring to.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I was actually going to use Gears as an example, but decided against it ^^’</p>
<p>It’s good to hear that. The thing is, Fallout’s only been recommended to me by testosterone junkie CoD-casuals. I suppose they can recognize a good game well enough to respond to it somewhat, while Half-Life forunately goes far enough over their heads for them not to reach for it.</p>
<p>Artistic presentation is a total dealbreaker for me, so thanks a lot ^^</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/fallout/6726/9">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/fallout/6726/9</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 Mar 2011 05:20:19 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-6726-9</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/fallout/6726.rss">Fallout (?)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Fallout (?)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[garrthbarrttinn]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="doomyshadowsquirrels">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/d/e36b37/40.png" class="avatar"> doomyshadowsquirrels:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I love the post-apocalypse setting with a passion ^^ one of my underlying fears is that the story won’t throw a P-A world at me with in-depth justification for it’s existence, which BioShock did very well and seductively. Also, that it might turn out to be a bastardization of the setting, and throw a stupid ‘macho-game’ into a P-A world to literally shit on art.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>That’s not it at all. It does post apocalypse very well. And it’s definitely not a testosterone fest like Gears of War (see Gears of Awesome) if that’s the kind of macho you’re referring to.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/fallout/6726/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/fallout/6726/8</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 Mar 2011 04:52:43 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-6726-8</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/fallout/6726.rss">Fallout (?)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Fallout (?)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[doomyshadowsquirrels]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I love the post-apocalypse setting with a passion ^^ one of my underlying fears is that the story won’t throw a P-A world at me with in-depth justification for it’s existence, which BioShock did very well and seductively. Also, that it might turn out to be a bastardization of the setting, and throw a stupid ‘macho-game’ into a P-A world to literally shit on art.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/fallout/6726/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/fallout/6726/7</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 Mar 2011 04:46:43 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-6726-7</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/fallout/6726.rss">Fallout (?)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Fallout (?)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[garrthbarrttinn]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Fallout 3 and Fallout New Vegas are both spectacular games. The storylines, though not stunning or intriguing, are enough to keep you interested. And the karma system really doesn’t have a huge affect on gameplay other than deciding which companions will travel with you in Fo3. As for eating and drinking, that’s only present in the “Hardcore” mode of New Vegas which is just for people looking for an extreme challenge. I think the one thing it could really use is a hotkey system that would allow you to quickly use items or equip weapons; it’s really a bother to change weapons in the middle of battle. Also, the lack of continuity between the DLCs and the main storyline is pretty disappointing; the only affect the DLCs have on the main game is to give you some extra rare weapons and items. And that goes for all the side quests; they could have really used a more significant impact to make you feel like you were really doing something. For example there was one large sidequest in Fo3 that could result in you drastically speeding up the process of the return of trees to the wasteland. It would have been really really cool if because of this you started seeing more and more trees scattered about the wasteland. Also, there should have been some sort of system that kept you from running out of things to do. Perhaps  have quests that could be repeated? Or have 100s of generic quests that would become available randomly.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/fallout/6726/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/fallout/6726/6</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 Mar 2011 04:40:56 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-6726-6</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/fallout/6726.rss">Fallout (?)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Fallout (?)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Bloodshot]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Definitely should get a fallout game. Like kaikarden said the story is in depth, and the gameplay is pretty fun as well. I personally much prefer the TES games over the fallout series, old or new, but fallout 1-3 and NV are all great games. NV hardcore is good too, it adds a better survival aspect, but you don’t need to eat or drink often enough for it to be annoying.</p>
<p>In fact, I think the only problem i ever had was way later on with water in NV. Food was never really a problem.</p>
<p>They are especially cool if you like the era they are centered around, or the destroyed wasteland look.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/fallout/6726/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/fallout/6726/5</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 Mar 2011 04:33:09 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-6726-5</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/fallout/6726.rss">Fallout (?)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Fallout (?)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[bigfan421]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Fallout series is great</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/fallout/6726/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/fallout/6726/4</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 Mar 2011 04:14:27 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-6726-4</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/fallout/6726.rss">Fallout (?)</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
