<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Computer Hangs</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/computer-hangs/12816</link>
    <description>I have this problem, my computer hangs and sometimes resumes. I&#39;m banned in CSGO and I&#39;m in low-priority matches in DOTA 2 because I can&#39;t reconnect in time. So I&#39;ve stopped playing until I solve this problem.

Sometimes I restart my computer and find that my computer can&#39;t detect my HDD. It&#39;s still connected though but in the BIOS it&#39;s not detected. So I Pull the Sata connection and reinsert it. Sometimes it works, sometimes not.

Every now and then it corrupts my OS so I have to reformat. My computer holds on for an hour or so, then hangs again. I restart and continue. Until it corrupts my OS again, then I reformat again.

I already bought a new HDD and the problem didn&#39;t go away. The technicians in PC Express couldn&#39;t help me. 

The RAM works fine, the temperature is fine... I&#39;ve cleaned up my computer to no avail. I also already replaced the SATA wire and it still didn&#39;t work. 

You guys are smart, any help I&#39;ll appreciate it.  :slight_smile:</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2013 18:37:45 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Help and Support</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/computer-hangs/12816.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Computer Hangs</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[sersoft]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>get a pci sata card or a new motherboard</p>
<p>also if you have a cheap no-name power supply that could be the cause as well</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/computer-hangs/12816/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/computer-hangs/12816/2</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2013 18:37:45 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12816-2</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/computer-hangs/12816.rss">Computer Hangs</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Computer Hangs</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[rx33gundam]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I have this problem, my computer hangs and sometimes resumes. I’m banned in CSGO and I’m in low-priority matches in DOTA 2 because I can’t reconnect in time. So I’ve stopped playing until I solve this problem.</p>
<p>Sometimes I restart my computer and find that my computer can’t detect my HDD. It’s still connected though but in the BIOS it’s not detected. So I Pull the Sata connection and reinsert it. Sometimes it works, sometimes not.</p>
<p>Every now and then it corrupts my OS so I have to reformat. My computer holds on for an hour or so, then hangs again. I restart and continue. Until it corrupts my OS again, then I reformat again.</p>
<p>I already bought a new HDD and the problem didn’t go away. The technicians in PC Express couldn’t help me.</p>
<p>The RAM works fine, the temperature is fine… I’ve cleaned up my computer to no avail. I also already replaced the SATA wire and it still didn’t work.</p>
<p>You guys are smart, any help I’ll appreciate it.  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=9" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/computer-hangs/12816/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/computer-hangs/12816/1</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2013 12:59:18 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12816-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/computer-hangs/12816.rss">Computer Hangs</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
