<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Forgetful Jones - Original Rock</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/forgetful-jones-original-rock/6861</link>
    <description>Yes its true, real people playing real instruments. Well, I&#39;m sry to say that the band has since broke up and gone seperate ways but I spent many years with some close friends of mine playing music in this band. 2 full length records, many shows, great times and probably thousands of beers, lol. It never paid the bills but it was a labor of love and like I said, it was a fun ride but its over now. I&#39;d like as many people as possible to leave some feedback, good, bad, indifferent, dosen&#39;t matter. Give a listen and tell me what you think. It might still be on Itunes, not sure. It might not be your cup of tea, thats fine, its music and its meant to be heard, its a waste to not put it out there. 

MySpace - [url]https://www.myspace.com/fjrock[/url]

Mainsite - [url]https://forgetfuljonesband.com/#/?p=1[/url]


Youtube links to other tracks are located 2 posts down.

PLEASE LEAVE COMMENTS AND FEEDBACK !!! THANKS and ENJOY !!!!</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 18 Feb 2012 20:30:55 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Show Off</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/forgetful-jones-original-rock/6861.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Forgetful Jones - Original Rock</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[CPU]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I quit playing years ago. Really enjoyed it but life moves on. Got to play with ZZ Top once in Houston. We were playing and they just happened to pop in and play too. Now, my best friend owns 3 music stores and I have access to everything from old Les Pauls, Strats and even Mosrites but, no longer have a need for them. He literally has thousands of guitars. I got rid of my last bit of equipment just last year.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/forgetful-jones-original-rock/6861/20">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/forgetful-jones-original-rock/6861/20</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 18 Feb 2012 20:30:55 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-6861-20</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/forgetful-jones-original-rock/6861.rss">Forgetful Jones - Original Rock</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Forgetful Jones - Original Rock</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Onemanwolfpack]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I think everyone is just taking a little break from playing at the moment, no new projects have formed as of yet. We actually did a short reunion show in early February because it was the gituar players 30th B-day and he asked us to do one more gig, but thats been it.</p>
<p>But yes, we all keep in touch. A little less obviously now that we’re not getting together 2 nights a week for practice. But we were all good friends before and during our time as a band and still are. No hard feelings between anyone after the split, just time to move on, thats all. Infact we were all over the gituar players house for the superbowl, good times, except for the part about the Patriots blowing the game.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/forgetful-jones-original-rock/6861/19">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/forgetful-jones-original-rock/6861/19</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 18 Feb 2012 04:06:07 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-6861-19</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/forgetful-jones-original-rock/6861.rss">Forgetful Jones - Original Rock</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Forgetful Jones - Original Rock</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[amazingcomedy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Nice, nice. By the way, what has happened to the band now? You guys still keep in touch?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/forgetful-jones-original-rock/6861/18">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/forgetful-jones-original-rock/6861/18</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 18 Feb 2012 03:38:09 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-6861-18</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/forgetful-jones-original-rock/6861.rss">Forgetful Jones - Original Rock</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Forgetful Jones - Original Rock</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Onemanwolfpack]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Right on, good luck with the new project. I hear ya, alot of jamming dosent always equate into a structured song, its a tough process sometimes. Let me know when you guys have some tracks down, I’d like to hear how its going.</p>
<p>I was in “Forgetful Jones” for about 5 years and another band before that for about the same amount of time. I plan on getting back into something at some point but truthfully I’m not in a huge rush after basically being in a band not stop for the last several years, need a little break. When I’m ready to get back behind the wheel something will come up. I play on some recordings for friends if they ask me but thats it for now.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/forgetful-jones-original-rock/6861/17">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/forgetful-jones-original-rock/6861/17</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 18 Feb 2012 02:01:20 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-6861-17</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/forgetful-jones-original-rock/6861.rss">Forgetful Jones - Original Rock</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Forgetful Jones - Original Rock</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Guzzi]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Onemanwolfpack">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/o/b487fb/40.png" class="avatar"> Onemanwolfpack:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>@ Guzzi - … I take it by the Jimmi avatar you are an axe man by trade? Again, thanks for taking the time to listen to us.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<pre><code>    You guessed it. I've done song writing mainly on my own. I'm with a band now so I can't take the same song writing approach that I did by myself. There are times where I'm scratching my head wondering how we can turn an endless jam into a somewhat base line structured idea. 

     We are a freshly started band so the obstacles seem to intrude on our lock out sessions pretty much every meet up. (And we have been meeting everyday for two weeks.) When we get our shit together and have an LP ready I can share our tracks. But man, we have ALLOT of work to get done...

   You guys no longer play together, but do you still play in other projects?</code></pre>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/forgetful-jones-original-rock/6861/16">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/forgetful-jones-original-rock/6861/16</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Feb 2012 23:18:01 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-6861-16</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/forgetful-jones-original-rock/6861.rss">Forgetful Jones - Original Rock</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Forgetful Jones - Original Rock</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Onemanwolfpack]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>The reel to reel (analog) was just something we had a chance to do and we decided to give it a shot. Analog is supposed to have a warmer overall tone than digital recording. Digital is easy in the aspect that if you fuck up something, you can just plug in at 1:46, fix it and move on. Analog recording, you literaly have to cut the reel and tape it back together and make it sound seemless, a dying art these days I’m sure. We just did takes until everyone played perfect all the way through. Everyone went one at a time, I went first (with a ghost track in my headohones) then bass, then gituar and then vocals, aux percussion or keyboard after that if we felt like it. It always seemed to go in that order. I cant remember exactly what I had for mics on my kit on that session. But it was always indiviual mics for each drum (snare, 2 rack tom, floor tom, bass drum) high hats got their own mic and then overhead mic to pick up cymbals. It was in a studio with really high cielings so we were going for a “bigger” sound. I edited the link above as I finally figured out how to make vids for youtube and added a bunch of studio tracks from the 2nd record, “Moonshine” is in there. Enjoy!</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/forgetful-jones-original-rock/6861/15">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/forgetful-jones-original-rock/6861/15</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Feb 2012 06:35:10 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-6861-15</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/forgetful-jones-original-rock/6861.rss">Forgetful Jones - Original Rock</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Forgetful Jones - Original Rock</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[CPU]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Onemanwolfpack">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/o/b487fb/40.png" class="avatar"> Onemanwolfpack:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>@ CPU - …The studio track “Not for nothing” and “Moonshine” were recorded elsewhere and was done on a reel to reel, my first experience with that, it was interesting.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>That’s really interesting. What’s the story behind doing reel to reel? Was it something you were wanting to do? How many tracks did you have available? Did you record individually and mix together or was it done all at once? If individually recorded, what order did you do it in? What instruments were used? How did you mic your kit?</p>
<p>I liked the acoustic version of Not for Nothing a lot. Thought it was much better than the electric version. It would be interesting to hear it with a 12 string Rick and begin your percussion using congas and then move to using the bass drum at the 1:24 mark. That would add a lot to the dynamics of the song. I’d probably play around with adding a chorus effect too.</p>
<p>Can you give me a link for Moonshine?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/forgetful-jones-original-rock/6861/14">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/forgetful-jones-original-rock/6861/14</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2012 21:10:25 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-6861-14</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/forgetful-jones-original-rock/6861.rss">Forgetful Jones - Original Rock</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Forgetful Jones - Original Rock</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Onemanwolfpack]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>@ BahamutBBob - Put those tracks back up. The “Not for nothing” - acoustic was recorded by our mutual friends little newphew as a recording project for school. Not sure if that was the one you were refering to. Thanks for taking the time to listen to us.</p>
<p>@ CPU - No worries, critisim is something I’ve learned to take being a musician for as many years as I have. Also, your probably right about the producing end of it. Mostly a “friend” of ours did most of the recordings but in truth he didn’t have much experience with bands of our genre (heavier) which I believe hindered the recordings. The studio track “Not for nothing” and “Moonshine” were recorded elsewhere and was done on a reel to reel, my first experience with that, it was interesting. I hear ya, you can give someone the fastest sports car in the world but if they suck at driving its not going to work out so well. I appreciate you taking the time to listen to us.</p>
<p>@ Guzzi - As far as song writting, everyone wrote their own parts. Suggestions on certain things to improve or change parts were all done between us. It usually stemed from a gituar riff and everyone built around that, not always though, the song “Salsa” was a drum beat I started and it turned into the finished product. It varied in that aspect. Most of the time it was just “jamming out” and cherry picking the stuff we liked and building off of that. Song writting definetly has its challenges, at least for us it did. Some songs wrote themselves, others you found yourselves banging your head against the wall until everyone could reach an agreement. I take it by the Jimmi avatar you are an axe man by trade? Again, thanks for taking the time to listen to us.</p>
<p>I’m going to try and figure out how to put some of the studio tracks on YouTube and just link them, might be a little easier. Thanks again all. Keep it coming. I’ve been around this forum a while now and it can get down right ruthless in here. So in turn, I’m feeling pretty damn good about the feedback thus far.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/forgetful-jones-original-rock/6861/13">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/forgetful-jones-original-rock/6861/13</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 15 Feb 2012 17:47:03 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-6861-13</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/forgetful-jones-original-rock/6861.rss">Forgetful Jones - Original Rock</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Forgetful Jones - Original Rock</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Guzzi]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>What was your guys’ song writing approach? As a band, or did someone bring in a set of chord changes with some lyrics and a tempo?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/forgetful-jones-original-rock/6861/12">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/forgetful-jones-original-rock/6861/12</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 15 Feb 2012 15:02:27 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-6861-12</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/forgetful-jones-original-rock/6861.rss">Forgetful Jones - Original Rock</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Forgetful Jones - Original Rock</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[BahamutBBob]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I thought you guys had potential from the one studio track that you posted in your bump, that you have since edited out, but the quality on the live tracks left something to be desired, most likely from the recording equipment and venue.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/forgetful-jones-original-rock/6861/11">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/forgetful-jones-original-rock/6861/11</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 15 Feb 2012 02:43:09 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-6861-11</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/forgetful-jones-original-rock/6861.rss">Forgetful Jones - Original Rock</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Forgetful Jones - Original Rock</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[CPU]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I didn’t mean to sound critical of your music because I wasn’t. I was trying to point out that the studio production of it left a lot to be desired. You can use the best studio equipment available but if you don’t have a great producer then it really doesn’t make any difference. Kind of like the results you would get if someone had your same kit but didn’t know how to use it.</p>
<p>It sounded like you had “a friend” handle the production when, in reality, that job was the most important and should have had a professional handling it. Instead of someone simply setting the master controls of the board for all of the mics it should have had individual settings tailored for each track.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/forgetful-jones-original-rock/6861/10">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/forgetful-jones-original-rock/6861/10</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 15 Feb 2012 01:43:09 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-6861-10</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/forgetful-jones-original-rock/6861.rss">Forgetful Jones - Original Rock</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Forgetful Jones - Original Rock</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Onemanwolfpack]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Not sure what kind of system you are listening to it on. Everyone was recorded seperately using pro tools and legit sound recording equiptment. Not Columbia records style mind you, we were never a national touring act at anytime. Recording costs alot of $$$, more than people realize I think, we did what we could within our budget. Just something a few friends did after work and on the weekends and played all the clubs in and around Boston. A few shows in NY and Montreal. All the same thanks for the advice, hope you like some of the songs. Thanks for checking us out!</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/forgetful-jones-original-rock/6861/9">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/forgetful-jones-original-rock/6861/9</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 15 Feb 2012 00:38:18 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-6861-9</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/forgetful-jones-original-rock/6861.rss">Forgetful Jones - Original Rock</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Forgetful Jones - Original Rock</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[CPU]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>The one suggestion I have is for you to get an experienced producer. The studio recordings sound like they were single track with two microphones. You cheated yourself by not getting a professional producer.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/forgetful-jones-original-rock/6861/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/forgetful-jones-original-rock/6861/8</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Feb 2012 23:36:11 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-6861-8</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/forgetful-jones-original-rock/6861.rss">Forgetful Jones - Original Rock</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Forgetful Jones - Original Rock</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Onemanwolfpack]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Dont forget to check out the links to the studio tracks in the third post, obviously they are alot cleaner than any of videos of the live performances. I appreciate the feedback. Keep it coming!</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/forgetful-jones-original-rock/6861/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/forgetful-jones-original-rock/6861/7</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Feb 2012 23:28:22 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-6861-7</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/forgetful-jones-original-rock/6861.rss">Forgetful Jones - Original Rock</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Forgetful Jones - Original Rock</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Fnork]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Not really my style, but I know what’s good playing when I hear it, and this does indeed belong in that category.</p>
<p>As staded above, I do agree that some songs could use a bit of polishing, but all in all it’s decent.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/forgetful-jones-original-rock/6861/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/forgetful-jones-original-rock/6861/6</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Feb 2012 13:32:03 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-6861-6</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/forgetful-jones-original-rock/6861.rss">Forgetful Jones - Original Rock</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Forgetful Jones - Original Rock</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Onemanwolfpack]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Bolteh">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/b/ecae2f/40.png" class="avatar"> Bolteh:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Good stuff, really. Could’ve used some polishing here and there, but that’s something that comes over the years.</p>
<p>What was your job within the band?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Drummer.</p>
<p>Thanks for checking us out.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/forgetful-jones-original-rock/6861/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/forgetful-jones-original-rock/6861/5</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Feb 2012 12:07:49 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-6861-5</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/forgetful-jones-original-rock/6861.rss">Forgetful Jones - Original Rock</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Forgetful Jones - Original Rock</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Bolteh]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Good stuff, really. Could’ve used some polishing here and there, but that’s something that comes over the years.</p>
<p>What was your job within the band?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/forgetful-jones-original-rock/6861/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/forgetful-jones-original-rock/6861/4</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Feb 2012 09:59:59 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-6861-4</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/forgetful-jones-original-rock/6861.rss">Forgetful Jones - Original Rock</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Forgetful Jones - Original Rock</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Onemanwolfpack]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <h2>Some studio tracks:</h2>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">2nd album “Sub-Atomic Phil-Harmonic”</span></p>
<p>Not for nothing - <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=krRpg-q-1yY&amp;context=C31acf60ADOEgsToPDskKXCGGKCx3jSvlkUWSjzG12" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=krRpg-q-1yY&amp;context=C31acf60ADOEgsToPDskKXCGGKCx3jSvlkUWSjzG12</a></p>
<p>Breaking Ground - <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=DMHZvcrBetQ&amp;context=C31acf60ADOEgsToPDskKXCGGKCx3jSvlkUWSjzG12" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=DMHZvcrBetQ&amp;context=C31acf60ADOEgsToPDskKXCGGKCx3jSvlkUWSjzG12</a></p>
<p>Salsa - <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=_-Oqeri6ODo&amp;context=C31acf60ADOEgsToPDskKXCGGKCx3jSvlkUWSjzG12" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=_-Oqeri6ODo&amp;context=C31acf60ADOEgsToPDskKXCGGKCx3jSvlkUWSjzG12</a></p>
<p>Moonshine - <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=hDnSc5feXjM&amp;context=C31acf60ADOEgsToPDskKXCGGKCx3jSvlkUWSjzG12" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=hDnSc5feXjM&amp;context=C31acf60ADOEgsToPDskKXCGGKCx3jSvlkUWSjzG12</a></p>
<p>Traffic - <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=U_2cGdU1tDU&amp;context=C31acf60ADOEgsToPDskKXCGGKCx3jSvlkUWSjzG12" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=U_2cGdU1tDU&amp;context=C31acf60ADOEgsToPDskKXCGGKCx3jSvlkUWSjzG12</a></p>
<p>Get outside the world - <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=T0X9r4rnn0A&amp;context=C31acf60ADOEgsToPDskKXCGGKCx3jSvlkUWSjzG12" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=T0X9r4rnn0A&amp;context=C31acf60ADOEgsToPDskKXCGGKCx3jSvlkUWSjzG12</a></p>
<p>Acapulco Gold - <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=bmWQYAj-fsU&amp;context=C31acf60ADOEgsToPDskKXCGGKCx3jSvlkUWSjzG12" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=bmWQYAj-fsU&amp;context=C31acf60ADOEgsToPDskKXCGGKCx3jSvlkUWSjzG12</a></p>
<p>Misdirected - <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=3Zq0ScBdzBM&amp;context=C31acf60ADOEgsToPDskKXCGGKCx3jSvlkUWSjzG12" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=3Zq0ScBdzBM&amp;context=C31acf60ADOEgsToPDskKXCGGKCx3jSvlkUWSjzG12</a></p>
<p>Not for nothing - (acoustic) - <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=nYIM4mpPDsY" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=nYIM4mpPDsY</a></p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">1st album “The Album” <span class="bbcode-i">coming soon</span></span></p>
<h2>Live performances:</h2>
<p>Not for nothing - (live) - <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=TdMLkC8gsJ4&amp;feature=related" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=TdMLkC8gsJ4&amp;feature=related</a></p>
<p>Idiot Box - (Incubus cover) - <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Wbgi_w_slfQ&amp;feature=related" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Wbgi_w_slfQ&amp;feature=related</a></p>
<p>Work (original) into De Do Do Do De Da Da Da (Police cover) - <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=fYiJ7z7krbA&amp;feature=related" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=fYiJ7z7krbA&amp;feature=related</a></p>
<p>Superpitfall - (original) - <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=gHQUVbTMFaM&amp;feature=related" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=gHQUVbTMFaM&amp;feature=related</a></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/forgetful-jones-original-rock/6861/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/forgetful-jones-original-rock/6861/3</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2012 01:52:02 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-6861-3</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/forgetful-jones-original-rock/6861.rss">Forgetful Jones - Original Rock</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Forgetful Jones - Original Rock</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Ramirezoid]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Not terrible. If badfish is any good I would definitely consider almost showing up at the Wilbur show.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/forgetful-jones-original-rock/6861/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/forgetful-jones-original-rock/6861/2</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 04 Apr 2011 02:02:56 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-6861-2</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/forgetful-jones-original-rock/6861.rss">Forgetful Jones - Original Rock</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Forgetful Jones - Original Rock</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Onemanwolfpack]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Yes its true, real people playing real instruments. Well, I’m sry to say that the band has since broke up and gone seperate ways but I spent many years with some close friends of mine playing music in this band. 2 full length records, many shows, great times and probably thousands of beers, lol. It never paid the bills but it was a labor of love and like I said, it was a fun ride but its over now. I’d like as many people as possible to leave some feedback, good, bad, indifferent, dosen’t matter. Give a listen and tell me what you think. It might still be on Itunes, not sure. It might not be your cup of tea, thats fine, its music and its meant to be heard, its a waste to not put it out there.</p>
<p>MySpace - <a href="https://www.myspace.com/fjrock" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://www.myspace.com/fjrock</a></p>
<p>Mainsite - <a href="https://forgetfuljonesband.com/#/?p=1" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://forgetfuljonesband.com/#/?p=1</a></p>
<p>Youtube links to other tracks are located 2 posts down.</p>
<p>PLEASE LEAVE COMMENTS AND FEEDBACK !!! THANKS and ENJOY !!!</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/forgetful-jones-original-rock/6861/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/forgetful-jones-original-rock/6861/1</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 04 Apr 2011 01:49:01 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-6861-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/forgetful-jones-original-rock/6861.rss">Forgetful Jones - Original Rock</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
