<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Creepypasta thread</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/creepypasta-thread/5168</link>
    <description>Post any good creepypastas or other miscellaneous creepy stuff you know here. (assuming it&#39;s not against forum rules...)  I&#39;ll start.

[i][COLOR=&#39;White&#39;]White and Red
[/i]
[quote]
A man went to a hotel and walked up to the front desk to check in. The woman at the desk gave him his key and told him that on the way to his room, there was a door with no number that was locked and no one was allowed in there. Especially no one should look inside the room, under any circumstances. So he followed the instructions of the woman at the front desk, going straight to his room, and going to bed.

The next night his curiosity would not leave him alone about the room with no number on the door. He walked down the hall to the door and tried the handle. Sure enough it was locked. He bent down and looked through the wide keyhole. Cold air passed through it, chilling his eye. What he saw was a hotel bedroom, like his, and in the corner was a woman whose skin was completely white. She was leaning her head against the wall, facing away from the door. He stared in confusion for a while. He almost knocked on the door, out of curiosity, but decided not to.

This disinclination saved his life. He crept away from the door and walked back to his room. The next day, he returned to the door and looked through the wide keyhole. This time, all he saw was redness. He couldn&#39;t make anything out besides a distinct red color, unmoving. Perhaps the inhabitants of the room knew he was spying the night before, and had blocked the keyhole with something red.

At this point he decided to consult the woman at the front desk for more information. She sighed and said, &quot;Did you look through the keyhole?&quot; The man told her that he had and she said, &quot;Well, I might as well tell you the story. A long time ago, a man murdered his wife in that room, and her ghost haunts it. But these people were not ordinary. They were white all over, except for their eyes, which were red.&quot;
[/quote]</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 14 Sep 2010 03:47:38 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Off Topic</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/creepypasta-thread/5168.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Creepypasta thread</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[papernick]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>facepunch + soaringscout + necroposting =</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/creepypasta-thread/5168/57">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/creepypasta-thread/5168/57</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Sep 2010 03:47:38 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-5168-57</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/creepypasta-thread/5168.rss">Creepypasta thread</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Creepypasta thread</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[SoaringScout]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><a href="https://www.facepunch.com/showthread.php?t=999830" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://www.facepunch.com/showthread.php?t=999830</a></p>
<p>It’s very long, but it’s well put together.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/creepypasta-thread/5168/56">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/creepypasta-thread/5168/56</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Sep 2010 03:33:57 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-5168-56</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/creepypasta-thread/5168.rss">Creepypasta thread</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Creepypasta thread</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[X_Mastershot_X]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>:fffuuu:</p>
<p>[COLOR=‘black’]rololololol ghost post you have found me yore a genius!!111</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/creepypasta-thread/5168/55">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/creepypasta-thread/5168/55</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 05 Sep 2010 20:21:42 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-5168-55</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/creepypasta-thread/5168.rss">Creepypasta thread</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Creepypasta thread</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Hazzmat]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>[COLOR=‘Black’]This post has no story</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/creepypasta-thread/5168/54">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/creepypasta-thread/5168/54</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 05 Sep 2010 19:38:08 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-5168-54</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/creepypasta-thread/5168.rss">Creepypasta thread</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Creepypasta thread</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[wheybags]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>But who was phone?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/creepypasta-thread/5168/53">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/creepypasta-thread/5168/53</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Aug 2010 19:51:57 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-5168-53</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/creepypasta-thread/5168.rss">Creepypasta thread</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Creepypasta thread</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Mr.Shadow]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>^best story so far</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/creepypasta-thread/5168/52">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/creepypasta-thread/5168/52</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Aug 2010 18:57:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-5168-52</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/creepypasta-thread/5168.rss">Creepypasta thread</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Creepypasta thread</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Combine]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>One night, I was in bed, beating my wife, when phone ring. I beat<br>
phone, then pick it up. I hear voice. Voice says;<br>
“What you do with my daughter?!”<br>
I turn to wife and demand to know why her father interrupt me beating<br>
her. But she say, her father is dead!<br>
Then, KGB break into house and arrest me for illegal possession of phone.</p>
<p>Such is life in Moscow.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/creepypasta-thread/5168/51">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/creepypasta-thread/5168/51</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Aug 2010 18:50:38 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-5168-51</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/creepypasta-thread/5168.rss">Creepypasta thread</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Creepypasta thread</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Wombat]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>hahahaha I loved the WITNESS one</p>
<p>if somebody knocks on my door I will shit in my pants  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/frowning.png?v=9" title=":frowning:" class="emoji" alt=":frowning:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/creepypasta-thread/5168/50">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/creepypasta-thread/5168/50</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Aug 2010 18:40:59 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-5168-50</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/creepypasta-thread/5168.rss">Creepypasta thread</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Creepypasta thread</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[X_Mastershot_X]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>rofl Combine is doin’ it rite but these are too lame for me  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/frowning.png?v=9" title=":frowning:" class="emoji" alt=":frowning:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/creepypasta-thread/5168/49">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/creepypasta-thread/5168/49</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Aug 2010 10:09:31 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-5168-49</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/creepypasta-thread/5168.rss">Creepypasta thread</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Creepypasta thread</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[sersoft]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Android11x">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/a/b9bd4f/40.png" class="avatar"> Android11x:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>This is getting me off. More please.</p>
<p>ALSO:</p>
<p><span alt="" class="broken-image" title="This image is broken"><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-unlink svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#unlink"></use></svg></span></p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>this is very on topic</p>
<p>everyone else should get banned for derailing, including OP</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/creepypasta-thread/5168/48">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/creepypasta-thread/5168/48</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Aug 2010 05:53:46 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-5168-48</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/creepypasta-thread/5168.rss">Creepypasta thread</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Creepypasta thread</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[DeleteThis]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Combine is the only one doing it right in this thread</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/creepypasta-thread/5168/47">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/creepypasta-thread/5168/47</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Aug 2010 05:45:27 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-5168-47</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/creepypasta-thread/5168.rss">Creepypasta thread</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Creepypasta thread</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Combine]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>I am currently sitting in front of my computer, scared witless. Any moment now I am going to be killed.</p>
<p>Today a friend of mine told me a story.</p>
<p>His aunt had taken care of him since he was a small boy, and she told him last night about how his parents died. He did a very fair imitation of her (I knew them both pretty well):</p>
<p>They were doing mission work in some nasty little south american country when a man burst into the mission hospital one night, terrified out of his mind. He told them that his sister had been killed by a Muerto blanco, and that he was certain that it was coming for him next. What is a Muerto blanco? Apparently it was some sort of bogey-man, something like that dumb chupacabra or whatever. They called it the White Death or the White Girl, because it was the soul of someone who hated life so much that they came back in their shrouds to kill those who told of them.</p>
<p>The man had been told about the vengeful spirit by his sister hours before her death. It was a girl with dead, black eyes that wept bile. The thing moved without ever actually moving its legs, and it stalked its victims back to their homes. Now, if you werent already aware that this thing was following you, once it got back to your house, it would start knocking on your door</p>
<p>Once for you skin, which shell use to patch her own decaying flesh. Twice for your muscle, which shell gnash her teeth on between victims. Thrice for your bones, which shell make knives to pick her teeth and kill her victims. Four times for your heart, which shell wear around her neck. Five times for your teeth, which shell polish and keep in a box. Six times for your eyes, which shell see the faces of your loved ones through. Seven times for your soul, which shell eat whole - you can never pass while youre in her stomach. She has to repeat this on any mirror or door between you and her.</p>
<p>You can try to outrun her, but shes faster than the fastest man. And if you leave your home while shes knocking on your door, she wont be so courteous when she catches up to you.</p>
<p>Now the man was certain that this thing had killed his sister, that he had tried to tell the police, but they would not listen. Next he had tried to tell his priest, but the priest turned him away when he saw that the thing was following him now - oh, thats right, I forgot about that - it can only get you if you tell someone else about it, or you saw it kill someone else. The man, after finishing his tale, stole a car from the mission, and was never seen again.</p>
<p>Apparently his mother and father had immediately called his aunt about this when it happened. They were found in the morning, skinned and dismembered. Their bodies were covered in tiny, child-like handprints.</p>
<p>His aunt was really drunk the night before, and had told him about that. He told me this story early in the morning today at school, before the cops arrived. His aunt had been murdered that night. I called him later that night, and he told me that he was being chased by someone, and now they were knocking on his door. I told him to stop shitting me.</p>
<p>He held the phone away from his face for a minute, and I could hear slow, deliberate knocking. A moment later, I heard the door rip from its hinges and the dying screams of my friend.</p>
<p>Then a little girls voice spoke over the line: WITNESS. I hung up.</p>
<p>Three minutes ago someone started knocking on my door. She has to knock 28 times on my front door, 28 times on the mirror in the hall, and another 28 times on the door to my bedroom. Shes doing it slowly I think she wants to scare me some more, let me know that my death is just moments away. I will not run - I couldnt get to my car in time anyway. She started knocking on my bedroom door a minute ago, she should be done any moment.</p>
<p>Nice knowing you guys, its been funjklm,.-</p>
<p>WITNESS</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/creepypasta-thread/5168/46">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/creepypasta-thread/5168/46</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Aug 2010 02:25:15 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-5168-46</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/creepypasta-thread/5168.rss">Creepypasta thread</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Creepypasta thread</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Combine]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="super lurker">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 super lurker:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>i remember a story someone had posted on here about some hunter sleeping in a cabin with a shitton of freaky portraits inside and when he woke up THERE WERE ONLY WINDOWS man it was good</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>There was a hunter in the woods, who, after a long day hunting, was in the middle of an immense forest. It was getting dark, and having lost his bearings, he decided to head in one direction until he was clear of the increasingly oppressive foliage. After a what seemed like hours, he came across a cabin in a small clearing. Realizing how dark it had grown, he decided to see if he could stay there for the night. He approached, and found the door ajar. Nobody was inside. The hunter flopped down on the single bed, deciding to explain himself to the owner in the morning. As he looked around, he was suprised to see the walls adorned by many portraits, all painted in incredible detail. Without exception, they appeared to be staring down at him, their features twisted into looks of hatred. Staring back, he grew increasingly uncomfortable. Making a concerted effort to ignore the many hateful faces, he turned to face the wall, and exhausted, he fell into a restless sleep.</p>
<p>Face down in an unfamiliar bed, he turned blinking in unexpected sunlight. Looking up, he discovered that the cabin had no portraits, only windows.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/creepypasta-thread/5168/45">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/creepypasta-thread/5168/45</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Aug 2010 02:17:14 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-5168-45</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/creepypasta-thread/5168.rss">Creepypasta thread</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Creepypasta thread</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Imonfire]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>You’re too late, boy.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Imonfire">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/i/e47c2d/40.png" class="avatar"> Imonfire:</div>
<blockquote>
<blockquote class="indent">
<p>“<span class="bbcode-i">So ur with ur honey and yur making out wen the phone rigns. U anser it n the vioce is “wut r u doing wit my daughter?” U tell ur girl n she say “my dad is ded”. THEN WHO WAS PHONE?</span>”</p>
</blockquote>
</blockquote>
</aside>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/creepypasta-thread/5168/44">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/creepypasta-thread/5168/44</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Aug 2010 00:03:12 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-5168-44</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/creepypasta-thread/5168.rss">Creepypasta thread</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Creepypasta thread</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[THRRRPT]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><span alt="" class="broken-image" title="This image is broken"><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-unlink svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#unlink"></use></svg></span></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/creepypasta-thread/5168/43">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/creepypasta-thread/5168/43</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Aug 2010 23:51:35 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-5168-43</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/creepypasta-thread/5168.rss">Creepypasta thread</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Creepypasta thread</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[super_lurker]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>i remember a story someone had posted on here about some hunter sleeping in a cabin with a shitton of freaky portraits inside and when he woke up THERE WERE ONLY WINDOWS man it was good</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/creepypasta-thread/5168/42">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/creepypasta-thread/5168/42</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Aug 2010 23:05:51 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-5168-42</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/creepypasta-thread/5168.rss">Creepypasta thread</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Creepypasta thread</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Android11x]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Well, some one these were interesting reads.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/creepypasta-thread/5168/41">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/creepypasta-thread/5168/41</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Aug 2010 21:31:21 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-5168-41</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/creepypasta-thread/5168.rss">Creepypasta thread</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Creepypasta thread</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Dias]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>That pretty much applies to this entire thread.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/creepypasta-thread/5168/40">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/creepypasta-thread/5168/40</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Aug 2010 21:29:24 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-5168-40</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/creepypasta-thread/5168.rss">Creepypasta thread</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Creepypasta thread</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Android11x]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Was that supposed to be scary? That was stupid.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/creepypasta-thread/5168/39">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/creepypasta-thread/5168/39</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Aug 2010 21:20:31 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-5168-39</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/creepypasta-thread/5168.rss">Creepypasta thread</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Creepypasta thread</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Wombat]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>A few years ago, a woman and her family had just moved to a new house somewhere in Melbourne, Victoria, Australia. One night, her baby son was crying so she got out of bed and went to see him. Suddenly, the baby stopped crying. The woman knew that he must have fallen asleep so she went back to bed. A few hours later, the baby cried again, so she got up and went over to check again. As she opened the door to her son’s room, she saw a boy, about 6 or 7 years old, calming the baby down. When he saw the woman, he disappeared. The woman was shocked and later told her neighbours what happened. The neighbours already knew about the ghost and told her that there was a boy who died from an illness, about 80 years ago, and was buried under the exact place where her baby son’s room is.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/creepypasta-thread/5168/38">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/creepypasta-thread/5168/38</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Aug 2010 20:52:53 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-5168-38</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/creepypasta-thread/5168.rss">Creepypasta thread</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Creepypasta thread</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[X_Mastershot_X]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Combine’s sstory was pretty good and made me see once again how stupid we humans are. And killer dolls :meh: meh</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/creepypasta-thread/5168/37">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/creepypasta-thread/5168/37</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 24 Aug 2010 22:45:06 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-5168-37</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/creepypasta-thread/5168.rss">Creepypasta thread</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Creepypasta thread</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Mr.Shadow]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>Once, there was a small girl, named Sarah. On her birthday, she got a doll. She loved it and played with it all day. In the evening her parents said to leave the doll on the table, to let Rebecca (that’s the doll’s name) get used to the house. At night, Sarah heard a voice singing “Rebecca on the first step, Rebecca on the second step, Rebecca on the thrid step”. That’s when Sarah screamed for her daddy and mommy. They came in her room where she explained everything. They watched and found the doll on the third step of the stairway. The father said that they must’ve left it there and Sarah must’ve imagined the voice.</p>
<p>The next night she heard the voice again. “Rebecca on the fourth step. Rebecca on the fifth step” Again she screamed her lungs out. The parents watched again and then the father knew something was happening and took the doll and cycled to the nearest forest and burried it as deep as he could dig. The same night, Sarah heard the voice again. “Rebecca on the sixth step”. Sarah thought she imagined it, because the doll was burried. “Rebecca in front of your door”. Sarah still thought she imagined it and kept her eyes closed. “Rebecca in your room”. Sarah was getting nervous now, having sweat on her forehead, struggling to keep her eyes closed and to keep herself from screaming. “Rebecca on your bed”. Sarah again struggled to keep her eyes closed. “Rebecca next to your pillow”. Sarah opened her eyes and automaticly opened her mouth after seeing the sight, but no sound came out of it, for she was already dead.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/creepypasta-thread/5168/36">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/creepypasta-thread/5168/36</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 24 Aug 2010 19:28:02 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-5168-36</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/creepypasta-thread/5168.rss">Creepypasta thread</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Creepypasta thread</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Combine]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>On the last day of every month, close the blinds or curtains before you sleep. If in the middle of the night, you hear a tapping noise at your window, don’t open your eyes.</p>
<p>If you’re one of the unlucky ones, you’ll hear that pebble sound at your window. It’s not a friend; just keep your eyes shut. The sound will get louder, the tapping will get faster and faster. Don’t let your curiosity get the better of you; don’t move. It’ll lose its patience, it’ll start thumping the window. Your window will shake and shudder and the noises will only get louder. It will furiously pound the window and shake the panes; don’t worry, the window won’t break but for goodness’ sake, DON’T OPEN YOUR EYES. No matter how scared you are, no matter how badly you want to scream, pretend like you don’t hear, pretend you’re still asleep.</p>
<p>After a while, the noises will stop. Don’t fall for it, keep your eyes shut. Try to sleep if you can. Don’t get up, don’t open your eyes, until the sun comes up.</p>
<p>Those who do open their eyes…well, no one really knows what happens.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/creepypasta-thread/5168/35">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/creepypasta-thread/5168/35</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 24 Aug 2010 18:52:46 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-5168-35</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/creepypasta-thread/5168.rss">Creepypasta thread</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Creepypasta thread</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Android11x]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>This is getting me off. More please.</p>
<p>ALSO:</p>
<p><span alt="" class="broken-image" title="This image is broken"><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-unlink svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#unlink"></use></svg></span></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/creepypasta-thread/5168/34">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/creepypasta-thread/5168/34</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Aug 2010 01:43:04 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-5168-34</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/creepypasta-thread/5168.rss">Creepypasta thread</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Creepypasta thread</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Fnoigy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Doop">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/d/5fc32e/40.png" class="avatar"> Doop:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>this kid was born then he died</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>AAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAHHHHH!!!</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/creepypasta-thread/5168/33">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/creepypasta-thread/5168/33</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 22 Aug 2010 14:42:33 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-5168-33</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/creepypasta-thread/5168.rss">Creepypasta thread</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
