<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>problems with Shogun 2</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/problems-with-shogun-2/6755</link>
    <description>I had some serious graphical issues with the game when I first got it, but that just came down to outdated driver support; however while the game is  now at a playable standard, I&#39;m still suffering from no antialiasing (as in, the menu won&#39;t even let me) and ugly, poor textures; my graphics card is a Nvidia GeForce 9800 GT which according to sega support is fine for the game. I&#39;m also now having an issue with steam which prevents me from playing the game whereupon I get an error message saying &quot;Incomplete installation of Total War: Shogun 2 (15)&quot;, which wasn&#39;t explained at the steam help and support section.

any help is appreciated, even just a simple explaination would be good enough.

many thanks</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 27 Mar 2011 16:20:48 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Help and Support</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/problems-with-shogun-2/6755.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>problems with Shogun 2</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Harun]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>any luck fixing the issue yet? just curious</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/problems-with-shogun-2/6755/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/problems-with-shogun-2/6755/4</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 27 Mar 2011 16:20:48 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-6755-4</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/problems-with-shogun-2/6755.rss">problems with Shogun 2</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>problems with Shogun 2</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[blackout]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>cheers, will check this out  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=9" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/problems-with-shogun-2/6755/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/problems-with-shogun-2/6755/3</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 24 Mar 2011 21:28:58 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-6755-3</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/problems-with-shogun-2/6755.rss">problems with Shogun 2</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>problems with Shogun 2</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Harun]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I guess you have tried reinstalling already? If not, then try that, would be easiest.<br>
Maybe something was for some reason not copied when you installed the game.<br>
Also, some games require software like Direct X or the C++ Redist and actually have it on the medium they’re on but don´t install the additional software automatically.(Happened to me sometimes, though never with Steam I think)<br>
If you have the game on DVD then try looking for additional software there. It´s often in a certain folder which is named in a plausible way(forgot what it exactly was) so you shouldn´t have problems finding it. Even if the game did install everything, you could try installing the required additional software again. Maybe there went something wrong when you installed it the first time.<br>
Maybe the game also requires software it doesn´t provide. You surely can find a list of software requirements online.<br>
Do other games run as they should with your GFX-Card? If yes then I guess there is really just something missing in your game files or software the game is using. If not then you got a hardware problem.(At least most likely)</p>
<p>This is not very technical help. Maybe it actually does help anyway. If no one else here is able to help you then you should go to the official forums and open a topic there or actually use the support.</p>
<p>Now that I come to think of it, could it have something to do with PhysX maybe?(Does the game even support PhysX?)</p>
<p>Anyway, good luck</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/problems-with-shogun-2/6755/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/problems-with-shogun-2/6755/2</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 24 Mar 2011 20:52:50 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-6755-2</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/problems-with-shogun-2/6755.rss">problems with Shogun 2</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>problems with Shogun 2</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[blackout]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I had some serious graphical issues with the game when I first got it, but that just came down to outdated driver support; however while the game is  now at a playable standard, I’m still suffering from no antialiasing (as in, the menu won’t even let me) and ugly, poor textures; my graphics card is a Nvidia GeForce 9800 GT which according to sega support is fine for the game. I’m also now having an issue with steam which prevents me from playing the game whereupon I get an error message saying “Incomplete installation of Total War: Shogun 2 (15)”, which wasn’t explained at the steam help and support section.</p>
<p>any help is appreciated, even just a simple explaination would be good enough.</p>
<p>many thanks</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/problems-with-shogun-2/6755/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/problems-with-shogun-2/6755/1</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 16 Mar 2011 21:43:17 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-6755-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/problems-with-shogun-2/6755.rss">problems with Shogun 2</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
