<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>NOSTALGIA ALERT: The Purist Manifesto</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/nostalgia-alert-the-purist-manifesto/9287</link>
    <description>For those who were members of the BM community back in 2006, prepare for an overdose in nostalgia. If you were not around during those dark times, don&#39;t take the following document seriously. At any rate, I give you lovely folks the legendary Purist Manifesto. Yes, I kept it around so that one day, we could all look back on it and laugh, and laugh... and laugh.  :stuck_out_tongue: 
[quote]
DISCLAIMER: All text in this document--even those based on real situations--is entirely fictional. All Breencasts are imitated..... poorly. It contains coarse rhetoric and due to its content should not be read by anyone.

[b][u][align=center]THE PURIST MANIFESTO: BY BLACK OP[/align][/u][/b]
     And just exactly are the benefits of following Half Life Revisionism, I may ask? You can make all the ideas for BM(S) in the world, but what are the chances that the BM(S) Team will heed what you say? Ask all the people that wanted to drive vehicles in BM(S), or those that wanted mirrors to be implemented, or even those that wanted the human grunts to wear PCVs. These people followed an ideology that failed to take into account what BM(S)&#39;s main objective is; to recreate the original content of HL1 on the Source engine and organize them in a way that&#39;s both faithful to the source material and make it fit with HL2 so that both BM(S) and HL2 flow seamlessly. Thus, these Revisionists set themselves up for disappointment when the BM(S) Team took Purist stances by declaring BM(S) will have no drivable vehicles, or when it became clear the PCVs would not appear on the grunts.

     Of course even I know that in some fields such as map design, Revisionism will be quite dominant. However this is so only because map design was limited compared to what can be achieved today. Because other core gameplay factors do not rely so heavily on visuals, they would not seem dated if translated onto the Source engine. As most people will download BM(S) to have their HL1 experience translated to the improved Source engine, they would be disheartened if one element was modified so that BM(S) didn&#39;t resemble HL1.

     But fear not, my fellow comrades. Even if the vilest of Revisionist filth makes its way onto these beloved forums, there is no assurance that the BM(S) Team would decide to heed it. Indeed, many ideas that are posted can be for naught if much of the gameplay factors have been decided upon by now. So what use is free thought in a community where technically free speech doesn’t exist as any thread can be locked at will? What happens when all the time and effort spent to make a suggestion is wasted because the BM(S) Team has already decided the course of the future? Furthermore, just what signs are there that the BM(S) is seriously considering changing the core elements of HL1 such as how weapons operate and how enemies attack? My friends, comrades, brothers....... there are none.

     It is a shame how Revisionists blindly assume that following the Purist ideology means that one can not support any progress at all. Therefore they claim false triumphs of their ideology over mentions of any BM(S) feature or element that is not the same as it was in HL1. The reality is that Purists are well aware of the fact that one of BM(S)&#39;s goals is to make HL1 flow with HL2 without any anomalies in various fields. Following this doctrine, the BM(S) Team is justified in inserting elements that are derived from HL2 such as multiple NPC variations and inserting notes. This rule even justifies deviations in level design, as what looks good in the HL1 engine may not look good on the Source engine. As for the so-called Revisionist victory with a Co-op mode, it must be emphasized that BM(S)&#39;s energy is mostly bent towards the singleplayer portion which mirrors the priorities of VALVe when they were creating HL1. As HL was not memorable for its multiplayer mode, a certain level of impurity can be accepted in that area. It must be added though that with the exception of Co-op, all other new multiplayer ideas have been rejected time and time again.

     Another falsehood originating from the followers of Revisionism is that they are different from Unpurists, and that their ideas are destined to be seen as improvements. Revisionists operate under the pretense that they can improve BM(S) for the better without being unfaithful to HL1. However the dark truth is that Revisionism has to be very much intertwined with Unpurism in order to make a noteworthy difference. Revisionists also assume that whatever they suggest will be an automatic improvement over the original, and therefore will be accepted by all who play BM(S). That my comrades is nothing more but their delusions, for there are people who will play BM(S) and reject a sign of Revisionist thinking should they find it disagreeable. Even now on these very forums, Revisionists debate amongst themselves on what should be improved and how so. In the vast majority of these debates, no clear decision is ever reached unless a BM(S) Developer intervenes. Finally, Revisionist thinking is ignorant of the fact that the capabilities of the Source engine are to be used wisely. BM(S) players will be disappointed if they think the Source engine is being abused to the point where BM(S) does not resemble HL1. Only now at the end do we understand how following the Purist way of thinking prevents any sort of conflict on how to proceed with how a game element or feature is supposed to work. Anything that didn&#39;t work in HL1 can be improved by using the already-mentioned doctrine that the BM(S) Team is justified to follow.

     Indeed at first glance, there is no apparent purpose for the Ideas Forum if none of the Developers ever bother to consider what is posted in there. Then again, nearly all mods have a forum to post ideas in. This is so because it serves as a way for a mod to cement its fanbase. By allowing for fans to post their suggestions, it will assure that they will return to the forum they posted at for further discussion. For mods such as BM(S), this means they will have the services a loyal community they can rely on in the event that they are required. Already with BM(S), we see this in the Purist-acceptable form of Community Projects and Media Updates. In the future, this will manifest itself in the form of betatesting. Aside for those things though, fans are expected to follow the mod until the time comes for its release when they&#39;ll be then expected to download it. To improve the chances of this happening, the BM(S) Team has come up with the grand illusion of a location where ideas can be discussed freely. As long as this illusion is maintained, it doesn&#39;t matter if the ideas posted there will actually be inserted into BM(S) or not.

     As for the Revisionist belief that the game they want will be for everyone, that is clearly a false statement. Unlike Purists, those that have the Revisionist mindset lack the benefit of a clearly defined guideline system which enables them to determine which ideas are good and which are not. Due to this lack of unification, Revisionists actually make suggestions that instead of being meant for everyone&#39;s enjoyment are really meant to shape BM(S) in their own personal image. Purists have long ago realized that Revisionists do not follow a true ideology; it is well known that Revisionists merely seek to impose their own personal views in order to influence BM(S) in a way that will benefit themselves. This disunity amongst the followers of Revisionism is most obvious in threads where multiple ideas are suggested by different Revisionists, all in their own quest to see BM(S) the way they want to see it. In contrast, Purists are generally consistent as a whole in what they want in BM(S). Because of this, any feature or element that remains Purist is automatically assured to be accepted by a good amount of people. On the other hand, anything with a Revisionist slant in it is not guaranteed to be accepted by all Revisionists. By learning to recognize how Revisionists operate only for their own ends, one can break through their web of propaganda and question if they really have the benefit of everyone in mind.

     Those forumers and team members who follow Purism know that Revisionism is inextricably bound to unreasoning impulses, and today we clearly see its true nature. Revisionism has always been aware of its irrelevance, and like a cornered n00b it will not go down without a bloody fight. Revisionism would inflict a major injury on BM(S). Revisionism creates its own flamers, and bids us rise up against them. Revisionism tells us that the unknown is a false opportunity, rather than the threat it really is. Revisionism slyly and covertly compels us away from the elements that made HL1 the Game of the Year as considered by many.

     Revisionism therefore must be expunged. It must be fought tooth and nail beginning with the basest of forumer urges: the urge to post new and original ideas. We should thank the Purist ideology for giving us respite from this overpowering force. Following Purism allows one to throw a switch and exercise the forum&#39;s demons in a single post. Purism has given us the strength we&#39;ve never could have summoned to overcome this compulsion. Purism has given us purpose; it has turned our eyes toward the stars. Let me assure you that the idea suppressing field will be shut off on the day that we have mastered ourselves, the day we can prove we no longer need it. And that day of transformation I have it on good authority comrades, is close at hand.

     Thus comrades, do not fear the Purist ideology. By following it, one will be assured that BM(S) to be just as enjoyable as HL1 if not even better. Why settle for an unholy faith that will either bring embarrassment upon the name of HL1 or will produce threads which go unnoticed by the BM(S) Team and find themselves locked anyways? Believe in Purism..... it&#39;s safer there.
[/quote]</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Sep 2012 09:01:32 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Off Topic</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/nostalgia-alert-the-purist-manifesto/9287.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>NOSTALGIA ALERT: The Purist Manifesto</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[zim]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Haha, arguing about mirrors and helmets. Things were simpler then. I remember when I first showed up here someone said the mod would probably come out in 2008 and I got all bent out of shape. “I’ll be 18, I’ll be old by then!”</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/nostalgia-alert-the-purist-manifesto/9287/77">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/nostalgia-alert-the-purist-manifesto/9287/77</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 08 Sep 2012 09:01:32 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9287-77</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/nostalgia-alert-the-purist-manifesto/9287.rss">NOSTALGIA ALERT: The Purist Manifesto</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>NOSTALGIA ALERT: The Purist Manifesto</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[sersoft]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="jambo">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/user_avatar/leakfree.org/jambo/40/4501_2.png" class="avatar"> jambo:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>12 bananas</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>So I bought a new Banana last week and it’s much better than my previous Banana because it has a Banana Banana with Banana Bananas of Banana. But it keeps dropping calls when in Banana mode, and it really pissed me off. Fuck this Banana.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/nostalgia-alert-the-purist-manifesto/9287/76">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/nostalgia-alert-the-purist-manifesto/9287/76</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Sep 2012 20:50:05 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9287-76</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/nostalgia-alert-the-purist-manifesto/9287.rss">NOSTALGIA ALERT: The Purist Manifesto</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>NOSTALGIA ALERT: The Purist Manifesto</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Schrikvis]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I should have made an account back then, oh well.<br>
I remember reading that while lurking.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/nostalgia-alert-the-purist-manifesto/9287/75">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/nostalgia-alert-the-purist-manifesto/9287/75</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Sep 2012 19:45:01 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9287-75</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/nostalgia-alert-the-purist-manifesto/9287.rss">NOSTALGIA ALERT: The Purist Manifesto</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>NOSTALGIA ALERT: The Purist Manifesto</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Skaevola]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>BLACK OP!!<br>
How I have missed your stupid purist face!<br>
When I joined this forum, I was twelve and I thought all your opinions were dumb. As the years have gone by, I have come to truly respect you and your ability to stay focused on a project which stayed true to the source material. Now, as a full-grown adult, I find that I agree with almost everything I remember you saying throughout the years. And there was many a time in the long development period of this mod when I wished you were here to kick some newbie ass.<br>
Just thought you’d like to know.</p>
<p>EDIT: Also, since that adolescent period in which I became acquainted with you, I read George Orwell’s 1984 and I thought of you the whole time because of your signature. You know, when I wasn’t horrified over the word-picture Orwell painted of a dystopian future, the edge upon which we are gloabally precariously balanced.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/nostalgia-alert-the-purist-manifesto/9287/74">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/nostalgia-alert-the-purist-manifesto/9287/74</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Sep 2012 07:08:21 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9287-74</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/nostalgia-alert-the-purist-manifesto/9287.rss">NOSTALGIA ALERT: The Purist Manifesto</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>NOSTALGIA ALERT: The Purist Manifesto</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[jambo]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="sersoft">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/user_avatar/leakfree.org/sersoft/40/5837_2.png" class="avatar"> sersoft:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>You want to buy James Bond briefcase yes? :lol:</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>12 bananas</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/nostalgia-alert-the-purist-manifesto/9287/73">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/nostalgia-alert-the-purist-manifesto/9287/73</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Sep 2012 02:52:25 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9287-73</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/nostalgia-alert-the-purist-manifesto/9287.rss">NOSTALGIA ALERT: The Purist Manifesto</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>NOSTALGIA ALERT: The Purist Manifesto</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[rtanger]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="BahamutBBob">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/b/e9bcb4/40.png" class="avatar"> BahamutBBob:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I sent RTanger a message on Xbox Live.  It’s only a matter of time before he sees it and joins us.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>More than a little late to this party. You really sent me a msg clear back in Feb? I really need to keep up on this stuff better. :fffuuu:</p>
<p>edit: aaaaannnnnd… now I think the dates are all European style on me and I really look like an idiot. Cool.</p>
<p>Just like the old days.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/nostalgia-alert-the-purist-manifesto/9287/72">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/nostalgia-alert-the-purist-manifesto/9287/72</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Sep 2012 02:24:45 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9287-72</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/nostalgia-alert-the-purist-manifesto/9287.rss">NOSTALGIA ALERT: The Purist Manifesto</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>NOSTALGIA ALERT: The Purist Manifesto</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[sersoft]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>You want to buy James Bond briefcase yes? :lol:</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/nostalgia-alert-the-purist-manifesto/9287/71">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/nostalgia-alert-the-purist-manifesto/9287/71</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 06 Sep 2012 23:04:33 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9287-71</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/nostalgia-alert-the-purist-manifesto/9287.rss">NOSTALGIA ALERT: The Purist Manifesto</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>NOSTALGIA ALERT: The Purist Manifesto</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Black_Op]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Well, I have that comic on my hard drive so there.  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=9" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/nostalgia-alert-the-purist-manifesto/9287/70">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/nostalgia-alert-the-purist-manifesto/9287/70</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 06 Sep 2012 22:57:35 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9287-70</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/nostalgia-alert-the-purist-manifesto/9287.rss">NOSTALGIA ALERT: The Purist Manifesto</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>NOSTALGIA ALERT: The Purist Manifesto</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[operative_lm]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>This is actually the first time it’s ever been posted in the wild.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/nostalgia-alert-the-purist-manifesto/9287/69">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/nostalgia-alert-the-purist-manifesto/9287/69</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 06 Sep 2012 22:16:37 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9287-69</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/nostalgia-alert-the-purist-manifesto/9287.rss">NOSTALGIA ALERT: The Purist Manifesto</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>NOSTALGIA ALERT: The Purist Manifesto</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[BahamutBBob]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I think I left before that one was made.</p>
<p>I approve, however.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/nostalgia-alert-the-purist-manifesto/9287/68">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/nostalgia-alert-the-purist-manifesto/9287/68</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 06 Sep 2012 21:28:27 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9287-68</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/nostalgia-alert-the-purist-manifesto/9287.rss">NOSTALGIA ALERT: The Purist Manifesto</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>NOSTALGIA ALERT: The Purist Manifesto</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[operative_lm]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="BahamutBBob">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/b/e9bcb4/40.png" class="avatar"> BahamutBBob:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Only if they also include the James Bond briefcase.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p><a href="https://img402.imageshack.us/img402/5233/comicp01.jpg" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://img402.imageshack.us/img402/5233/comicp01.jpg</a><br>
<a href="https://img268.imageshack.us/img268/3262/comicp02.jpg" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://img268.imageshack.us/img268/3262/comicp02.jpg</a></p>
<p>?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/nostalgia-alert-the-purist-manifesto/9287/67">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/nostalgia-alert-the-purist-manifesto/9287/67</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 06 Sep 2012 05:05:15 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9287-67</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/nostalgia-alert-the-purist-manifesto/9287.rss">NOSTALGIA ALERT: The Purist Manifesto</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>NOSTALGIA ALERT: The Purist Manifesto</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Dias]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="xalener">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/x/cc9497/40.png" class="avatar"> xalener:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Never change.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Bitching: It’s what I do. :3</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/nostalgia-alert-the-purist-manifesto/9287/66">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/nostalgia-alert-the-purist-manifesto/9287/66</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 06 Sep 2012 04:46:25 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9287-66</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/nostalgia-alert-the-purist-manifesto/9287.rss">NOSTALGIA ALERT: The Purist Manifesto</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>NOSTALGIA ALERT: The Purist Manifesto</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[bur]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="xalener">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/x/cc9497/40.png" class="avatar"> xalener:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>They made it in something.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>badum tum tsh</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/nostalgia-alert-the-purist-manifesto/9287/65">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/nostalgia-alert-the-purist-manifesto/9287/65</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 06 Sep 2012 00:25:02 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9287-65</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/nostalgia-alert-the-purist-manifesto/9287.rss">NOSTALGIA ALERT: The Purist Manifesto</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>NOSTALGIA ALERT: The Purist Manifesto</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[BahamutBBob]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="jambo">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/user_avatar/leakfree.org/jambo/40/4501_2.png" class="avatar"> jambo:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Post the comics!*</p>
<p>*just ones with me in them</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Only if they also include the James Bond briefcase.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/nostalgia-alert-the-purist-manifesto/9287/64">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/nostalgia-alert-the-purist-manifesto/9287/64</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 05 Sep 2012 20:33:47 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9287-64</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/nostalgia-alert-the-purist-manifesto/9287.rss">NOSTALGIA ALERT: The Purist Manifesto</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>NOSTALGIA ALERT: The Purist Manifesto</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[jnts]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Dude, i totaly forgot about the old forum, i was trying to log in with my old account, i even mailed the moderator. That is sad. By the way, like a lot of people i coming back here.  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/smiley.png?v=9" title=":smiley:" class="emoji" alt=":smiley:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/nostalgia-alert-the-purist-manifesto/9287/63">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/nostalgia-alert-the-purist-manifesto/9287/63</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 05 Sep 2012 16:17:27 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9287-63</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/nostalgia-alert-the-purist-manifesto/9287.rss">NOSTALGIA ALERT: The Purist Manifesto</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>NOSTALGIA ALERT: The Purist Manifesto</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[xalener]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="bur">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/b/87869e/40.png" class="avatar"> bur:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>man, I <span class="bbcode-i">really</span> hope the dick gibs made it in :3</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>They made it in something.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/nostalgia-alert-the-purist-manifesto/9287/62">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/nostalgia-alert-the-purist-manifesto/9287/62</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 05 Sep 2012 16:03:26 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9287-62</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/nostalgia-alert-the-purist-manifesto/9287.rss">NOSTALGIA ALERT: The Purist Manifesto</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>NOSTALGIA ALERT: The Purist Manifesto</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[bur]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>man, I <span class="bbcode-i">really</span> hope the dick gibs made it in :3</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Bloodshot">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/b/839c29/40.png" class="avatar"> Bloodshot:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I did not know that was Ram.</p>
<p>For some reason I always pictured him as being fairly muscular, and I have no idea why.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>it’s an ancient picture though</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/nostalgia-alert-the-purist-manifesto/9287/61">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/nostalgia-alert-the-purist-manifesto/9287/61</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 05 Sep 2012 06:54:52 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9287-61</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/nostalgia-alert-the-purist-manifesto/9287.rss">NOSTALGIA ALERT: The Purist Manifesto</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>NOSTALGIA ALERT: The Purist Manifesto</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[SVD]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="(rot)(fodder">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 (rot)(fodder:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I wonder if the alien dick gib ever made it into black mesa…</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Yeah the forums back then was a whole other level of strange  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=9" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/nostalgia-alert-the-purist-manifesto/9287/60">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/nostalgia-alert-the-purist-manifesto/9287/60</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 05 Sep 2012 06:53:59 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9287-60</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/nostalgia-alert-the-purist-manifesto/9287.rss">NOSTALGIA ALERT: The Purist Manifesto</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>NOSTALGIA ALERT: The Purist Manifesto</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[jambo]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="operative lm">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 operative lm:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>You fools! I am eternal!</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Post the comics!*</p>
<p>*just ones with me in them</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/nostalgia-alert-the-purist-manifesto/9287/59">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/nostalgia-alert-the-purist-manifesto/9287/59</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 05 Sep 2012 04:49:08 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9287-59</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/nostalgia-alert-the-purist-manifesto/9287.rss">NOSTALGIA ALERT: The Purist Manifesto</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>NOSTALGIA ALERT: The Purist Manifesto</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Bloodshot]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I did not know that was Ram.</p>
<p>For some reason I always pictured him as being fairly muscular, and I have no idea why.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/nostalgia-alert-the-purist-manifesto/9287/58">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/nostalgia-alert-the-purist-manifesto/9287/58</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 05 Sep 2012 04:11:56 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9287-58</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/nostalgia-alert-the-purist-manifesto/9287.rss">NOSTALGIA ALERT: The Purist Manifesto</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>NOSTALGIA ALERT: The Purist Manifesto</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[bur]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>it is</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/nostalgia-alert-the-purist-manifesto/9287/57">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/nostalgia-alert-the-purist-manifesto/9287/57</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 05 Sep 2012 03:37:54 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9287-57</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/nostalgia-alert-the-purist-manifesto/9287.rss">NOSTALGIA ALERT: The Purist Manifesto</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>NOSTALGIA ALERT: The Purist Manifesto</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[King_Kaddo]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Don’t tell me that is Raminator.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/nostalgia-alert-the-purist-manifesto/9287/56">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/nostalgia-alert-the-purist-manifesto/9287/56</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 05 Sep 2012 01:32:08 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9287-56</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/nostalgia-alert-the-purist-manifesto/9287.rss">NOSTALGIA ALERT: The Purist Manifesto</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>NOSTALGIA ALERT: The Purist Manifesto</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[bur]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Atomic Waffle">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Atomic Waffle:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I missed you guys. ;(</p>
<p>So… here’s a picture of Raminator in a dress.</p>
<p><img src="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/original/2X/2/2f0984456f8dd47c5beb0a68b72c3d6cf62ef2aa.jpeg" alt="" data-base62-sha1="6I6PuuEmauXO02up6hgyYXrei26" width="300" height="300"></p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>BOOMERA®M</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/nostalgia-alert-the-purist-manifesto/9287/55">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/nostalgia-alert-the-purist-manifesto/9287/55</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 05 Sep 2012 01:30:20 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9287-55</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/nostalgia-alert-the-purist-manifesto/9287.rss">NOSTALGIA ALERT: The Purist Manifesto</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>NOSTALGIA ALERT: The Purist Manifesto</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[xalener]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I want the first release of BM to coincide with an up to date picture of raminator’s arm.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Dias">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/d/4491bb/40.png" class="avatar"> Dias:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>(My first post was complaining about the size of the Bullsquid’s legs. )</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Never change.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/nostalgia-alert-the-purist-manifesto/9287/54">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/nostalgia-alert-the-purist-manifesto/9287/54</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 05 Sep 2012 01:14:08 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9287-54</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/nostalgia-alert-the-purist-manifesto/9287.rss">NOSTALGIA ALERT: The Purist Manifesto</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>NOSTALGIA ALERT: The Purist Manifesto</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[_rot_fodder]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="SVD">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/s/3ab097/40.png" class="avatar"> SVD:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I remember the community projects way before the crash, there where made some sick Xen art and models, miss lurking around the old forums  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/frowning.png?v=9" title=":frowning:" class="emoji" alt=":frowning:"><br>
Wonder how much of the community made stuff that still is around in the mod?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I wonder if the alien dick gib ever made it into black mesa…</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/nostalgia-alert-the-purist-manifesto/9287/53">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/nostalgia-alert-the-purist-manifesto/9287/53</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 05 Sep 2012 01:05:41 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9287-53</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/nostalgia-alert-the-purist-manifesto/9287.rss">NOSTALGIA ALERT: The Purist Manifesto</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
