<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>It&#39;s time to replace my laptop</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/its-time-to-replace-my-laptop/13569</link>
    <description>Heyyyyyy. I know we have a few threads about laptops, but I haven&#39;t really found what I&#39;m looking for while sifting through all the recommendations.

I currently own an HP Laptop (I can&#39;t tell you the specs off the top of my head, so I&#39;ll edit this with the specs when I wake up this afternoon) and I&#39;ve had it for 4-5 years. It&#39;s gotten quite slow, to the point where doing ANYTHING causes the computer to crawl by. Videos aren&#39;t even able to be watched usually, and basic computer functions take forever to come up.

Anyways, I&#39;m looking to replace my current laptop with a new one. I don&#39;t do all that much gaming on my laptops, as I prefer a desktop (and am going to eventually begin building one). However, I need a laptop for my travelling and some programs I&#39;ll be looking into running.

What I will be using said laptop for:
-Basic writing functions (I.e  Microsoft Word)
-possibly some recording and mixing 
-possibly some light gaming (I&#39;m rather fond of a couple mmorpg&#39;s and some online shooters such as DoD)
-Internet browsing (such as watching videos and such, normal business)

I&#39;d prefer to spend less than 400 U.S. dollars if possible, and a DVDS drive would be nice (but not wholly necessary as most things can be downloaded). I&#39;d like a 13 in or larger screen as well, but the price is more important than that (I have a monitor if it&#39;s too small.)

Sooo...any suggestions for a laptop?

Edit: not that I wanna shoot down any proposals or anything from the start, but I don&#39;t do Dell&#39;s. I&#39;ve never had a good run with any of them. Unless you&#39;re sure its a stable laptop (and not a massive POS from the box), then I won&#39;t take the risk. Again.

Edit #2: alright so I went to go and retrieve some of the information off of the laptop to give some specs, and now it won&#39;t even start up all the way -.- it spins it&#39;s wheels for hours and makes almost no progress. I haven&#39;t touched it in months cause it got a BSOD and then somehow kept working long enough for me to reset it.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2014 18:20:27 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Help and Support</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/its-time-to-replace-my-laptop/13569.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>It&#39;s time to replace my laptop</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[GilCMassey]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>It’s a little pricey, but it’s definitely a good laptop. Thanks for the suggestion!</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Kamikal">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Kamikal:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Well, if you do go for the Chromebook option, <a href="https://www.webupd8.org/2013/12/install-ubuntu-on-your-chromebook-using.html" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">here</a> is a pretty good tutorial on installing a Linux distro on one, and <a href="https://www.webupd8.org/2013/12/things-to-do-after-installing-ubuntu-on.html" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">here</a> is a guide on making it feel and work nicer post-install.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Thanks! I’ll definitely use those if I decide to go with a chrome book.</p>
<p>If anyone has any more suggestions, I’d love to hear them. I’m researching chrome books now, as well as that Lenovo you’ve suggested Boyce.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/its-time-to-replace-my-laptop/13569/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/its-time-to-replace-my-laptop/13569/6</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2014 18:20:27 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13569-6</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/its-time-to-replace-my-laptop/13569.rss">It&#39;s time to replace my laptop</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>It&#39;s time to replace my laptop</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[boyce]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Actually the lenovo G50s is a pretty good deal <a href="https://gaminglaptopunder1000.org/best-cheap-gaming-laptops-under-500-dollars/" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://gaminglaptopunder1000.org/best-cheap-gaming-laptops-under-500-dollars/</a></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/its-time-to-replace-my-laptop/13569/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/its-time-to-replace-my-laptop/13569/5</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2014 16:37:44 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13569-5</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/its-time-to-replace-my-laptop/13569.rss">It&#39;s time to replace my laptop</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>It&#39;s time to replace my laptop</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[boyce]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Have a quick look here, you’ll find the one you need <a href="https://pcgamerhome.com/gaming-laptops-under-500/" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://pcgamerhome.com/gaming-laptops-under-500/</a></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/its-time-to-replace-my-laptop/13569/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/its-time-to-replace-my-laptop/13569/4</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2014 14:27:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13569-4</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/its-time-to-replace-my-laptop/13569.rss">It&#39;s time to replace my laptop</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>It&#39;s time to replace my laptop</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[boyce]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I suggest you the Lenovo G505s,  the specs as far as I know are:<br>
AMD A10-5750M 2.5 GHz Processor<br>
6 GB DDR3 RAM<br>
1 TB 5400 rpm Hard Drive<br>
15.6-Inch Screen<br>
Windows 8.1; 5-Hour Battery Life</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/its-time-to-replace-my-laptop/13569/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/its-time-to-replace-my-laptop/13569/3</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2014 14:25:47 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13569-3</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/its-time-to-replace-my-laptop/13569.rss">It&#39;s time to replace my laptop</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>It&#39;s time to replace my laptop</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[GilCMassey]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I’ll definitely consider it. However, I’ve looked at chrome books before and while they seem ok, I’m a little iffy on the power of one. Like I said, I’m not planning on being a serious PC gamer with it, but I will be possibly using it primarily for mixing/recording my music.</p>
<p>Also, I’m not an extremely tech savvy guy. I can fix some general issues with my computers, but beyond that (such as anything to do with Linux as I’ve never even touched nor seen Linux) is far above my skill level (or at least far out of my comfort zone.)</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/its-time-to-replace-my-laptop/13569/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/its-time-to-replace-my-laptop/13569/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2014 08:03:04 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13569-2</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/its-time-to-replace-my-laptop/13569.rss">It&#39;s time to replace my laptop</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>It&#39;s time to replace my laptop</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[GilCMassey]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Heyyyyyy. I know we have a few threads about laptops, but I haven’t really found what I’m looking for while sifting through all the recommendations.</p>
<p>I currently own an HP Laptop (I can’t tell you the specs off the top of my head, so I’ll edit this with the specs when I wake up this afternoon) and I’ve had it for 4-5 years. It’s gotten quite slow, to the point where doing ANYTHING causes the computer to crawl by. Videos aren’t even able to be watched usually, and basic computer functions take forever to come up.</p>
<p>Anyways, I’m looking to replace my current laptop with a new one. I don’t do all that much gaming on my laptops, as I prefer a desktop (and am going to eventually begin building one). However, I need a laptop for my travelling and some programs I’ll be looking into running.</p>
<p>What I will be using said laptop for:<br>
-Basic writing functions (I.e  Microsoft Word)<br>
-possibly some recording and mixing<br>
-possibly some light gaming (I’m rather fond of a couple mmorpg’s and some online shooters such as DoD)<br>
-Internet browsing (such as watching videos and such, normal business)</p>
<p>I’d prefer to spend less than 400 U.S. dollars if possible, and a DVDS drive would be nice (but not wholly necessary as most things can be downloaded). I’d like a 13 in or larger screen as well, but the price is more important than that (I have a monitor if it’s too small.)</p>
<p>Sooo…any suggestions for a laptop?</p>
<p>Edit: not that I wanna shoot down any proposals or anything from the start, but I don’t do Dell’s. I’ve never had a good run with any of them. Unless you’re sure its a stable laptop (and not a massive POS from the box), then I won’t take the risk. Again.</p>
<p>Edit <span class="hashtag">#2:</span> alright so I went to go and retrieve some of the information off of the laptop to give some specs, and now it won’t even start up all the way -.- it spins it’s wheels for hours and makes almost no progress. I haven’t touched it in months cause it got a BSOD and then somehow kept working long enough for me to reset it.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/its-time-to-replace-my-laptop/13569/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/its-time-to-replace-my-laptop/13569/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 22 Nov 2014 09:08:28 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13569-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/its-time-to-replace-my-laptop/13569.rss">It&#39;s time to replace my laptop</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
