<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Small suggestion regarding Gargantua Chase Scene</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/small-suggestion-regarding-gargantua-chase-scene/14824</link>
    <description>So basically I felt like the Gargantua chase scene (which got 127% more epic in the Surface Tension: Uncut update, I might add) had a pretty harsh transition between the looping, quiet, &quot;mysterious&quot; part of the soundtrack and the following, more exciting part of the soundtrack that starts playing as soon as the Gargantua blows up the tank truck. I think this is kind of weird in particular because in Joel Nielsen&#39;s OST ([url=&#39;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=D6nywODlcfk&#39;]Surface Tension 3[/url]) there actually is a transition between the two parts of the track. Unfortunately, this transition is not used ingame.
To demonstrate the difference it makes (it&#39;s very slim, but very noticable in my eyes/ears) I made a quick little video. Also, I&#39;m kind of bored and got nothing else to do...
[youtube.com/watch?v=2GRmHQBbcP4](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=2GRmHQBbcP4)
Cheers!</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 16 Jun 2016 02:49:30 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>The Cafeteria</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/small-suggestion-regarding-gargantua-chase-scene/14824.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Small suggestion regarding Gargantua Chase Scene</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[AsinoEsel]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>So basically I felt like the Gargantua chase scene (which got 127% more epic in the Surface Tension: Uncut update, I might add) had a pretty harsh transition between the looping, quiet, “mysterious” part of the soundtrack and the following, more exciting part of the soundtrack that starts playing as soon as the Gargantua blows up the tank truck. I think this is kind of weird in particular because in Joel Nielsen’s OST (<a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=D6nywODlcfk" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Surface Tension 3</a>) there actually is a transition between the two parts of the track. Unfortunately, this transition is not used ingame.<br>
To demonstrate the difference it makes (it’s very slim, but very noticable in my eyes/ears) I made a quick little video. Also, I’m kind of bored and got nothing else to do…<br>
<a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=2GRmHQBbcP4" rel="nofollow noopener">youtube.com/watch?v=2GRmHQBbcP4</a><br>
Cheers!</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/small-suggestion-regarding-gargantua-chase-scene/14824/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/small-suggestion-regarding-gargantua-chase-scene/14824/1</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jun 2016 02:49:30 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14824-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/small-suggestion-regarding-gargantua-chase-scene/14824.rss">Small suggestion regarding Gargantua Chase Scene</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
