<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>My Research Paper</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/my-research-paper/11427</link>
    <description>I thought it would be interesting to post this. I just need help and suggestion cause I&#39;m sort of stuck on where to go after the 4th paragraph. Thanks  :slight_smile: 

[u]The Internet Today – How It Connects Us[/u]
There is more information on the internet than one person can learn in his/her lifetime. This seeming less technology we take for granted is used every day by billions. It holds the keys to becoming successful, inspiring creativity, motivation, and everything in-between. Should we really rely on the internet as far as we’ve come today? The obvious answer is reasonably yes. It has many benefits, but where there is success there’s also downfalls.

I use the internet just about every day, either for information and help, or entertainment. Everybody in my immediate family uses the internet to, and for the same purpose as I do. We use it so much that we never question ourselves why we use it, and it’s just there- a part of our lives. Almost as breathing is our instinct, the computer is a reflex to solve problems, and be entertained. In rare occasions, I even open up Google and forget what I’m searching for. I think that’s instinct itself, and it opens my eyes to how dependent I am on the internet.

I know I’m not the only one who does this, and it makes me question how safe the internet really is. Do we take the internet for granted because we’ve never had problems with it? I’ve never experienced problems except for occasional ads and pop-ups, but that’s about it. Most people assume theirs hackers out there, waiting to hack another Facebook page at any moment. Are there really hackers that can make the internet unsafe? Sure, theirs hack groups like anonymous that have already hacked into the PlayStation network, and stolen thousands of identities.

I don’t think the whole internet is susceptible to a cyber-attack simply because nothing could bypass millions of cloud and network storages. That’s just a simple fact. I’m sure with today’s technology that even if a cyber-attack were to happen on a large scale, a reset button is in place and it would be as easy as deleting a file on a desktop. This is probably why today’s hackers utilize surprise to “download” information when no one’s expecting it, but this is also why most of us expect to be cautious when doing online activity.

[Don&#39;t know where to go from here]

25% of earth’s population uses the internet- a number that’s rapidly increasing. This is a rather small number, but as technology and production progresses, the more and more people will be able to access the World Wide Web. After seeing this staggering statistic, a few questions come to mind. Will my children have access to the internet or some type of data connection at an early age? Is online school a real possibility? Is the future internet safe from hackers? Over time I’ll eventually see how these possibilities end up, and hopefully in a good direction.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 10 Oct 2012 01:03:15 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Help and Support</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/my-research-paper/11427.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>My Research Paper</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[CPU]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><span class="bbcode-b">" This seeming less technology we take for granted is used every day by billions."</span><br>
Doesn’t make sense. What is “seeming less”?</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">“Everybody in my immediate family uses the internet to”</span><br>
change “to” to “too”.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">“Most people assume theirs hackers out there”</span><br>
change “theirs hackers” to “there are hackers”</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">“Sure, theirs hack groups”</span><br>
change to “there are hack groups”</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">“but as technology and production progresses, the more and more people will be able to access the World Wide Web”</span><br>
remove the word “the” in “the more and more people”</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">“25% of earth’s population uses the internet”</span><br>
Don’t start sentences with numerals. Use “Twenty-five percent” instead.</p>
<p>Not trying to be cute but, what age group are you in? The paper reads as being written by someone in their pre-teens or teens.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/my-research-paper/11427/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/my-research-paper/11427/3</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 10 Oct 2012 01:03:15 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11427-3</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/my-research-paper/11427.rss">My Research Paper</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My Research Paper</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Thatamos]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Oh man.</p>
<p>Do you mind if I edit the shit out of your paper?</p>
<p>e/ What year of what education system are you in?</p>
<p>e2/ Having read your paper, I have to say, you’re profoundly naive about the physical nature of the internet. The internet can certainly be shut off, and yes, on a global scale. Despite cloud sourcing being huge, the internet is connected worldwide through fiber optic cables that span the globe. Cut those and goodbye interweb.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/my-research-paper/11427/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/my-research-paper/11427/2</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 10 Oct 2012 00:42:12 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11427-2</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/my-research-paper/11427.rss">My Research Paper</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My Research Paper</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[GravityGun]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I thought it would be interesting to post this. I just need help and suggestion cause I’m sort of stuck on where to go after the 4th paragraph. Thanks  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=9" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
<p><span class="bbcode-u">The Internet Today – How It Connects Us</span><br>
There is more information on the internet than one person can learn in his/her lifetime. This seeming less technology we take for granted is used every day by billions. It holds the keys to becoming successful, inspiring creativity, motivation, and everything in-between. Should we really rely on the internet as far as we’ve come today? The obvious answer is reasonably yes. It has many benefits, but where there is success there’s also downfalls.</p>
<p>I use the internet just about every day, either for information and help, or entertainment. Everybody in my immediate family uses the internet to, and for the same purpose as I do. We use it so much that we never question ourselves why we use it, and it’s just there- a part of our lives. Almost as breathing is our instinct, the computer is a reflex to solve problems, and be entertained. In rare occasions, I even open up Google and forget what I’m searching for. I think that’s instinct itself, and it opens my eyes to how dependent I am on the internet.</p>
<p>I know I’m not the only one who does this, and it makes me question how safe the internet really is. Do we take the internet for granted because we’ve never had problems with it? I’ve never experienced problems except for occasional ads and pop-ups, but that’s about it. Most people assume theirs hackers out there, waiting to hack another Facebook page at any moment. Are there really hackers that can make the internet unsafe? Sure, theirs hack groups like anonymous that have already hacked into the PlayStation network, and stolen thousands of identities.</p>
<p>I don’t think the whole internet is susceptible to a cyber-attack simply because nothing could bypass millions of cloud and network storages. That’s just a simple fact. I’m sure with today’s technology that even if a cyber-attack were to happen on a large scale, a reset button is in place and it would be as easy as deleting a file on a desktop. This is probably why today’s hackers utilize surprise to “download” information when no one’s expecting it, but this is also why most of us expect to be cautious when doing online activity.</p>
<p>[Don’t know where to go from here]</p>
<p>25% of earth’s population uses the internet- a number that’s rapidly increasing. This is a rather small number, but as technology and production progresses, the more and more people will be able to access the World Wide Web. After seeing this staggering statistic, a few questions come to mind. Will my children have access to the internet or some type of data connection at an early age? Is online school a real possibility? Is the future internet safe from hackers? Over time I’ll eventually see how these possibilities end up, and hopefully in a good direction.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/my-research-paper/11427/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/my-research-paper/11427/1</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 09 Oct 2012 21:55:28 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11427-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/my-research-paper/11427.rss">My Research Paper</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
