<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Diablo III Beta</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/diablo-iii-beta/7108</link>
    <description>&#39;Lo,

Anybody else looking forward to Diablo III? Blizzard is currently in a conferance call and has suggested that the DIII External Beta will be Quarter 3 this year (July, Aug, Sep) - Still awaiting a more detailed date.

Hope I get a Beta key. haha. xD

They&#39;ve said they&#39;re still aiming for a 2011 release, however nothing is set in stone. I&#39;d be pretty happy if we do get a 2011 release, as the game is pretty much complete from what I&#39;ve seen and all they&#39;re doing is tweaking...

EDIT: Just confirmed from &#39;Bashiok&#39;, Quarter 3 is confirmed for the External Beta.

Edit edit: [url]https://www.youtube.com/ForceSC2strategy#p/l/s/0/OzJQX1Pt3ZQ[/url] - For anybody that&#39;s interested in the call.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 19 May 2011 05:05:22 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Technology and Gaming</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/diablo-iii-beta/7108.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Diablo III Beta</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[OldDirtyBastard]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Shout from 1999 about Diablo II:</p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>GS: Why did you guys decide not to use classic fantasy images like elves, dwarves, and dragons?</p>
<p>Phil: Well, there’s always the balance between the familiar and the new. If we use something like a skeleton or a zombie, we’ve got to put a spin on it. People don’t like things that are so far out that they don’t have any idea what it is. So we like the monsters to appear familiar, but at the same time, interesting. The designers of the game just aren’t big fans of the typical goblins, dragons, trolls group of monsters. It makes for a more interesting balance of, I don’t know…</p>
<p>Matt: We go for the more Gothic stuff. We’re more into Gothic as opposed to the traditional RPG stuff.</p>
<p>GS: So is that how you would characterize the look of Diablo II? It’d be more Gothic than it would be the traditional D&amp;D type of fantasy theme?</p>
<p>Phil: Yeah, definitely. There’s more of a Gothic core element to it."</p>
<p><a href="https://www.gamespot.com/features/diablo2diary_dd/091498/page4.html" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://www.gamespot.com/features/diablo2diary_dd/091498/page4.html</a></p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/diablo-iii-beta/7108/42">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/diablo-iii-beta/7108/42</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 19 May 2011 05:05:22 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7108-42</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/diablo-iii-beta/7108.rss">Diablo III Beta</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Diablo III Beta</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[OldDirtyBastard]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=VLdjOyoUr5U" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=VLdjOyoUr5U</a><br>
Seriously, fuck the cyan. It’s not the worst problem.</p>
<p>But seriously, everything screams ‘hey warcraft got a facelift with a brdand new korean overhaul!’. Monsters, tiles, architecture, character, armour - it reeeeeeks of overblown fantasy.</p>
<p>I just loved how they kept bragging about DH being gothic and medieval and shit, when in fact, she looks like a straight rip-off from lineage, granado espada or some shit like that</p>
<p>Diablo was medieval. Yeah, Gothic too, but mainly it was medieval.</p>
<p>Fantasy =/= Medieval. Can someone remind that to people in Irvine and smack them a good one in the face?<br>
Or at least show them  the first Assassin’s Creed to show them how medieval looks? And make them stop laying themselves out and pulling the designs out of their asses to ‘make them stand out’?<br>
Seriously, those people are doing nothing but stroking their own egos here in a pretentious attempt to appear cool to the target audience.<br>
‘Oh look what a badass art dzinr I am, look at my epic 3d modelling and sketching skillz’ - this is the first mistake when you are doing a sequel to something that already has been with us for 15 years. On top of that, modesty is really a virtue.<br>
But, hey, they’re only humans like all of us and it’s natural:</p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>There is something about yourself that you don’t know. Something that you will deny even exists, until it’s too late to do anything about it. It’s the only reason you get up in the morning. The only reason you suffer the shitty puss, the blood, the sweat and the tears. This is because you want people to know how good, attractive, generous, funny, wild and clever you really are. Fear or revere me, but please, think I’m special. We share an addiction. We’re approval junkies. We’re all in it for the slap on the back and the gold watch. The hip-hip-hoo-fuckin’ rah. Look at the clever boy with the badge, polishing his trophy. Shine on you crazy diamond, because we’re just monkeys wrapped in suits, begging for the approval of others</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>But Bill Roper and the co. were smart enough not to fall for it.<br>
I guess it’s the shitty times we currently live in.</p>
<p>Sorry for a rant, I swore once not to talk about D3 art direction any more, but I guess i can’t help it.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/diablo-iii-beta/7108/41">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/diablo-iii-beta/7108/41</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 18 May 2011 18:02:52 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7108-41</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/diablo-iii-beta/7108.rss">Diablo III Beta</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Diablo III Beta</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Sidewinder]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I’ll buy it regardless.</p>
<p>Unless ofcourse I play the BETA and seriously dislike it. I was that much of a DII nutt that’d i’d be crazy not to atleast try it.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/diablo-iii-beta/7108/40">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/diablo-iii-beta/7108/40</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 18 May 2011 17:15:11 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7108-40</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/diablo-iii-beta/7108.rss">Diablo III Beta</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Diablo III Beta</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[johnyo]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>DII was awesome. I’m trying to stay neutral till I get to try DIII on the off chance it’s actually good.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/diablo-iii-beta/7108/39">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/diablo-iii-beta/7108/39</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 18 May 2011 15:12:39 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7108-39</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/diablo-iii-beta/7108.rss">Diablo III Beta</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Diablo III Beta</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Dreadmoth]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>ODB, you just made my day, that post was great <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=9" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/diablo-iii-beta/7108/38">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/diablo-iii-beta/7108/38</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 18 May 2011 11:47:15 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7108-38</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/diablo-iii-beta/7108.rss">Diablo III Beta</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Diablo III Beta</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[JayJay]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>lol burn.</p>
<p>I’m going to have to get me some DII on the go, installed it last weekend to show the girlfriend (she found it boring… don’t worry, steps have been taken).</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/diablo-iii-beta/7108/37">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/diablo-iii-beta/7108/37</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 18 May 2011 08:07:21 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7108-37</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/diablo-iii-beta/7108.rss">Diablo III Beta</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Diablo III Beta</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[OldDirtyBastard]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Really, after playing me some Meteorb and Whirlybarb on ladder, I can’t help myself but be pissed off at the direction the Irvine guys take with DIII.<br>
Fuck the gay cyan colour overload, just look at fucking character designs.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b"><font face="Verdana"><span class="bbcode-b">[COLOR=‘DarkOrange’]BARB:[/SIZE]</span></font></span><br>
<img src="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/original/2X/3/3b8d6cf108c4642ee6f1436d57b039f35a035e9e.gif" alt="" data-base62-sha1="8uPaLlcu1s0gjuvMV7QO2IoJ79Y" width="97" height="203"> <font face="Franklin Gothic Medium"><span class="bbcode-b">[COLOR=‘Red’]DII: I’ll rip your head off and shit down your neck.[/SIZE]</span></font><br>
<span alt="" class="broken-image" title="This image is broken"><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-unlink svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#unlink"></use></svg></span> [COLOR=‘DeepSkyBlue’]<font face="Franklin Gothic Medium"><span class="bbcode-b">DIII: I’m big, stupid, overweight 제외하고 and I love korean mmoerpgeeez and kosplay 제외하고 ololol</span>[/SIZE]</font></p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b"><font face="Verdana"><span class="bbcode-b">[COLOR=‘DarkOrange’]DRUID/MANCER - Witch Doctor[/SIZE]</span></font></span><br>
<img src="https://www.ociototal.com/recopila2/r_juegos/imag/diablo2_necro.jpg" alt="" width="" height=""> <font face="Franklin Gothic Medium"><span class="bbcode-b">[COLOR=‘Red’]DII : I’ll boil your eyes and fuck your corpse! All hail the Dark Lord Satan! [/SIZE]</span></font><br>
<img src="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/original/2X/4/45e2b93e7f42f8c107a8a599e1271d292b2a420f.gif" alt="" data-base62-sha1="9YeHjfbGa2LZSqwIhwOaAYXOMYD" width="112" height="241"><span class="bbcode-b">[COLOR=‘Red’]DII : One of us is in deeeeep trouble. [/SIZE]</span><br>
<span alt="" class="broken-image" title="This image is broken"><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-unlink svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#unlink"></use></svg></span> [COLOR=‘DeepSkyBlue’]<font face="Franklin Gothic Medium"><span class="bbcode-b">DIII: <em>cough cough</em> ughhh, malaria <em>cough cough</em> 마 사냥꾼 제외하고 거시기를 <em>cough</em> </span>[/SIZE]</font></p>
<p>NO, SERIOUSLY:<br>
<span alt="" class="broken-image" title="This image is broken"><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-unlink svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#unlink"></use></svg></span><br>
You’ve picked the wrong alley, punk…</p>
<p>vs.</p>
<p><span alt="" class="broken-image" title="This image is broken"><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-unlink svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#unlink"></use></svg></span><br>
우리는 악마 사냥꾼 제외하고 거시기를 빨아 좋아하세요?</p>
<p>Demon Huntress: I wish I could switch sides now.<br>
Really, if someone would show you the last picture without any prior knowledge on your part, would you recognize <span class="bbcode-b">Diablo </span>in it? and not some knockoff cheap mmorpg clone <span class="hashtag">#23531</span>?</p>
<p>p.S. Seriously, what’s up with blue and green everywhere? I thought color temperature knowledge was a prerequisite for a designer?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/diablo-iii-beta/7108/36">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/diablo-iii-beta/7108/36</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 18 May 2011 00:57:53 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7108-36</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/diablo-iii-beta/7108.rss">Diablo III Beta</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Diablo III Beta</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[JayJay]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Ah, well then I agree entirely.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/diablo-iii-beta/7108/35">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/diablo-iii-beta/7108/35</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 12 May 2011 19:23:28 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7108-35</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/diablo-iii-beta/7108.rss">Diablo III Beta</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Diablo III Beta</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[OldDirtyBastard]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>He meant art style.<br>
P.S. I’m sure someone will mod the shit out of DIII like they did with Stalker.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/diablo-iii-beta/7108/34">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/diablo-iii-beta/7108/34</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 12 May 2011 19:05:57 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7108-34</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/diablo-iii-beta/7108.rss">Diablo III Beta</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Diablo III Beta</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[JayJay]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Just saw that video now, the colour scheme that guy uses definitely fits the D3 world better.</p>
<p>Also graphics =/= art style.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/diablo-iii-beta/7108/33">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/diablo-iii-beta/7108/33</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 12 May 2011 18:50:53 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7108-33</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/diablo-iii-beta/7108.rss">Diablo III Beta</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Diablo III Beta</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[OldDirtyBastard]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Well, yeah, that’s what everyone meant in this thread.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/diablo-iii-beta/7108/32">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/diablo-iii-beta/7108/32</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 12 May 2011 18:43:55 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7108-32</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/diablo-iii-beta/7108.rss">Diablo III Beta</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Diablo III Beta</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[JayJay]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Er, yes?</p>
<p>From that article I’m starting to think that The Bad Guys means art style and not graphics?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/diablo-iii-beta/7108/31">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/diablo-iii-beta/7108/31</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 12 May 2011 10:07:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7108-31</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/diablo-iii-beta/7108.rss">Diablo III Beta</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Diablo III Beta</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[OldDirtyBastard]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Do you know what literal and not literal means?<br>
Here’s a couple inteviews:</p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p><span class="bbcode-b"><a href="http://IncGamers.com" rel="nofollow noopener">IncGamers.com</a>: </span>To go further back in your career, you worked on Diablo, and that’s coming up on a third sequel. How do you think it’s been handled?<br>
<span class="bbcode-b">Bill Roper:</span> Ultimately they’re going to do a great job, because Blizzard always does a great job on products. I was interested by the big explosion that happened online when they released the first gameplay footage and screenshots, when that vocal minority was outraged that it didn’t have that dark, gothic, gritty look. But that actually made sense, because it’s not Blizzard North doing it anymore. That’s the art style that the guys down at Irvine do. So it looks to me as what I would’ve expected from those guys, handling the Diablo universe. I always thought that was a real strength between having development teams in Irvine and San Mateo. Blizzard North had a different art direction, a different style, and different thought processes towards mechanics that were all very solid, and allowed the Diablo games to expand out on their own in a lot of different ways. I think that what you’re seeing now is that mechanic being taken over by the guys in Irvine because it’s involves them now, and so it’s going to have that flavour. I want it to be great because I love Diablo, and I want another one.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b"><a href="http://IncGamers.com" rel="nofollow noopener">IncGamers.com</a>:</span> From your comments I get the feeling you’d prefer the Diablo 1 or Diablo 2 art style.<br>
<span class="bbcode-b"><span class="bbcode-b">Bill Roper:</span></span> I don’t dislike how it looks now. I didn’t look at it and have the appalled reaction a lot of people did, I just appreciated that it had a very distinct look. The Diablo games looked different to the Craft games, and I liked the fact that it was very dark, gothic fantasy. I just think that it’s nice to be able to have different worlds represented with very different visuals… When WoW came out, there were plenty of people who didn’t like the way it looked, and I think that with Diablo 3 there’ll be some people who don’t like it and prefer the look of the first two Diablo games. When they first released the the videos and the screenshots, there was definitely an uprising from certain sections of Blizzard and Diablo fans, but Blizzard does what it’s going to do so I’m sure that all those people who were really upset will still be in line with the rest of us, getting a copy! As long as it’s good and cohesive and takes the stories that they’re telling, I’m okay if it doesn’t look exactly like it did before, although I did like that really dark, edgy, gothic look.<br>
Bill expounded further on this in an interview with <a href="http://VideoGamer.com" rel="nofollow noopener">VideoGamer.com</a>. [5]<br>
<span class="bbcode-b"><a href="http://VideoGamer.com" rel="nofollow noopener">VideoGamer.com</a></span>: You mention that you can understand the art style and direction Blizzard has taken with Diablo III, but are you pleased with it or disappointed with it? You were one of the chief architects of the original Diablo games which, as you’ve said, were darker and grittier than the Craft games.<br>
<span class="bbcode-b">Bill Roper:</span> You know, I liked the darker grittier. I liked the differences in art style, to be honest. So, I think I would personally from a player standpoint prefer that. One of the things that we always tried to get across was that Diablo was Gothic fantasy and I think there was just a need that was put in there from the visuals that I didn’t necessarily get. I got it from the architecture and to a degree from the character design but not the feeling of the world. I can’t say that I dislike it. I didn’t look at it and go, oh my God that’s horrible. But I looked at it and went, it’s not really… to me as a player it just didn’t really ring with Diablo.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I guess it just nails it.</p>
<p>Like it or not, those people have got the point:<br>
<a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=2-nS-Pyu-a8" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=2-nS-Pyu-a8</a></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/diablo-iii-beta/7108/30">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/diablo-iii-beta/7108/30</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 12 May 2011 09:19:38 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7108-30</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/diablo-iii-beta/7108.rss">Diablo III Beta</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Diablo III Beta</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[JayJay]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Ibanez">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/i/a4c791/40.png" class="avatar"> Ibanez:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Actually the fact that the game has the same graphics, more or less, as WoW and Warcraft 3 does piss me off a fair amount. I’ve been an avid Diablo player since I was around 10 years old. But what can I do?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Same graphics?</p>
<p>WoW:</p>
<p><img src="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/original/2X/0/0b09adf22ce05b746583cebf60445da07f48d495.jpeg" alt="" data-base62-sha1="1zDZoVZJDwyu307Hzf0oSGC2Qlv" width="320" height="426"></p>
<p>Diablo 3:</p>
<p><span alt="" class="broken-image" title="This image is broken"><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-unlink svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#unlink"></use></svg></span></p>
<p>Wat <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/expressionless.png?v=9" title=":expressionless:" class="emoji" alt=":expressionless:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/diablo-iii-beta/7108/29">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/diablo-iii-beta/7108/29</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 12 May 2011 08:14:32 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7108-29</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/diablo-iii-beta/7108.rss">Diablo III Beta</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Diablo III Beta</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[The_Bad_Guys]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Sadly, not much other than leak everything like that German hacker did during Half-Life 2’s original development time to try and set D3 back a couple of years, spending that period of time honing your programming and modelling skills until getting hired by Blizzard, infiltrating the D3 Dev team and firebombing everything after urinating all over it in the dark of night.</p>
<p>After covertly murdering a few interns, security personnel, and some other developers to cover your tracks afterwards; take control of the development and design teams and shape it in <span class="bbcode-i"><span class="bbcode-b">your</span></span> image.</p>
<p>Extreme yes, but more effective and still a better and more productive use of your time than signing angry internet petitions (because internet petitions have never worked, ever).</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/diablo-iii-beta/7108/28">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/diablo-iii-beta/7108/28</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 12 May 2011 01:43:18 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7108-28</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/diablo-iii-beta/7108.rss">Diablo III Beta</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Diablo III Beta</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Surplus]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Ibanez">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/i/a4c791/40.png" class="avatar"> Ibanez:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I meant ‘what can I do to change its current state’, not ‘what can I do to fight the man’.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>You see in this case they are one in the same. As a consumer your greatest power to effect the industry is to think about what you buy.  If you dislike the direction that Blizzard is taking with Diablo then simply do not purchase it. Perhaps go as far as to email or make a post on their forums about it.  Although being a large company I doubt they give a shit if you email them and you’d probably get flamed for the latter.</p>
<p>TL;DR: If you don’t like it don’t buy it.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/diablo-iii-beta/7108/27">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/diablo-iii-beta/7108/27</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 12 May 2011 01:41:15 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7108-27</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/diablo-iii-beta/7108.rss">Diablo III Beta</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Diablo III Beta</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Ibanez]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I meant ‘what can I do to change its current state’, not ‘what can I do to fight the man’.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/diablo-iii-beta/7108/26">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/diablo-iii-beta/7108/26</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 12 May 2011 00:37:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7108-26</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/diablo-iii-beta/7108.rss">Diablo III Beta</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Diablo III Beta</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Surplus]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Not play it, accept it’s death like Sonic fans accepted sonic is dead and gone.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/diablo-iii-beta/7108/25">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/diablo-iii-beta/7108/25</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 12 May 2011 00:23:14 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7108-25</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/diablo-iii-beta/7108.rss">Diablo III Beta</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Diablo III Beta</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Ibanez]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Actually the fact that the game has the same graphics, more or less, as WoW and Warcraft 3 does piss me off a fair amount. I’ve been an avid Diablo player since I was around 10 years old. But what can I do?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/diablo-iii-beta/7108/24">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/diablo-iii-beta/7108/24</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 11 May 2011 22:57:09 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7108-24</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/diablo-iii-beta/7108.rss">Diablo III Beta</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Diablo III Beta</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Jack_Freeman]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I think Diablo 3 looks good i dont say it was good they fired the original team but well its still gonna be a awesome game.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/diablo-iii-beta/7108/23">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/diablo-iii-beta/7108/23</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 11 May 2011 16:53:49 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7108-23</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/diablo-iii-beta/7108.rss">Diablo III Beta</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Diablo III Beta</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[JayJay]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Saying that the creators of WoW had all these features in their game ergo Diablo 3 will as well is incredibly small minded.</p>
<p>What I was getting at was the team is obviously very good at storytelling and creating interesting and balanced gameplay.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/diablo-iii-beta/7108/22">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/diablo-iii-beta/7108/22</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 11 May 2011 08:14:50 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7108-22</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/diablo-iii-beta/7108.rss">Diablo III Beta</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Diablo III Beta</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[The_Wandering_God]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Everyone who’s played it has loved it.</p>
<p>All the things I’ve heard about it, I like.</p>
<p>I am going to punch every single demon’s face in as a monk.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/diablo-iii-beta/7108/21">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/diablo-iii-beta/7108/21</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 11 May 2011 07:06:17 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7108-21</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/diablo-iii-beta/7108.rss">Diablo III Beta</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Diablo III Beta</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[OldDirtyBastard]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Blizzard sucked ever since Roper left North.<br>
/thread</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/diablo-iii-beta/7108/20">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/diablo-iii-beta/7108/20</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 11 May 2011 02:20:08 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7108-20</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/diablo-iii-beta/7108.rss">Diablo III Beta</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Diablo III Beta</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[The_Bad_Guys]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Design style is different too.</p>
<p>Diablo I &amp; II = takes place in a defined dark, Gothic fantasy atmosphere although almost all weapons, armor, and architecture is done with realistic sensibilities. (Ex. : A spear looks like a spear, not <span class="bbcode-b">OMGWTFBBGSKULLDRAGONEATINGAFLAMINGSPIKE DOING 2,300.76 DPS WHILE BEING ONE-HANDED!1!!1!eleven!</span>)</p>
<p>WoW = Spikes, over-sized shoulder armor, skulls, flaming skulls, bright flashy colors, <span class="bbcode-b">EVERYTHING TURNED UP TO FUCKING ELEVEN TO FIT THE SENSIBILITIES OF TEN YEAR OLDS</span>, and having absolutely no idea how to create a Gothic atmosphere without over-doing it (Ex. : a <span class="bbcode-i">slightly darker pallete swap</span> of a <span class="bbcode-b">OMGWTFBBGSKULLDRAGONEATINGAFLAMINGSPIKE DOING 2,300.76 DPS WHILE BEING ONE-HANDED!1!!1!eleven!</span>) .</p>
<p>Hell, I’ll still play it because I’m intrigued and because it <span class="bbcode-b"><span class="bbcode-i">is</span></span> a Diablo sequel, but I know that there will be moments in the game where I will cringe uncontrollably.</p>
<p>Seriously: dual-wielding crossbows akimbo-style? God damn it, is everyone who works at Blizz completely blasted off their ass for most of the development stage on these things?  I got over the fact that everything was in bright primary colors in a dungeon level and that all character models were all out of proportion and cartoony, but there’s only so far they can go with just saying “magic explains all, ‘rule of cool’ determines everything” before I have a stroke from the stupidity emanating the idea. (/rant)</p>
<p>TLDR; The new Diablo team has none of the sensibilities or design philosophies of the original team and made it in the same vein as World of Warcraft. It strikes a nerve.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/diablo-iii-beta/7108/19">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/diablo-iii-beta/7108/19</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 11 May 2011 02:12:21 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7108-19</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/diablo-iii-beta/7108.rss">Diablo III Beta</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Diablo III Beta</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Surplus]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Wow is an MMO, Diablo is not an MMO.  Their success is meaningless.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/diablo-iii-beta/7108/18">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/diablo-iii-beta/7108/18</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 11 May 2011 00:25:34 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7108-18</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/diablo-iii-beta/7108.rss">Diablo III Beta</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
