<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>My toughts about Black Mesa (SPOILERS)</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/my-toughts-about-black-mesa-spoilers/10403</link>
    <description>So I beat Black Mesa a few hours ago, and I felt like I needed to share my opinion

Black Mesa is probably one of the few (or the only one) mods that seem to blow Half-Life 2 out in the water.

___SPOILER ALERTS___

It is an excellent remake of one of my favorite games of my childhood. It bought back some great memories and still felt like something fresh. Even though, I wasn&#39;t surprised about everything, because I already knew what i&#39;m going to encounter. (Like the tentacles or the first Bullsquid at the broken bridge) 
But still, they changed some things to surprise us. For example, they made a brilliant move of putting the crowbar later in the game and let you encounter lots of Zombies without you having any weapon. Still, there were some parts that I saw coming. Like after fighting your first assassins (fighting them was absolutely fantastic in this mod) you get captured by the HECU. I knew that, and Black Mesa did a great job remaking that scene.

The mapping is excellent! Even though, in the Blast Pit chapter I wanted to see a Zombie breaking a door instead of waiting for you in a corner. But still, the game feels modern and you can still imagine the original game while playing it.

The soundtrack.... what can I say... GENIUS! I love what they did with the music. For example, at the beginning of the Unforseen Consequences, the sad music is amazing and describes what&#39;s inside Gordon Freeman&#39;s mind. The Resonance Cascade feels real! How would you feel when the whole world is doomed because of you ? Also later in that chapter, the elevator part when it rains with headcrabs, the music fits perfect. Another thing I will say about the soundtrack, the We&#39;ve Got Hostiles chapter is awesome! The elevator is rising, music kicks in, and right when you shot your first bullet, the amazing Rock music kicks in. It felt like the greatest gaming moment of my life.

Some things are missing in Half-Life (because the standards of game developing wasn&#39;t that high in 1998 I think) was brought back in Black Mesa. I played Half-Life a long time ago, but in Black Mesa I actually know what I am going to do and what my mission is (apart from surviving). In the beginning, Eli and Kleiner (I love how they are refrered by names) tell you to get to the surface and tell people that we are stranded deep in the Black Mesa. And then at some point, one scientist tells you that you have to go to the Lambda Complex, so I already knew where i&#39;m heading to.

Also, sometimes the game makes Gordon Freeman look like an asshole. At the end of Office Complex chapter, one scientist tells you something like &quot;When you reach to the surface, don&#39;t forget about us down here. Come back to save us!&quot;, but it&#39;s obvious Gordon won&#39;t just go back after all hard work. 

The voice acting is great. It really feels like it was made by Valve. I just love the Woman&#39;s voice in the tram ride in the beginning. And I also like how the first guard tells you about Barney, and the second guard says to you &quot;aww man, you cut the ponytail!&quot; That line... was genius!  :smiley:  

Well, well , well. I ran out of good things to say about this mod. Looks like I have to admit the bad parts as well.

I had to crouch-jump in like 90% of the mod. I don&#39;t mind it, but I always felt like it was a bug instead of a feature. Maybe is just me.

Sometimes, the maps are confusing. I spent a hour at a certain part in the Lambda Complex chapter. Also in Surface Tension sometimes... Also, sometimes when i&#39;m walking on corridors there are crossroads and I have no idea which way to go (Sometimes i&#39;m afraid to not miss a story part or a weapon and ammo) 

There are also some small details (which sometimes don&#39;t really matter) that really feels that it needs to be polished. For example, the first dead guard you see has the eyes open. Also there is a point in Blast Pit where I have to jump a small border, but there is an useless ladder that doesn&#39;t even work. Also in Surface Tension, when you are in the mounts there is a gray unfinished texture. It really destroyed all the chapter&#39;s beauty. Damn... the mounts where so beautiful.. (from the 2008 trailer, I thought it&#39;s a 2D skybox and that it won&#39;t fit with the level, but the water actually moves and some small buildings are 3D.. I love you for that).

I guess that&#39;s all I had to say about this mod.

So on short:

Pros:

Voice Acting
Soundtrack
Map Design
Enemies and Bosses (fighting the assassins was awesome!)
Gameplay
Ballance between action and puzzles

Cons:

Few details that needs to be polished 
Sometimes confusion.

My verdict is, that Black Mesa is simply one of the best mods/games I ever played in the last few years. It felt fresh, new, and nostalgic at the same time. I love the BM team for giving us this game FOR FREE without charging us anything (I will buy some of your soundtrack when it&#39;s on iTunes. It&#39;s what made the mod from better to best.) but, needs some small details fixed. But I won&#39;t complain since it&#39;s for free.

I rate this mod 9.5/10</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 17 Sep 2012 11:17:02 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>The Cafeteria</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/my-toughts-about-black-mesa-spoilers/10403.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>My toughts about Black Mesa (SPOILERS)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Ergates]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I got headcrabs galore in the elevator. They probably just didn’t find the OP very appetising <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=9" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"></p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>Also, sometimes the game makes Gordon Freeman look like an asshole. At the end of Office Complex chapter, one scientist tells you something like “When you reach to the surface, don’t forget about us down here. Come back to save us!”, but it’s obvious Gordon won’t just go back after all hard work.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>To be fair, Gordan wouldn’t have been able to safely go back and collect the scientists after reaching the surface, due to the area being crawling with HECU, shooting everything that moves.</p>
<p>It could be argued that he felt it safer to wait until he’d helped resolved the problem via reaching the Lamda lab… but then of course he was then pursuaded into tackling the problem head-on in Xen.</p>
<p>More to the point, the entire Black Mesa complex was nuked by Black Ops shortly after.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/my-toughts-about-black-mesa-spoilers/10403/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/my-toughts-about-black-mesa-spoilers/10403/4</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 17 Sep 2012 11:17:02 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-10403-4</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/my-toughts-about-black-mesa-spoilers/10403.rss">My toughts about Black Mesa (SPOILERS)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My toughts about Black Mesa (SPOILERS)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[The_Glock]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Yeah I think it’s glitched for you. The headcrabs ate me there.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/my-toughts-about-black-mesa-spoilers/10403/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/my-toughts-about-black-mesa-spoilers/10403/3</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 17 Sep 2012 10:43:48 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-10403-3</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/my-toughts-about-black-mesa-spoilers/10403.rss">My toughts about Black Mesa (SPOILERS)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My toughts about Black Mesa (SPOILERS)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Dotard]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Sorry for bringing this, but since you mentioned it… the “headcrab elevator” in BM actually didn’t drop/rain any headcrabs, at least for me… want to know if that’s it or I had it glitched</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/my-toughts-about-black-mesa-spoilers/10403/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/my-toughts-about-black-mesa-spoilers/10403/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 16 Sep 2012 22:14:56 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-10403-2</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/my-toughts-about-black-mesa-spoilers/10403.rss">My toughts about Black Mesa (SPOILERS)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My toughts about Black Mesa (SPOILERS)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[The_Glock]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>So I beat Black Mesa a few hours ago, and I felt like I needed to share my opinion</p>
<p>Black Mesa is probably one of the few (or the only one) mods that seem to blow Half-Life 2 out in the water.</p>
<p><em><strong>SPOILER ALERTS</strong></em></p>
<p>It is an excellent remake of one of my favorite games of my childhood. It bought back some great memories and still felt like something fresh. Even though, I wasn’t surprised about everything, because I already knew what i’m going to encounter. (Like the tentacles or the first Bullsquid at the broken bridge)<br>
But still, they changed some things to surprise us. For example, they made a brilliant move of putting the crowbar later in the game and let you encounter lots of Zombies without you having any weapon. Still, there were some parts that I saw coming. Like after fighting your first assassins (fighting them was absolutely fantastic in this mod) you get captured by the HECU. I knew that, and Black Mesa did a great job remaking that scene.</p>
<p>The mapping is excellent! Even though, in the Blast Pit chapter I wanted to see a Zombie breaking a door instead of waiting for you in a corner. But still, the game feels modern and you can still imagine the original game while playing it.</p>
<p>The soundtrack… what can I say… GENIUS! I love what they did with the music. For example, at the beginning of the Unforseen Consequences, the sad music is amazing and describes what’s inside Gordon Freeman’s mind. The Resonance Cascade feels real! How would you feel when the whole world is doomed because of you ? Also later in that chapter, the elevator part when it rains with headcrabs, the music fits perfect. Another thing I will say about the soundtrack, the We’ve Got Hostiles chapter is awesome! The elevator is rising, music kicks in, and right when you shot your first bullet, the amazing Rock music kicks in. It felt like the greatest gaming moment of my life.</p>
<p>Some things are missing in Half-Life (because the standards of game developing wasn’t that high in 1998 I think) was brought back in Black Mesa. I played Half-Life a long time ago, but in Black Mesa I actually know what I am going to do and what my mission is (apart from surviving). In the beginning, Eli and Kleiner (I love how they are refrered by names) tell you to get to the surface and tell people that we are stranded deep in the Black Mesa. And then at some point, one scientist tells you that you have to go to the Lambda Complex, so I already knew where i’m heading to.</p>
<p>Also, sometimes the game makes Gordon Freeman look like an asshole. At the end of Office Complex chapter, one scientist tells you something like “When you reach to the surface, don’t forget about us down here. Come back to save us!”, but it’s obvious Gordon won’t just go back after all hard work.</p>
<p>The voice acting is great. It really feels like it was made by Valve. I just love the Woman’s voice in the tram ride in the beginning. And I also like how the first guard tells you about Barney, and the second guard says to you “aww man, you cut the ponytail!” That line… was genius!  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/smiley.png?v=9" title=":smiley:" class="emoji" alt=":smiley:"></p>
<p>Well, well , well. I ran out of good things to say about this mod. Looks like I have to admit the bad parts as well.</p>
<p>I had to crouch-jump in like 90% of the mod. I don’t mind it, but I always felt like it was a bug instead of a feature. Maybe is just me.</p>
<p>Sometimes, the maps are confusing. I spent a hour at a certain part in the Lambda Complex chapter. Also in Surface Tension sometimes… Also, sometimes when i’m walking on corridors there are crossroads and I have no idea which way to go (Sometimes i’m afraid to not miss a story part or a weapon and ammo)</p>
<p>There are also some small details (which sometimes don’t really matter) that really feels that it needs to be polished. For example, the first dead guard you see has the eyes open. Also there is a point in Blast Pit where I have to jump a small border, but there is an useless ladder that doesn’t even work. Also in Surface Tension, when you are in the mounts there is a gray unfinished texture. It really destroyed all the chapter’s beauty. Damn… the mounts where so beautiful… (from the 2008 trailer, I thought it’s a 2D skybox and that it won’t fit with the level, but the water actually moves and some small buildings are 3D… I love you for that).</p>
<p>I guess that’s all I had to say about this mod.</p>
<p>So on short:</p>
<p>Pros:</p>
<p>Voice Acting<br>
Soundtrack<br>
Map Design<br>
Enemies and Bosses (fighting the assassins was awesome!)<br>
Gameplay<br>
Ballance between action and puzzles</p>
<p>Cons:</p>
<p>Few details that needs to be polished<br>
Sometimes confusion.</p>
<p>My verdict is, that Black Mesa is simply one of the best mods/games I ever played in the last few years. It felt fresh, new, and nostalgic at the same time. I love the BM team for giving us this game FOR FREE without charging us anything (I will buy some of your soundtrack when it’s on iTunes. It’s what made the mod from better to best.) but, needs some small details fixed. But I won’t complain since it’s for free.</p>
<p>I rate this mod 9.5/10</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/my-toughts-about-black-mesa-spoilers/10403/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/my-toughts-about-black-mesa-spoilers/10403/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 16 Sep 2012 21:50:21 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-10403-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/my-toughts-about-black-mesa-spoilers/10403.rss">My toughts about Black Mesa (SPOILERS)</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
