<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Flickering pixels on video</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/flickering-pixels-on-video/13551</link>
    <description>Hey folks!

I am getting something strange happening on videos.  There seems to be random pixels that flash through many different colors in the video.  I thought, at first, it was a messed up pixel in my monitor, but if I move the window that&#39;s playing the video, the flickering pixel travels with the window.

I&#39;m clueless as to what to even search for to figure out what&#39;s going on here.

I&#39;m not sure, but it appears to only happen on one monitor (my Samsung SyncMaster 940BW).

Any ideas?

UPDATE: It&#39;s not just on videos.  It&#39;s any part of a webpage. It travels if I move the browser window.  I don&#39;t know if it only happens in a browser.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2014 10:17:15 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Help and Support</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/flickering-pixels-on-video/13551.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Flickering pixels on video</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[danielsangeo]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Possibly.  The problem is that it’s so random that I never have the ability to actually test it.  When the pixel flashes, it only does so for like 2-3 seconds before reverting to normal.  Then it might not reoccur for another 10 minutes or it could happen 4-5 times in one minute.  Or I just might not be noticing the other times.  And it seems to be in a different place each time it happens.</p>
<p>A thought I had was that it was some sort of weird poke-through with Aero, such as a pure magenta pixel that had somehow been tricked into being “transparent” and the computer’s background appeared.  But since it appeared next to a letter on a text portion and then it disappeared as quickly as it appeared, that hypothesis was busted.</p>
<p>Again, it only happens on the one monitor.  I have three monitors and I haven’t noticed this on the other monitors.</p>
<p>It’s not a big deal, it’s just curious.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/flickering-pixels-on-video/13551/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/flickering-pixels-on-video/13551/3</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2014 10:17:15 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13551-3</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/flickering-pixels-on-video/13551.rss">Flickering pixels on video</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Flickering pixels on video</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Maxey]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Might be your gpu.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/flickering-pixels-on-video/13551/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/flickering-pixels-on-video/13551/2</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2014 09:41:39 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13551-2</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/flickering-pixels-on-video/13551.rss">Flickering pixels on video</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Flickering pixels on video</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[danielsangeo]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Hey folks!</p>
<p>I am getting something strange happening on videos.  There seems to be random pixels that flash through many different colors in the video.  I thought, at first, it was a messed up pixel in my monitor, but if I move the window that’s playing the video, the flickering pixel travels with the window.</p>
<p>I’m clueless as to what to even search for to figure out what’s going on here.</p>
<p>I’m not sure, but it appears to only happen on one monitor (my Samsung SyncMaster 940BW).</p>
<p>Any ideas?</p>
<p>UPDATE: It’s not just on videos.  It’s any part of a webpage. It travels if I move the browser window.  I don’t know if it only happens in a browser.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/flickering-pixels-on-video/13551/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/flickering-pixels-on-video/13551/1</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2014 06:51:19 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13551-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/flickering-pixels-on-video/13551.rss">Flickering pixels on video</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
