<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Some bugs I found</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/some-bugs-i-found/13851</link>
    <description>[b]Here are some issues I&#39;ve found so far in both SP and MP:[/b]

In Unforeseen Consequences, the black security guard dude who helps you doesn&#39;t gesture (or really move) anymore during the &quot;Gordon!  Man am I glad to see you&quot; sequence, as well as his face expression changing very disjointedly.  Additionally, when he gets to the main lobby and tries to call for help, he doesn&#39;t play the &quot;press button&quot; animation and instead magically turns on the radio with his mind and speaks the lines while in the idle animation.

In the encounter in WGH where the scientist goes &quot;Rescued at last!&quot;, if you save him, he doesn&#39;t say the &quot;Goodness gracious!  I do believe he was trying to kill me!&quot; line and will remain silent.

Sometimes, in Surface Tension. when the Osprey tries to drop off grunts, they get stuck inside the Osprey and will cause the Osprey to stop moving and also stop dropping grunts.  The grunts will be inside the Osprey&#39;s hitbox, so they are basically unkillable and it messes up the entire sequence.

The HECU will still occasionally rush your position with reckless abandon if you hide behind cover away from their line of fire, albeit slower.

When you hit a soda machine, all the cans have no collision and come out in the same place at the same time resulting in a giant blobby mass of soda cans.

In dm_subtransit, if you&#39;re positioned correctly the tram can push you into the railing and get you stuck inside it.

Sometimes, MP playermodels will go into a T-pose.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 15 May 2015 22:42:26 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>In-game Issues</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/some-bugs-i-found/13851.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Some bugs I found</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Madcat1030]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>That bug with the rocket test fire chamber light being on by default!  I ran into it on all three of my playthroughs.  It turns off after you finally do the test-fire.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/some-bugs-i-found/13851/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/some-bugs-i-found/13851/3</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 May 2015 22:42:26 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13851-3</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/some-bugs-i-found/13851.rss">Some bugs I found</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Some bugs I found</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[maxximo]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>i will add one more that only happend me sometimes, in ‘Blast Pit’ the rocket activation room (where the tentacle attacks the scientist) have the explosion lights by default, when i enter the control room the first time (when the scientist is killed) and when i go to launch the rocket both the control room and the Silo are already with orange light and when i press a door button (in any of the 2 doors) it turns to normal light.</p>
<p>I hope you dont mind that i use your post to add a few bugs.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/some-bugs-i-found/13851/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/some-bugs-i-found/13851/2</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 07 May 2015 01:24:13 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13851-2</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/some-bugs-i-found/13851.rss">Some bugs I found</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Some bugs I found</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Kaleidescoop]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><span class="bbcode-b">Here are some issues I’ve found so far in both SP and MP:</span></p>
<p>In Unforeseen Consequences, the black security guard dude who helps you doesn’t gesture (or really move) anymore during the “Gordon!  Man am I glad to see you” sequence, as well as his face expression changing very disjointedly.  Additionally, when he gets to the main lobby and tries to call for help, he doesn’t play the “press button” animation and instead magically turns on the radio with his mind and speaks the lines while in the idle animation.</p>
<p>In the encounter in WGH where the scientist goes “Rescued at last!”, if you save him, he doesn’t say the “Goodness gracious!  I do believe he was trying to kill me!” line and will remain silent.</p>
<p>Sometimes, in Surface Tension. when the Osprey tries to drop off grunts, they get stuck inside the Osprey and will cause the Osprey to stop moving and also stop dropping grunts.  The grunts will be inside the Osprey’s hitbox, so they are basically unkillable and it messes up the entire sequence.</p>
<p>The HECU will still occasionally rush your position with reckless abandon if you hide behind cover away from their line of fire, albeit slower.</p>
<p>When you hit a soda machine, all the cans have no collision and come out in the same place at the same time resulting in a giant blobby mass of soda cans.</p>
<p>In dm_subtransit, if you’re positioned correctly the tram can push you into the railing and get you stuck inside it.</p>
<p>Sometimes, MP playermodels will go into a T-pose.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/some-bugs-i-found/13851/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/some-bugs-i-found/13851/1</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 06 May 2015 23:58:58 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13851-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/some-bugs-i-found/13851.rss">Some bugs I found</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
