<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Console Commands &amp; Settings Not Applying</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/console-commands-settings-not-applying/14802</link>
    <description>This may belong in bug reporting, bit new here, so let me know. I had been running the game flawlessly up until &quot;Power Up&quot; with the nostalgia sound package from steam workshop downloaded, when I ran into an issue. The AI became disabled, I tried to enter some console commands to restart AI, but to no avail. So, I uninstalled and re-installed the game.

Now, none of my installed workshop mods are working (all for sound) and snd_restart doesn&#39;t seem to have any effect. In addition to this, my settings are locked in the options menu; I cannot turn off fast weapon swap (I&#39;m clicking apply after every try) or change some of my key assignments. While trying to test it out, I changed my move forward key from W to G and after clicking apply, both keys performed the same function (though I was able to remove G as the forward key).

Last bit, when I have the developer console open, it pops in this line every second or so:

Ignoring unreasonable position (-950.346497,-433.009644,-1030704.562500) from vphysics! (entity weapon_shotgun)


Any ideas? Did I break the game?</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 06 Jun 2016 00:01:09 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Help!</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/console-commands-settings-not-applying/14802.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Console Commands &amp; Settings Not Applying</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Shrike1991]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>This may belong in bug reporting, bit new here, so let me know. I had been running the game flawlessly up until “Power Up” with the nostalgia sound package from steam workshop downloaded, when I ran into an issue. The AI became disabled, I tried to enter some console commands to restart AI, but to no avail. So, I uninstalled and re-installed the game.</p>
<p>Now, none of my installed workshop mods are working (all for sound) and snd_restart doesn’t seem to have any effect. In addition to this, my settings are locked in the options menu; I cannot turn off fast weapon swap (I’m clicking apply after every try) or change some of my key assignments. While trying to test it out, I changed my move forward key from W to G and after clicking apply, both keys performed the same function (though I was able to remove G as the forward key).</p>
<p>Last bit, when I have the developer console open, it pops in this line every second or so:</p>
<p>Ignoring unreasonable position (-950.346497,-433.009644,-1030704.562500) from vphysics! (entity weapon_shotgun)</p>
<p>Any ideas? Did I break the game?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/console-commands-settings-not-applying/14802/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/console-commands-settings-not-applying/14802/1</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jun 2016 00:01:09 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14802-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/console-commands-settings-not-applying/14802.rss">Console Commands &amp; Settings Not Applying</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
