<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Sound and Blue Lines</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/sound-and-blue-lines/12477</link>
    <description>Hey there,

I&#39;ve just got 2 little issues that I&#39;m hoping someone could maybe spread some light on?

1. Sometimes (not often), I get these weird blue lines appearing in games and I have no real idea how to explain it, so I took 2 screenshots of it.
- [url]https://puu.sh/468gS/48a6c203b6.png[/url]
- [url]https://puu.sh/468hl/2f098efa71.png[/url]
It&#39;s also happened in Bioshock 2 at 2 points so far early into the game, and I&#39;m not really sure why or how it&#39;s happening.
My graphics card is a Nvidia Geforce GTX 670. If you need more specs, let me know. 

2. A lesser issue, but it seems that if I unplug headphones and swap pairs, the sound in a current session is just gone. As in, if I swapped from my Sennheiser headphones to my simple apple earpod things, the game wont have any more sound until I fully close it and re-open it. The same goes for firefox. If I&#39;m on youtube and swap, I&#39;ll have to restart FF or no sound will come about.
It rarely happens since the only reason I&#39;ve been swapping was because I was comparing the sounds between them, but it does occassionally happen if I take out and put back in the [i]same[/i] set of headphones.

3. (Sorry just remembered this one). On my PC I have a regular USB 2.0 port, and that works fine. But I also have a USB 3.0 port, which doesn&#39;t seem to work at all. I&#39;ve installed the correct drivers for it and everything, and it still seems to not respond or even recognise itself.
Thanks for any help.  :slight_smile:</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2013 03:48:25 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Help and Support</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/sound-and-blue-lines/12477.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Sound and Blue Lines</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[papernick]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Just open the case and look if every cable coming out from the usb ports is connected. It’s not that hard, really.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/sound-and-blue-lines/12477/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/sound-and-blue-lines/12477/4</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2013 03:48:25 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12477-4</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/sound-and-blue-lines/12477.rss">Sound and Blue Lines</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Sound and Blue Lines</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[BendyBread]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <ol>
<li>Did this and checked temperatures. All seemed perfectly fine, its weird. :S</li>
<li>I’ll check it out.</li>
<li>Nope. My friend said that could be the issue as well. It was custom made/built, but I didn’t do it myself, the place where I ordered the parts and whatnot did since I’m not very tech savvy at these things. My friend does know how to fix it if it isn’t plugged in, so I’ll probably just get him to come around some day.</li>
</ol>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/sound-and-blue-lines/12477/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/sound-and-blue-lines/12477/3</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2013 07:35:39 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12477-3</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/sound-and-blue-lines/12477.rss">Sound and Blue Lines</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Sound and Blue Lines</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[papernick]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>1- Looks like a driver thing. Uninstall and reinstall your GPU drivers. If that fails, it could be that overheating is causing artifacts - check your gpu temps.</p>
<p>2- Also could be a driver-related issue.</p>
<p>3- Have you checked if it’s plugged into the MB?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/sound-and-blue-lines/12477/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/sound-and-blue-lines/12477/2</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2013 05:37:03 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12477-2</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/sound-and-blue-lines/12477.rss">Sound and Blue Lines</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Sound and Blue Lines</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[BendyBread]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Hey there,</p>
<p>I’ve just got 2 little issues that I’m hoping someone could maybe spread some light on?</p>
<ol>
<li>Sometimes (not often), I get these weird blue lines appearing in games and I have no real idea how to explain it, so I took 2 screenshots of it.</li>
</ol>
<ul>
<li><a href="https://puu.sh/468gS/48a6c203b6.png" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://puu.sh/468gS/48a6c203b6.png</a></li>
<li>
<a href="https://puu.sh/468hl/2f098efa71.png" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://puu.sh/468hl/2f098efa71.png</a><br>
It’s also happened in Bioshock 2 at 2 points so far early into the game, and I’m not really sure why or how it’s happening.<br>
My graphics card is a Nvidia Geforce GTX 670. If you need more specs, let me know.</li>
</ul>
<ol start="2">
<li>
<p>A lesser issue, but it seems that if I unplug headphones and swap pairs, the sound in a current session is just gone. As in, if I swapped from my Sennheiser headphones to my simple apple earpod things, the game wont have any more sound until I fully close it and re-open it. The same goes for firefox. If I’m on youtube and swap, I’ll have to restart FF or no sound will come about.<br>
It rarely happens since the only reason I’ve been swapping was because I was comparing the sounds between them, but it does occassionally happen if I take out and put back in the <span class="bbcode-i">same</span> set of headphones.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>(Sorry just remembered this one). On my PC I have a regular USB 2.0 port, and that works fine. But I also have a USB 3.0 port, which doesn’t seem to work at all. I’ve installed the correct drivers for it and everything, and it still seems to not respond or even recognise itself.<br>
Thanks for any help.  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=9" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
</li>
</ol>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/sound-and-blue-lines/12477/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/sound-and-blue-lines/12477/1</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2013 03:56:11 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12477-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/sound-and-blue-lines/12477.rss">Sound and Blue Lines</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
