<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Glitchy Glitch</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/glitchy-glitch/11099</link>
    <description>Hi there, ok so this is my first time posting a thread in the bugs section. So ill try to make it worth while. If theres a thread similar to this, please tell me so i could put it there.

So the main thing here is, there is this guy on youtube whose playing black mesa for the first time. Apparently thought his game play he is been lucky to find some glitches... some may be too bothersome, or some may just be a feature...


[url]https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=9gMCaeRUMYc[/url]  13: 35 - 13:50
Here i think he found a glitch where when you zoomed and reload at the same time, your gun trips out???

[url]https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=hGVYB0Q7NRE&amp;feature=relmfu[/url] 5:23 - 5: 32

Here he sort of tippy toed across the handrails... its kinda funny, not really bothering me, its just weird.. maybe on the update, when the pipe explodes, few handrails break off..

[url]https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=B63D1NXieS8&amp;feature=relmfu[/url] 14:40 - 15:15

This one might bother some people... Once you load to surface tension and load back to QE. Youre left with your crowbar, which might happen to some new players, who wander to much with only few health.

[url]https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=fDpWRi_qLmE&amp;feature=watch_response[/url] 10: 30 - 11: 35

This might be rare, the helicopter just went blind or something, shooting nothing. And the flames are way too far out of the main model...



Also, i seem to notice, that the laser beam of the tau cannon, come out UNDER/ LOWER the gun rather than the center of the circular orange thing of the tau cannon


Ill add some more once he finds another one.... and again, if theres a similar thread to this one, please tell me.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 24 Sep 2012 00:11:31 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>In-game Issues (Mod)</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/glitchy-glitch/11099.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Glitchy Glitch</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Cpl_Shephard]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Hi there, ok so this is my first time posting a thread in the bugs section. So ill try to make it worth while. If theres a thread similar to this, please tell me so i could put it there.</p>
<p>So the main thing here is, there is this guy on youtube whose playing black mesa for the first time. Apparently thought his game play he is been lucky to find some glitches… some may be too bothersome, or some may just be a feature…</p>
<p><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=9gMCaeRUMYc" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=9gMCaeRUMYc</a>  13: 35 - 13:50<br>
Here i think he found a glitch where when you zoomed and reload at the same time, your gun trips out???</p>
<p><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=hGVYB0Q7NRE&amp;feature=relmfu" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=hGVYB0Q7NRE&amp;feature=relmfu</a> 5:23 - 5: 32</p>
<p>Here he sort of tippy toed across the handrails… its kinda funny, not really bothering me, its just weird… maybe on the update, when the pipe explodes, few handrails break off…</p>
<p><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=B63D1NXieS8&amp;feature=relmfu" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=B63D1NXieS8&amp;feature=relmfu</a> 14:40 - 15:15</p>
<p>This one might bother some people… Once you load to surface tension and load back to QE. Youre left with your crowbar, which might happen to some new players, who wander to much with only few health.</p>
<p><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=fDpWRi_qLmE&amp;feature=watch_response" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=fDpWRi_qLmE&amp;feature=watch_response</a> 10: 30 - 11: 35</p>
<p>This might be rare, the helicopter just went blind or something, shooting nothing. And the flames are way too far out of the main model…</p>
<p>Also, i seem to notice, that the laser beam of the tau cannon, come out UNDER/ LOWER the gun rather than the center of the circular orange thing of the tau cannon</p>
<p>Ill add some more once he finds another one… and again, if theres a similar thread to this one, please tell me.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/glitchy-glitch/11099/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/glitchy-glitch/11099/1</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 24 Sep 2012 00:11:31 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11099-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/glitchy-glitch/11099.rss">Glitchy Glitch</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
