<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>TF2: the most unbalanced game ever made</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/tf2-the-most-unbalanced-game-ever-made/7526</link>
    <description>NO this is not trolling. I&#39;m sure 90% of you will remain blissfully ignorant of just how badly made the classes are and dismiss this as trolling. Either way I will not stick around to see the results of this thread as it will obviously just be verbal assault and actual trolling.

The two most fun by far classes in TF2: Spy and Sniper. They are bother incredibly fun. Two of the weakest classes in TF2: spy (occasionally he does well, but it requires lots of skill and luck unlike other classes) and sniper (also requires lots of skill).The Heavy the engie and the medic are all so overpowered it&#39;s not even funny. The engie though by a massive lead. The engie is more overpowered than the MW2 noob toob and the BFBC2 PBR all rolled into one. In EVERY server there is at least one noob who can&#39;t aim for shit so he hides at his intel/cp/whatever and spends ten minutes setting up a literally impenetrable row of turrets and then spends the rest of the game popping out of the resupply to repair his turrets. In most cases, after wasting several llives, you can take out most of the turrets with the demoman or something. But every once in a while a douchebag sets up turrets in such a position that it can&#39;t be shot easily by the demoman and he can repair it without getting hurt. In this case the only reasonable way to attack the turrets is with the spy&#39;s sapper. However that is almmost entirely useless seeing as it takes about 2 seconds for an engie to repair a sapped structure and most engies hide around their turrets spy checking anyone who gets too close to their turrets. Sure there are some ways to kill it effectively, but that takes lots of skill and a cooperating pair of at least two. And why should it be that ONE skilless douchebag should take AT LEAST two cooperating skilled players and many lives to kill?

TL;DR Spy and Sniper are insanely fun, and, gnereally, TF2 is insanely fun. However, the engie class especially is ABSURDLY overpowered. So much so it&#39;s not even funny. It stuns me that Valve could make such a colossal blunder and include a strategy so insanely overpowered, let alone one that requires the skill of a seven year old vietnamese downs crack baby to use it effectively. Why is it that mp games are always oriented around exploiting the game as much as possible to get the best k/d rather than using the tactics that aren&#39;t necessarily the most powerful but are the most fun??</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 25 Sep 2011 09:51:50 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Technology and Gaming</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/tf2-the-most-unbalanced-game-ever-made/7526.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>TF2: the most unbalanced game ever made</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[brokenfridgehinge]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Thanks for that overly long and insightful comment on this month and a half old thread. We really need more of those around here.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/tf2-the-most-unbalanced-game-ever-made/7526/161">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/tf2-the-most-unbalanced-game-ever-made/7526/161</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 25 Sep 2011 09:51:50 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7526-161</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/tf2-the-most-unbalanced-game-ever-made/7526.rss">TF2: the most unbalanced game ever made</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>TF2: the most unbalanced game ever made</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[calhoun_freeman]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>OI. LET THIS THREAD DIE.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/tf2-the-most-unbalanced-game-ever-made/7526/160">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/tf2-the-most-unbalanced-game-ever-made/7526/160</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 25 Sep 2011 09:18:45 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7526-160</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/tf2-the-most-unbalanced-game-ever-made/7526.rss">TF2: the most unbalanced game ever made</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>TF2: the most unbalanced game ever made</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Iceman154435]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="garrthbarrttinn">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/g/977dab/40.png" class="avatar"> garrthbarrttinn:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>NO this is not trolling. I’m sure 90% of you will remain blissfully ignorant of just how badly made the classes are and dismiss this as trolling. Either way I will not stick around to see the results of this thread as it will obviously just be verbal assault and actual trolling.</p>
<p>The two most fun by far classes in TF2: Spy and Sniper. They are bother incredibly fun. Two of the weakest classes in TF2: spy (occasionally he does well, but it requires lots of skill and luck unlike other classes) and sniper (also requires lots of skill).The Heavy the engie and the medic are all so overpowered it’s not even funny. The engie though by a massive lead. The engie is more overpowered than the MW2 noob toob and the BFBC2 PBR all rolled into one. In EVERY server there is at least one noob who can’t aim for shit so he hides at his intel/cp/whatever and spends ten minutes setting up a literally impenetrable row of turrets and then spends the rest of the game popping out of the resupply to repair his turrets. In most cases, after wasting several llives, you can take out most of the turrets with the demoman or something. But every once in a while a douchebag sets up turrets in such a position that it can’t be shot easily by the demoman and he can repair it without getting hurt. In this case the only reasonable way to attack the turrets is with the spy’s sapper. However that is almmost entirely useless seeing as it takes about 2 seconds for an engie to repair a sapped structure and most engies hide around their turrets spy checking anyone who gets too close to their turrets. Sure there are some ways to kill it effectively, but that takes lots of skill and a cooperating pair of at least two. And why should it be that ONE skilless douchebag should take AT LEAST two cooperating skilled players and many lives to kill?</p>
<p>TL;DR Spy and Sniper are insanely fun, and, gnereally, TF2 is insanely fun. However, the engie class especially is ABSURDLY overpowered. So much so it’s not even funny. It stuns me that Valve could make such a colossal blunder and include a strategy so insanely overpowered, let alone one that requires the skill of a seven year old vietnamese downs crack baby to use it effectively. Why is it that mp games are always oriented around exploiting the game as much as possible to get the best k/d rather than using the tactics that aren’t necessarily the most powerful but are the most fun??</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p><em>Sigh</em> How much have you played TF2? Because if you would have played a decent amount you would know that it is one of the most balanced games on the market.  It has gone through years of real testing and has stood the greatest test; the test of time.  People still enjoy it.  And since when does the amount of fun you have with a class have anything to do with the balance issues?  Each class has specific weaknesses and strengths.  No class is perfect.  With any sort of skill it isn’t hard for a spy to sap a sentry and backstab the engineer before he takes off the sapper.  Its quite simple.  And with the your eternal reward knife the spy will disguise so quick that the sentries won’t know its a spy and then it cake from then on.  Snipers can shoot around the corners without being detected by the sentry and soldier and demoman can use splash damage to take them out.  The sniper can even take out the engineer if they want.  I’ve even seen scouts run around sentries so fast that it can’t catch them.  And then there’s the good old Uber-charge that’s takes “lots of skill and a cooperating pair.”  Yeah, heaven forbid we put the “Team” in “Team Fortress 2.”  If you think that the spy sapper is the only way to go you obviously have no sense of creativity or problem solving.  And yeah, the team may have a bunch of engineers.  Most good servers put a cap on how many of a particular class you can have at once.  Particularly the engineers.  And even so, being an engineer doesn’t guarantee points.  Points are not just earned through killing people and to be honest the engineer doesn’t get to many kills either.  I have never seen a leaderboard topped by an engineer who has been playing engineer for the whole game.</p>
<p>There are so many items out now that you can even change the way you play that class.  For instance, the soldier can be played by dealing out hurt and retreiving life with the black box or rocket jump around the map with something like the liberty launcher.  All at a cost.  For those who think pyros are OP I’ll speak from personal experience and say that a good pyro is still nothing without others.  I’m a very good pyro and I need people to distract the other team so I can get in close.  The pyro is the DPS class.  They provide support to an extent.  And the sniper class doesn’t have to take skill, especially whilst using the huntsman.  The huntsman gets lucky headshots all the time because for some reason the hitbox for headshots is larger.  It takes no skill to lob arrows in the direction of your enemy either.</p>
<p>In conclusion, it is an extremely balanced game.  Any one class and more specifically any TYPE in that class (mentioned above with the soldiers) can be beaten with the right class and type of class to counter it.  Its just up to you to figure out how.  The fact that you think that its extremely imbalanced represents a lack for sight and problem solving on your part.  And even if certain weapons are imbalanced at times, odds are it will be evaluated by valve and fixed.  Weapon specs are changing and TF2 is the game with the most updates I know.  So have I convinced you?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/tf2-the-most-unbalanced-game-ever-made/7526/159">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/tf2-the-most-unbalanced-game-ever-made/7526/159</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 25 Sep 2011 09:09:40 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7526-159</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/tf2-the-most-unbalanced-game-ever-made/7526.rss">TF2: the most unbalanced game ever made</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>TF2: the most unbalanced game ever made</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[calhoun_freeman]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Disturbulator">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/d/cc9497/40.png" class="avatar"> Disturbulator:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I’m a diehard Scout.</p>
<p>All out Vintage FaN.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Seriously?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/tf2-the-most-unbalanced-game-ever-made/7526/158">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/tf2-the-most-unbalanced-game-ever-made/7526/158</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 07 Aug 2011 18:00:42 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7526-158</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/tf2-the-most-unbalanced-game-ever-made/7526.rss">TF2: the most unbalanced game ever made</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>TF2: the most unbalanced game ever made</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Savant]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Disturbulator">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/d/cc9497/40.png" class="avatar"> Disturbulator:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I’m a diehard Scout.</p>
<p>Vintage FaN.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>what</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/tf2-the-most-unbalanced-game-ever-made/7526/157">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/tf2-the-most-unbalanced-game-ever-made/7526/157</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 07 Aug 2011 15:42:31 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7526-157</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/tf2-the-most-unbalanced-game-ever-made/7526.rss">TF2: the most unbalanced game ever made</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>TF2: the most unbalanced game ever made</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Someonerandm]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Bot matches.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/tf2-the-most-unbalanced-game-ever-made/7526/156">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/tf2-the-most-unbalanced-game-ever-made/7526/156</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 07 Aug 2011 15:03:49 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7526-156</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/tf2-the-most-unbalanced-game-ever-made/7526.rss">TF2: the most unbalanced game ever made</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>TF2: the most unbalanced game ever made</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Jethrosoup]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>There’s a “training” mode or something like that.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/tf2-the-most-unbalanced-game-ever-made/7526/155">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/tf2-the-most-unbalanced-game-ever-made/7526/155</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 07 Aug 2011 07:47:47 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7526-155</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/tf2-the-most-unbalanced-game-ever-made/7526.rss">TF2: the most unbalanced game ever made</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>TF2: the most unbalanced game ever made</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[ac3d]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>There is, you just haven’t unlocked it yet.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/tf2-the-most-unbalanced-game-ever-made/7526/154">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/tf2-the-most-unbalanced-game-ever-made/7526/154</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 07 Aug 2011 07:41:01 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7526-154</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/tf2-the-most-unbalanced-game-ever-made/7526.rss">TF2: the most unbalanced game ever made</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>TF2: the most unbalanced game ever made</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Deimos]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Jokerine">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Jokerine:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Same here, it’s my favorite class, but I really suck at it.<br>
Guess I’ll stick to playing singleplayer eh &lt;.&lt;</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>But… there is no singeplayer.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/tf2-the-most-unbalanced-game-ever-made/7526/153">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/tf2-the-most-unbalanced-game-ever-made/7526/153</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 07 Aug 2011 07:37:21 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7526-153</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/tf2-the-most-unbalanced-game-ever-made/7526.rss">TF2: the most unbalanced game ever made</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>TF2: the most unbalanced game ever made</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[kaikarden]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>If this was a u raff u ruse contest, i lost right off the bat, when i saw his rage post and then the fact that be was banned “due to popular demand”. Shit is so cash. Also, my 2 cents, his statement about snipers and spys being the 2 most fun classes is opinion not fact, so his argument remains invalid.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/tf2-the-most-unbalanced-game-ever-made/7526/152">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/tf2-the-most-unbalanced-game-ever-made/7526/152</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 07 Aug 2011 00:14:16 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7526-152</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/tf2-the-most-unbalanced-game-ever-made/7526.rss">TF2: the most unbalanced game ever made</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>TF2: the most unbalanced game ever made</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Disturbulator]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I’m a diehard Scout.</p>
<p>All out Vintage FaN, vintage Luger, and bat.</p>
<p>I go out all strange for demo (targe, grenade launcher, eyelander).</p>
<p>For spy I use Deadringer, Eternal reward and L’etranger (with fez, fezzes are cool).<br>
-Want to try out that Kunai, though.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/tf2-the-most-unbalanced-game-ever-made/7526/151">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/tf2-the-most-unbalanced-game-ever-made/7526/151</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 06 Aug 2011 22:54:37 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7526-151</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/tf2-the-most-unbalanced-game-ever-made/7526.rss">TF2: the most unbalanced game ever made</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>TF2: the most unbalanced game ever made</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[TheOneAndOnly]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="DenDrio">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/d/82dd89/40.png" class="avatar"> DenDrio:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I can’t play scout to save my shit life. I get nervous and I shoot around them instead of shooting them. I HATE PLAYING SCOUT</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Same here, it’s my favorite class, but I really suck at it.<br>
Guess I’ll stick to playing singleplayer eh &lt;.&lt;</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/tf2-the-most-unbalanced-game-ever-made/7526/150">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/tf2-the-most-unbalanced-game-ever-made/7526/150</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 06 Aug 2011 21:16:35 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7526-150</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/tf2-the-most-unbalanced-game-ever-made/7526.rss">TF2: the most unbalanced game ever made</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>TF2: the most unbalanced game ever made</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Savant]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>what</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/tf2-the-most-unbalanced-game-ever-made/7526/149">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/tf2-the-most-unbalanced-game-ever-made/7526/149</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 06 Aug 2011 13:05:09 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7526-149</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/tf2-the-most-unbalanced-game-ever-made/7526.rss">TF2: the most unbalanced game ever made</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>TF2: the most unbalanced game ever made</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Kaweebo]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I died more in CSS more than I do in TF2. There are WAAY too many hackers in CSS.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/tf2-the-most-unbalanced-game-ever-made/7526/148">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/tf2-the-most-unbalanced-game-ever-made/7526/148</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 30 Jul 2011 19:17:30 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7526-148</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/tf2-the-most-unbalanced-game-ever-made/7526.rss">TF2: the most unbalanced game ever made</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>TF2: the most unbalanced game ever made</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[calhoun_freeman]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Practice. Playing quake and stuff will toughen ya up. You will die a lot, I guarantee that, but since when was TF2 played like CSS?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/tf2-the-most-unbalanced-game-ever-made/7526/147">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/tf2-the-most-unbalanced-game-ever-made/7526/147</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 30 Jul 2011 08:00:13 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7526-147</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/tf2-the-most-unbalanced-game-ever-made/7526.rss">TF2: the most unbalanced game ever made</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>TF2: the most unbalanced game ever made</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[DenDrio]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I can’t play scout to save my shit life. I get nervous and I shoot around them instead of shooting them. I HATE PLAYING SCOUT</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/tf2-the-most-unbalanced-game-ever-made/7526/146">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/tf2-the-most-unbalanced-game-ever-made/7526/146</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 30 Jul 2011 06:57:41 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7526-146</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/tf2-the-most-unbalanced-game-ever-made/7526.rss">TF2: the most unbalanced game ever made</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>TF2: the most unbalanced game ever made</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Shinobi]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I realize we kinda already moved past the sniper discussion but I feel it is worth pointing out this video.<br>
<a href="https://www.youtube.com/user/IcyToonie" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://www.youtube.com/user/IcyToonie</a><br>
Yeah anyone can pick up a sniper rifle and do decent, but really, there is skill involved to be able to do this^ on a regular basis. Makes me depressed since sniping is my main class and I’m no where near this skill level.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/tf2-the-most-unbalanced-game-ever-made/7526/145">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/tf2-the-most-unbalanced-game-ever-made/7526/145</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 30 Jul 2011 06:05:36 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7526-145</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/tf2-the-most-unbalanced-game-ever-made/7526.rss">TF2: the most unbalanced game ever made</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>TF2: the most unbalanced game ever made</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Fuskox]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Vanilla class is the best? I don’t think I could give up my Force-a-Nature, and the Fan is awesome for marking spies. The pistol is very nice, but both Bonk! and Crit-a-Cola are very nice as well, 2 hitting everyone with my cola and force is awesome.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/tf2-the-most-unbalanced-game-ever-made/7526/144">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/tf2-the-most-unbalanced-game-ever-made/7526/144</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 30 Jul 2011 05:12:29 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7526-144</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/tf2-the-most-unbalanced-game-ever-made/7526.rss">TF2: the most unbalanced game ever made</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>TF2: the most unbalanced game ever made</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[calhoun_freeman]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>For scout, vanilla class is the best. If you change your secondary to bonk, you lose your capability to cover/harass/damage in mid-range.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/tf2-the-most-unbalanced-game-ever-made/7526/143">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/tf2-the-most-unbalanced-game-ever-made/7526/143</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 30 Jul 2011 05:05:08 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7526-143</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/tf2-the-most-unbalanced-game-ever-made/7526.rss">TF2: the most unbalanced game ever made</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>TF2: the most unbalanced game ever made</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Kaweebo]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Fuskox">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/f/ea666f/40.png" class="avatar"> Fuskox:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>New question, what class does everyone here think requires the most skill to play well? I’m leaning towards scout, any other opinions?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>If I had to rank them:</p>
<ol>
<li>
<p>Spy. I dunno what it is but I’m just not Solid Snake enough yet to be good as this class. Occasionally I get lucky.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Demoman. Probably because I don’t use him too often but Demoman is frustrating for me to play, not really because he’s challenging gameplay-wise (in some cases he is) but because of the drastic choices you can make equipment wise. Sometimes different situations call for different tactics and I always seem to pick the wrong ones. Melee with chargin’ targe and some other weapon that boosts THAT but doesn’t let me use sticky bombs…or sticky bombs. And apparently I suck with sticky bombs. Demoman is mostly a melee only class for me.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Scout. The difficulty in this is really about three things: Low health, trying desperately to dodge every bit of fire coming your way, and my regretted neglect to use Bonk every once in a while. I’m too in love with Lugermorph.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Sniper. This and Scout are almost tied. Whether it’s my hand shaking violently to get a decent headshot on a moving target, or someone killing me while I’m in scope, Snipers (at least for me) take some practice to get used to.</p>
</li>
</ol>
<p>The rest of them are mostly tied because easy to use. (To me.)</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/tf2-the-most-unbalanced-game-ever-made/7526/142">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/tf2-the-most-unbalanced-game-ever-made/7526/142</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 30 Jul 2011 04:48:39 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7526-142</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/tf2-the-most-unbalanced-game-ever-made/7526.rss">TF2: the most unbalanced game ever made</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>TF2: the most unbalanced game ever made</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Fuskox]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Hm, idk. I don’t really have much of a challenge playing spy when I have Eternal Reward, really easy for me. I love Scout more than any other class and can play it pretty well, but I think Scouts are very underrated and underplayed because they can be challenging.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/tf2-the-most-unbalanced-game-ever-made/7526/141">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/tf2-the-most-unbalanced-game-ever-made/7526/141</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jul 2011 20:20:58 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7526-141</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/tf2-the-most-unbalanced-game-ever-made/7526.rss">TF2: the most unbalanced game ever made</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>TF2: the most unbalanced game ever made</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[DethklokSoldier]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="OrderOfDagon">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/user_avatar/leakfree.org/orderofdagon/40/4963_2.png" class="avatar"> OrderOfDagon:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Spy?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I agree 100%. Anyone can play spy, but it takes skill to play spy effectively.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/tf2-the-most-unbalanced-game-ever-made/7526/140">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/tf2-the-most-unbalanced-game-ever-made/7526/140</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jul 2011 19:44:08 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7526-140</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/tf2-the-most-unbalanced-game-ever-made/7526.rss">TF2: the most unbalanced game ever made</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>TF2: the most unbalanced game ever made</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[OrderOfDagon]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Fuskox">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/f/ea666f/40.png" class="avatar"> Fuskox:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>New question, what class does everyone here think requires the most skill to play well? I’m leaning towards scout, any other opinions?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Spy?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/tf2-the-most-unbalanced-game-ever-made/7526/139">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/tf2-the-most-unbalanced-game-ever-made/7526/139</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jul 2011 17:08:29 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7526-139</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/tf2-the-most-unbalanced-game-ever-made/7526.rss">TF2: the most unbalanced game ever made</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>TF2: the most unbalanced game ever made</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Fuskox]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>New question, what class does everyone here think requires the most skill to play well? I’m leaning towards scout, any other opinions?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/tf2-the-most-unbalanced-game-ever-made/7526/138">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/tf2-the-most-unbalanced-game-ever-made/7526/138</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jul 2011 17:03:14 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7526-138</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/tf2-the-most-unbalanced-game-ever-made/7526.rss">TF2: the most unbalanced game ever made</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>TF2: the most unbalanced game ever made</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Lamsey]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>There are a lot of people in this thread who don’t know what they’re talking about.</p>
<p>That is all.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/tf2-the-most-unbalanced-game-ever-made/7526/137">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/tf2-the-most-unbalanced-game-ever-made/7526/137</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jul 2011 16:04:15 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7526-137</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/tf2-the-most-unbalanced-game-ever-made/7526.rss">TF2: the most unbalanced game ever made</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
