<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Left 4 Dead weapon mod</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/left-4-dead-weapon-mod/2198</link>
    <description>*Just a disclaimer: all mods I&#39;m talking about are for offline use only. Probably wouldn&#39;t even work in online anyways.*

Hey guys, I haven&#39;t tried installing a [i]whole[/i] lot of mods on Left 4 Dead but so far it has taken pretty well to them. I&#39;m working with one mod right now that replaces the automatic rifle with the aliens m41a pulse rifle. I downloaded and replaced the models and textures so I had the look, but I wanted it to shoot more like the aliens weapon, so I upped the clip size to 99 and increased the rate of fire in the weapon_rifle script. To balance that out I lowered the damage of each bullet also. Now it feels awesome, but this leaves me with a problem: I run out of bullets too fast. I&#39;ve tried searching through the scripts and config files but I can&#39;t find any parameter to increase the max ammo. Anyone know a way I can do this?

Eventually I want to try to get the sound right too, so if anyone knows of a sound file that sounds like one single shot from the pulse rifle I&#39;d appreciate knowing where I could get that too.

Thanks for looking!</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 18 Dec 2009 07:38:34 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Technology and Gaming</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/left-4-dead-weapon-mod/2198.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Left 4 Dead weapon mod</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Orpheon]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Well, in case anyone was interested, I found a workaround for the ammo and sounds.</p>
<p>For the ammo, I discovered that the number of rounds you can carry in addition to your clip is set by a variable called “primary_ammo” in the weapon settings scripts. primary_ammo can be set to ammo types like “AMMO_TYPE_ASSAULTRIFLE”, so I looked for the file which set the parameters for the ammo type values, but I couldn’t find it. It’s probably locked up in a coded file like a .vpk or .pak or something else difficult to edit. So in order to work around this, I just replaced the ammo type for the assault rifle with the ammo type of the pistol, magically granting me infinite ammo. Woo hoo!</p>
<p>I was thinking of just using the Uzi’s ammo type (420 rounds), but surprisingly, even with infinite ammo, 99 round clip and a rapid rate of fire, the pulse rifle doesn’t grant me a big advantage in battle. It may even be a disadvantage, because it makes me feel like I’ve got a superweapon when really, because of the settings I used, each bullet does not do much damage and they get spent quite quickly. So, it’s a different feel now, but it doesn’t change much since it’s still deals similar dps and has to be reloaded about as often.</p>
<p>As far as the sounds go, I noticed that when firing at such a high speed, the default assault rifle gunshot sounds pretty close to the sound in Aliens. With a little tweaking in the weapon sound script, I changed the pitch to make it even closer. I might need to edit the sound file or get a slightly different one to make it perfect, but I’m pretty happy with it so far.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/left-4-dead-weapon-mod/2198/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/left-4-dead-weapon-mod/2198/4</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Dec 2009 07:38:34 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2198-4</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/left-4-dead-weapon-mod/2198.rss">Left 4 Dead weapon mod</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Left 4 Dead weapon mod</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Scentedwiind]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>search through Garrys mod downloads. They have lots of weapons and more importantly their sounds</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/left-4-dead-weapon-mod/2198/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/left-4-dead-weapon-mod/2198/3</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Dec 2009 01:32:12 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2198-3</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/left-4-dead-weapon-mod/2198.rss">Left 4 Dead weapon mod</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Left 4 Dead weapon mod</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Neon_Impulse]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>sounds pretty interesting, I’ll be sure to give it a go!</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/left-4-dead-weapon-mod/2198/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/left-4-dead-weapon-mod/2198/2</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Dec 2009 00:44:22 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2198-2</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/left-4-dead-weapon-mod/2198.rss">Left 4 Dead weapon mod</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Left 4 Dead weapon mod</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Orpheon]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><em>Just a disclaimer: all mods I’m talking about are for offline use only. Probably wouldn’t even work in online anyways.</em></p>
<p>Hey guys, I haven’t tried installing a <span class="bbcode-i">whole</span> lot of mods on Left 4 Dead but so far it has taken pretty well to them. I’m working with one mod right now that replaces the automatic rifle with the aliens m41a pulse rifle. I downloaded and replaced the models and textures so I had the look, but I wanted it to shoot more like the aliens weapon, so I upped the clip size to 99 and increased the rate of fire in the weapon_rifle script. To balance that out I lowered the damage of each bullet also. Now it feels awesome, but this leaves me with a problem: I run out of bullets too fast. I’ve tried searching through the scripts and config files but I can’t find any parameter to increase the max ammo. Anyone know a way I can do this?</p>
<p>Eventually I want to try to get the sound right too, so if anyone knows of a sound file that sounds like one single shot from the pulse rifle I’d appreciate knowing where I could get that too.</p>
<p>Thanks for looking!</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/left-4-dead-weapon-mod/2198/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/left-4-dead-weapon-mod/2198/1</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Dec 2009 00:00:17 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2198-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/left-4-dead-weapon-mod/2198.rss">Left 4 Dead weapon mod</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
