<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Missing Textures</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/missing-textures/11074</link>
    <description>I am missing multiple textures, and my cross hair disappears over certain objects like npcs. Particles, like fire, show up as yellow, orange, and red squares with diagonal lines through them. During the resonance cascade, there was also a white web of lines, which I assume would normally be rendered as another effect. I am missing eyes from human and vorts, but that is all I&#39;ve seen so far. All weapons I&#39;ve seen are pink and black checkerboard (like the eyes), and most of the clothing on humans has blood splatter decals all over it. Screenshots of most of my Issues below.

[img]https://dl.dropbox.com/u/14466246/2012-09-22_00001.jpg[/img]
[img]https://dl.dropbox.com/u/14466246/2012-09-22_00002.jpg[/img]
[img]https://dl.dropbox.com/u/14466246/2012-09-22_00003.jpg[/img]

I&#39;ve looked for awhile for a solution in these forums but to no avail. I&#39;ve tried launching with -directx 90, 9.0, and 110. I&#39;ve redownloaded from the torrent on the site and the zip on moddb, but neither has fixed this issue. When I check the console, I see messages like BMS/Models/Human/eyeball_1a is missing and stuff like that. When I check the advanced video settings, I see the software level as 9.0 and my hardware as 0.9, when I know I have directx 11 installed. My hardware specs are:

ATI Radeon HD 5750 1GB of GDDR5 memory
2.93GHz Quad-Core Intel Core i7 8MB level 3 cache
8gb ddr3 RAM
My resolution is 2560x1440 also if that helps

I see I typed a bunch, but I&#39;m just trying to be as specific as possible to help out anyone willing to help me. Thanks in advance to anyone with advice. Last thing: If anyone has the models that the console tells me I&#39;m missing, maybe you could upload some of those, and I could put them in and check to see if that works? Thanks again.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 23 Sep 2012 13:56:11 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>In-game Issues (Mod)</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/missing-textures/11074.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Missing Textures</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Nitro]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I’ve looked into it some  more and it seems like the problem is that my game crashes when I try to launch with any directx level higher than 81. Does anyone know how to fix this?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/missing-textures/11074/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/missing-textures/11074/4</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 23 Sep 2012 13:56:11 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11074-4</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/missing-textures/11074.rss">Missing Textures</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Missing Textures</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Nitro]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I think all the broken textures has to do with my hardware directx version. when I add -dxlevel 90, 95, or 98 I get a white screen and then a message saying hl2.exe has stopped working. When I use +mat_dxlevel 90/95/98, I get the normal loading screen, then hl2.exe has stopped working. My game will run if I set dxlevel to 79, 80 or 81, but I have major problems with 8.0 and 8.1, while only relatively problematic aesthetic issues with 7.9 (the broken/missing textures and effects mentioned earlier). Here is the minidump when I try to run with the command -dxlevel 90. 	<br>
goo.gl/FAWU0</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/missing-textures/11074/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/missing-textures/11074/3</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 23 Sep 2012 04:37:26 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11074-3</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/missing-textures/11074.rss">Missing Textures</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Missing Textures</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Jenova19]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Try changing your Launch Options to “<span class="bbcode-b">-dxlevel 95</span>” or “<span class="bbcode-b">-dxlevel 98</span>”, then starting the game and removing the line from said Launch Options, after closing the game.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-i">(Refer to this thread, for more information on the subject (mainly “<span class="bbcode-b">Q6a</span>”): <a href="https://forums.blackmesasource.com/showthread.php?t=14063" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">[FAQ] Semi-complete Black Mesa FAQ - READ FIRST</a>)</span></p>
<hr>
<p>A listing of the missing file’s <span class="bbcode-u">exact</span> path would be nice to add to your post, as well.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/missing-textures/11074/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/missing-textures/11074/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 23 Sep 2012 01:30:45 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11074-2</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/missing-textures/11074.rss">Missing Textures</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Missing Textures</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Nitro]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I am missing multiple textures, and my cross hair disappears over certain objects like npcs. Particles, like fire, show up as yellow, orange, and red squares with diagonal lines through them. During the resonance cascade, there was also a white web of lines, which I assume would normally be rendered as another effect. I am missing eyes from human and vorts, but that is all I’ve seen so far. All weapons I’ve seen are pink and black checkerboard (like the eyes), and most of the clothing on humans has blood splatter decals all over it. Screenshots of most of my Issues below.</p>
<p><span alt="" class="broken-image" title="This image is broken"><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-unlink svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#unlink"></use></svg></span><br>
<span alt="" class="broken-image" title="This image is broken"><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-unlink svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#unlink"></use></svg></span><br>
<span alt="" class="broken-image" title="This image is broken"><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-unlink svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#unlink"></use></svg></span></p>
<p>I’ve looked for awhile for a solution in these forums but to no avail. I’ve tried launching with -directx 90, 9.0, and 110. I’ve redownloaded from the torrent on the site and the zip on moddb, but neither has fixed this issue. When I check the console, I see messages like BMS/Models/Human/eyeball_1a is missing and stuff like that. When I check the advanced video settings, I see the software level as 9.0 and my hardware as 0.9, when I know I have directx 11 installed. My hardware specs are:</p>
<p>ATI Radeon HD 5750 1GB of GDDR5 memory<br>
2.93GHz Quad-Core Intel Core i7 8MB level 3 cache<br>
8gb ddr3 RAM<br>
My resolution is 2560x1440 also if that helps</p>
<p>I see I typed a bunch, but I’m just trying to be as specific as possible to help out anyone willing to help me. Thanks in advance to anyone with advice. Last thing: If anyone has the models that the console tells me I’m missing, maybe you could upload some of those, and I could put them in and check to see if that works? Thanks again.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/missing-textures/11074/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/missing-textures/11074/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 23 Sep 2012 00:55:07 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11074-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/missing-textures/11074.rss">Missing Textures</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
