<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>MSI 1.5.1 may cause hl2.exe to crash on launch</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/msi-1-5-1-may-cause-hl2-exe-to-crash-on-launch/10847</link>
    <description>I am not sure if this is the correct place to post this, but I figure it may help some people and that if I have it in the wrong place someone will surely tell me. I have a ATI Radion 5850 running catalyst 12.4 and I regularly use MSI afterburner 1.5.1 to overclock it and set the fan speed. When I first downloaded black mesa it would crash to desktop every time I tried to load it. I tried many things (too many to list, and most were basic troubleshooting things that most in the community already know about) but none worked. I decided to shut down MSI, something I never do, and lo and behold it loaded right up. I have no problems now, as long as I never have MSI running in the back ground. If anyone needs logs or reports of the crash I will need some info on how to provide it, because I am a total noob. I am only getting into this to support this game and it&#39;s makers. Thank you all so much for creating this, and letting me relive a seminal gaming moment in my life in a way that makes things fresh again.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 19 Sep 2012 18:18:38 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>In-game Issues (Mod)</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/msi-1-5-1-may-cause-hl2-exe-to-crash-on-launch/10847.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>MSI 1.5.1 may cause hl2.exe to crash on launch</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[sarkunit]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I am not sure if this is the correct place to post this, but I figure it may help some people and that if I have it in the wrong place someone will surely tell me. I have a ATI Radion 5850 running catalyst 12.4 and I regularly use MSI afterburner 1.5.1 to overclock it and set the fan speed. When I first downloaded black mesa it would crash to desktop every time I tried to load it. I tried many things (too many to list, and most were basic troubleshooting things that most in the community already know about) but none worked. I decided to shut down MSI, something I never do, and lo and behold it loaded right up. I have no problems now, as long as I never have MSI running in the back ground. If anyone needs logs or reports of the crash I will need some info on how to provide it, because I am a total noob. I am only getting into this to support this game and it’s makers. Thank you all so much for creating this, and letting me relive a seminal gaming moment in my life in a way that makes things fresh again.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/msi-1-5-1-may-cause-hl2-exe-to-crash-on-launch/10847/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/msi-1-5-1-may-cause-hl2-exe-to-crash-on-launch/10847/1</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 19 Sep 2012 18:18:38 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-10847-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/msi-1-5-1-may-cause-hl2-exe-to-crash-on-launch/10847.rss">MSI 1.5.1 may cause hl2.exe to crash on launch</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
