<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Account name origin</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/account-name-origin/15061</link>
    <description>Just wondering what´s the background story of your (present) account name here? Is or was there a specific meaning behind it or was it just randomly created?</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2017 06:01:30 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Off Topic</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/account-name-origin/15061.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Account name origin</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypt]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Because look at it, that looks awful</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/account-name-origin/15061/41">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/account-name-origin/15061/41</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2017 06:01:30 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-15061-41</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/account-name-origin/15061.rss">Account name origin</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Account name origin</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Tiki]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Why not Chrypt? I bet nobody else uses it</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/account-name-origin/15061/40">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/account-name-origin/15061/40</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2017 04:10:47 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-15061-40</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/account-name-origin/15061.rss">Account name origin</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Account name origin</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypt]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I’m also Chris on Steam.<br>
“Crypt” is a little more distinctive than “Chris,” so that’s more frequently available to use as a username first, and more recognizable. That’s mostly it. I’ve just been slowly shying away from usernames, but Chris is a crazy common name.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/account-name-origin/15061/39">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/account-name-origin/15061/39</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2017 01:58:33 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-15061-39</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/account-name-origin/15061.rss">Account name origin</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Account name origin</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Raziel_ZV]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Just out of curiousity Crypt …</p>
<p>Why are you here and on the Moddb page registered as “Crypt”, but on the tripmine studios forum you´re “Chris”? Why not “Crypt” as well? Or vice versa?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/account-name-origin/15061/38">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/account-name-origin/15061/38</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2017 19:52:43 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-15061-38</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/account-name-origin/15061.rss">Account name origin</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Account name origin</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypt]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Off topic, but “Even an atrocity becomes inviting” would make a sick book chapter title.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/account-name-origin/15061/37">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/account-name-origin/15061/37</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 01 Feb 2017 07:44:13 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-15061-37</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/account-name-origin/15061.rss">Account name origin</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Account name origin</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Tiki]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Admiral Sakai">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Admiral Sakai:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Well, remember, the HECU are <span class="bbcode-i">dicks</span>. They seemed to have no problem whatsoever with gunning down hundreds of innocent civilians (only one ever even brings it up), so I imagine they wouldn’t be too concerned about falling back to let the place get nuked as long as they thought it’d get rid of the Xenians.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p><span class="bbcode-i">Everyone</span> with real jobs in the military are dicks. But they’re still people. A mission like this, killing civilians, probably wasn’t delivered as straightforward as you’re imagining.</p>
<p>There wasn’t a lot of time for response-planning, but I’m betting the assignment included some of these elements:</p>
<ul>
<li>Voluntary basis:</li>
</ul>
<p>[list][*]Some will volunteer because “<span class="bbcode-i">Your country needs you</span>”</p>
<ul>
<li>Others volunteer to support their colleagues and unit</li>
<li>More volunteer because they don’t want to be a pussy (…they <span class="bbcode-i">are</span> Marines, after all)<br>
So, 95% of the people you ask to go on this assignment are gonna agree. The only guys to turn it down will be the one or two weirdos of the bunch. And then, once you get people to volunteer for the mission, they’re going to go all the way. So once you get people to volunteer for such a mission, they won’t want to let down their buddies, their superiors, <span class="bbcode-i">or themselves</span>.[/<em>:m]<br>
[</em>]Demonization:</li>
<li>Things work more smoothly if you tell the underlings false information which makes their job easier. Things like… “<span class="bbcode-i">Witnesses are likely exposed to alien contagion</span>” or “<span class="bbcode-i">Researchers are guilty of intentionally subjecting Earth to alien invasion</span>”<br>
[/<em>:m][</em>]More to the picture than what Gordon encountered:</li>
<li>While we did witness a bunch of grunt-on-sci violence, we can’t say for sure the executions weren’t localized to everything witnessed by Gordon (in what happened to be highly infested areas where capture and extraction weren’t feasible)</li>
<li>While you calim that the HECU were dicks and had no problem with it, you weren’t there, man. You’re going off the example set by a fairly repetitive implementation of enemies in a videogame – there’s much more variety that has gone unseen. Plus, when you’re sleep-deprived and used to following orders and genuinely tired of not having real missions to do, you’d be surprised how even an atrocity becomes inviting, no matter how questionable it may seem at first.<br>
[/*:m][/list:u]</li>
</ul>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/account-name-origin/15061/36">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/account-name-origin/15061/36</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 01 Feb 2017 03:55:24 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-15061-36</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/account-name-origin/15061.rss">Account name origin</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Account name origin</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Admiral_Sakai]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Well, remember, the HECU are <span class="bbcode-i">dicks</span>. They seemed to have no problem whatsoever with gunning down hundreds of innocent civilians (only one ever even brings it up), so I imagine they wouldn’t be too concerned about falling back to let the place get nuked as long as they thought it’d get rid of the Xenians.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/account-name-origin/15061/35">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/account-name-origin/15061/35</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 31 Jan 2017 13:11:29 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-15061-35</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/account-name-origin/15061.rss">Account name origin</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Account name origin</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypt]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>And <span class="bbcode-i">that</span> is a fantastic baseline for Opposing Force 2.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/account-name-origin/15061/34">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/account-name-origin/15061/34</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 31 Jan 2017 08:00:50 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-15061-34</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/account-name-origin/15061.rss">Account name origin</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Account name origin</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Tiki]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>You know, sometimes I wonder what became of the handful of HECU members that successfully made it out of Black Mesa.</p>
<hr>
<p>I mean, <span class="bbcode-i">first</span> they’re assigned to wipe out all the personnel of a big facility. That’s considerably taxing on the conscience.<br>
Then they start losing colleagues, <span class="bbcode-i">quickly</span>, to both supersuit-rambo Freeman <span class="bbcode-b">and</span> the eldritch-abomination invading xenofauna.<br>
THEN they hastily withdraw from the facility, in what must have felt like a mission-failure walk-of-shame.<br>
And the place gets nuked, to-boot, so that all the blood and sacrifice becomes for naught.</p>
<p>Then the Seven Hour War happens, and you face the realization that <span class="bbcode-b">as you</span> were ordered to sweep some aliens [and witnesses] under the rug, <span class="bbcode-b">the cat was going to come out of the bag anyway</span>… also, it’s a tiger.</p>
<p>And <span class="bbcode-i">then</span>, a decade later, out of nowhere, the guy who was killing your buddies with much gusto decides to come out of retirement as a messianic figure and become the celebrated figurehead to humanity’s uprising.</p>
<hr>
<p>Like, shit. Humanity’s great and all, but there must be a sore spot left over from old grudges when it comes to championing Mr. Freeman.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/account-name-origin/15061/33">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/account-name-origin/15061/33</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 31 Jan 2017 07:27:53 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-15061-33</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/account-name-origin/15061.rss">Account name origin</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Account name origin</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Massey]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Yore ded freemun</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/account-name-origin/15061/32">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/account-name-origin/15061/32</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 31 Jan 2017 05:32:04 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-15061-32</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/account-name-origin/15061.rss">Account name origin</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Account name origin</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[JeffMOD]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Crypt">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/user_avatar/leakfree.org/crypt/40/4394_2.png" class="avatar"> Crypt:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>You’re name</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Your*</p>
<p>Of, if you’re a member of the HECU, Yore.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/account-name-origin/15061/31">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/account-name-origin/15061/31</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 31 Jan 2017 04:34:50 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-15061-31</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/account-name-origin/15061.rss">Account name origin</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Account name origin</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[lambdaman]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>For some reason I thought you weren’t an American due to that name.<br>
Racism confirmed!</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/account-name-origin/15061/30">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/account-name-origin/15061/30</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 30 Jan 2017 01:00:46 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-15061-30</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/account-name-origin/15061.rss">Account name origin</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Account name origin</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Johnwalter]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Do<br>
Kill<br>
Yourself</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/account-name-origin/15061/29">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/account-name-origin/15061/29</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 29 Jan 2017 09:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-15061-29</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/account-name-origin/15061.rss">Account name origin</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Account name origin</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypt]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>You’re name is such bullshit. I didn’t start calling you Ryan due to familiarity, just dkytehskindbs is a pain and DKY feels wrong</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/account-name-origin/15061/28">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/account-name-origin/15061/28</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 29 Jan 2017 02:43:29 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-15061-28</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/account-name-origin/15061.rss">Account name origin</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Account name origin</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[dky.tehkingd.u]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Oh dear.</p>
<p>So… once upon a time, long long ago, when Halo PC still had a thriving multiplayer community, I always joined servers using the username “king”. It was short and sweet, and to the point. The name itself was a reference to my first name, Ryan, which means “Little King”.</p>
<p>A few years later, in about fifth grade, I went to a summer camp during which me and a bunch of friends banded together and gave each other Sith names because we were ten years old and wanted to be badasses. I ended up taking on the name Darth Killyou, because I was ten years old and I wasn’t very clever. The name “darthkillyou” ended up being my go-to username on various websites for several years. Today it still lives on in my <a href="https://developer.valvesoftware.com/wiki/User%20:smiley:%20arthkillyou" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Valve Developer Community Wiki Account</a>.</p>
<p>At some point during my escapades on the VDCW, some guy started referring to me as “DKY” for short. It was nice and concise, so I adopted the initialism. But for most username purposes, I still used the full “darthkillyou” name.</p>
<p>Around the same time, I got an Xbox 360. I needed a username for my console profile, and it couldn’t be anything particularly objectionable to my parents, since I pretty much set up the Xbox account in front of my dad. So I re-used my old name “king” from my Halo PC days. I thought it was appropriate, since I mainly got that thing to play Halo 2. (Yes, I was a few years late to the party…)</p>
<p>Eventually, when I first subscribed to Xbox Live to play Halo 2 with friends, obviously the name “king” had already been taken. So I decided to go with the “darthkillyou” thing because it was unique, and because I was already using it for Counter-Strike anyway, so I thought it was good to be consistent. I was quite proud that it didn’t need to have any annoying embedded numbers or xX_Xx things in it.</p>
<p>That all changed, however, when the admin of a Counter-Strike server one day kept kicking me from the match because my username “darthkillyou” was “too violent”. (Seriously, who the hell cares about that in a video game? <span class="bbcode-i">Some people…</span>  ?(  ) Since I was playing with a group of friends and was eager to get back into the game to help them out, I shrugged and changed my name to the shortened “DKY”. It was at this point that I realized that people were <span class="bbcode-i">probably</span> getting the wrong impression of the kind of person I am based on that name, so it was at that point that I decided to stop using the full “darthkillyou” name from then on.</p>
<p>Over time, I kept changing and corrupting “DKY” and “king” in various ways to use as a username while playing on various Counter-Strike servers. The transition went roughly something like: “DKY_theking” -&gt; “DKY_tehtheking” -&gt; “DKY_tehthekinged_u” -&gt; “DKY_tehtheking.d_u” -&gt; “dky_tehking.d_u” -&gt; “dky.tehkingd.u”, plus or minus a few other variations. I thought I was being <span class="bbcode-i">cool</span> for abusing the word “king” as a past-tense transitive verb, in the sense of “DKY kinged you!” or similar.</p>
<p>Eventually I converged on consistently using the form “dky.tehkingd.u”. And it has stuck ever since.</p>
<p>And no, I have no idea how to pronounce it. Don’t even try. Just call me DKY. The last time someone tried to pronounce the full name (in a video published by an EA community manager, back when they still had a Command &amp; Conquer franchise community to actually manage), he completely butchered it. Because <span class="bbcode-i">every</span> way you pronounce it will be butchering it. And I was quite amused.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/account-name-origin/15061/27">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/account-name-origin/15061/27</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Jan 2017 06:21:10 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-15061-27</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/account-name-origin/15061.rss">Account name origin</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Account name origin</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Ikkosen]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><span class="bbcode-b">“shingeki”</span> -<span class="bbcode-i"> from my AoT blog in Tumblr : <span class="mention">@shingekinoheadcannons</span></span><br>
<span class="bbcode-b">“is_real” </span>- <span class="bbcode-i">AoT hype is friggin real this SUMMER 2017, so is BM Xen hype.</span></p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b"><span class="bbcode-i">heheh, this is so weird.</span></span></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/account-name-origin/15061/26">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/account-name-origin/15061/26</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2017 09:52:13 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-15061-26</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/account-name-origin/15061.rss">Account name origin</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Account name origin</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[CatzEyes93]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Been my online name since 1997. It describes how I used to do my makeup + the year I married prince charming.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/account-name-origin/15061/25">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/account-name-origin/15061/25</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jan 2017 21:10:20 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-15061-25</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/account-name-origin/15061.rss">Account name origin</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Account name origin</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Shaddy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Shadon (weird villain from comic I drew when I was like 5) -&gt; Shadic (bad Sonic fan character) -&gt; Shadyk (thinking a stupider spelling would make it more unique) -&gt; Shaddy (some bastardization of that to hopefully make it less Sonic-y at first glance)</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/account-name-origin/15061/24">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/account-name-origin/15061/24</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 14 Jan 2017 04:03:21 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-15061-24</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/account-name-origin/15061.rss">Account name origin</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Account name origin</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[k3nny1550]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Oh absolutely.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/account-name-origin/15061/23">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/account-name-origin/15061/23</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 14 Jan 2017 00:39:15 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-15061-23</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/account-name-origin/15061.rss">Account name origin</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Account name origin</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[lambdaman]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="k3nny1550">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/user_avatar/leakfree.org/k3nny1550/40/4952_2.png" class="avatar"> k3nny1550:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I die too much in online MP games, so “Kenny” made it funny.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Do you call them a bastard afterwards?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/account-name-origin/15061/22">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/account-name-origin/15061/22</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jan 2017 03:20:34 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-15061-22</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/account-name-origin/15061.rss">Account name origin</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Account name origin</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[k3nny1550]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I die too much in online MP games, so “Kenny” made it funny.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/account-name-origin/15061/21">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/account-name-origin/15061/21</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jan 2017 01:29:23 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-15061-21</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/account-name-origin/15061.rss">Account name origin</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Account name origin</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[wayne_acoba]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Hey look, I actually found some - blurry - pics of that w.a.acoba shirt! Couldn’t find the shirt, though. Maybe I sold it…wait. maybe…I should look out for another w.a.a. … <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/confused.png?v=9" title=":confused:" class="emoji" alt=":confused:"></p>
<div class="spoiler">
<p><div class="lightbox-wrapper"><a class="lightbox" href="https://i.imgur.com/6893jaP.jpg" title="" rel="nofollow noopener"><img src="https://i.imgur.com/6893jaP.jpg" alt="" width="375" height="500"><div class="meta"><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-far-image svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#far-image"></use></svg><span class="filename"></span><span class="informations">1200×1600</span><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-discourse-expand svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#discourse-expand"></use></svg></div></a></div></p>
</div>
<div class="spoiler">
<p><div class="lightbox-wrapper"><a class="lightbox" href="https://i.imgur.com/HmBDdp7.jpg" title="" rel="nofollow noopener"><img src="https://i.imgur.com/HmBDdp7.jpg" alt="" width="666" height="500"><div class="meta"><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-far-image svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#far-image"></use></svg><span class="filename"></span><span class="informations">1600×1200</span><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-discourse-expand svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#discourse-expand"></use></svg></div></a></div></p>
</div>
<div class="spoiler">
<p><div class="lightbox-wrapper"><a class="lightbox" href="https://i.imgur.com/gwTxHTi.jpg" title="" rel="nofollow noopener"><img src="https://i.imgur.com/gwTxHTi.jpg" alt="" width="666" height="500"><div class="meta"><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-far-image svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#far-image"></use></svg><span class="filename"></span><span class="informations">1600×1200</span><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-discourse-expand svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#discourse-expand"></use></svg></div></a></div></p>
</div>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/account-name-origin/15061/20">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/account-name-origin/15061/20</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jan 2017 22:27:41 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-15061-20</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/account-name-origin/15061.rss">Account name origin</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Account name origin</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[MisterDigitalGuy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I’ve gone under the username “MisterDigitalGuy” for such a long time that it’s kind of hard to remember what went into it. As far as I can remember, I originally started using the name back in middle school (those were the dark and evil days…) for an account on some educational website. Usually, when it came to usernames, I would just pull something out of thin air and set that as my username- and that’s what “MisterDigitalGuy” essentially started out as. I was just going to use it for this one website, and I’d think of another username when I wanted to create an account on another website. However, something about this name stuck. I had no idea why this name worked so well, but whatever the reason, it soon became my go-to internet pseudonym. Ever since, pretty much every online account that I’ve created has used this name (specifically, my steam account and this account).</p>
<p>As for what went into the name, like I said before, it was mostly pulled out of thin air. That said, I do have a pretty good idea of what went into the name. The more formal “Mister” and the more casual “Guy” come from me being a guy myself, and the “Digital” comes from my unending fascination with technology. It’s worked for me so far, and it’s a heckuva lot better than some of the other usernames I used to use.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/account-name-origin/15061/19">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/account-name-origin/15061/19</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jan 2017 21:23:19 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-15061-19</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/account-name-origin/15061.rss">Account name origin</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Account name origin</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Massey]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Haha yeah Wayne, but honestly I accept both pronunciations. The only one I keep strict is Massey, which is pronounced Mahs-e not Mace-e. A lot of people use the second one, which I still respond to but Massey is pretty set after like 5 or 6 years of it existing haha</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/account-name-origin/15061/18">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/account-name-origin/15061/18</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jan 2017 21:15:28 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-15061-18</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/account-name-origin/15061.rss">Account name origin</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Account name origin</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypt]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Oh good, I’m not alone in this. Makes me think of when people realize Thee and Acade have no R.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/account-name-origin/15061/17">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/account-name-origin/15061/17</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jan 2017 18:14:40 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-15061-17</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/account-name-origin/15061.rss">Account name origin</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
