<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Various bugs</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/various-bugs/11257</link>
    <description>Meant to post this a week or so ago, when I was playing through the game I made a list of some bugs I encountered.  Not sure if some of these have already been posted or not as there&#39;s pages of them, but hopefully they&#39;re of some use:

*The keyboard options menu has an option for you to bind a key to the Gravity Gun.

*When the Zombie bursts out of the toilet just after the Resonance Cascade, you can interrupt its animation for getting up (it never does it, it INSTANTLY comes after you if you&#39;re next to it).

*In the scripted sequence where the zombie starts to strangle the guard who beckons you over after mentioning that a headcrab has latched on to &#39;his buddy&#39;s head&#39;, you cannot kill the zombie when it has started to strangle him, even when he asks for help.  There seems ample time to kill it, but it is indestructable during the sequence, you must kill it before it gets to the guard in order to save him

*At the beginning of &#39;We&#39;ve got Hostiles!&#39;, the glass to the door button is unbreakable until the scientist dies (ie, if you save him by destroying the laser-explosive before the scientist gets to it, you cannot get through the door without murdering the scientist first).

*If a portable turret has an &#39;ERROR&#39;, when you try and move it you hold it by the very bottom of the very back foot rather than in the usual position.

*In the first encounter with the Assassins, after you have killed them all, if you reload a save, any save, the game&#39;s performance is massively reduced.

*Reloading a save during the final Lamda Core teleporter part once it is partly running (blue laser, enemies spawning) seems to cause a massive performance drop.

*Scientist line &quot;I don&#39;t know how much more of this I can endure&quot; - lips did not move

*If you release snarks directly below you, they do not/cannot move until you move.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 01 Oct 2012 22:48:04 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>In-game Issues (Mod)</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/various-bugs/11257.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Various bugs</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Metritutus]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Jenova19">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/j/f6c823/40.png" class="avatar"> Jenova19:</div>
<blockquote>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">To 4. (unbreakable glass /w scientist):</span></p>
<p><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=-MkIhO8HCps" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Black Mesa: How-To “Save” The Scientist Being Stuck In We’ve Got Hostiles! - YouTube</a>  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=9" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
<p>It’s not really a “fix” (hence the quotation marks), but if you do happen to get stuck and want to progress (without loading an earlier savegame), try it out - it is one way to free yourself (and the scientist… well, sort of).</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Ah, I didn’t realise you could use USE on the fire doors (in fact I could have sworn it didn’t work when I tried it).</p>
<p>Anyway, when I played it through I simply shot the trip-mine and ran under the door before it closed leaving the scientist behind but alive on the other side of the door.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/various-bugs/11257/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/various-bugs/11257/3</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 Oct 2012 22:48:04 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11257-3</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/various-bugs/11257.rss">Various bugs</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Various bugs</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Jenova19]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Metritutus">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/m/7bcc69/40.png" class="avatar"> Metritutus:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>-Snip-</p>
<p>*At the beginning of ‘We’ve got Hostiles!’, the glass to the door button is unbreakable until the scientist dies (ie, if you save him by destroying the laser-explosive before the scientist gets to it, you cannot get through the door without murdering the scientist first).</p>
<p>-Snip-</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">To 4. (unbreakable glass /w scientist):</span></p>
<p><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=-MkIhO8HCps" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Black Mesa: How-To “Save” The Scientist Being Stuck In We’ve Got Hostiles! - YouTube</a>  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=9" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
<p>It’s not really a “fix” (hence the quotation marks), but if you do happen to get stuck and want to progress (without loading an earlier savegame), try it out - it is one way to free yourself (and the scientist… well, sort of).</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/various-bugs/11257/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/various-bugs/11257/2</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 Oct 2012 20:02:03 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11257-2</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/various-bugs/11257.rss">Various bugs</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Various bugs</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Metritutus]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Meant to post this a week or so ago, when I was playing through the game I made a list of some bugs I encountered.  Not sure if some of these have already been posted or not as there’s pages of them, but hopefully they’re of some use:</p>
<p>*The keyboard options menu has an option for you to bind a key to the Gravity Gun.</p>
<p>*When the Zombie bursts out of the toilet just after the Resonance Cascade, you can interrupt its animation for getting up (it never does it, it INSTANTLY comes after you if you’re next to it).</p>
<p>*In the scripted sequence where the zombie starts to strangle the guard who beckons you over after mentioning that a headcrab has latched on to ‘his buddy’s head’, you cannot kill the zombie when it has started to strangle him, even when he asks for help.  There seems ample time to kill it, but it is indestructable during the sequence, you must kill it before it gets to the guard in order to save him</p>
<p>*At the beginning of ‘We’ve got Hostiles!’, the glass to the door button is unbreakable until the scientist dies (ie, if you save him by destroying the laser-explosive before the scientist gets to it, you cannot get through the door without murdering the scientist first).</p>
<p>*If a portable turret has an ‘ERROR’, when you try and move it you hold it by the very bottom of the very back foot rather than in the usual position.</p>
<p>*In the first encounter with the Assassins, after you have killed them all, if you reload a save, any save, the game’s performance is massively reduced.</p>
<p>*Reloading a save during the final Lamda Core teleporter part once it is partly running (blue laser, enemies spawning) seems to cause a massive performance drop.</p>
<p>*Scientist line “I don’t know how much more of this I can endure” - lips did not move</p>
<p>*If you release snarks directly below you, they do not/cannot move until you move.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/various-bugs/11257/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/various-bugs/11257/1</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 Oct 2012 18:04:09 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11257-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/various-bugs/11257.rss">Various bugs</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
