<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Long Term Fate of a Xenian Invasion</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/long-term-fate-of-a-xenian-invasion/14837</link>
    <description>Ok, I don&#39;t have any [i]formal[/i] training in tactics or military history, but I&#39;m wondering about whether, even if the Lambda scientists didn&#39;t destroy the Nihilanth, Xen would actually have been able to [i]succeed[/i] in an invasion of Earth.

We know that in Black Mesa the human military [i]was [/i]losing by the end of the game, but there&#39;s a number of factors that I think make the incident not representative of human-Xen warfare as a whole:
* The Resonance Cascade itself filled Black Mesa with[i] large[/i] reserves of pre-existing dead bodies for headcrabs to parasitize- I really don&#39;t think zombies could ever present any [i]serious[/i] threat to trained soldiers, especially if the latter are free to move about and stay out of the way of their claws, but they [i]do[/i] require some expenditure of ammo to bring down and can push squads out of safe or valuable positions.
* The military seems to have almost as difficult a time moving around the facility as the player does, while the Xenians can teleport basically anywhere within it.
* I don&#39;t think Freeman was singlehandedly responsible for the military pulling out or anything like that, or for that matter have any [i]real[/i] effect on their numbers, but he did seem to have a tendency to smash right through fortified positions, blow up walls, collapse tunnels, activate dangerous machinery, and just in general wreck any attempt at a coherent battle plan.
* For that matter, they were also facing reasonably organized resistance from the BM security staff, who aren&#39;t [i]terrible[/i] combatants and are a little better able to actually navigate the place.
* Perhaps most importantly, up until the very end of the game the military seems to want to secure different important objectives [i]inside[/i] of Black Mesa- possibly they&#39;re trying to get weapons research, etc., possibly they actually think they can clean out the facility and get it operational again. Either way, that means both that they have objectives they need to worry about [i]other[/i] than the Xenians, and that they have to hold back for fear of further damaging the place. The airstrikes don&#39;t happen until they&#39;ve been routed on the ground, after all, and if they&#39;d started out using their air power to its full effect things may have gone very differently.


I think that in a straight fight out in the open desert, the Xenians would actually end up [i]losing [/i]quite handily. It seems as though their biotechnology never actually developed effective explosives, and while their &quot;heavies&quot; (gargs and flyers) certainly seem impressive from Freeman&#39;s scale I don&#39;t think they&#39;re quite competitive with human tanks, etc. in terms of maneuverability, actual damage-on-targets, or availability. For that matter, those manta flyers don&#39;t seem to have very effective air-to-air weapons, so human air forces might be able to pretty easily get control of the airspace- and furthermore, that electrical attack seems to work pretty well on large, slow-moving targets, but I don&#39;t think it has the broad, infantry-killing area of effect that human explosive bombs do. Add to all of this the fact that Xen has to push [i]into[/i] human territory where we just have to defend, and the fact that I doubt they can teleport in ready-made fortifications, and I&#39;d conclude that even with a significant numerical disadvantage overall human military forces would be able to push a Xenian incursion back.

Of course, all of this is predicated on one assumption, which is implied but never confirmed- that the Xenians [i]can only teleport into the area around Black Mesa[/i]. If they can go anywhere on the planet, unless they were very stupid and expended all of their forces on a single assault I could only ever see the humans losing outright or managing an extremely Pyrrhic victory where major population centers end up under 24-hour armed watch for additional incursions.



Thoughts?</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 15 Aug 2016 20:35:06 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>The Cafeteria</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/long-term-fate-of-a-xenian-invasion/14837.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Long Term Fate of a Xenian Invasion</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Admiral_Sakai]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>According to Kleiner in one of his HL2 monologues, the whole event left behind a very small, contained portal to… somewhere. This is what the Combine used to get to Earth.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/long-term-fate-of-a-xenian-invasion/14837/38">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/long-term-fate-of-a-xenian-invasion/14837/38</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 15 Aug 2016 20:35:06 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14837-38</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/long-term-fate-of-a-xenian-invasion/14837.rss">Long Term Fate of a Xenian Invasion</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Long Term Fate of a Xenian Invasion</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Agent6]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Scorpion42">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/s/e495f1/40.png" class="avatar"> Scorpion42:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Not entirely on topic, but definitely related: What was the point of the Satellite Delivery Rocket from On A Rail?<br>
<a href="https://combineoverwiki.net/wiki/Black_Mesa_satellite" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://combineoverwiki.net/wiki/Black_Mesa_satellite</a><br>
It’s supposed to stop the invasion, but aliens keep warping in in the subsequent chapters, not to mention the Portal storms leading up to Half-Life 2…</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Yes, that was its purpose. However, as if was found out in Lambda Core, the portals couldn’t be shut down because something (Nihilanth) was keeping them open from the other side, thus the requirement to kill him to close them once and for all.</p>
<p>Or so they thought. The thing is, that didn’t seem to work at all, as the number of Portal Storms only increased, ultimately leading to the Combine invasion during the 7HW. Why, no idea.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/long-term-fate-of-a-xenian-invasion/14837/37">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/long-term-fate-of-a-xenian-invasion/14837/37</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 15 Aug 2016 18:22:58 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14837-37</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/long-term-fate-of-a-xenian-invasion/14837.rss">Long Term Fate of a Xenian Invasion</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Long Term Fate of a Xenian Invasion</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Massey]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I always assumed they had a similar mineral in it to what you start the cascade with, and that it’s able to redirect the power fluxes on earth back into space again. Turns the earth into a big ass Faraday cage, I guess.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/long-term-fate-of-a-xenian-invasion/14837/36">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/long-term-fate-of-a-xenian-invasion/14837/36</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 14 Aug 2016 06:01:55 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14837-36</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/long-term-fate-of-a-xenian-invasion/14837.rss">Long Term Fate of a Xenian Invasion</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Long Term Fate of a Xenian Invasion</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Admiral_Sakai]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>The holograms in Mission Control mention a “satellite portal array”, so it is likely somehow related to travel to and from Xen- and, therefore, the ultimate plan to destroy the Nihilanth. <span class="bbcode-i">How</span> satellites in orbit would help with that is anybody’s guess, as is the problem of how, if these satellites were so important, Black Mesa had been going to Xen without them for years.</p>
<p>It’s possible that the satellites orbiting the Earth are able to open portals to corresponding locations in Xen and thus provide a vantage point from which the Nihilanth could be located/identified, but that’s pure speculation.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/long-term-fate-of-a-xenian-invasion/14837/35">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/long-term-fate-of-a-xenian-invasion/14837/35</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 14 Aug 2016 00:50:49 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14837-35</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/long-term-fate-of-a-xenian-invasion/14837.rss">Long Term Fate of a Xenian Invasion</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Long Term Fate of a Xenian Invasion</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Scorpion42]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Not entirely on topic, but definitely related: What was the point of the Satellite Delivery Rocket from On A Rail?<br>
<a href="https://combineoverwiki.net/wiki/Black_Mesa_satellite" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://combineoverwiki.net/wiki/Black_Mesa_satellite</a><br>
It’s supposed to stop the invasion, but aliens keep warping in in the subsequent chapters, not to mention the Portal storms leading up to Half-Life 2…</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/long-term-fate-of-a-xenian-invasion/14837/34">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/long-term-fate-of-a-xenian-invasion/14837/34</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 13 Aug 2016 23:50:41 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14837-34</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/long-term-fate-of-a-xenian-invasion/14837.rss">Long Term Fate of a Xenian Invasion</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Long Term Fate of a Xenian Invasion</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Nova_Terra]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="AsinoEsel">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/user_avatar/leakfree.org/asinoesel/40/4348_2.png" class="avatar"> AsinoEsel:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Personally I’ve never really seen Gordon as the “good guy”. He’s definitely not the bad guy <span class="bbcode-b">(even less so in Half-Life 2</span>) but I wouldn’t call somebody who kills hundreds of marines a “good guy”. Even if they are murdering your friends / colleagues and planning on doing the same to you. Gordon can’t even be considered a hero in any way (not in the original at least), as his only concern is his own survival - something that made Half-Life so much more relatable and realistic in my opinion (I believe Valve was very much aware of this).<br>
<span class="bbcode-b">In Half-Life 2, as previously mentioned, the conflict between “good” and “bad” isn’t as complicated,</span> but it’s still there. After all, Gordon kills plenty of Civil Protection units in City17. (Remember: Civil Protection is <em>not</em> augmented or brainwashed in any way, they’re just normal ordinary people following the Combine’s orders for better living conditions.) Of course the Civil Protection are acting extremely immoral and cruel throughout the games, but they are not completely to blame for their behavior, just like the marines in Half-Life 1.</p>
<p>Secondly: Thanks for the hint! Xen is gonna be great.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>That’s why HL1 is much better than HL2 and especially Opposing Force when it’s even more complicated.Gordon is neutrall and playing on both sides and while in HL2 rebels are  good guys without doubt, but in EP1 you can hear that some rebels against combine but in the same time against Keiner rhetoric.Combine is the pure evil of course at least by our standarts and it will be interesing to see their main world,their buildings,nature,objectives in other worlds and on Earth and especially their true form and head.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/long-term-fate-of-a-xenian-invasion/14837/33">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/long-term-fate-of-a-xenian-invasion/14837/33</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 05 Jul 2016 08:27:32 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14837-33</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/long-term-fate-of-a-xenian-invasion/14837.rss">Long Term Fate of a Xenian Invasion</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Long Term Fate of a Xenian Invasion</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[AsinoEsel]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Personally I’ve never really seen Gordon as the “good guy”. He’s definitely not the bad guy (even less so in Half-Life 2) but I wouldn’t call somebody who kills hundreds of marines a “good guy”. Even if they are murdering your friends / colleagues and planning on doing the same to you. Gordon can’t even be considered a hero in any way (not in the original at least), as his only concern is his own survival - something that made Half-Life so much more relatable and realistic in my opinion (I believe Valve was very much aware of this).<br>
In Half-Life 2, as previously mentioned, the conflict between “good” and “bad” isn’t as complicated, but it’s still there. After all, Gordon kills plenty of Civil Protection units in City17. (Remember: Civil Protection is <em>not</em> augmented or brainwashed in any way, they’re just normal ordinary people following the Combine’s orders for better living conditions.) Of course the Civil Protection are acting extremely immoral and cruel throughout the games, but they are not completely to blame for their behavior, just like the marines in Half-Life 1.</p>
<p>Secondly: Thanks for the hint! Xen is gonna be great.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/long-term-fate-of-a-xenian-invasion/14837/32">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/long-term-fate-of-a-xenian-invasion/14837/32</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 05 Jul 2016 03:26:51 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14837-32</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/long-term-fate-of-a-xenian-invasion/14837.rss">Long Term Fate of a Xenian Invasion</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Long Term Fate of a Xenian Invasion</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Massey]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I’ve always looked at the resistance as the actual “good guys” but the scientists as the “good guys but did bad/wrong things and kinda got what they had coming” and that the rest of humanity kinda paid for that too.</p>
<p>As for the Xenians, I think they’re good, but we’re desperate to escape the Combine and acted out of fear and that desperation.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/long-term-fate-of-a-xenian-invasion/14837/31">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/long-term-fate-of-a-xenian-invasion/14837/31</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 05 Jul 2016 03:05:59 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14837-31</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/long-term-fate-of-a-xenian-invasion/14837.rss">Long Term Fate of a Xenian Invasion</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Long Term Fate of a Xenian Invasion</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[TextFAMGUY1]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>One of the fun things about Half-Life is that it’s got a lot of grey areas; whether intentional by Valve or not.</p>
<p>I mean, you still always know who the “bad guys” are because they’re the ones trying to kill you, but you’re never quite sure if your guys are pure and good either. And for the gentleman who requested a hint about where we’re going with Xen: yes, we are exploring the concept of scientists in Xen in some good depth. It will form a part of the Xen adventure.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/long-term-fate-of-a-xenian-invasion/14837/30">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/long-term-fate-of-a-xenian-invasion/14837/30</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 05 Jul 2016 02:50:24 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14837-30</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/long-term-fate-of-a-xenian-invasion/14837.rss">Long Term Fate of a Xenian Invasion</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Long Term Fate of a Xenian Invasion</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[AsinoEsel]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Exactly. The scientists didn’t have any right to just come to Xen and mess with its lifeforms and biotope just for the sake of scientific progress (well… mostly weapons research?), it’s really ignorant and somewhat questionable from an ethical viewpoint (Questionable Ethics anyone?). Reminds me of America’s colonialization in the 16th century… and that didn’t turn out too well for the natives, did it…</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/long-term-fate-of-a-xenian-invasion/14837/29">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/long-term-fate-of-a-xenian-invasion/14837/29</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 05 Jul 2016 02:11:36 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14837-29</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/long-term-fate-of-a-xenian-invasion/14837.rss">Long Term Fate of a Xenian Invasion</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Long Term Fate of a Xenian Invasion</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[drgibbles]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="General Gravel">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 General Gravel:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I don’t know about you, but I don’t think Humans are the bad guys in this story. Wallace Breen is a different case, Black Mesa may have been going to xen for a while and studying Xen fauna but that would not make sense to be the reason behind the invasion.</p>
<p>Black Mesa is definitely not an evil corporation like Umbrella from the Resident Evil Universe or Horzine from the Killing Floor Universe.  You could say that the invasion and all the destruction is the cost of progress.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I don’t think there has been any evil intent by any scientist, just a whole lot of ignorance , trying to run before learning to walk.  But at the same time, being manipulated by the G-man and his “employers”</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/long-term-fate-of-a-xenian-invasion/14837/28">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/long-term-fate-of-a-xenian-invasion/14837/28</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 05 Jul 2016 01:20:36 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14837-28</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/long-term-fate-of-a-xenian-invasion/14837.rss">Long Term Fate of a Xenian Invasion</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Long Term Fate of a Xenian Invasion</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[_rot_fodder]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>What if I told you Breen was actually the good guy, that the earth surrender was the only way to save the dimension and that when Gordon killed Breen, it prompted the Combine beings who were controlling the guys that were controlling the advisors to open a superportal to a black hole, essentially erasing the half-life-earth dimention’s solar system. When the game fades out at the end of Half life 2 episode 2, that was actually the portal being opened and the half life universe being wiped from existence.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/long-term-fate-of-a-xenian-invasion/14837/27">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/long-term-fate-of-a-xenian-invasion/14837/27</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 05 Jul 2016 00:51:08 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14837-27</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/long-term-fate-of-a-xenian-invasion/14837.rss">Long Term Fate of a Xenian Invasion</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Long Term Fate of a Xenian Invasion</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[General_Gravel]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I don’t know about you, but I don’t think Humans are the bad guys in this story. Wallace Breen is a different case, Black Mesa may have been going to xen for a while and studying Xen fauna but that would not make sense to be the reason behind the invasion.</p>
<p>Black Mesa is definitely not an evil corporation like Umbrella from the Resident Evil Universe or Horzine from the Killing Floor Universe.  You could say that the invasion and all the destruction is the cost of progress.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/long-term-fate-of-a-xenian-invasion/14837/26">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/long-term-fate-of-a-xenian-invasion/14837/26</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 05 Jul 2016 00:35:51 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14837-26</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/long-term-fate-of-a-xenian-invasion/14837.rss">Long Term Fate of a Xenian Invasion</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Long Term Fate of a Xenian Invasion</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[AsinoEsel]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Beautifully said.<br>
I’m actually really wondering how the devs are going to handle Xen regarding its exploitation (maybe a little hint Chon?  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/smiley.png?v=9" title=":smiley:" class="emoji" alt=":smiley:"> ). In Half-Life Blue Shift and Opposing Force you can see that the Black Mesa scientists have been stealing crystals and Xen’s native lifeforms and ruining the landscape with human technology cluttered everywhere. I really hope they expand on this idea further, showing the destruction of the Xenians’ natural habitat that the scientists have caused on Xen… makes you wonder whether the humans even are the “good guys” in Half-Life. After all, the aliens are just fighting for their survival themselves, and I doubt that the Xenian wildlife that’s teleporting to earth is invading our world with any motives in mind. They’re just (more or less randomly) being teleported in, first used by the Nihilanth as “military”, then later abused by the Combine for their own needs.<br>
<span class="hashtag">#spreadawarenessforheadcrabs</span></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/long-term-fate-of-a-xenian-invasion/14837/25">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/long-term-fate-of-a-xenian-invasion/14837/25</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 04 Jul 2016 23:35:55 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14837-25</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/long-term-fate-of-a-xenian-invasion/14837.rss">Long Term Fate of a Xenian Invasion</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Long Term Fate of a Xenian Invasion</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[drgibbles]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I think we were responsible for the invasion, by the xenians and the combine.  Xenians being enslaved, and or/soldiers.  We have been visiting xen for quite some time, and also, quite some time.(swidt)  We have been pulling critters from xen and who knows where.  When messing with space time and teleportation, we really don’t know the extent of the benefits/consequences from teleportation.  What we have seen though,  has been mostly catastrophic. From the initial invasion, to the 7 hour war.  A large amount of study has been done in bimolecular engineering and technology.  From some of the white boards, we can see that, not only are we dealing with an unknown number of alien species, but also, we are finding that there has been some tinkering under the hood.  Species  being altered for combat, toxin resistance, pretty much our worst nightmares.  From insect like features, to fully robotic implementations.  Now, looking at the Half-life, Black Mesa and Portal lore.  Time travel elements seem to be there, from events spanning thousands and thousands of years, to things being noticed all through Black Mesa from different time periods, real world events, pay wages by year, transportation disasters, posters from conventions in specific years.  But looking at it from another way, what if time travel isn’t happening.  What if its visiting multiple parallel universes, countless universes that have exactly the same string of events and timeline, mirroring our own, but just at different stages of time.  Like Portals PETI program. Then others that are slightly different than our own, to some that are radically different.  Eventually, things would start to get jumbled up.  From parallel universes at different times, crossing back and forth. There could be many Dr. Horns at the same time and over many different times.  We (Black Mesa Scientist) could very well be responsible for altering any number of alien species, crossing it with some of our own found in our reality,  being shipped back and forth through time and different reality’s, eventually leading to the combine.  The ieil, a combination of big brother, bigger brother, and our reality as we know it. An  Illuminati type class of species.  Ones that know what is going on behind the scenes, guiding different versions and timelines to do different things at different times.  A multi dimensional game of chess, being orchestrated by unknown forces.  An invasion would have to be planned, not just a spur of the moment event.</p>
<p>Our reality could be the ground zero for the creation of the combine and its invading forces…</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/long-term-fate-of-a-xenian-invasion/14837/24">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/long-term-fate-of-a-xenian-invasion/14837/24</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 04 Jul 2016 23:20:30 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14837-24</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/long-term-fate-of-a-xenian-invasion/14837.rss">Long Term Fate of a Xenian Invasion</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Long Term Fate of a Xenian Invasion</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[General_Gravel]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Sorry, I get excited when talking about Half-Life.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/long-term-fate-of-a-xenian-invasion/14837/23">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/long-term-fate-of-a-xenian-invasion/14837/23</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jun 2016 18:48:40 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14837-23</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/long-term-fate-of-a-xenian-invasion/14837.rss">Long Term Fate of a Xenian Invasion</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Long Term Fate of a Xenian Invasion</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[TextFAMGUY1]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>That is indeed a cool theory, and one I hadn’t considered.</p>
<p>And I agree that we should keep canonicity debates away from this thread, please. No more OP4/Blue Shift stuff please. Let’s talk about the Xenians, that’s a way more interesting discussion anyway. Canonicity debates are never ending in any fandom for anything, and are just never really that productive as everyone has their own headcanon for their favourite series.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/long-term-fate-of-a-xenian-invasion/14837/22">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/long-term-fate-of-a-xenian-invasion/14837/22</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jun 2016 06:22:01 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14837-22</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/long-term-fate-of-a-xenian-invasion/14837.rss">Long Term Fate of a Xenian Invasion</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Long Term Fate of a Xenian Invasion</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[General_Gravel]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>That is a cool theory.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/long-term-fate-of-a-xenian-invasion/14837/21">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/long-term-fate-of-a-xenian-invasion/14837/21</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jun 2016 15:55:41 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14837-21</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/long-term-fate-of-a-xenian-invasion/14837.rss">Long Term Fate of a Xenian Invasion</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Long Term Fate of a Xenian Invasion</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Admiral_Sakai]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>My theory is still that the Xenians were (in their minds, at least) <span class="bbcode-i">counter</span>attacking due to perceived abductions and incursions from Earth- after all, the Lambda Team had been going there for years already. I don’t think they would have stopped at Black Mesa, though. They probably considered humans enough of a threat to completely wipe out (plus they just in general seem pretty trigger-happy), although they may have drastically underestimated the size of the planet and the number of humans on it.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/long-term-fate-of-a-xenian-invasion/14837/20">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/long-term-fate-of-a-xenian-invasion/14837/20</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jun 2016 15:40:25 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14837-20</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/long-term-fate-of-a-xenian-invasion/14837.rss">Long Term Fate of a Xenian Invasion</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Long Term Fate of a Xenian Invasion</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[General_Gravel]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Do you really think Xenians came to Earth to literally dominate it?  They were just trying to escape by any means necessary with huge force. They may have been preparing to do this judging by the massive manufacturing of Alien Grunts and the factory like place from the chapter: Interloper.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/long-term-fate-of-a-xenian-invasion/14837/19">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/long-term-fate-of-a-xenian-invasion/14837/19</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jun 2016 15:21:05 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14837-19</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/long-term-fate-of-a-xenian-invasion/14837.rss">Long Term Fate of a Xenian Invasion</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Long Term Fate of a Xenian Invasion</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Admiral_Sakai]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Wow.</p>
<p>I wanted to limit the thread to the events of HL1 specifically to <span class="bbcode-i">prevent</span> this from happening…</p>
<p>Anyway, it looks like there’s a general consensus that the deciding variable is the ability of Xen to teleport. If they can only do it around Black Mesa, the humans win, and I’d say that holds true even if Xen’s numbers are vastly superior- they can only fit so many forces into BM at once, and the humans can put nukes and walls and all sorts of things around that specific area. If they can teleport anywhere, the humans lose- either they’re defeated outright, or the need to guard every square inch of space against teleportations fundamentally alters the world economy as we know it.</p>
<p>Race X really is very similar to Xen in its hardware (wetware?) and tactics, so I don’t think it would <span class="bbcode-i">really</span> alter the results one way or another.</p>
<p>Not sure what to go on from here, I was expecting there to be more debate over whether the Xenians would actually be able to win. However, as Cyan pointed out, I think the “feeling” I get regarding teleportation is that the area where Xen could actually do it was slowly <span class="bbcode-i">expanding</span> (possibly, larger and larger things could be sent through as well)- that means that if Lambda Core was not around to shut down the whole process, the situation would have ended up very much like the default Xenian victory condition.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/long-term-fate-of-a-xenian-invasion/14837/18">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/long-term-fate-of-a-xenian-invasion/14837/18</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jun 2016 15:12:47 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14837-18</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/long-term-fate-of-a-xenian-invasion/14837.rss">Long Term Fate of a Xenian Invasion</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Long Term Fate of a Xenian Invasion</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[General_Gravel]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I have the same opinion as Nova Terra, I consider all Half-Life games canon since those expansions don’t affect the storyline to a point where everybody hates it and are disappointed with it, it’s a fact that Valve doesn’t like to talk.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/long-term-fate-of-a-xenian-invasion/14837/17">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/long-term-fate-of-a-xenian-invasion/14837/17</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jun 2016 14:21:11 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14837-17</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/long-term-fate-of-a-xenian-invasion/14837.rss">Long Term Fate of a Xenian Invasion</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Long Term Fate of a Xenian Invasion</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Massey]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Ehh OP4/BS are kinda hit or miss for canon bits. They’ve never confirmed nor denied the entire plot lines for those games, but they’ve admitted a couple bits are ok.</p>
<p>As for my opinion- I feel that if you placed a unit of Xenian combatants (likely 3 vorts, 2 grunts, 2 squids, and a small group of zombies) against a unit of HECU/DOD troops (similar numbers, but obviously they’re all multi-skilled and such so there isn’t “classes”), the HECU/DOD troops would win, with maybe a couple casualties.</p>
<p>Howeveeerrrrrr…Nihilanth is able to basically put his guys wherever the hell he wants in a specific area, and I believe as the game goes on that area grows. That’s what gets the attention of the Combine (that’s all I’m saying on them, I know this is about xenians, but I just remembered reading about how they took notice of the growing portals on earth and took advantage.)</p>
<p>Anyways, with that ability, like TextFamGuy said, it makes it hard to coordinate counter-attacks and even assaults against enemy positions. Imagine trying to plan an attack on nothing in the hopes that SOMETHING appears. Basically, that’d be our tactics.</p>
<p>If Nihilanth and the Xenian forces (of which we can see no direct example of how many there are, but we can see they’re “expendable” and easy enough to make more of) went head to head directly against the DOD and HECU’s, I believe that the Xenians would win with their Gurilla style teleporting in and out and their cannon fodder/easy to replace with new grunts abilities. Not to mention, like TextFamGuy said, watching your buddies get zombified would be fucking gross and terrifying and very, very demoralizing to see, so that wouldn’t help.</p>
<p>BUT. If the teleporting was taken from the aliens, this would probably be a much different fight, one we’d likely win.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/long-term-fate-of-a-xenian-invasion/14837/16">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/long-term-fate-of-a-xenian-invasion/14837/16</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jun 2016 12:46:55 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14837-16</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/long-term-fate-of-a-xenian-invasion/14837.rss">Long Term Fate of a Xenian Invasion</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Long Term Fate of a Xenian Invasion</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Nova_Terra]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Opposing Force and Blue Shift are canons since we have a nuke,Barney from Blue Shift that were used in HL2 plot.So,we can assume that the whole OpFor and Blue Shift games are canons,especially since we heard a conversation in Blue Shift about the dirty work that Shephard can’t do and it would be strange to have Barney,nuke in sequel and deny existence of  A.Shephard,X-Race etc.Only plot hole that I can’t accept about OpFor that we didn’t kill the scientists and securities aren’t immediately shooting us because they have no idea are we good or evil.Shepard didn’t recieve an order to kill them because his commaner died in helicopter crash is BS since we have enough soldiers in facility which can tell us about the order.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/long-term-fate-of-a-xenian-invasion/14837/15">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/long-term-fate-of-a-xenian-invasion/14837/15</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jun 2016 08:51:29 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14837-15</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/long-term-fate-of-a-xenian-invasion/14837.rss">Long Term Fate of a Xenian Invasion</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Long Term Fate of a Xenian Invasion</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Agent6]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="(rot)(fodder">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 (rot)(fodder:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Remember what Gearbox did to the Aliens canon? Gearbox does not come into this discussion.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Please don’t remind me about that abomination X_X. I had such high expectations due to the E3 presentations only get a painful slap over my face. Oh and btw, they also own DN now, which you surely know, to make matters worse, and apparently are working on a new version of DN3D. For some reason I expect their port to be a total disaster.</p>
<p>Like, literally, I think the only games they still know how to make are Borderlands and <span class="bbcode-i"><span class="bbcode-b">maybe</span></span> HL expansions (well OP4 and BS were good).</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="darkone">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/user_avatar/leakfree.org/darkone/40/4296_2.png" class="avatar"> darkone:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>yeah the only things they gave us that are KNOWN, canon as I mentioned are the nuke, Adrian shephard, and the black ops teams. race X is questionable at best, valve stated that if they find a way to use them they will but that is unlikely. And shephard is something even valve has stated tehy want to use but can’t find a reason. Keep in mind he is in temporal cryo do to gman.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Sorry for bringing OP4 into the discussion in this case. To my knowledge, both BS and OP4 were entirely cannon, but I guess I was mistaken.</p>
<p>That’s basically just an intention. Given how much interest they’ve put into HL in the past decade, I find it hard to believe that will ever come to fruition…</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/long-term-fate-of-a-xenian-invasion/14837/14">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/long-term-fate-of-a-xenian-invasion/14837/14</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jun 2016 07:33:20 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14837-14</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/long-term-fate-of-a-xenian-invasion/14837.rss">Long Term Fate of a Xenian Invasion</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
