<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Surface Tension Apache At Cliffs</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/surface-tension-apache-at-cliffs/9888</link>
    <description>I just want to point out that in Surface Tension, the section where you get attacked by the Apache while traversing the cliffs, it&#39;s not very well designed. In fact, it&#39;s very badly designed for the following four reasons:

1. There&#39;s no reason why it should take as much as 15 rockets to take out the Apache.

2. There&#39;s no reason why there should be an infinite rocket ammo crate there.

3. There&#39;s no reason why the Apache should be a carbon copy of the Half Life 2 gunship.

4. There&#39;s no reason why that section should be frustrating at all. The player gets hit completely randomly, even when sitting behind hard cover. Because this section drags on for such a long time, by the end of it, the player is almost dead or already dead, even if he was sitting behind hard cover all the time.

It&#39;s not hard to make this section less frustrating, more original, while keeping it challenging. Just do  the following:

- Make it so the gunship goes down quicker, like with 4 rocket hits.

- Remove all rocket pickups prior to arriving at this section. Remove the infinite rocket crate and replace it with 5 or 6 rockets. Also, maybe add 1 or 2 Gauss ammo as a backup means to take out the gunship.

- Remove the sound before the gunship fires its cannon. There&#39;s no need for it. This should ensure the encounter stays challenging and doesn&#39;t rip off the Half Life 2 gunship so much.

- Add a better sound for the Apache cannon. One that sounds more impressive and is better quality.

Until such changes are made. I recommend to everyone to put on godmode once you start this section, so that you don&#39;t get frustrated and you can quickly get to the fun part again.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 15 Sep 2012 19:58:22 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>In-game Issues (Mod)</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/surface-tension-apache-at-cliffs/9888.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Surface Tension Apache At Cliffs</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[BlackAlpha]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="sersoft">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/user_avatar/leakfree.org/sersoft/40/5837_2.png" class="avatar"> sersoft:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I found out that you have to hide behind very specific cover, a pile of ammo boxes closer to the cave entrance and not the infinite ammo crate. Also use the tau cannon.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I was hiding behind the rocks, on the opposite side of the infinite rocket box.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/surface-tension-apache-at-cliffs/9888/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/surface-tension-apache-at-cliffs/9888/5</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 15 Sep 2012 19:58:22 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9888-5</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/surface-tension-apache-at-cliffs/9888.rss">Surface Tension Apache At Cliffs</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Surface Tension Apache At Cliffs</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[MrrBon]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>How do you activate god mode? Also, my game wont let select the gauss gun (even though I have it and can pick up ammo) do you know of any cheat to force give me it or something?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/surface-tension-apache-at-cliffs/9888/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/surface-tension-apache-at-cliffs/9888/4</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 15 Sep 2012 16:20:58 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9888-4</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/surface-tension-apache-at-cliffs/9888.rss">Surface Tension Apache At Cliffs</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Surface Tension Apache At Cliffs</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Solokiller]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I didn’t realize there was an infinite ammo crate there O.O.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/surface-tension-apache-at-cliffs/9888/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/surface-tension-apache-at-cliffs/9888/3</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 15 Sep 2012 16:14:42 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9888-3</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/surface-tension-apache-at-cliffs/9888.rss">Surface Tension Apache At Cliffs</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Surface Tension Apache At Cliffs</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[sersoft]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I found out that you have to hide behind very specific cover, a pile of ammo boxes closer to the cave entrance and not the infinite ammo crate. Also use the tau cannon.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/surface-tension-apache-at-cliffs/9888/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/surface-tension-apache-at-cliffs/9888/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 15 Sep 2012 15:59:26 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9888-2</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/surface-tension-apache-at-cliffs/9888.rss">Surface Tension Apache At Cliffs</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Surface Tension Apache At Cliffs</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[BlackAlpha]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I just want to point out that in Surface Tension, the section where you get attacked by the Apache while traversing the cliffs, it’s not very well designed. In fact, it’s very badly designed for the following four reasons:</p>
<ol>
<li>
<p>There’s no reason why it should take as much as 15 rockets to take out the Apache.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>There’s no reason why there should be an infinite rocket ammo crate there.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>There’s no reason why the Apache should be a carbon copy of the Half Life 2 gunship.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>There’s no reason why that section should be frustrating at all. The player gets hit completely randomly, even when sitting behind hard cover. Because this section drags on for such a long time, by the end of it, the player is almost dead or already dead, even if he was sitting behind hard cover all the time.</p>
</li>
</ol>
<p>It’s not hard to make this section less frustrating, more original, while keeping it challenging. Just do  the following:</p>
<ul>
<li>
<p>Make it so the gunship goes down quicker, like with 4 rocket hits.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Remove all rocket pickups prior to arriving at this section. Remove the infinite rocket crate and replace it with 5 or 6 rockets. Also, maybe add 1 or 2 Gauss ammo as a backup means to take out the gunship.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Remove the sound before the gunship fires its cannon. There’s no need for it. This should ensure the encounter stays challenging and doesn’t rip off the Half Life 2 gunship so much.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Add a better sound for the Apache cannon. One that sounds more impressive and is better quality.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<p>Until such changes are made. I recommend to everyone to put on godmode once you start this section, so that you don’t get frustrated and you can quickly get to the fun part again.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/surface-tension-apache-at-cliffs/9888/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/surface-tension-apache-at-cliffs/9888/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 15 Sep 2012 15:24:14 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9888-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/surface-tension-apache-at-cliffs/9888.rss">Surface Tension Apache At Cliffs</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
