<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Really bad balancing</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/really-bad-balancing/9703</link>
    <description>I can appreciate that the game should be challenging. I actually like it. But certain aspects are really bullshit, to be honest. This game wasn&#39;t lacking for time to beta test, but on normal difficulty, the soldiers are too accurate and do WAY too much damage. I have to reload zones multiple times because two half-missing bursts will take me from 98/75 down to 60/0, and one more burst from there leaves me at 20.

The guns are also really poor feeling. The shotgun and pistol do their jobs, but the .357 feels fiddly and inaccurate (iknorite?) and the combat rifle has too small of a clip to kill two soldiers, even when you are hitting every round home, along with too poor of an accuracy compared to their OWN rifles.

Zombies hit hard enough, headcrabs are really hard to hit for some reason with anything but the crowbar (I used to hit those little bastards midair with a pistol) and I feel the chargeup time on the vortigaunts is too fast, and does too little damage. I like the bullsquid spray, but with every ranged monster, bullsquids a slight exception, I feel like I can NEVER get the kill without taking a guaranteed hit or ten. it just isn&#39;t that tactical feeling, when it really should be (the AI is great!)

My only concern with almost everything&#39;s AI (soldier in particular) is that they respond to your presence way too fast. Add a minor, 0.2-0.5 second delay before a monster recognizes your presence, because their reaction speed is so computer-tastic that they always get the first shot off, even when they shouldn&#39;t. I don&#39;t feel satisfied or rewarded for good shots or good play, like I do in HL1 or other games where my good aim and suprise attacks leave my opponents wrecked and me without a scratch. the first time I felt like I did something cool was sending a satchel charge up the lift in power up. I then had to reload five times because every time a soldier that I knew precisely where he was, at about 20 yards, just as I round the corner to clock him with a .357 round, he and his mates manage to pump a full burst into me and take off all of my suit power and half of my health. It&#39;s just not fun having to redo fights simply because the AI is better than you can possibly be.

Hopefully this can be taken as constructive criticism. Patch the combat rifle&#39;s clip to 50,  increase the accuracy just a tiny bit, improve the .357&#39;s accuracy dramatically and take that stupid iron sights motion out (it&#39;s just so out of place it&#39;s laughable) and increase the vortigaunt charge time and damage to where we can kill them before they shoot if we see them first, as well as take the soldier combat rifle damage down a ton, as well as ding the accuracy they have about 5-10%. The combat rifle soldiers should NOT feel as terrifying at any range as the shotgun wielding ones are when their barrel is six inches away from your face!

Also, make the blast pit tentacles more distractable. grenades should distract them for more seconds, and they should have more random patterns of banging. I was more successful just sprinting, which felt dumb.



(this feedback is based on gameplay up to on a rail)</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2014 17:49:33 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>In-game Issues (Mod)</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/really-bad-balancing/9703.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Really bad balancing</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Kaleidescoop]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I feel that a way to balance the glock, MP5, and marines would be to seperate the damage like in the original (I think so, at least).  Like, have a 9mm for the Glock and a 9mm_AR for the MP5.</p>
<p>EDIT: Crap, just realised that nobody had posted in this thread since june.  Sorry!</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/really-bad-balancing/9703/296">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/really-bad-balancing/9703/296</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2014 17:49:33 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9703-296</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/really-bad-balancing/9703.rss">Really bad balancing</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Really bad balancing</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[coldroll]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I 100% agree with the Bull squids they are much more challenging to fight than the one’s in Hal-Life. I wish they’d make them spit acid in a small ball, like they did in the original instead of the huge ball of acid in Black Mesa. I also thought is was kind of weird giving them the same kind eyes as the Vortigaunts. But it still looks good none the less. Other than that I thought the Bull squid was well done .</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/really-bad-balancing/9703/295">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/really-bad-balancing/9703/295</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jun 2014 05:39:04 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9703-295</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/really-bad-balancing/9703.rss">Really bad balancing</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Really bad balancing</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Medkit]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>In part, I agree.  With the proper use MP5 is quite a handy weapon. On the other hand,  the weapon is cleary less effective against the marines than it was in Half-Life.  Especially in the early chapters it’s safer to take out the marines with either the Magnum, or camping behind the door - with the superfast and attack interrupting crowbar. Marines and mp5 are the most inbalanced in the game.</p>
<p>Regarding our beloved vortigaunts, I think one can get used to them the way they are.  As for the Bullsquids, now those are way better this time. They give us sufficent challange, while in Half-Life they are effectively harmless.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/really-bad-balancing/9703/294">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/really-bad-balancing/9703/294</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2014 12:58:15 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9703-294</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/really-bad-balancing/9703.rss">Really bad balancing</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Really bad balancing</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[dky.tehkingd.u]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>You can take on a large group of HECU with nothing but an MP5. You just need some cover and an idea of the correct way to use it.</p>
<p>Most people just spray it. That’s not how you’re supposed to use it. You need to burst-fire at the neck and pull down with your wrist. If you do that, you can drop a grunt in 3 to 5 bursts at mid-range on Hard, while taking relatively little damage from him in return (because you actually have an accuracy advantage versus HECU, no matter what difficulty).</p>
<p>This gets much harder if you’re getting flanked. So the trick is to try and lure them out from a single direction so that you never have to watch your back for random flankers. In some areas this is easy, in others, not so much. That’s what makes it fun.  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=9" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/really-bad-balancing/9703/293">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/really-bad-balancing/9703/293</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2014 05:36:30 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9703-293</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/really-bad-balancing/9703.rss">Really bad balancing</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Really bad balancing</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Dalek]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I edited the mp5 to have a 50 round magazine, and it feels way more balanced</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/really-bad-balancing/9703/292">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/really-bad-balancing/9703/292</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 22 Jun 2014 22:27:29 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9703-292</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/really-bad-balancing/9703.rss">Really bad balancing</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Really bad balancing</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[AMX679]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Givekidsmeth">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/g/50afbb/40.png" class="avatar"> Givekidsmeth:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>The guns are also really poor feeling. The shotgun and pistol do their jobs, but the .357 feels fiddly and inaccurate (iknorite?) and the combat rifle has too small of a clip to kill two soldiers, even when you are hitting every round home, along with too poor of an accuracy compared to their OWN rifles.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Have you ever played Half-life 2? The .357 magnum could be horrible! I like the Black Mesa one because of the increase of acuracy (don’t like the sight, though).</p>
<p>The mp5 cannot do anything with multiple solders. I like the half-life SMG since it has more ammo and the grenade launcher feels better to fire in general.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/really-bad-balancing/9703/291">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/really-bad-balancing/9703/291</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 22 Jun 2014 13:26:41 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9703-291</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/really-bad-balancing/9703.rss">Really bad balancing</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Really bad balancing</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[rikt]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Great thanks!</p>
<p>Much better like this…</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/really-bad-balancing/9703/290">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/really-bad-balancing/9703/290</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2013 22:12:35 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9703-290</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/really-bad-balancing/9703.rss">Really bad balancing</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Really bad balancing</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[MSKyuuni]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>^Don’t worry, it’s not like in Half-Life. Just change it in the options menu.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/really-bad-balancing/9703/289">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/really-bad-balancing/9703/289</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2013 21:37:59 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9703-289</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/really-bad-balancing/9703.rss">Really bad balancing</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Really bad balancing</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[rikt]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Do you know if there´s any way to change the difficulty after you start the game or you have to start from the beginning again?</p>
<p>I started on normal, which is usually ok, but on this games it´s actually not ok. It takes me a lot of time to go through some areas. Reload, reload, reload and so on.</p>
<p>Thanks.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/really-bad-balancing/9703/288">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/really-bad-balancing/9703/288</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2013 18:46:28 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9703-288</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/really-bad-balancing/9703.rss">Really bad balancing</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Really bad balancing</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Desolatemm]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="fuegerstef">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/f/a4c791/40.png" class="avatar"> fuegerstef:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Wow, some people never fail to amaze.</p>
<p>I have seen lot’s of stupid things on gaming forums. This one is close to the winner.</p>
<p>It is NOT the users job to balance out gameplay. It is the developers job (PS: I am one, professional, btw).</p>
<p>Just give every enemy 1 healthpoint. I mean, the player can shoot five times into the air before aiming at the enemy and let himself hit 3 times before shooting at that enemy. That way the user isn’t forced into a playstyle and can make the game challeging. BTW: what drugs made thinking challeging to you ?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>All he is saying is that if a weapon is too easy to use, try something a bit more challenging.</p>
<p>Take Dead Space for example. This game was done very well with one exception, all you EVER need is the first gun in the game, the plasma cutter. Anything else might have been better suited for one situation or another, but all you needed was that ONE weapon. With all the game development, testing, and design from a huge company like EA, they still had this issue when the game released.</p>
<p>At least in Black Mesa you have to use other weapons depending on your situation.</p>
<p>Weapon balance is a much bigger issue when playing in multiplayer games. How is the weapon balance in multiplayer? do you see the same issues there? Is there a weapon that everyone seems to use because it always wins?</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="bbsiteuser">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/b/8baadc/40.png" class="avatar"> bbsiteuser:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>“critique” like ‘your shotgun sucks!’, ‘your mp5 sucks’, ‘your  sucks’ does not necessarily make the sun rise in any developers mood.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>To devs:<br>
Your G17 is boss, haven’t seen a better model for that gun in a game to date.<br>
Your .357 is perfect, love the sights, shoots true like a chap.<br>
Your MP5 sprays like crazy, but I still love it.<br>
Your SPAS-12 is a beast, find I have to constantly fall back to it to win the day. (my favorite gun in BF3 BTW).<br>
Your Crossbow is… well… a crossbow. Kills them dead good.<br>
Your Tau Cannon was an honor to wield and explode organics with.<br>
Your Gluon Gun was breathtaking and a hoot to fire every time. I only wish it has infinity energy as I run down the halls screaming like a celtic warrior into battle.<br>
Your RPG helped me get revenge against that Apache that made me rage again and again at the damn dam scene.<br>
Your Grenades were useful in rooting those sniper posts.<br>
Your Satchel Charges were great for crowd control. Popping out of the sewer tunnels and throwing a charge at 3 unsuspecting soldiers was a great moment.<br>
Your Snarks were fun to watch eat at those two soldiers. Although I never picked them up for some reason… Never found them in game… Will look next time<br>
Your Trip mines… well I never used a single one so… next time. would have been useful though!<br>
Your TOW was very creative.<br>
Your Mortar was like playing a C130 game on the iPad. Lots of fun. I look forward to using this in Half Life every time.<br>
Your .50 Cal hurt me very badly. Also hurt a lot of soldiers and aliens! The sound was great!<br>
Your Hive Hand was actually useable. I never used this weapon in the original HL. Was a lot of fun in BM<br>
Your Crowbar… saved me a lot of ammo…<br>
Your Exploding Barrels were very useful in trolling the enemy!<br>
IMHO</p>
<p>I guess my playstyle is more “I wonder if I can do this with this gun” or “Lets try to roll exploding barrels to key places and kill everything”</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="bbsiteuser">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/b/8baadc/40.png" class="avatar"> bbsiteuser:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Thanks for the mod, BMS-team, thanks for the patience, readers  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=9" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"><br>
(being not a native speaker, pls, excuse punctuation and erros)</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>That was a very nice and enlightening response (didn’t want to quote the whole thing), but honestly BRAVO</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/really-bad-balancing/9703/287">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/really-bad-balancing/9703/287</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 15 Oct 2012 22:43:07 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9703-287</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/really-bad-balancing/9703.rss">Really bad balancing</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Really bad balancing</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[bbsiteuser]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>In short: it is one of the most awesome, inspired, detailed and ambitious mods/games that i have witnessed so far. The levels are just wonderfully modeled and textured, the music is devine and where the dev-team/designers have left the paths of the original game, they did with expertise and ton of great ideas and wit.</p>
<p>But where there is a lot of light, there also is shadow … which brings us to …</p>
<p>The looong sermon:<br>
I/we am/are running a little game-studio here, all of us HUGE HL1/2-fans and so a test group of 5 persons was immediately assembled (skill above avg to really good).</p>
<p>My main personal problem with the mod is: What’s the target group?</p>
<p>If it is made for hardcore CounterStrikers, well, excellent! That’s what these guys &amp; girls need and want.</p>
<p>If it is made for broad public: the designers and developers may have missed their target.</p>
<p>All of my testers, including me, love the mod - love it NOW! After having played it 4 times minimum on all difficulty settings. But the first time around it was like a brawl in Gomorrha, ppl cursing the developers to infinity and back  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=9" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"> )</p>
<p>In a nutshell: the 1st time around we all were really frustrated at times (dying 20+ times and not even at Blast Pit). Speaking only for myself, one of the eeriest things I can encounter is something I TOTALLY LUUURVE, but which doesn’t let me get “in sync” with it. But let me say: I synced into the mod the 2nd time around, coz I didn’t expect it to be a total likeness of HL1 anymore. Once I had accepted that the BMS-team was partly doing their own thing, I played it like it was a new game to me and it all got a lot easier.</p>
<p>But even without that, the fact that nobody even considered abandoning the test is a rock-solid testimony to the superlative level of immersion the developers/designers have achieved.</p>
<p>On the other hand, I cannot fully subscribe to some points that developers have made in this thread: “the guy who wrote the music” (GREAT! work, btw) suggests to lay low and use items to achieve your goal. That shifts BMS too much into the genre of a “semi-tactical” shooter for me, coz it’s not what I have “learned” in HL1. Then again, playing it the sneaksy way (which I enjoy a lot) is not really possible as the enemies are super-observant and each encounter with foes results in a furious fight.</p>
<p>What I am saying is: I haven’t found much opportunity to outwit opponents and stealth-kill them or take them by surprise (Crossbow/357 aside, which i do not use in BMS, which I find quite ok as I do not like sniper-action much, not in a HL1 mod that is).</p>
<p>I actually WANT to run into a room full of soldiers, blazing guns and all, and I expect to live … to live, coz I took them by surprise. But this is simply not possible (partly due to the Source Engine).</p>
<p>But enough of that banter. What we all need to understand is that the BMS team fulfilled THEIR dream. They sure have thought about every single aspect that has been mentioned in this thread long and thoroughly and they made their decision for their “baby”, knowing that accolades and critiques alike will be theirs too.</p>
<p>Upon us gamers falls the honor of reporting back to the developers and doing so I’d like to finish by saying: Let’s tread lightly and treat them with the respect they deserve. Having read the 15 pages of this thread, I can assure you - as a developer - that after years of hard work, “critique” like ‘your shotgun sucks!’, ‘your mp5 sucks’, ‘your  sucks’ does not necessarily make the sun rise in any developers mood.</p>
<p>I am also positively convinced that the BMS-team will blow us away with an update including many fixes for many players and with a full Xen-chapter that will be certainly up to par with everything up to LamdaCore.</p>
<p>Thanks for the mod, BMS-team, thanks for the patience, readers  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=9" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"><br>
(being not a native speaker, pls, excuse punctuation and erros)</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/really-bad-balancing/9703/286">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/really-bad-balancing/9703/286</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 15 Oct 2012 21:07:19 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9703-286</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/really-bad-balancing/9703.rss">Really bad balancing</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Really bad balancing</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[fuegerstef]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="raiseer">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/r/a587f6/40.png" class="avatar"> raiseer:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Hm, silly suggestion: Choose for yourself whether to use the hivehand or not. If you find it to be overpowered, don’t use it. If you find it practical, use it. Why is it the developer’s job to force you into a playstyle? Do what you want instead of complaining about what you could do but don’t want to.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Wow, some people never fail to amaze.</p>
<p>I have seen lot’s of stupid things on gaming forums. This one is close to the winner.</p>
<p>It is NOT the users job to balance out gameplay. It is the developers job (PS: I am one, professional, btw).</p>
<p>Just give every enemy 1 healthpoint. I mean, the player can shoot five times into the air before aiming at the enemy and let himself hit 3 times before shooting at that enemy. That way the user isn’t forced into a playstyle and can make the game challeging. BTW: what drugs made thinking challeging to you ?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/really-bad-balancing/9703/285">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/really-bad-balancing/9703/285</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 11 Oct 2012 04:38:03 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9703-285</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/really-bad-balancing/9703.rss">Really bad balancing</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Really bad balancing</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Comrade_Tiki]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>It’s hard to keep track of how many houndeye remains I’ve tossed to the abyss.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/really-bad-balancing/9703/284">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/really-bad-balancing/9703/284</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 10 Oct 2012 07:49:22 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9703-284</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/really-bad-balancing/9703.rss">Really bad balancing</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Really bad balancing</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Unit24]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="k3nny1550">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/user_avatar/leakfree.org/k3nny1550/40/4952_2.png" class="avatar"> k3nny1550:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>You can also pick up gibs. I particularly enjoy throwing around human grunt torsos.</p>
<p>Yes, I’m a freak.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Then we’re all freaks, because picking up and tossing around mangled corpses for giggles is one of the most fun side activities in the game.</p>
<p>I’m trying to imagine Gordon tossing corpses over ledges and into walls, giggling like a schoolgirl as he does so. It’s not a pretty sight.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/really-bad-balancing/9703/283">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/really-bad-balancing/9703/283</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 10 Oct 2012 07:14:33 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9703-283</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/really-bad-balancing/9703.rss">Really bad balancing</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Really bad balancing</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[k3nny1550]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="lunertexcosmo">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/l/2acd7d/40.png" class="avatar"> lunertexcosmo:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>You can pick up Houndeyes.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>You can also pick up gibs. I particularly enjoy throwing around human grunt torsos.</p>
<p>Yes, I’m a freak.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/really-bad-balancing/9703/282">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/really-bad-balancing/9703/282</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 10 Oct 2012 06:49:48 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9703-282</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/really-bad-balancing/9703.rss">Really bad balancing</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Really bad balancing</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Fendleton]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I think the grenades point is a fair issue. While I’m kinda glad squad leaders no longer spam 40mm grenades at me (pretty sure they don’t use them at all in Black Mesa), the increased speed of the shot would make dodging HARD. But the standard “ambassador pineapple” grenade? I’ve had playthroughs where they’ve tossed a few grenades, but an alarming number where I’ve never faced a grenade (I don’t count grenades that are thrown at the wrong place by the AI)… The soldier AI is generally really good, and I love the balance of the MP5 (not so keen on the enforced minimum-burst, but eh, it’s not that bad), but switching them to use grenades a little more, and use their guns slightly less (and be a little slower on the uptake to make surprise attacks work better) might work wonders. That said, I quite like the fast reaction times, so slowing them down too much  could be an issue.</p>
<p>Currently I feel that Easy mode is too easy, Normal is a little too hard, and I haven’t tried Hard yet.</p>
<p>One big problem I do find is with Snarks. They’re frankly adorable little critters…but they’re not that useful. I can generally use them at some point, since I got pretty good with them in Half Life and can see “Hey, if I throw ten of them in, I don’t have to waste my much more valuable ammo for [insertgunthatisn’tthehivehandhere]”… but they’re always just a “well, they’re useless anywhere else” weapon. They feel like they’re there because they’re in the original, rather than being there because they’re needed. This is probably due to the cut areas in Surface Tension…a few more nests of them, and some places where using them is the best way to get through to the next area would have made them feel more worthwhile. They’re really well done (as a biology student, I love cute little things that will gladly kill you), but there’s only a few places to use them.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/really-bad-balancing/9703/281">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/really-bad-balancing/9703/281</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 10 Oct 2012 02:41:38 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9703-281</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/really-bad-balancing/9703.rss">Really bad balancing</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Really bad balancing</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Unit24]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="raiseer">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/r/a587f6/40.png" class="avatar"> raiseer:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Hm, silly suggestion: Choose for yourself whether to use the hivehand or not. If you find it to be overpowered, don’t use it. If you find it practical, use it. Why is it the developer’s job to force you into a playstyle? Do what you want instead of complaining about what you could do but don’t want to.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Ensuring that the combat is balanced is the developers’ job. If something is overpowered or underpowered, you should always point it out. For instance, why are the snarks so horribly useless? You only get them once, and it’s later than in the original. And they can barely do anything.</p>
<p>I really don’t get this mindset of “if there’s something you don’t like, shut up and deal with it”. Everyone should report what they did or didn’t like. Devs need input from players. It’s how games get better.</p>
<p>Regarding the soldiers, after playing the game some more, I have come to the conclusion that this isn’t an issue of having “too much” difficulty, so much as it is about “wrong” difficulty. The soldiers would be more fun if they threw more grenades or moved around more, rather than have insane reaction times and accuracy. Most of the time, they don’t even bother moving much. Once I’m in view, they’ll usually just stand in place, aim at me, and hold the trigger. Even when I’m in cover, they’ll almost never throw grenades. Even the Combine soldiers were more interesting, because at least they looked like they were doing stuff.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/really-bad-balancing/9703/280">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/really-bad-balancing/9703/280</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 09 Oct 2012 23:26:25 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9703-280</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/really-bad-balancing/9703.rss">Really bad balancing</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Really bad balancing</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[raiseer]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Hm, silly suggestion: Choose for yourself whether to use the hivehand or not. If you find it to be overpowered, don’t use it. If you find it practical, use it. Why is it the developer’s job to force you into a playstyle? Do what you want instead of complaining about what you could do but don’t want to.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/really-bad-balancing/9703/279">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/really-bad-balancing/9703/279</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 09 Oct 2012 11:20:46 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9703-279</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/really-bad-balancing/9703.rss">Really bad balancing</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Really bad balancing</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Leijonasisu]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="quadpl">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/q/c5a1d2/40.png" class="avatar"> quadpl:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>The kind of “noob” that knows how to strategically use it. The homing hornets make it easy to pick off enemies whenever they are spread out. The rapid fire is good whenever enemies are stationary and firing/preparing to fire at you. The slow ammo regeneration keeps it from being overpowered so you still have to find cover.</p>
<p>I found it particularly useful to pick off barnacles and headcrabs as well as a handful of vorts on catwalks.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Right because after you get the hivehand you’re totally supposed to abandon every other weapon in the game. Hence why the devs continued to include various types of other weapon’s ammunition throughout further levels! /sarcasm</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/really-bad-balancing/9703/278">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/really-bad-balancing/9703/278</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 04 Oct 2012 10:38:13 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9703-278</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/really-bad-balancing/9703.rss">Really bad balancing</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Really bad balancing</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Unit24]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="No Stress">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 No Stress:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I’ve been playing Black Mesa on Hard and nothing else, and I like the challenge.</p>
<p>So to all those who complain about Normal being too hard, why not just go to easy? I’m tired of the Half-life series being way too easy on hard, so for me Black Mesa’s difficulty level is better than anything I dared hope for.</p>
<p>That said, I agree with the people who think the balance between aliens and grunts is unbalanced; I would want the aliens to be tougher, though, not the grunts to be weakened.</p>
<p>Also, what’s up with the Ichtyosaur only needing 2 arrows? I remember it being 5+ on hard in the original.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Funny thing is, I tried BM on easy mode, and it was just too easy. The soldiers had very little health and didn’t do that much damage. Then I switched it back to normal mode, and it still felt like they were way too accurate etc. They definitely need to be nerfed. And the aliens need to stop trying to do their damn melee attack so much, because it gets them killed.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/really-bad-balancing/9703/277">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/really-bad-balancing/9703/277</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 04 Oct 2012 03:51:28 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9703-277</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/really-bad-balancing/9703.rss">Really bad balancing</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Really bad balancing</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[No_Stress]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I’ve been playing Black Mesa on Hard and nothing else, and I like the challenge.</p>
<p>So to all those who complain about Normal being too hard, why not just go to easy? I’m tired of the Half-life series being way too easy on hard, so for me Black Mesa’s difficulty level is better than anything I dared hope for.</p>
<p>That said, I agree with the people who think the balance between aliens and grunts is unbalanced; I would want the aliens to be tougher, though, not the grunts to be weakened.</p>
<p>Also, what’s up with the Ichtyosaur only needing 2 arrows? I remember it being 5+ on hard in the original.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/really-bad-balancing/9703/276">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/really-bad-balancing/9703/276</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 04 Oct 2012 01:07:44 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9703-276</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/really-bad-balancing/9703.rss">Really bad balancing</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Really bad balancing</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Eltripas]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Devoc">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/d/bbce88/40.png" class="avatar"> Devoc:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>To be honest, I didn’t even know there was an option to change the difficulty so I guess the standard difficulty is normal… which was too easy for my taste.</p>
<p>I think the soldiers on HL1 were a lot harder to kill than they are on BMS, but that might be because I was only 11 years old or so back then.</p>
<p>That chopper closing in on me at the canyon got to murder me a couple of times though…</p>
<p>Guess I’ll have to check out hard mode too now c:</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>The default difficulty is easy. At least it was for me.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/really-bad-balancing/9703/275">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/really-bad-balancing/9703/275</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 03 Oct 2012 21:58:58 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9703-275</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/really-bad-balancing/9703.rss">Really bad balancing</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Really bad balancing</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[quadpl]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>What kind of noob just whores the hivehand though?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>The kind of “noob” that knows how to strategically use it. The homing hornets make it easy to pick off enemies whenever they are spread out. The rapid fire is good whenever enemies are stationary and firing/preparing to fire at you. The slow ammo regeneration keeps it from being overpowered so you still have to find cover.</p>
<p>I found it particularly useful to pick off barnacles and headcrabs as well as a handful of vorts on catwalks.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/really-bad-balancing/9703/274">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/really-bad-balancing/9703/274</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 03 Oct 2012 15:34:58 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9703-274</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/really-bad-balancing/9703.rss">Really bad balancing</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Really bad balancing</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[lunertexcosmo]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Midnightcoast">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/m/9fc348/40.png" class="avatar"> Midnightcoast:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>This isn’t a bug report or anything, but I was wondering why we can pick up a dead headcrab but not anything else that we shot.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>You can pick up Houndeyes.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/really-bad-balancing/9703/273">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/really-bad-balancing/9703/273</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 03 Oct 2012 14:31:36 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9703-273</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/really-bad-balancing/9703.rss">Really bad balancing</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Really bad balancing</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Ed1]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Lawl leijon, the hivehand regenerated hornets at like 4 per second…but there’s a slightly longer delay for ammo regen after shooting a hornet, so it’s not too good if you’re in an intense firefight with 4+ marines and their Assassin-level training.</p>
<p>Rapid fire is quite beast, you do know that it fires the hornets in a very tight 3x3 grid…fire all 8 using secondary fire at a stationary target, you’ll see what I mean.</p>
<p>Speaking of Assassins…I wonder how 3 of them would cope against 3 HECU soldiers…heheheh</p>
<p>By the way, if you’re willing/know how to tweak the game to your taste, go to<br>
C:/Program Files/Steam/steamapps/common/sourcemods/BMS/cfg/<br>
and find a file called skill.cfg, in it are the damage values for all weapons used by the player and NPCs, as well as the reaction time, but this was explained in greater detail in a “Post your BMS tweaks” thread somewhere…</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/really-bad-balancing/9703/272">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/really-bad-balancing/9703/272</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 03 Oct 2012 13:35:07 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9703-272</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/really-bad-balancing/9703.rss">Really bad balancing</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
