<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Teleportation inconistancy</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/teleportation-inconistancy/11388</link>
    <description>Just thinking of the teleport scenes in HL2 and how they compare to the chapters anomalous materials / lambda core

Now check this Vid

[url]https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=axhw-3oFcIk[/url]

Is there any possible way to include this overlay texture for when teleporting in black mesa to keep consistancy with the sequals...

It seems at the last teleport scene there was some kind of overlay texture ....

Basically I think Anomalous materials needs these effects and a very short effect when going into the teleport orbs aswell as The final Lamda core scene should have leading to xen.


What are your thoughts on the teleportation and associated effects seen in half life 2 also the negative render effect as you teleport in

also some kind of music ambience at the very start of unforseen consequences would perhaps work well when you first wake from the disaster perhaps fading in from negative

example of photo negative effect
[img]https://news.indonewyork.com/images/articles/2012_02/2541/u1_130-negative-woman-jpg_002600.jpg[/img]</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 29 Oct 2012 16:56:31 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>The Cafeteria</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/teleportation-inconistancy/11388.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Teleportation inconistancy</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Ronster]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="TehBoxNoob">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 TehBoxNoob:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>The lambda core is one big ass map, so I think you hit the max entities.<br>
SourceEngine can handle 2048 entities, and I really don’t know how much Lambda has but probably a few under it.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Yeah I want to make an improvement here but the headache it will give me for the small improvement factor vs amount of work not worth it.</p>
<p>it’s not the point entities… It’s all the func_details got ungrouped during decompile so it means going over the whole map grouping all the func_details and such to get it to run. (Not worth  it for adding 2 entities and a shed load of In/Out strings of whicj I already did before figuring out the map had problems  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/frowning.png?v=9" title=":frowning:" class="emoji" alt=":frowning:">  )</p>
<p>I will make a test map though and get the effect and the settings for the fx to work just right as an example of what to do and this is a lot easier to do for an example</p>
<p>Only then if it’s a good call to introduce a white flash effect then this will be made readily available with the settings and how it can work with the effect.</p>
<p>of which I have figured out just need to play with the effects settings this could then be replicated in the map by the devs if people think it’s a good idea as they can do this in 2 hours as opposed to 3 days or somthing by myself</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/teleportation-inconistancy/11388/25">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/teleportation-inconistancy/11388/25</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 29 Oct 2012 16:56:31 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11388-25</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/teleportation-inconistancy/11388.rss">Teleportation inconistancy</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Teleportation inconistancy</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[D3lta]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>The lambda core is one big ass map, so I think you hit the max entities.<br>
SourceEngine can handle 2048 entities, and I really don’t know how much Lambda has but probably a few under it.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/teleportation-inconistancy/11388/24">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/teleportation-inconistancy/11388/24</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 29 Oct 2012 16:43:40 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11388-24</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/teleportation-inconistancy/11388.rss">Teleportation inconistancy</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Teleportation inconistancy</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Ronster]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>1.No it would not compile in the first place if it was at limit… Decompiling it does not always keep the correct infomation entirely… Only adding 1 entity and setting the triggers for the teleports to delay should not be any strain for the game at all.</p>
<ol start="2">
<li>it’s a teleport to a white room with another teleport in the white room too the final destination…You would have to take in to account an extra second or whatever time span it was so yes your correct on that though</li>
</ol>
<p>To set a delay up would mean you would see the white room even if it was only for a second or half a second (extremely flexible like even a 20th of a second)… I was going for 2 (1.5) seconds with a 0.5 second fade from white either side. but probably need a fade to and a fade from white either side thinking again so 2 x env_fade entities</p>
<p>I will eventually set up a proper test map to get the effect right as I have not seen it yet</p>
<p>The way it is set up now it’s pretty much instantaneous so not noticeable and the groundwork has been done for this effect to happen it’s a shame really but the point you have made it needs to be very sharp white flash well taken into acount there mouse perhaps the whole effect last 1 second 0.33 fade to white in 0.33 in the white room and 0.33 fade in from white on the other side This will mean a total of 0.66 in the white room just over half a second</p>
<p>I think this is how I will set up the test thanks for that input</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/teleportation-inconistancy/11388/23">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/teleportation-inconistancy/11388/23</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 29 Oct 2012 14:02:13 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11388-23</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/teleportation-inconistancy/11388.rss">Teleportation inconistancy</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Teleportation inconistancy</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[UnhingedMouse0]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Knowing nothing about how mapping works I have two points/questions for ya:</p>
<ol>
<li>
<p>Isn’t it entirely possible that the map was already at its limit for entities and so you adding anything to it causes errors? Maybe those entities were originally supposed to be in-game but were intentionally trimmed out to meet the limit.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Wouldn’t adding a delay in the ‘white room’ cause problems for the player as far as timing goes? You’d have to freeze the rotating platforms for the same amount of time you’re in the white room or else you will drop out of the exit portal behind where you do now. It wouldn’t be a huge difference, but as it sits already, timing those jumps can be tricky.</p>
</li>
</ol>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/teleportation-inconistancy/11388/22">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/teleportation-inconistancy/11388/22</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 29 Oct 2012 11:21:13 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11388-22</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/teleportation-inconistancy/11388.rss">Teleportation inconistancy</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Teleportation inconistancy</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Ronster]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Ok I just decompiled the map for the Lambda core bm_c3a2g in order to change the teleportation effects on the orbs… i.e. make white flashes.</p>
<p>Whats interesting is is that the teleports are set-up correctly to do white flashes every teleport is 2 teleports into a white box with lights white texture applied but there is no delay set on the 2 triggers for the effect and and no env_fade effect to transition smoothly. I have done the transition in’s and outs on the entities to make the white flashes but the map won’t compile</p>
<p>Basically I have done the entity work but the decompiled map has serious errors in it.</p>
<p>Anyone have a clue how to fix this up? I am getting the num_entities == MAX_MAP_ENTITIES.</p>
<p>So does this mean the map has too many entities or somthing else is causing the error?</p>
<p>If the map has too many entities in it how did it complie in the first place? That’s why I think it’s something else…</p>
<p>Anyway any help would be appreciated on how to fix this without having to delete geometry seeing as all I have done is add an entity and a lot of in and out strings… I have moved some brushes to world and put some to func_details and this has fixed some of the brush number errors relating to num_entities == MAX_MAP_ENTITIES… But theres alot of brushes particularly in this map</p>
<p>no other planned changes but want to put in the teleportation effects that the map is aleady set up for funnily enough missing only env_fade</p>
<p>Right now like this I cannot fix it so please Dev’s fix this one</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/teleportation-inconistancy/11388/21">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/teleportation-inconistancy/11388/21</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 28 Oct 2012 18:28:30 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11388-21</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/teleportation-inconistancy/11388.rss">Teleportation inconistancy</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Teleportation inconistancy</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Pettifogg]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="OldDirtyBastard">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/o/dec6dc/40.png" class="avatar"> OldDirtyBastard:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Just like Magnusson, kay.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Well, they <span class="bbcode-i">did</span> put in a nod to him.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/teleportation-inconistancy/11388/20">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/teleportation-inconistancy/11388/20</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 09 Oct 2012 20:03:52 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11388-20</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/teleportation-inconistancy/11388.rss">Teleportation inconistancy</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Teleportation inconistancy</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Ronster]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>OK the white flash is an env_fade just decompiled the map from HL2 and got the settings I think this would be beneficial when going into the orbs and also whenever there is a teleport sequence Orbs should not include the screen overlay effect (Perhaps a short stab)  but I hope for some screen overlay effects in Anom Materials / Lambda Core and Xen which I think would make the scenes more updated and trippy in line with half life 2</p>
<ul>
<li>Settings for env_fade* Teleportation effect</li>
</ul>
<p>Duration 5<br>
Hold Fade 0<br>
Fade Alpha 200<br>
Fade Colour 255 255 255 (white)</p>
<p>Input normally on trigger with a 3 second delay probably have to customize</p>
<p>Flags Fade from (selected)</p>
<p>I was wrong about the modulation I think it is the alpha settings that produce the light and dark with the flash.</p>
<p>but that is the visual cue settings used in HL2</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/teleportation-inconistancy/11388/19">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/teleportation-inconistancy/11388/19</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 09 Oct 2012 19:51:40 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11388-19</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/teleportation-inconistancy/11388.rss">Teleportation inconistancy</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Teleportation inconistancy</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Ronster]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I am at work writing on my phone… But i don’t need to decompile anomalous materials need to decompile kleiners lab in hl2 to get answers because the effect i am talking about is missing from Bms totally</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/teleportation-inconistancy/11388/18">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/teleportation-inconistancy/11388/18</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 09 Oct 2012 13:40:37 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11388-18</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/teleportation-inconistancy/11388.rss">Teleportation inconistancy</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Teleportation inconistancy</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypt]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Why don’t you crack open the Anom. Mats. map and take a look? I can’t be assed to do that right now.</p>
<p>The flashbang effect isn’t a Hammer entity, as Hammer can’t predict when a player is getting hit by a flashbang. In Half-Life² I’m sure it’s an env_screenoverlay entity  for teleportaion effects, or some sort of complex network on them.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/teleportation-inconistancy/11388/17">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/teleportation-inconistancy/11388/17</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 09 Oct 2012 13:18:14 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11388-17</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/teleportation-inconistancy/11388.rss">Teleportation inconistancy</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Teleportation inconistancy</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Ronster]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Crypt19">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Crypt19:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Actually, env_fade is used for the opposite: fading to black, usually to cut to credits.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-i">Nothing</span> was missing. They intentionally kept that section brief and vague to help keep Xen a surprise.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>do you know what the entity is that is used for the white flash… I am pretty sure that it is an env fade with modulation attenuation applied but never used it before… Does anyone know what entity is used for the effect of fladhing the screen in from white while other colours are in black / blue</p>
<p>thanks crypt… I am going to play through again soon but it is good to know there will be another reason to play again to see changes and updates</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/teleportation-inconistancy/11388/16">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/teleportation-inconistancy/11388/16</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 09 Oct 2012 13:03:41 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11388-16</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/teleportation-inconistancy/11388.rss">Teleportation inconistancy</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Teleportation inconistancy</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypt]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Actually, env_fade is used for the opposite: fading to black, usually to cut to credits.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-i">Nothing</span> was missing. They intentionally kept that section brief and vague to help keep Xen a surprise.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/teleportation-inconistancy/11388/15">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/teleportation-inconistancy/11388/15</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 09 Oct 2012 12:20:04 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11388-15</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/teleportation-inconistancy/11388.rss">Teleportation inconistancy</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Teleportation inconistancy</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Ronster]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Never used the entity before but i wondering about env_fade is the entity that creates the flashbang effects in counterstrike and in hl2 teleportation but half life 2 might have modulation attenuation applied.</p>
<p>Dont know if env fade is the entity used but this in conjuction with env screenoverlay should be utilised perhaps in all teleportation sequences.?</p>
<p>Also what happened to the bullsquid…in anomalous materials teleport?  Is this stuff being kept secret to not reveal xen properly?</p>
<p>Is that why some effects seem missing?</p>
<p>Either way the teleport orbs need somthing short and sharp visual effects</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/teleportation-inconistancy/11388/14">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/teleportation-inconistancy/11388/14</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 09 Oct 2012 11:34:20 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11388-14</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/teleportation-inconistancy/11388.rss">Teleportation inconistancy</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Teleportation inconistancy</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Dragunov2]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>The Black Mesa technology is older, so normally it takes longer to transport a person/object from one place to another…</p>
<p>In Half Life 2 they have improved the technology, so it has to be faster, more stabile (except if lamarr is interupting  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/wink.png?v=9" title=":wink:" class="emoji" alt=":wink:"> )</p>
<p>But on the other hand, Black Mesa is a million dollar company, and Dr. Kleiner just made one in his backyard…</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/teleportation-inconistancy/11388/13">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/teleportation-inconistancy/11388/13</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 09 Oct 2012 09:18:02 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11388-13</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/teleportation-inconistancy/11388.rss">Teleportation inconistancy</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Teleportation inconistancy</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[OldDirtyBastard]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="JezMM">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/j/f14d63/40.png" class="avatar"> JezMM:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Any form of bonus continuity with HL2 like this would be appreciated IMO.  Nice idea.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Just like Magnusson, kay.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/teleportation-inconistancy/11388/12">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/teleportation-inconistancy/11388/12</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 09 Oct 2012 03:36:28 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11388-12</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/teleportation-inconistancy/11388.rss">Teleportation inconistancy</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Teleportation inconistancy</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[loghete]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Speaking of the teleportation; did anyone else miss the teleported-in-water part from the original HL? I thought that was a great, with the Ichthyosaur swimming towards you, and I don’t really see why the devs cut it out?</p>
<p>EDIT: Wait, I just realised I’m mixing it all up with HL2. Whoops, nevermind then!</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/teleportation-inconistancy/11388/11">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/teleportation-inconistancy/11388/11</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 08 Oct 2012 22:55:40 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11388-11</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/teleportation-inconistancy/11388.rss">Teleportation inconistancy</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Teleportation inconistancy</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[JezMM]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Any form of bonus continuity with HL2 like this would be appreciated IMO.  Nice idea.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/teleportation-inconistancy/11388/10">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/teleportation-inconistancy/11388/10</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 08 Oct 2012 20:34:24 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11388-10</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/teleportation-inconistancy/11388.rss">Teleportation inconistancy</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Teleportation inconistancy</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Ronster]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Pettifogg">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/p/ebca7d/40.png" class="avatar"> Pettifogg:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>This implies that the tech used in HL2 is more advanced than that in HL, which might explain why there’s a different visual effect.</p>
<p>I did feel the local teleports in BM lacked something, though - the screen just instantly snapped to the new location. Maybe just having the screen flash white for a second or something would be enough.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>That was exactly my thought on the orb teleports - white flash / photo negative effect</p>
<p>As far as anomalous materials goes the original had a green flash which I think was upgraded to the screen overlay effect for half life 2 but I can understand the devs wanted to keep it more retro in some respects but I would have really liked to have seen screen overlay effects during anomalous materials to give it more punch and make it more trippy</p>
<p>If comparing the green flash was dimensional tear and the screen overlay in half life 2 was a slingshot effect… i.e. bending space and time</p>
<p>perhaps an overlay of the teleport spawns for vorts and headcrabs should be converted to an overlay for the flashes Gordon sees mixed with a short overlay deom HL2 when flashing out to white when reaching the teleport destination</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/teleportation-inconistancy/11388/9">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/teleportation-inconistancy/11388/9</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 08 Oct 2012 16:29:35 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11388-9</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/teleportation-inconistancy/11388.rss">Teleportation inconistancy</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Teleportation inconistancy</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Pettifogg]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Judith Mossman">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Judith Mossman:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Dr. Kliener compressed the xen relay far beyond anything he imagined at Black Mesa. We figured out how to use xen as an  unexpressed axis, effectively a dimensional slingshot so we can swing around  the borderworld and come back in local space without having to pass through.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>This implies that the tech used in HL2 is more advanced than that in HL, which might explain why there’s a different visual effect.</p>
<p>I did feel the local teleports in BM lacked something, though - the screen just instantly snapped to the new location. Maybe just having the screen flash white for a second or something would be enough.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/teleportation-inconistancy/11388/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/teleportation-inconistancy/11388/8</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 08 Oct 2012 16:17:12 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11388-8</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/teleportation-inconistancy/11388.rss">Teleportation inconistancy</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Teleportation inconistancy</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Dotard]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I agree, would be cool</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/teleportation-inconistancy/11388/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/teleportation-inconistancy/11388/7</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 08 Oct 2012 14:40:21 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11388-7</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/teleportation-inconistancy/11388.rss">Teleportation inconistancy</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Teleportation inconistancy</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Ronster]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Trigger_Proximity">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/t/50afbb/40.png" class="avatar"> Trigger_Proximity:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Yeah no, the teleportation that happens in HL2 is a different kind of teleportation. Similar but not the same.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>It’s still a dimensional rift that creates a portal… Altthough the portal gun created seamless gateways the difference is that the players matter is not deconstructed and then rebuilt.</p>
<p>In the events in the resonance cascade is still a quantum event and should by definition be treated the same as Black Mesas technology.</p>
<p>The half life wiki says this on teleportation in relation to aperture science</p>
<p>“Another method was investigated by Black Mesa, and later improved upon by the Resistance.”</p>
<p><a href="https://half-life.wikia.com/wiki/Teleportation" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://half-life.wikia.com/wiki/Teleportation</a></p>
<p>So It is the same technology but further developed and different to aperture science technology… But there is no visual cue to the fact that teleportation or dimensional rifts are happening like we saw in HL2 I just think it would be beneficial to have visual cues to accompany teleportation</p>
<p>env_screenoverlay and is also quite easy to do… Perhaps they did not have the textures for this or could not use them</p>
<p><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=LVjaFo6esWw" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=LVjaFo6esWw</a></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/teleportation-inconistancy/11388/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/teleportation-inconistancy/11388/6</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 08 Oct 2012 06:39:47 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11388-6</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/teleportation-inconistancy/11388.rss">Teleportation inconistancy</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Teleportation inconistancy</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Trigger_Proximity]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Yeah no, the teleportation that happens in HL2 is a different kind of teleportation. Similar but not the same.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/teleportation-inconistancy/11388/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/teleportation-inconistancy/11388/5</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 07 Oct 2012 22:20:17 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11388-5</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/teleportation-inconistancy/11388.rss">Teleportation inconistancy</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Teleportation inconistancy</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Eli_Vance]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>…the same effects occurred with the teleport that went mostly right in Nova Propekt, I think.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/teleportation-inconistancy/11388/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/teleportation-inconistancy/11388/4</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 07 Oct 2012 21:20:22 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11388-4</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/teleportation-inconistancy/11388.rss">Teleportation inconistancy</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Teleportation inconistancy</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Ronster]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="bur">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/b/87869e/40.png" class="avatar"> bur:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>different time, different technology</p>
<p>also, something went wrong during that teleportation in HL2, which could explain the negative effect</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I’d also say somthing went wrong in the experiment in anomalous materials… Thats why I think It should be included or somthing similar to visually pronounce the fact you are being teleported…</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/teleportation-inconistancy/11388/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/teleportation-inconistancy/11388/3</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 07 Oct 2012 20:48:50 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11388-3</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/teleportation-inconistancy/11388.rss">Teleportation inconistancy</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Teleportation inconistancy</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[bur]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>different time, different technology</p>
<p>also, something went wrong during that teleportation in HL2, which could explain the negative effect</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/teleportation-inconistancy/11388/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/teleportation-inconistancy/11388/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 07 Oct 2012 20:46:26 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11388-2</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/teleportation-inconistancy/11388.rss">Teleportation inconistancy</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Teleportation inconistancy</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Ronster]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Just thinking of the teleport scenes in HL2 and how they compare to the chapters anomalous materials / lambda core</p>
<p>Now check this Vid</p>
<p><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=axhw-3oFcIk" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=axhw-3oFcIk</a></p>
<p>Is there any possible way to include this overlay texture for when teleporting in black mesa to keep consistancy with the sequals…</p>
<p>It seems at the last teleport scene there was some kind of overlay texture …</p>
<p>Basically I think Anomalous materials needs these effects and a very short effect when going into the teleport orbs aswell as The final Lamda core scene should have leading to xen.</p>
<p>What are your thoughts on the teleportation and associated effects seen in half life 2 also the negative render effect as you teleport in</p>
<p>also some kind of music ambience at the very start of unforseen consequences would perhaps work well when you first wake from the disaster perhaps fading in from negative</p>
<p>example of photo negative effect<br>
<span alt="" class="broken-image" title="This image is broken"><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-unlink svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#unlink"></use></svg></span></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/teleportation-inconistancy/11388/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/teleportation-inconistancy/11388/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 07 Oct 2012 20:37:22 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11388-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/teleportation-inconistancy/11388.rss">Teleportation inconistancy</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
