<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Torrents not uploading/seeding</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/torrents-not-uploading-seeding/11904</link>
    <description>I&#39;ve noticed recently that when I download a torrent, it almost never seeds. The downloading is perfectly fine, it commonly maxes my download speed. But for some reason the upload speed stays at zero all the time. I would prefer to fix this as private trackers will ban you if you can&#39;t keep a decent ratio. I set up some ports in my router forwarded and put them into my client. The icon that shows my connection status doesn&#39;t indicate a problem but still, no uploading for some reason. Anyone know how to fix this?

Edit: And I&#39;ve noticed the same thing with multiple clients so it&#39;s not specific to the one I use most.

Edit 2: Hold on hold on. What I&#39;m downloading right now is uploading, albeit at 4 kbps. Still better than nothing. Still getting nothing from the stuff that counts though, as right now I&#39;m using a public tracker. Maybe it&#39;s because nobody&#39;s downloading what I&#39;ve downloaded from there?</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 28 Dec 2012 13:10:26 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Help and Support</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/torrents-not-uploading-seeding/11904.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Torrents not uploading/seeding</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Jethrosoup]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Kairouseki">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/k/57b2e6/40.png" class="avatar"> Kairouseki:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Maybe it’s because nobody’s downloading what I’ve downloaded from there?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>This was going to be my answer. Happens, man. Start downloading newer shit.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/torrents-not-uploading-seeding/11904/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/torrents-not-uploading-seeding/11904/2</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Dec 2012 13:10:26 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11904-2</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/torrents-not-uploading-seeding/11904.rss">Torrents not uploading/seeding</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Torrents not uploading/seeding</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Kairouseki]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I’ve noticed recently that when I download a torrent, it almost never seeds. The downloading is perfectly fine, it commonly maxes my download speed. But for some reason the upload speed stays at zero all the time. I would prefer to fix this as private trackers will ban you if you can’t keep a decent ratio. I set up some ports in my router forwarded and put them into my client. The icon that shows my connection status doesn’t indicate a problem but still, no uploading for some reason. Anyone know how to fix this?</p>
<p>Edit: And I’ve noticed the same thing with multiple clients so it’s not specific to the one I use most.</p>
<p>Edit 2: Hold on hold on. What I’m downloading right now is uploading, albeit at 4 kbps. Still better than nothing. Still getting nothing from the stuff that counts though, as right now I’m using a public tracker. Maybe it’s because nobody’s downloading what I’ve downloaded from there?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/torrents-not-uploading-seeding/11904/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/torrents-not-uploading-seeding/11904/1</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Dec 2012 03:57:21 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11904-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/torrents-not-uploading-seeding/11904.rss">Torrents not uploading/seeding</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
