<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>A few minor bugs</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/a-few-minor-bugs/9554</link>
    <description>I don&#39;t have pos info yet. I just took screenshots. I&#39;ll try to re-edit the post later if needed.

1. Human sounds are seemingly muted when I press the call button for the elevator of death (the one in Unforeseen Consequences from which someone calls &quot;help us!&quot; and then crashes). No screams no nothing. I don&#39;t know if this was intended or not.

2. A few computer keyboards are sort of misplaced on the desks. This could be due to the sitting/typing animations of the scientist models though.
[url]https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=96071422[/url]
[url]https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=96064330[/url]

3. In the first room [url=&#39;https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=96073576&#39;]where this is[/url], the elecronic panel/cabinet has some collisions disabled, because I could throw a bin and a barrel and it clipped through it. 
[url]https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=96073029[/url]

4. The first alive guard I meet in Unforeseen Consequences (the one who you get the hint to add him to your team), had some weird glitches interacting with the zombies. This one in particular was quite interesting. He was stuck in a loop where the zombie was hitting him and he was doing nothing, but he wouldn&#39;t die (I know he could die, because in my previous play of this scene I send him towards the two fake-dead zombies, and one of them grabbed him and killed him). 
[url]https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=96073918[/url]</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 14 Sep 2012 21:26:30 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>In-game Issues (Mod)</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/a-few-minor-bugs/9554.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>A few minor bugs</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[ShadowNate]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I don’t have pos info yet. I just took screenshots. I’ll try to re-edit the post later if needed.</p>
<ol>
<li>
<p>Human sounds are seemingly muted when I press the call button for the elevator of death (the one in Unforeseen Consequences from which someone calls “help us!” and then crashes). No screams no nothing. I don’t know if this was intended or not.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>A few computer keyboards are sort of misplaced on the desks. This could be due to the sitting/typing animations of the scientist models though.<br>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=96071422" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=96071422</a><br>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=96064330" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=96064330</a></p>
</li>
<li>
<p>In the first room <a href="https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=96073576" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">where this is</a>, the elecronic panel/cabinet has some collisions disabled, because I could throw a bin and a barrel and it clipped through it.<br>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=96073029" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=96073029</a></p>
</li>
<li>
<p>The first alive guard I meet in Unforeseen Consequences (the one who you get the hint to add him to your team), had some weird glitches interacting with the zombies. This one in particular was quite interesting. He was stuck in a loop where the zombie was hitting him and he was doing nothing, but he wouldn’t die (I know he could die, because in my previous play of this scene I send him towards the two fake-dead zombies, and one of them grabbed him and killed him).<br>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=96073918" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=96073918</a></p>
</li>
</ol>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/a-few-minor-bugs/9554/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/a-few-minor-bugs/9554/1</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 14 Sep 2012 21:26:30 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9554-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/a-few-minor-bugs/9554.rss">A few minor bugs</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
