<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Bringing Half-Life 0.52 into Black Mesa</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/bringing-half-life-0-52-into-black-mesa/14317</link>
    <description>[font=&#39;Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif&#39;]Some of you may have heard about the leaked Half-Life alpha released to the public a few years ago, which included early versions of some of the Half-Life levels- as well as items which never made it into the final game, such as cut chapters, cut weapons, cut enemies, and so on. Seeing Half-Life in its alpha state got me thinking: if Valve had stuck to what it had originally had in mind for Half-Life, what would Black Mesa look like then? How would the maps of the alpha look if redesigned in the more versatile Source engine and redesigned in a way that would make more logical sense? So I have decided to re-map the 15 alpha maps in the style of Black Mesa (they might not be quite as good, but I&#39;m trying to bring them as close to Black Mesa quality as I can), adding in various improvements to them along the way. I might have a few questions about mapping, as I am not without areas in which I could use improvement. But enough introduction, let&#39;s take a look of what I have in mind for this small project.
[/font]
[b][font=&#39;Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif&#39;][i][u]The Maps[/u][/i][/font][/b]
[font=&#39;Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif&#39;]If you were paying attention in my introduction, you&#39;d know that this project involves re-mapping and improving the 15 maps released in the leaked alpha of Half-Life. However, this won&#39;t be 100% loyal to the alpha, as many areas need improvement. Be it an issue with realistic design, or poor level design in general (some of the levels are somewhat mazelike, and I don&#39;t want the player to be confused about where to go next), the alpha maps are in need of some serious work. You can also expect an improvement in continuity- some of the alpha maps had no clear connection to the next level. Most of these fixes won&#39;t be too large, like a connection from the Security Complex&#39;s C map to A map, or a connection from the end of Alien Research Labs to the start of Communications Center. However, I am planning to add an original C map to the first chapter (The Portal Device), which will establish a linkage between it and the Office Complex- as well as integrating two areas seen in early Half-Life concept art. Another thing that will have to be added to the maps is health and ammunition pickups. Since I&#39;m not an expert on pickup placement, don&#39;t hesitate to tell me your ideas on how I could improve the placement of items around the map. Furthermore, I am only planning to remake the maps included in the alpha [u]at this point[/u]. If all goes well, I may also start mapping some of the chapters that were going to be in the alpha, but didn&#39;t make it in (such as the early version of Blast Pit). Don&#39;t count on anything at this point,  but if I decide to work on the missing chapters, I&#39;ll let you know. Finally, if you see something, and you think it needs improvement (or you just have an idea), tell me! I am fully open to your suggestions.


[b][i][u]The Team[/u][/i][/b]
At this point, this is a one man project. However, if you think you can help me out, just tell me. I&#39;m not setting a quota for team members, but I would say about 5 mappers maximum- one per chapter including me (Quick edit: It would probably also be a good idea to have people to run detail work on the maps), so it shouldn&#39;t matter what your area of expertise is. And who knows? Maybe I&#39;ll have a team, maybe I won&#39;t. If I have a team, it would mean that this could be released sooner, but if I don&#39;t have a team, I&#39;ll manage. My only criteria is that you have a fair amount of knowledge of Hammer editor (that is, if you would like to help with the mapping). You don&#39;t have to be phenomenally good at making maps (although if you are, that&#39;s great!), just fairly good. It shouldn&#39;t really matter how you ask me- ask on the post, send me a message, it doesn&#39;t really make a difference. Just remember that if you are helping with mapping, I might feel it necessary to make some changes to your map- however, as good teamwork goes, you can also make changes to the maps I make, should you find it necessary. But hey, that&#39;s how development works. If the black mesa team can properly work together, I don&#39;t see why we shouldn&#39;t be able to (okay, there might be a few reasons why we might not be able to get along, but I&#39;m hoping that we won&#39;t have to deal with them).


[b][i][u]The Release[/u][/i][/b]
I can&#39;t say much for a release date around now- it all depends on who&#39;s working on it, as well as motivation. However, I will say that you can expect a release in two parts- the first part will feature chapters 1-3, and the second part will feature chapters 8-10 (as for chapters 4-7,as I said earlier, it will depend on how well the rest of it works out). At this point, my plan is to finish working on the first part before moving on to the second part. However, that plan might change depending on the number of people working on the project. If I&#39;m nearing a release, I&#39;ll let you know.


Hope that wasn&#39;t too long. Let me know what you think, and I&#39;ll get back to you (someday).[/font]</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 23 Aug 2015 16:20:43 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Source 1</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/bringing-half-life-0-52-into-black-mesa/14317.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Bringing Half-Life 0.52 into Black Mesa</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[MisterDigitalGuy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Alright, so currently I am working on the alpha version of office complex. Since the maps are somewhat resemblent of the maps in the final version, I’ve been decompiling and editing them to match the alpha’s geometry.</p>
<p>Here is the entrance to the offices. You’ll notice that the doors are now grey instead of red, the elevator has been moved forward, and the lounge area is smaller (I’m thinking it will be a bonus area with ammunition and other goodies)</p>
<p>[attach=4161,none,1024][/attach]</p>
<p>Another big difference is this area. The pathway to the warehouse has been replaced with an inaccessible hallway, the doors have been removed, and the desk has been relocated.</p>
<p>[attach=4162,none,1024][/attach]</p>
<p>During this stage in development, the flooded office area did not exist (the concept was located in one of the levels of The Portal Device, but that’s a different story). Rather, it was an explorable area, and where the sequence with the scientist being pulled into the ceiling was originally located.</p>
<p>[attach=4163,none,1024][/attach]</p>
<p>Finally, the storage area. Originally, there was no turret guarding the room, and a security room was to overlook it (the lighting is really bad there, probably should have adjusted it more).</p>
<p>[attach=4164,none,1024][/attach]</p>
<p>Remember, it’s all WIP, and nothing is final (especially the lighting, I’m going to need to spend a good amount of time getting it to work). Feel free to tell me what you think.</p>
<p>By the way, we’re still open to new team members- if you’re interested, let me know.</p>
<p>EDIT: Decided that calling my errors “horrible mistakes” was a bit too harsh. Don’t want to discourage feedback by looking like I have low self-esteem.<br>
<div class="lightbox-wrapper"><a class="lightbox" href="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/original/2X/8/8a454bfefd72a45967438e4b3a7f8d877cf90a48.jpeg" data-download-href="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/8a454bfefd72a45967438e4b3a7f8d877cf90a48" title="2015-08-23_00001.jpg"><img src="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/original/2X/8/8a454bfefd72a45967438e4b3a7f8d877cf90a48.jpeg" alt="2015-08-23_00001.jpg" data-base62-sha1="jJcmf4ieBGyYyBej1sQJlKU3FSE" width="690" height="500" data-small-upload="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/optimized/2X/8/8a454bfefd72a45967438e4b3a7f8d877cf90a48_2_10x10.png"><div class="meta"><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-far-image svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#far-image"></use></svg><span class="filename">2015-08-23_00001.jpg</span><span class="informations">1024×768 119 KB</span><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-discourse-expand svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#discourse-expand"></use></svg></div></a></div><br>
<div class="lightbox-wrapper"><a class="lightbox" href="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/original/2X/a/a7223b14c2464e430ac55c5fc5d2b8bf7089a6e8.jpeg" data-download-href="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/a7223b14c2464e430ac55c5fc5d2b8bf7089a6e8" title="2015-08-23_00002.jpg"><img src="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/original/2X/a/a7223b14c2464e430ac55c5fc5d2b8bf7089a6e8.jpeg" alt="2015-08-23_00002.jpg" data-base62-sha1="nQx4KM6UaY0leEE6gALPWVtBSLC" width="690" height="500" data-small-upload="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/optimized/2X/a/a7223b14c2464e430ac55c5fc5d2b8bf7089a6e8_2_10x10.png"><div class="meta"><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-far-image svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#far-image"></use></svg><span class="filename">2015-08-23_00002.jpg</span><span class="informations">1024×768 126 KB</span><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-discourse-expand svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#discourse-expand"></use></svg></div></a></div><br>
<div class="lightbox-wrapper"><a class="lightbox" href="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/original/2X/a/a145198023bf03b7f6abedafd6734ec402c276b9.jpeg" data-download-href="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/a145198023bf03b7f6abedafd6734ec402c276b9" title="2015-08-23_00003.jpg"><img src="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/original/2X/a/a145198023bf03b7f6abedafd6734ec402c276b9.jpeg" alt="2015-08-23_00003.jpg" data-base62-sha1="n0EUUHF7pRIHbsh0PD4s9RLRxKF" width="690" height="500" data-small-upload="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/optimized/2X/a/a145198023bf03b7f6abedafd6734ec402c276b9_2_10x10.png"><div class="meta"><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-far-image svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#far-image"></use></svg><span class="filename">2015-08-23_00003.jpg</span><span class="informations">1024×768 152 KB</span><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-discourse-expand svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#discourse-expand"></use></svg></div></a></div><br>
<div class="lightbox-wrapper"><a class="lightbox" href="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/original/2X/e/e459b6bc498da66bcb584b5e214caef22d9ac575.jpeg" data-download-href="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/e459b6bc498da66bcb584b5e214caef22d9ac575" title="2015-08-23_00004.jpg"><img src="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/original/2X/e/e459b6bc498da66bcb584b5e214caef22d9ac575.jpeg" alt="2015-08-23_00004.jpg" data-base62-sha1="wA54BhvDU41ZLd1RZ2qz8nmL7fL" width="690" height="500" data-small-upload="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/optimized/2X/e/e459b6bc498da66bcb584b5e214caef22d9ac575_2_10x10.png"><div class="meta"><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-far-image svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#far-image"></use></svg><span class="filename">2015-08-23_00004.jpg</span><span class="informations">1024×768 134 KB</span><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-discourse-expand svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#discourse-expand"></use></svg></div></a></div></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/bringing-half-life-0-52-into-black-mesa/14317/20">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/bringing-half-life-0-52-into-black-mesa/14317/20</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 23 Aug 2015 16:20:43 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14317-20</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/bringing-half-life-0-52-into-black-mesa/14317.rss">Bringing Half-Life 0.52 into Black Mesa</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Bringing Half-Life 0.52 into Black Mesa</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[MisterDigitalGuy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Sage J. Fox">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Sage J. Fox:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Would like to add that this was the first compiling of the area, the big blob shadow on the electrical boxes is already dealt with, please don’t insult my mother while commenting on how horrible my mapping is and how I should probably just kill myself because of it. Feel free to do so on any other details.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Careful, don’t want to give anybody any ideas.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/bringing-half-life-0-52-into-black-mesa/14317/19">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/bringing-half-life-0-52-into-black-mesa/14317/19</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 11 Aug 2015 00:53:56 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14317-19</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/bringing-half-life-0-52-into-black-mesa/14317.rss">Bringing Half-Life 0.52 into Black Mesa</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Bringing Half-Life 0.52 into Black Mesa</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Sage_J_Fox]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Would like to add that this was the first compiling of the area, the big blob shadow on the electrical boxes is already dealt with, please don’t insult my mother while commenting on how horrible my mapping is and how I should probably just kill myself because of it. Feel free to do so on any other details.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/bringing-half-life-0-52-into-black-mesa/14317/18">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/bringing-half-life-0-52-into-black-mesa/14317/18</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 10 Aug 2015 20:26:10 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14317-18</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/bringing-half-life-0-52-into-black-mesa/14317.rss">Bringing Half-Life 0.52 into Black Mesa</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Bringing Half-Life 0.52 into Black Mesa</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[MisterDigitalGuy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Some more media to hold you over. Here’s a screenshot of the electrical room:</p>
<p>[attach=4123,none,798][/attach]</p>
<p>Note that this is very early in development. Nothing should be interpreted as final, and design is subject to change.</p>
<p>As always, feedback is appreciated!<br>
<div class="lightbox-wrapper"><a class="lightbox" href="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/original/2X/0/0d5a736f8546db215ba035d2969852343e5770bf.png" data-download-href="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/0d5a736f8546db215ba035d2969852343e5770bf" title="4f39e87c3a4fccd1552e0e9516183f0f.png"><img src="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/optimized/2X/0/0d5a736f8546db215ba035d2969852343e5770bf_2_690x448.png" alt="4f39e87c3a4fccd1552e0e9516183f0f.png" data-base62-sha1="1U7ZPH3UkUH3GO4RJ99UV1X2VWf" width="690" height="448" srcset="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/optimized/2X/0/0d5a736f8546db215ba035d2969852343e5770bf_2_690x448.png, https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/original/2X/0/0d5a736f8546db215ba035d2969852343e5770bf.png 1.5x, https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/original/2X/0/0d5a736f8546db215ba035d2969852343e5770bf.png 2x" data-small-upload="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/optimized/2X/0/0d5a736f8546db215ba035d2969852343e5770bf_2_10x10.png"><div class="meta"><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-far-image svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#far-image"></use></svg><span class="filename">4f39e87c3a4fccd1552e0e9516183f0f.png</span><span class="informations">798×448 485 KB</span><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-discourse-expand svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#discourse-expand"></use></svg></div></a></div></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/bringing-half-life-0-52-into-black-mesa/14317/17">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/bringing-half-life-0-52-into-black-mesa/14317/17</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 10 Aug 2015 19:56:44 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14317-17</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/bringing-half-life-0-52-into-black-mesa/14317.rss">Bringing Half-Life 0.52 into Black Mesa</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Bringing Half-Life 0.52 into Black Mesa</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[MisterDigitalGuy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Admiral Sakai">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Admiral Sakai:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Other than the general “moar detail” comment that you don’t really need because these are early WIP maps and we all know it,  there are a few things that immediately jump out to me:</p>
<p>On Screenshot 1, I really like the ceiling and glass stairway wall, but <span class="bbcode-i">really</span> don’t like the security-room wall’s metal-plate texture: I’d suggest you experiment with the office-freezer and lab texture sets more for this.</p>
<p>On Screenshot 2, I’m not sure about the metal dividing wall between the two glassed-in sections- perhaps it should be some other texture, either itself glass or something else entirely. That blue-striped desk is also rarely if ever used in BM, and should probably be replaced with one of the regular metal ones (table_square).</p>
<p>On both 2 and 3, I am not a big fan of having so many HL2 environment props around, especially in the labs. Some of those props just don’t fit BM’s style, and others are grimy enough that they only really work in the more industrial areas.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I think one of the problems here is that The Portal Device is supposed to have its own unique aesthetic. Problem is, we haven’t really established <span class="bbcode-i">what </span>that aesthetic is going to be yet. As a result, there’s a large mix of different textures and models throughout. Once we figure out how we want it to look exactly, we’ll probably change up the textures; but for now, things will be a bit messy.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/bringing-half-life-0-52-into-black-mesa/14317/16">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/bringing-half-life-0-52-into-black-mesa/14317/16</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 06 Aug 2015 15:06:39 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14317-16</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/bringing-half-life-0-52-into-black-mesa/14317.rss">Bringing Half-Life 0.52 into Black Mesa</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Bringing Half-Life 0.52 into Black Mesa</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Admiral_Sakai]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Other than the general “moar detail” comment that you don’t really need because these are early WIP maps and we all know it,  there are a few things that immediately jump out to me:</p>
<p>On Screenshot 1, I really like the ceiling and glass stairway wall, but <span class="bbcode-i">really</span> don’t like the security-room wall’s metal-plate texture: I’d suggest you experiment with the office-freezer and lab texture sets more for this.</p>
<p>On Screenshot 2, I’m not sure about the metal dividing wall between the two glassed-in sections- perhaps it should be some other texture, either itself glass or something else entirely. That blue-striped desk is also rarely if ever used in BM, and should probably be replaced with one of the regular metal ones (table_square).</p>
<p>On both 2 and 3, I am not a big fan of having so many HL2 environment props around, especially in the labs. Some of those props just don’t fit BM’s style, and others are grimy enough that they only really work in the more industrial areas.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/bringing-half-life-0-52-into-black-mesa/14317/15">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/bringing-half-life-0-52-into-black-mesa/14317/15</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 05 Aug 2015 23:12:47 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14317-15</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/bringing-half-life-0-52-into-black-mesa/14317.rss">Bringing Half-Life 0.52 into Black Mesa</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Bringing Half-Life 0.52 into Black Mesa</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[MisterDigitalGuy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Alright, figured I’d give you some media so you can at least see what we’re working on.</p>
<p>Be advised, these levels are very heavy WIP, nothing here should be interpreted as final.</p>
<p>[attach=4117,none,1600][/attach]</p>
<p>Seen here is the entrance to the Laboratories area, where the player encounters their first headcrabs.</p>
<p>[attach=4118,none,1600][/attach]</p>
<p>Here is a better view of the work area outside the lobby. Seen in the distance is a burning laboratory which the player must find a way around.</p>
<p>[attach=4119,none,1600][/attach]</p>
<p>Here is the stairwell leading down to the maintenance areas. There, the player will find a vent system that they’ll use to access the computer room, and get around the burning labs.</p>
<p>That’ll be all for now. Feedback is appreciated!<br>
<div class="lightbox-wrapper"><a class="lightbox" href="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/original/2X/d/d72680068644157bdd120a7365ba61d4303be1ee.jpeg" data-download-href="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/d72680068644157bdd120a7365ba61d4303be1ee" title="2015-08-05_00006.jpg"><img src="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/optimized/2X/d/d72680068644157bdd120a7365ba61d4303be1ee_2_690x500.jpeg" alt="2015-08-05_00006.jpg" data-base62-sha1="uHj8OJfJEp40Zb6mszPZSkO1QmO" width="690" height="500" srcset="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/optimized/2X/d/d72680068644157bdd120a7365ba61d4303be1ee_2_690x500.jpeg, https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/optimized/2X/d/d72680068644157bdd120a7365ba61d4303be1ee_2_1035x750.jpeg 1.5x, https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/optimized/2X/d/d72680068644157bdd120a7365ba61d4303be1ee_2_1380x1000.jpeg 2x" data-small-upload="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/optimized/2X/d/d72680068644157bdd120a7365ba61d4303be1ee_2_10x10.png"><div class="meta"><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-far-image svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#far-image"></use></svg><span class="filename">2015-08-05_00006.jpg</span><span class="informations">1600×900 338 KB</span><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-discourse-expand svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#discourse-expand"></use></svg></div></a></div><br>
<div class="lightbox-wrapper"><a class="lightbox" href="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/original/2X/c/c68001a92581dcc62c9b0961229f45cdeb970373.jpeg" data-download-href="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/c68001a92581dcc62c9b0961229f45cdeb970373" title="2015-08-05_00008.jpg"><img src="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/optimized/2X/c/c68001a92581dcc62c9b0961229f45cdeb970373_2_690x500.jpeg" alt="2015-08-05_00008.jpg" data-base62-sha1="sk0N5C2OD5PTc5shokrb9khD2dJ" width="690" height="500" srcset="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/optimized/2X/c/c68001a92581dcc62c9b0961229f45cdeb970373_2_690x500.jpeg, https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/optimized/2X/c/c68001a92581dcc62c9b0961229f45cdeb970373_2_1035x750.jpeg 1.5x, https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/optimized/2X/c/c68001a92581dcc62c9b0961229f45cdeb970373_2_1380x1000.jpeg 2x" data-small-upload="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/optimized/2X/c/c68001a92581dcc62c9b0961229f45cdeb970373_2_10x10.png"><div class="meta"><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-far-image svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#far-image"></use></svg><span class="filename">2015-08-05_00008.jpg</span><span class="informations">1600×900 209 KB</span><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-discourse-expand svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#discourse-expand"></use></svg></div></a></div><br>
<div class="lightbox-wrapper"><a class="lightbox" href="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/original/2X/8/832d95d54cd213f474d3752aad95035e8f98b879.jpeg" data-download-href="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/832d95d54cd213f474d3752aad95035e8f98b879" title="2015-08-05_00010.jpg"><img src="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/optimized/2X/8/832d95d54cd213f474d3752aad95035e8f98b879_2_690x500.jpeg" alt="2015-08-05_00010.jpg" data-base62-sha1="iIsdj7WU17vpDvJoLpkIUp2zHg5" width="690" height="500" srcset="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/optimized/2X/8/832d95d54cd213f474d3752aad95035e8f98b879_2_690x500.jpeg, https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/optimized/2X/8/832d95d54cd213f474d3752aad95035e8f98b879_2_1035x750.jpeg 1.5x, https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/optimized/2X/8/832d95d54cd213f474d3752aad95035e8f98b879_2_1380x1000.jpeg 2x" data-small-upload="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/optimized/2X/8/832d95d54cd213f474d3752aad95035e8f98b879_2_10x10.png"><div class="meta"><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-far-image svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#far-image"></use></svg><span class="filename">2015-08-05_00010.jpg</span><span class="informations">1600×900 441 KB</span><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-discourse-expand svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#discourse-expand"></use></svg></div></a></div></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/bringing-half-life-0-52-into-black-mesa/14317/14">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/bringing-half-life-0-52-into-black-mesa/14317/14</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 05 Aug 2015 22:22:46 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14317-14</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/bringing-half-life-0-52-into-black-mesa/14317.rss">Bringing Half-Life 0.52 into Black Mesa</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Bringing Half-Life 0.52 into Black Mesa</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[MisterDigitalGuy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Indeed it will be! 15 maps is no small task!</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/bringing-half-life-0-52-into-black-mesa/14317/13">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/bringing-half-life-0-52-into-black-mesa/14317/13</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jul 2015 14:51:19 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14317-13</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/bringing-half-life-0-52-into-black-mesa/14317.rss">Bringing Half-Life 0.52 into Black Mesa</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Bringing Half-Life 0.52 into Black Mesa</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Admiral_Sakai]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>This should be interesting! Good luck, this sounds like a major undertaking!</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/bringing-half-life-0-52-into-black-mesa/14317/12">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/bringing-half-life-0-52-into-black-mesa/14317/12</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jul 2015 12:48:51 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14317-12</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/bringing-half-life-0-52-into-black-mesa/14317.rss">Bringing Half-Life 0.52 into Black Mesa</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Bringing Half-Life 0.52 into Black Mesa</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Dadster]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>God speed, to you.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/bringing-half-life-0-52-into-black-mesa/14317/11">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/bringing-half-life-0-52-into-black-mesa/14317/11</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jul 2015 05:54:59 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14317-11</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/bringing-half-life-0-52-into-black-mesa/14317.rss">Bringing Half-Life 0.52 into Black Mesa</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Bringing Half-Life 0.52 into Black Mesa</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[MisterDigitalGuy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Ooooh, good thing you caught that! Up to this point, I completely forgot that that isn’t possible in a simple map pack. One of the things that would kind of prevent me from wanting it to be a mod is the fact that the alpha is incomplete. I’d say at least 4 chapters are missing from the alpha, and if we make this one mod, it might feel somewhat incomplete without those 4 chapters. Then again, it could be a 2-part release (like in my original plan) with both sets of chapters coming out separately, but I don’t know. I’ll think of something eventually (although hopefully sooner- we know what a lack of planning can do to a project).</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="dky.tehkingd.u">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/user_avatar/leakfree.org/dky.tehkingd.u/40/4377_2.png" class="avatar"> dky.tehkingd.u:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Our Hazard Course is six maps long, and I’ll be honest here, a good amount of the reason WHY it’s taken this long is because of the aforementioned feature creep problem, and our failure to come together early with a unified vision. If you establish a solid vision with your teammates early on, and come up with a very clear project scope right from the start, you could probably make a LOT more progress than we did, in a shorter amount of time. I only mention that because it’s one of the many things I regret about HC. Just wanna make sure others don’t fall into the same traps that we did!</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I am currently brainstorming an idea for the layout of The Portal Device’s A map. It’s pretty difficult, to be honest- there’s a lot of things I have to consider if it’s going to be as realistic as possible. I’ll also make sure Sage gets some input into the level’s design. That way we won’t have the problem you had with conflicting versions.</p>
<p>Guess It’s been a while since I visited your Mod DB page- forgot that the Hazard Course is 6 maps long, not 4. Glad I checked it again, looks like we might get a release later this year. Looking forward to it!</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/bringing-half-life-0-52-into-black-mesa/14317/10">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/bringing-half-life-0-52-into-black-mesa/14317/10</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jul 2015 00:37:09 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14317-10</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/bringing-half-life-0-52-into-black-mesa/14317.rss">Bringing Half-Life 0.52 into Black Mesa</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Bringing Half-Life 0.52 into Black Mesa</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Sage_J_Fox]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I suppose one big thing that wasn’t stated, is this going to be just a <span class="bbcode-i">map pack</span> for Black Mesa, or a full-on mod? We won’t be able to do things like new weapons or NPCs (beyond just simple model swaps) without making a mod, and we won’t be able to do those things in a mod if we don’t have a programmer.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/bringing-half-life-0-52-into-black-mesa/14317/9">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/bringing-half-life-0-52-into-black-mesa/14317/9</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jul 2015 22:56:34 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14317-9</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/bringing-half-life-0-52-into-black-mesa/14317.rss">Bringing Half-Life 0.52 into Black Mesa</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Bringing Half-Life 0.52 into Black Mesa</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[dky.tehkingd.u]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Our Hazard Course is six maps long, and I’ll be honest here, a good amount of the reason WHY it’s taken this long is because of the aforementioned feature creep problem, and our failure to come together early with a unified vision. If you establish a solid vision with your teammates early on, and come up with a very clear project scope right from the start, you could probably make a LOT more progress than we did, in a shorter amount of time.</p>
<p>I only mention that because it’s one of the many things I regret about HC. Just wanna make sure others don’t fall into the same traps that we did!</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/bringing-half-life-0-52-into-black-mesa/14317/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/bringing-half-life-0-52-into-black-mesa/14317/8</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jul 2015 21:48:56 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14317-8</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/bringing-half-life-0-52-into-black-mesa/14317.rss">Bringing Half-Life 0.52 into Black Mesa</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Bringing Half-Life 0.52 into Black Mesa</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[MisterDigitalGuy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Yeah, I do think that I should probably plan it out a bit more- at this point almost all the plans are in my head (which isn’t always the best idea), and the plan I have written down for the original map in The Portal Device is somewhat vague, only producing a very rudimentary image of the level. Problem is, I haven’t attempted to tackle such a large project before. Your Hazard Course remake is only about 4 maps long, but work is still ongoing- so you can probably imagine how long 15+ maps will take to recreate. That said, I’ll probably start laying out a plan tonight. Fortunately, it’s not too late for me to start planning. The first map is still heavy WIP, mostly dev textures and a few props. The planning will probably be the most important when it comes to detailing, but I do think having it around, even in the early phases, would be a good idea. Plus, there might be some points in which I want to share my plans with the public (that is, if they want spoilers).</p>
<p>As someone who is working on a remake project themselves, you can probably come up with all sorts of helpful advice for someone who hasn’t done something like this before. And hey, if I don’t succeed, I probably will have leaned a good deal. There are a lot of areas in which I could use improvement, but hopefully I can iron those out during the course of this project.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/bringing-half-life-0-52-into-black-mesa/14317/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/bringing-half-life-0-52-into-black-mesa/14317/7</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jul 2015 21:18:49 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14317-7</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/bringing-half-life-0-52-into-black-mesa/14317.rss">Bringing Half-Life 0.52 into Black Mesa</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Bringing Half-Life 0.52 into Black Mesa</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[dky.tehkingd.u]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Good luck!</p>
<p>If there’s one thing I would want to stress though, especially if you’re working as part of a team, it’s that I highly recommend that you sit down and plan out the exact scope of your project and your ideas on paper, before you do any major implementation. That will help to prevent <span class="bbcode-i">feature creep</span>, which can become a huge problem on projects that are based upon vague general ideas (such as “remake the Hazard Course” <em>cough cough</em>  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/wink.png?v=9" title=":wink:" class="emoji" alt=":wink:">  or in your case, “implement the alpha levels in Black Mesa”).</p>
<p>I know you’re probably excited about it, but if there’s anything I can tell you from experience, it’s that sometimes just charging guns blazing into Hammer isn’t always the best move!</p>
<p>Hope you succeed, and if not, I hope you at least learn a good amount from this project!</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/bringing-half-life-0-52-into-black-mesa/14317/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/bringing-half-life-0-52-into-black-mesa/14317/6</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jul 2015 19:33:10 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14317-6</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/bringing-half-life-0-52-into-black-mesa/14317.rss">Bringing Half-Life 0.52 into Black Mesa</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Bringing Half-Life 0.52 into Black Mesa</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[MisterDigitalGuy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Dragunov2">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/d/f08c70/40.png" class="avatar"> Dragunov2:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Looking forward to it, but it’s gonna take a long journey till an actual playable version…</p>
<p>Don’t underestimate the work needed to achieve this!</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I am quite aware that this kind of project is not something to be taken lightly. There will need to be a lot of work involved, and I am willing to do all that’s needed to make this a quality product. This project will also be somewhat of a learning experience- at this point I can make a decent map, but it’s not Black Mesa quality yet. I am sure that I’ll receive a fair amount of advice along the way that will help improve the quality of my maps, which is one of the ways I’m hoping to be able to improve my mapping skill. So yes, it will be a long journey, but it is one I am fully willing to take.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/bringing-half-life-0-52-into-black-mesa/14317/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/bringing-half-life-0-52-into-black-mesa/14317/5</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jul 2015 18:50:44 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14317-5</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/bringing-half-life-0-52-into-black-mesa/14317.rss">Bringing Half-Life 0.52 into Black Mesa</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Bringing Half-Life 0.52 into Black Mesa</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Sage_J_Fox]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Oh no doubt, but, I have a good feeling. Even in its Alpha, some of that Half-Life magic is there. The levels are very sparse on details in many places, but, you can <span class="bbcode-i">feel</span> the intent. It’s why I’m choosing to tackle the Alien Research Labs, in many places I feel like I see what was in Valve’s head for that level way back in '97.</p>
<p>It’s very clearly what ended up becoming Questionable Ethics in retail, but, it has its own flair that I think will really shine with a Black Mesa level of detail.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/bringing-half-life-0-52-into-black-mesa/14317/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/bringing-half-life-0-52-into-black-mesa/14317/4</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jul 2015 17:46:25 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14317-4</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/bringing-half-life-0-52-into-black-mesa/14317.rss">Bringing Half-Life 0.52 into Black Mesa</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Bringing Half-Life 0.52 into Black Mesa</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Dragunov2]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Looking forward to it, but it’s gonna take a long journey till an actual playable version…</p>
<p>Don’t underestimate the work needed to achieve this!</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/bringing-half-life-0-52-into-black-mesa/14317/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/bringing-half-life-0-52-into-black-mesa/14317/3</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jul 2015 17:35:21 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14317-3</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/bringing-half-life-0-52-into-black-mesa/14317.rss">Bringing Half-Life 0.52 into Black Mesa</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Bringing Half-Life 0.52 into Black Mesa</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[MisterDigitalGuy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Double posting here, but I thought I’d give a quick update for anyone watching this thread. Sage J. Fox has volunteered to help out on the project, and will be helping with the recreate of Alien Research Labs, as well as providing models of some of the cut enemies and weapons (such as the flamethrower). You might see a media update in the near future, possibly for the chapter I’m currently working on (The Portal Device). That’s all for now, I’ll keep you informed of any future updates.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/bringing-half-life-0-52-into-black-mesa/14317/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/bringing-half-life-0-52-into-black-mesa/14317/2</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jul 2015 17:25:23 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14317-2</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/bringing-half-life-0-52-into-black-mesa/14317.rss">Bringing Half-Life 0.52 into Black Mesa</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Bringing Half-Life 0.52 into Black Mesa</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[MisterDigitalGuy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><font face="Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif">Some of you may have heard about the leaked Half-Life alpha released to the public a few years ago, which included early versions of some of the Half-Life levels- as well as items which never made it into the final game, such as cut chapters, cut weapons, cut enemies, and so on. Seeing Half-Life in its alpha state got me thinking: if Valve had stuck to what it had originally had in mind for Half-Life, what would Black Mesa look like then? How would the maps of the alpha look if redesigned in the more versatile Source engine and redesigned in a way that would make more logical sense? So I have decided to re-map the 15 alpha maps in the style of Black Mesa (they might not be quite as good, but I’m trying to bring them as close to Black Mesa quality as I can), adding in various improvements to them along the way. I might have a few questions about mapping, as I am not without areas in which I could use improvement. But enough introduction, let’s take a look of what I have in mind for this small project.<br>
</font><br>
<span class="bbcode-b"><font face="Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif"><span class="bbcode-i"><span class="bbcode-u">The Maps</span></span></font></span><br>
[font=‘Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif’]If you were paying attention in my introduction, you’d know that this project involves re-mapping and improving the 15 maps released in the leaked alpha of Half-Life. However, this won’t be 100% loyal to the alpha, as many areas need improvement. Be it an issue with realistic design, or poor level design in general (some of the levels are somewhat mazelike, and I don’t want the player to be confused about where to go next), the alpha maps are in need of some serious work. You can also expect an improvement in continuity- some of the alpha maps had no clear connection to the next level. Most of these fixes won’t be too large, like a connection from the Security Complex’s C map to A map, or a connection from the end of Alien Research Labs to the start of Communications Center. However, I am planning to add an original C map to the first chapter (The Portal Device), which will establish a linkage between it and the Office Complex- as well as integrating two areas seen in early Half-Life concept art. Another thing that will have to be added to the maps is health and ammunition pickups. Since I’m not an expert on pickup placement, don’t hesitate to tell me your ideas on how I could improve the placement of items around the map. Furthermore, I am only planning to remake the maps included in the alpha <span class="bbcode-u">at this point</span>. If all goes well, I may also start mapping some of the chapters that were going to be in the alpha, but didn’t make it in (such as the early version of Blast Pit). Don’t count on anything at this point,  but if I decide to work on the missing chapters, I’ll let you know. Finally, if you see something, and you think it needs improvement (or you just have an idea), tell me! I am fully open to your suggestions.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b"><span class="bbcode-i"><span class="bbcode-u">The Team</span></span></span><br>
At this point, this is a one man project. However, if you think you can help me out, just tell me. I’m not setting a quota for team members, but I would say about 5 mappers maximum- one per chapter including me (Quick edit: It would probably also be a good idea to have people to run detail work on the maps), so it shouldn’t matter what your area of expertise is. And who knows? Maybe I’ll have a team, maybe I won’t. If I have a team, it would mean that this could be released sooner, but if I don’t have a team, I’ll manage. My only criteria is that you have a fair amount of knowledge of Hammer editor (that is, if you would like to help with the mapping). You don’t have to be phenomenally good at making maps (although if you are, that’s great!), just fairly good. It shouldn’t really matter how you ask me- ask on the post, send me a message, it doesn’t really make a difference. Just remember that if you are helping with mapping, I might feel it necessary to make some changes to your map- however, as good teamwork goes, you can also make changes to the maps I make, should you find it necessary. But hey, that’s how development works. If the black mesa team can properly work together, I don’t see why we shouldn’t be able to (okay, there might be a few reasons why we might not be able to get along, but I’m hoping that we won’t have to deal with them).</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b"><span class="bbcode-i"><span class="bbcode-u">The Release</span></span></span><br>
I can’t say much for a release date around now- it all depends on who’s working on it, as well as motivation. However, I will say that you can expect a release in two parts- the first part will feature chapters 1-3, and the second part will feature chapters 8-10 (as for chapters 4-7,as I said earlier, it will depend on how well the rest of it works out). At this point, my plan is to finish working on the first part before moving on to the second part. However, that plan might change depending on the number of people working on the project. If I’m nearing a release, I’ll let you know.</p>
<p>Hope that wasn’t too long. Let me know what you think, and I’ll get back to you (someday).[/font]</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/bringing-half-life-0-52-into-black-mesa/14317/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/bringing-half-life-0-52-into-black-mesa/14317/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 18 Jul 2015 21:53:55 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14317-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/bringing-half-life-0-52-into-black-mesa/14317.rss">Bringing Half-Life 0.52 into Black Mesa</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
