<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Tank in Garage on Lambda Core [Fixed]</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/tank-in-garage-on-lambda-core-fixed/10397</link>
    <description>I got stuck in at the beginning of Lambda Core in the garage area. I opened the closed double doors and the tank&#39;s turret started turning to face me so I pulled out the rocket launcher and destroyed it.

After killing the remaining aliens and soldiers I wandered around trying to figure out where to go next for about 15 mins or so before figuring something probably didn&#39;t go as scripted and so I reloaded an auto-save.

This time I waited and didn&#39;t open the doors right away and let the battle inside the garage play out a little and the tank blew open the doors like it should have.

TL;DR: I blew up the tank in Lambda Core before it destroyed the doors and I was unable to proceed.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 16 Sep 2012 21:33:12 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>In-game Issues (Mod)</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/tank-in-garage-on-lambda-core-fixed/10397.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Tank in Garage on Lambda Core [Fixed]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[supercanadaboy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I got stuck in at the beginning of Lambda Core in the garage area. I opened the closed double doors and the tank’s turret started turning to face me so I pulled out the rocket launcher and destroyed it.</p>
<p>After killing the remaining aliens and soldiers I wandered around trying to figure out where to go next for about 15 mins or so before figuring something probably didn’t go as scripted and so I reloaded an auto-save.</p>
<p>This time I waited and didn’t open the doors right away and let the battle inside the garage play out a little and the tank blew open the doors like it should have.</p>
<p>TL;DR: I blew up the tank in Lambda Core before it destroyed the doors and I was unable to proceed.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/tank-in-garage-on-lambda-core-fixed/10397/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/tank-in-garage-on-lambda-core-fixed/10397/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 16 Sep 2012 21:33:12 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-10397-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/tank-in-garage-on-lambda-core-fixed/10397.rss">Tank in Garage on Lambda Core [Fixed]</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
