<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>computer freezing/crashing</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/computer-freezing-crashing/3239</link>
    <description>Hey guys,

I recently got a problem with my computer. After a few minutes of using it, it freezes or even crashes entirely. Weird thing is I also had it on for a very long time without doing anything, and it didn&#39;t crash. I&#39;m thinking this may be happening everytime I&#39;m doing something related to the internet(browsing the internet, chatting on steam, etc...) but I&#39;m not sure...

Also the way it crashes often varies, most of the time it just stops responding to my keyboard and mouse and I have to turn it off. Other times it just crashes, or restarts instantly, one time it even crashed and went into a weird long-ongoing beep noise, like those heart meters in hospital when someone dies... I also had some BSODs.

I&#39;m typing this from my school computer, hoping to get this fixed soon. It might be a while before I again respond to this thread, for obvious reasons. I guess I&#39;ll have to make do with playing PS2 games and watching TV for now, oh well. Tomb Raider is always fun ^^.

Well, bye... :fffuuu:</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 04 Mar 2010 09:47:51 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Technology and Gaming</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/computer-freezing-crashing/3239.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>computer freezing/crashing</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Doom]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I just brought it away to a guy who knows a lot about computers, hoping he sees what’s going on.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/computer-freezing-crashing/3239/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/computer-freezing-crashing/3239/4</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 04 Mar 2010 09:47:51 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3239-4</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/computer-freezing-crashing/3239.rss">computer freezing/crashing</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>computer freezing/crashing</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[sersoft]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Disable your network adapter and play a few games offline, if it stops freezing you might have to get a new network card.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/computer-freezing-crashing/3239/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/computer-freezing-crashing/3239/3</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 03 Mar 2010 14:29:28 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3239-3</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/computer-freezing-crashing/3239.rss">computer freezing/crashing</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>computer freezing/crashing</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[hammythomas]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Check for recently installed software or hardware.If the lockups started to happen after you installed a new peace of hardware, new software program, or new drivers, uninstall it and see if the problem goes away.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/computer-freezing-crashing/3239/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/computer-freezing-crashing/3239/2</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 03 Mar 2010 12:10:54 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3239-2</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/computer-freezing-crashing/3239.rss">computer freezing/crashing</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>computer freezing/crashing</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Doom]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Hey guys,</p>
<p>I recently got a problem with my computer. After a few minutes of using it, it freezes or even crashes entirely. Weird thing is I also had it on for a very long time without doing anything, and it didn’t crash. I’m thinking this may be happening everytime I’m doing something related to the internet(browsing the internet, chatting on steam, etc…) but I’m not sure…</p>
<p>Also the way it crashes often varies, most of the time it just stops responding to my keyboard and mouse and I have to turn it off. Other times it just crashes, or restarts instantly, one time it even crashed and went into a weird long-ongoing beep noise, like those heart meters in hospital when someone dies… I also had some BSODs.</p>
<p>I’m typing this from my school computer, hoping to get this fixed soon. It might be a while before I again respond to this thread, for obvious reasons. I guess I’ll have to make do with playing PS2 games and watching TV for now, oh well. Tomb Raider is always fun ^^.</p>
<p>Well, bye… :fffuuu:</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/computer-freezing-crashing/3239/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/computer-freezing-crashing/3239/1</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 03 Mar 2010 10:52:44 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3239-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/computer-freezing-crashing/3239.rss">computer freezing/crashing</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
