<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Wrong achievement being displayed in top right hand corner (Nuclear Fishin)</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/wrong-achievement-being-displayed-in-top-right-hand-corner-nuclear-fishin/14807</link>
    <description>I can&#39;t really screenshot the issue since I can&#39;t really reproduce it,  but it&#39;s easy to explain:
When I unlocked the achievement Nuclear Fishin by killing the ichthyosaurs in the dam section of ST with the tau cannon, I got the Steam achievement, BUT instead in the top right hand corner (on the ingame-achievement-display-thingy) it displayed &quot;Universal Gravitation (1/1)&quot; - the achievement you get by getting killed by one of your own snarks.
This MAY have something to do with the fact that the achievement I unlocked prior to Nuclear Fishin was indeed Universal Gravitation, that a coincidence?!
Anyway, it&#39;s a really small glitch and not that important, but whatever... still counts I suppose.

EDIT: Okay, it&#39;s an issue with Achievements in general. Just minutes later I got the achievement &quot;Unified Coupling Theorem&quot; when a headcrab got eaten by a barnacle (or... coupled.. with it I suppose), but it instead displayed &quot;Nuclear Fishin&#39; (1/1)&quot; in the top right hand corner. So apparently it simply displays an achievement you unlocked previously instead of the correct one. Is that only an issue for me or have others experienced this as well? It&#39;s pretty strange.
Oh, and this time I got a screenshot of it, but I dont think it&#39;s gonna help a lot.

[spoiler]
[attach=4862,none,1920][/attach]
[/spoiler]
![20160607224839_1.jpg|690x500](upload://mMRHDHVdgIqSwQD4qhfIsLUzILW.jpeg)</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2016 20:47:29 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>In-game Issues</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/wrong-achievement-being-displayed-in-top-right-hand-corner-nuclear-fishin/14807.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Wrong achievement being displayed in top right hand corner (Nuclear Fishin)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[AsinoEsel]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I can’t really screenshot the issue since I can’t really reproduce it,  but it’s easy to explain:<br>
When I unlocked the achievement Nuclear Fishin by killing the ichthyosaurs in the dam section of ST with the tau cannon, I got the Steam achievement, BUT instead in the top right hand corner (on the ingame-achievement-display-thingy) it displayed “Universal Gravitation (1/1)” - the achievement you get by getting killed by one of your own snarks.<br>
This MAY have something to do with the fact that the achievement I unlocked prior to Nuclear Fishin was indeed Universal Gravitation, that a coincidence?!<br>
Anyway, it’s a really small glitch and not that important, but whatever… still counts I suppose.</p>
<p>EDIT: Okay, it’s an issue with Achievements in general. Just minutes later I got the achievement “Unified Coupling Theorem” when a headcrab got eaten by a barnacle (or… coupled… with it I suppose), but it instead displayed “Nuclear Fishin’ (1/1)” in the top right hand corner. So apparently it simply displays an achievement you unlocked previously instead of the correct one. Is that only an issue for me or have others experienced this as well? It’s pretty strange.<br>
Oh, and this time I got a screenshot of it, but I dont think it’s gonna help a lot.</p>
<div class="spoiler">
<p>[attach=4862,none,1920][/attach]</p>
</div>
<p><div class="lightbox-wrapper"><a class="lightbox" href="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/original/2X/9/9fb5ee6ba5784b366219dcf46a9e0926169327d4.jpeg" data-download-href="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/9fb5ee6ba5784b366219dcf46a9e0926169327d4" title="20160607224839_1.jpg"><img src="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/optimized/2X/9/9fb5ee6ba5784b366219dcf46a9e0926169327d4_2_690x500.jpeg" alt="20160607224839_1.jpg" data-base62-sha1="mMRHDHVdgIqSwQD4qhfIsLUzILW" width="690" height="500" srcset="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/optimized/2X/9/9fb5ee6ba5784b366219dcf46a9e0926169327d4_2_690x500.jpeg, https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/optimized/2X/9/9fb5ee6ba5784b366219dcf46a9e0926169327d4_2_1035x750.jpeg 1.5x, https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/optimized/2X/9/9fb5ee6ba5784b366219dcf46a9e0926169327d4_2_1380x1000.jpeg 2x" data-small-upload="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/optimized/2X/9/9fb5ee6ba5784b366219dcf46a9e0926169327d4_2_10x10.png"><div class="meta"><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-far-image svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#far-image"></use></svg><span class="filename">20160607224839_1.jpg</span><span class="informations">1920×1080 809 KB</span><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-discourse-expand svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#discourse-expand"></use></svg></div></a></div></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/wrong-achievement-being-displayed-in-top-right-hand-corner-nuclear-fishin/14807/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/wrong-achievement-being-displayed-in-top-right-hand-corner-nuclear-fishin/14807/1</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2016 20:47:29 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14807-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/wrong-achievement-being-displayed-in-top-right-hand-corner-nuclear-fishin/14807.rss">Wrong achievement being displayed in top right hand corner (Nuclear Fishin)</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
