<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>BLACK MESA MULTIPLAYER (BMP)</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/black-mesa-multiplayer-bmp/14136</link>
    <description>i wrote it in steam discussions but it seems that crowbar collective are most likely to read it through here
(ill just copy paste what i said to here)

the MP is very much like the original DM (maps and weapon obviously) and its nice.
but i think there&#39;s few things that crowbar collective should change.
*the game is not fast enough, while in the original DM you jumped and ran and moved very quickly in BMS_MP you move very slowly every time i jump i feel &quot;fat&quot; and climbing on ladders and etc. anyway the game needs to get faster IN EVERYTHING (including fire rate).
*the FOV must get higher i know that some computers can&#39;t handle high FOV but still put that option its critical for me at least
*put voice chat feature

besides all of thos i think the game is awesome and your&#39;e awesome keep the good work (best MOD ever) 

P.S. i found one bug that says &quot;warning: overflowed CClientRenderablesList group 7&quot;</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 27 May 2015 21:25:22 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>The Cafeteria</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/black-mesa-multiplayer-bmp/14136.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>BLACK MESA MULTIPLAYER (BMP)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[onder_lite]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>i wrote it in steam discussions but it seems that crowbar collective are most likely to read it through here<br>
(ill just copy paste what i said to here)</p>
<p>the MP is very much like the original DM (maps and weapon obviously) and its nice.<br>
but i think there’s few things that crowbar collective should change.<br>
*the game is not fast enough, while in the original DM you jumped and ran and moved very quickly in BMS_MP you move very slowly every time i jump i feel “fat” and climbing on ladders and etc. anyway the game needs to get faster IN EVERYTHING (including fire rate).<br>
*the FOV must get higher i know that some computers can’t handle high FOV but still put that option its critical for me at least<br>
*put voice chat feature</p>
<p>besides all of thos i think the game is awesome and your’e awesome keep the good work (best MOD ever)</p>
<p>P.S. i found one bug that says “warning: overflowed CClientRenderablesList group 7”</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/black-mesa-multiplayer-bmp/14136/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/black-mesa-multiplayer-bmp/14136/1</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 27 May 2015 21:25:22 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14136-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/black-mesa-multiplayer-bmp/14136.rss">BLACK MESA MULTIPLAYER (BMP)</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
