<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>My Ordeal</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/my-ordeal/12119</link>
    <description>Hello Guys

Its been forever since I have posted or been on the site. I have had issues upon issues in my life and gaming has been pushed aside for the most part til I get it together. Most recently my life changed significantly as a result of A recent surgery I had, the surgery I had was for a spinal deformity known as scoliosis which is a curvature of the spine. The Surgeon I went to said that my spine has become progressively worse in the past 6 years and il require an extensive correction of the spine, after months of waiting I was given a date for my surgery, November 14th which was the worse possible day as it was my birthday. The surgery crept up on me and I was getting a little worried and nervous but the day finally came my 20th birthday and spinal fusion surgery I was taken into the operating room and there were tons of people preparing knifes tools and whatever they were going use to invade my back and then I was put to sleep. I woke up more then 6 hours later in intensive care and then eventually was moved to the ward to further recover. The day after my surgery they started me walking for the first time with the new hardware, the pain was immense but it probably could have been twice as bad without the medication button I was given. Day 3 after my surgery they noticed I was very weak and likely anemic from the surgery so they gave me a blood transfusion which is where everything went downhill very fast because within six hours i was coughing so much i brought up blood that I was rushed to the ICU, eventually I could no longer breath on my own, all this was caused by a rare reaction to the blood/plasma given to me. no longer being able to breath on my own i was on a forced air mask that was so painful having just had surgery. Eventually things became so bad that I went psycho due to lack of oxygen to the brain I was told I was throwing stuff at the nurses and I tried to kick my own mother in the face and calling them every bad word in the book so eventually i was tied down. I fought the restraints so much that I had bruises the length of my arms I wouldn&#39;t stop so they had to put me into an induced coma which I remained for 2 days. During my episode I was having very traumatic hallucinations and nightmares of people trying to kill me and forcing me to take illicit drugs and most of these people in my episode were the nurses which made it much more real in my mind. After the 2 days I awoke by mistake when a ICU nurse left the room for a few minutes, I ripped the feeding tube from out of my throat and was yelling and screaming thinking that everyone was trying to kill me. They assured me I was safe but I never believed them until my father showed up and I knew I was finally safe in my own head. I remained in the ICU for another week fighting off kidney failure and recovering from the respiratory distress. The cruelness of the ICU was the worst as I could not eat or drink for a very long time and the oxygen given would dry my mouth out. They swabbed my mouth but it was never enough, nurses would walk by when starting their shifts carrying coffee and food and I was stuck in a bed! Eventually I was given the right to drink and then slowly food and eventually finally moved to the ward again where I started physio again. More walking each day which took so much out of me having low hemoglobin in the blood causing severe weakness and a heart that nearly raced on out of my chest cavity hitting 170 bps, my family visited almost every day as I was lost and alone most of the time and eventually a few friends came regularly to see me each one making and brightening my day. Finally after 27 days in the hospital I was finally able to go home and recover. Today I feel great and am almost back to normal, i still have pain but nothing unmanageable. I am now looking to pursue my job in IT and get a job within the next few months.

Below are a few picture of the x-rays and scar I have 2 titanium rods and 22 screws! Sorry for the rotation issues :fffuuu:

Before X-ray
![](upload://6I6PuuEmauXO02up6hgyYXrei26.jpeg)

Before and after X-ray
![](upload://6I6PuuEmauXO02up6hgyYXrei26.jpeg)

Before and after X-ray Side View
![](upload://6I6PuuEmauXO02up6hgyYXrei26.jpeg)

Chest X-ray of semi clear lungs
![](upload://6I6PuuEmauXO02up6hgyYXrei26.jpeg)

Chest X-ray of bad lungs
![](upload://6I6PuuEmauXO02up6hgyYXrei26.jpeg)

Photo of Scar
![](upload://6I6PuuEmauXO02up6hgyYXrei26.jpeg)</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 19 Feb 2013 06:31:23 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Show Off</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/my-ordeal/12119.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>My Ordeal</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[k3nny1550]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Okay, tried copying page links for the photos. Holy shit. O.o;</p>
<p>Glad you made it back in one piece.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/my-ordeal/12119/10">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/my-ordeal/12119/10</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 19 Feb 2013 06:31:23 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12119-10</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/my-ordeal/12119.rss">My Ordeal</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My Ordeal</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[brokenfridgehinge]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Did you Cook some meth to raise money for your surgery? But seriously, hope you recover quickly.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/my-ordeal/12119/9">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/my-ordeal/12119/9</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 19 Feb 2013 05:40:42 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12119-9</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/my-ordeal/12119.rss">My Ordeal</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My Ordeal</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Heisenberg]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>If you have a similar problem don’t let it progress. Thanks guys for the kind words! Use my x-rays for wallpaper I don’t mind lol, use it in your mods aswell lol and yea it was pretty messed up. Message me om here or add me on steam if you have questions about anything</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/my-ordeal/12119/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/my-ordeal/12119/8</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 19 Feb 2013 04:57:57 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12119-8</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/my-ordeal/12119.rss">My Ordeal</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My Ordeal</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[warpedfreeman]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>im afraid that i have a similar issue :[</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/my-ordeal/12119/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/my-ordeal/12119/7</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 Feb 2013 15:41:52 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12119-7</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/my-ordeal/12119.rss">My Ordeal</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My Ordeal</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[xalener]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Holy shit welcome back.</p>
<p>Good to see you recovering.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/my-ordeal/12119/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/my-ordeal/12119/6</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 Feb 2013 15:06:24 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12119-6</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/my-ordeal/12119.rss">My Ordeal</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My Ordeal</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Disturbulator]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I really don’t want to sound mean or anything like that but hoooly shit your Pre-op spine in the second picture is the nastiest thing Ive seen for a long long time.<br>
Like, fresh out of an F16 Accident kind of bent.</p>
<p>On a more upright note, the recovery period will be gone before you know it, it was for me at least. But then again, I was shot in the face with a laser; you had your spine readjusted. Each to their own, I guess.</p>
<p>And best of luck with your back!</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/my-ordeal/12119/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/my-ordeal/12119/5</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 Feb 2013 09:31:19 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12119-5</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/my-ordeal/12119.rss">My Ordeal</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My Ordeal</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[k3nny1550]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>All of the links are broken for me. -_-</p>
<p>Glad to hear you’re doing better, that must have been one crazy month…</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/my-ordeal/12119/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/my-ordeal/12119/4</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 Feb 2013 06:52:19 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12119-4</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/my-ordeal/12119.rss">My Ordeal</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My Ordeal</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypt]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Is it in bad taste to say I’d use one of your X-Rays as a desktop wallpaper?</p>
<p>Anyway, good to hear your starting to feel normal again. Sounds like a hell of an experience.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/my-ordeal/12119/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/my-ordeal/12119/3</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 Feb 2013 06:26:51 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12119-3</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/my-ordeal/12119.rss">My Ordeal</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My Ordeal</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Eric_Fong]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Wow… hope you get better faster.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/my-ordeal/12119/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/my-ordeal/12119/2</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 Feb 2013 05:39:57 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12119-2</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/my-ordeal/12119.rss">My Ordeal</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My Ordeal</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Heisenberg]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Hello Guys</p>
<p>Its been forever since I have posted or been on the site. I have had issues upon issues in my life and gaming has been pushed aside for the most part til I get it together. Most recently my life changed significantly as a result of A recent surgery I had, the surgery I had was for a spinal deformity known as scoliosis which is a curvature of the spine. The Surgeon I went to said that my spine has become progressively worse in the past 6 years and il require an extensive correction of the spine, after months of waiting I was given a date for my surgery, November 14th which was the worse possible day as it was my birthday. The surgery crept up on me and I was getting a little worried and nervous but the day finally came my 20th birthday and spinal fusion surgery I was taken into the operating room and there were tons of people preparing knifes tools and whatever they were going use to invade my back and then I was put to sleep. I woke up more then 6 hours later in intensive care and then eventually was moved to the ward to further recover. The day after my surgery they started me walking for the first time with the new hardware, the pain was immense but it probably could have been twice as bad without the medication button I was given. Day 3 after my surgery they noticed I was very weak and likely anemic from the surgery so they gave me a blood transfusion which is where everything went downhill very fast because within six hours i was coughing so much i brought up blood that I was rushed to the ICU, eventually I could no longer breath on my own, all this was caused by a rare reaction to the blood/plasma given to me. no longer being able to breath on my own i was on a forced air mask that was so painful having just had surgery. Eventually things became so bad that I went psycho due to lack of oxygen to the brain I was told I was throwing stuff at the nurses and I tried to kick my own mother in the face and calling them every bad word in the book so eventually i was tied down. I fought the restraints so much that I had bruises the length of my arms I wouldn’t stop so they had to put me into an induced coma which I remained for 2 days. During my episode I was having very traumatic hallucinations and nightmares of people trying to kill me and forcing me to take illicit drugs and most of these people in my episode were the nurses which made it much more real in my mind. After the 2 days I awoke by mistake when a ICU nurse left the room for a few minutes, I ripped the feeding tube from out of my throat and was yelling and screaming thinking that everyone was trying to kill me. They assured me I was safe but I never believed them until my father showed up and I knew I was finally safe in my own head. I remained in the ICU for another week fighting off kidney failure and recovering from the respiratory distress. The cruelness of the ICU was the worst as I could not eat or drink for a very long time and the oxygen given would dry my mouth out. They swabbed my mouth but it was never enough, nurses would walk by when starting their shifts carrying coffee and food and I was stuck in a bed! Eventually I was given the right to drink and then slowly food and eventually finally moved to the ward again where I started physio again. More walking each day which took so much out of me having low hemoglobin in the blood causing severe weakness and a heart that nearly raced on out of my chest cavity hitting 170 bps, my family visited almost every day as I was lost and alone most of the time and eventually a few friends came regularly to see me each one making and brightening my day. Finally after 27 days in the hospital I was finally able to go home and recover. Today I feel great and am almost back to normal, i still have pain but nothing unmanageable. I am now looking to pursue my job in IT and get a job within the next few months.</p>
<p>Below are a few picture of the x-rays and scar I have 2 titanium rods and 22 screws! Sorry for the rotation issues :fffuuu:</p>
<p>Before X-ray<br>
<img src="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/original/2X/2/2f0984456f8dd47c5beb0a68b72c3d6cf62ef2aa.jpeg" alt="" data-base62-sha1="6I6PuuEmauXO02up6hgyYXrei26" width="300" height="300"></p>
<p>Before and after X-ray<br>
<img src="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/original/2X/2/2f0984456f8dd47c5beb0a68b72c3d6cf62ef2aa.jpeg" alt="" data-base62-sha1="6I6PuuEmauXO02up6hgyYXrei26" width="300" height="300"></p>
<p>Before and after X-ray Side View<br>
<img src="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/original/2X/2/2f0984456f8dd47c5beb0a68b72c3d6cf62ef2aa.jpeg" alt="" data-base62-sha1="6I6PuuEmauXO02up6hgyYXrei26" width="300" height="300"></p>
<p>Chest X-ray of semi clear lungs<br>
<img src="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/original/2X/2/2f0984456f8dd47c5beb0a68b72c3d6cf62ef2aa.jpeg" alt="" data-base62-sha1="6I6PuuEmauXO02up6hgyYXrei26" width="300" height="300"></p>
<p>Chest X-ray of bad lungs<br>
<img src="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/original/2X/2/2f0984456f8dd47c5beb0a68b72c3d6cf62ef2aa.jpeg" alt="" data-base62-sha1="6I6PuuEmauXO02up6hgyYXrei26" width="300" height="300"></p>
<p>Photo of Scar<br>
<img src="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/original/2X/2/2f0984456f8dd47c5beb0a68b72c3d6cf62ef2aa.jpeg" alt="" data-base62-sha1="6I6PuuEmauXO02up6hgyYXrei26" width="300" height="300"></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/my-ordeal/12119/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/my-ordeal/12119/1</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 Feb 2013 04:38:34 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12119-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/my-ordeal/12119.rss">My Ordeal</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
