<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>My List of bugs + Spinning &#39;limb&#39; in vent where scientists are massacred. [Video]</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/my-list-of-bugs-spinning-limb-in-vent-where-scientists-are-massacred-video/10595</link>
    <description>Here is a video of the glitch: [url]https://youtu.be/GMof0tZefm4[/url]

It&#39;s the first little scene for 10 seconds.

It happens again and again no matter what save I reload just after the Calamity in Chapter 1.

The limb spins around for about 30 seconds before dropping out of thin air. Shooting it, and well, doing anything, even cheating and getting grenades/charges/etc. and throwing them in the vent does nothing to stop it spinning until it just stops on its own lol.

It&#39;s not really a big deal. But this is the section for bugs.

Also I&#39;ve found that sometimes while walking in any level my player will &#39;teleport&#39; about 7 spaces in the direction I am walking. It&#39;s not lag, it&#39;s like a &#39;super run&#39; almost like the game messed up my movement speed for a moment.

On top of this, the game crashes very, VERY often if I am doing something whilst walking through a loading screen. For instance, reloading, jumping, shooting etc. The game almost always exists whilst walking through any loading point if I am not simply just &#39;walking&#39;.

Another bug was in the very first elevator after the Calamity. If you run out of the elevator and hurt yourself when you fall deliberately. The loading screen will either cause you to be stuck, after it loads. So you can&#39;t move at all, even when you are standing on solid ground with absolutely nothing in your way.

I&#39;ve got a few more but I&#39;ve forgotten lots. I just focused more on enjoying the game, than pointing out on bugs.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 17 Sep 2012 18:26:38 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>In-game Issues (Mod)</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/my-list-of-bugs-spinning-limb-in-vent-where-scientists-are-massacred-video/10595.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>My List of bugs + Spinning &#39;limb&#39; in vent where scientists are massacred. [Video]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Leijonasisu]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Here is a video of the glitch: <a href="https://youtu.be/GMof0tZefm4" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://youtu.be/GMof0tZefm4</a></p>
<p>It’s the first little scene for 10 seconds.</p>
<p>It happens again and again no matter what save I reload just after the Calamity in Chapter 1.</p>
<p>The limb spins around for about 30 seconds before dropping out of thin air. Shooting it, and well, doing anything, even cheating and getting grenades/charges/etc. and throwing them in the vent does nothing to stop it spinning until it just stops on its own lol.</p>
<p>It’s not really a big deal. But this is the section for bugs.</p>
<p>Also I’ve found that sometimes while walking in any level my player will ‘teleport’ about 7 spaces in the direction I am walking. It’s not lag, it’s like a ‘super run’ almost like the game messed up my movement speed for a moment.</p>
<p>On top of this, the game crashes very, VERY often if I am doing something whilst walking through a loading screen. For instance, reloading, jumping, shooting etc. The game almost always exists whilst walking through any loading point if I am not simply just ‘walking’.</p>
<p>Another bug was in the very first elevator after the Calamity. If you run out of the elevator and hurt yourself when you fall deliberately. The loading screen will either cause you to be stuck, after it loads. So you can’t move at all, even when you are standing on solid ground with absolutely nothing in your way.</p>
<p>I’ve got a few more but I’ve forgotten lots. I just focused more on enjoying the game, than pointing out on bugs.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/my-list-of-bugs-spinning-limb-in-vent-where-scientists-are-massacred-video/10595/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/my-list-of-bugs-spinning-limb-in-vent-where-scientists-are-massacred-video/10595/1</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 17 Sep 2012 18:26:38 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-10595-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/my-list-of-bugs-spinning-limb-in-vent-where-scientists-are-massacred-video/10595.rss">My List of bugs + Spinning &#39;limb&#39; in vent where scientists are massacred. [Video]</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
