<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Some thoughts and feedback on BM:DM.</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/some-thoughts-and-feedback-on-bm-dm/14022</link>
    <description>So I&#39;m quite new to the forums but I&#39;ve been following Black Mesa for years. To be more specific, I saw the project 6 years ago, thought it was cool and moved on with my life.
Now that it has been released on Steam, no matter how bad I am or was on Half Life series in general I still love playing it. I feel like my money was well spent, and I spent them specifically to support the developers and not just to buy the game.
So why am I directing my feedback to BM :smiley: M?
Well, because it has a lot of potential. Think of CS:GO.
I know there&#39;s a lot of people coming here with the same idea in mind, but I feel like it&#39;s easy to direct feedback to Dev&#39;s on these forums.
So what am I talking about? First of all, my general gameplay feedback on multiplayer, and on the second part will be some feature requests.
The first thing that I found awkward was the menu, it&#39;s not related to BM :smiley: M but when you go to change video settings in the middle of the game it tends to glitch out, not being able to press the buttons you need to press Esc twice.
Having to rejoin the game to change some graphical settings is also something I&#39;m not used to, as in CS:GO when I normally change those same settings (graphics quality) I don&#39;t have to leave the server.
But these things are in somewhat different boundary of fixing whats necessary and whats not, obviously the bug should be squashed but it&#39;s just a minor distraction having to rejoin most of the time.
The next thing that I found pretty weird was finding weapons in multiplayer. Now, as stupid as it may sound I&#39;ve never been or am an hardcore HL :smiley: M player. In fact, I suck (I don&#39;t even know the spawns). But one thing that I do remember is that the weapons in original Half Life were VERY visible from long distance, they were bulky bold weapons.
In BM :smiley: M I&#39;ve had struggle finding a revolver (again, I&#39;m a noob, don&#39;t hate me, just pointing out). I generally play on a decent resolution, my eyesight is also fine, but from time to time when taking the games pace into consideration, I don&#39;t have time to stare at the ground looking for a weapon. Finding darker guns in dark environments is an big issue, so one of the ways to resolve that would be to actually make them highlighted when close to them or aiming at them.
I know some hardcore players will be OUTRAGED by that. We won&#39;t want &quot;noobification&quot; of the game, but I think that the gameplay shouldn&#39;t be cluttered by graphics being a distraction (although I appreciate them), even if it&#39;s foliage (which is quite abundant).
Longjumps for everybody! Cant hate it, right? Nuuh, it&#39;s very bad. I can bail out of situations very easily even upon spawn just because I already have a LJ module. Everybody has one, so although it makes things more fast paced the LJ module doesn&#39;t feel rewarded.
I don&#39;t care if it even takes to add killstreaks to the game to get the LJ module, but as long as it&#39;s a spawned entity or not obtainable to everybody upon spawn I&#39;ll be fine.
I don&#39;t know what others think about that, but in HL :smiley: M I had to go through egon and gauss gun lava just to get that one silly LJ module.
The pistol was awkward (or glock, as you may call it), it really was. It felt like secondary fire was way too inaccurate while the primary fire was way too slow. I&#39;m not saying buff the pistol, but primary fire is nearly useless in such a fast paced game. Maybe switching RMB to LMB would help?

Here&#39;s some of my feature requests, besides the feedback. Interpret my feedback as you may, I may be wrong on some things but that&#39;s just my feedback from noob&#39;s POV.
One thing that I would like to request is some sort of matchmaking. Ridiculous, right? But that&#39;s one of the ways to help the game grow, as well as invite new players to the game a bit more engagingly. ALA CS:GO!
I think that griefers, trolls and cheaters would be inevitable, but it would have it&#39;s upside. BM :smiley: M truly is a game that could have a competitive scene (again, I might be retarded here but I would watch BM competitive matches over CS:GO any day).

Also, I think it would be really awesome if we could change our characters color (Hev suit, pants). Some sort of customization to make the game a bit more interactive would be cool.

So that&#39;s about it! Take it easy on me guys, and have a respectful discussion. Feel free to disagree and counterpoint my feedback, correct me!  :smiley:  


P.S - Are jihad suicide grenade bombers a feature or just something overlooked? I can easily LJ/bhop to an enemy with a premature grenade getting a few kills along a suicide.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 14 May 2015 17:07:49 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>The Cafeteria</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/some-thoughts-and-feedback-on-bm-dm/14022.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Some thoughts and feedback on BM:DM.</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[TextFAMGUY1]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Craig made a bunch of optimisations to this map which we’re putting in the next update. Hopefully this will help some of its issues.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/some-thoughts-and-feedback-on-bm-dm/14022/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/some-thoughts-and-feedback-on-bm-dm/14022/7</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 14 May 2015 17:07:49 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14022-7</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/some-thoughts-and-feedback-on-bm-dm/14022.rss">Some thoughts and feedback on BM:DM.</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Some thoughts and feedback on BM:DM.</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[TheGuma]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I am glad you guys have responded!<br>
Here is some more feedback I have gathered over the day.<br>
Mainly, performance related issues and possible fixes.</p>
<p>My PC is fairly decent, although not the best. I am planning on getting 2k RIG but for now I have to resort to what I have. It’s pretty humble, runs Bf3, CS:GO and GTA 5 just fine (without the highest settings, of course).<br>
I never get below 60 fps on any other game.<br>
However, here’s what happened today.<br>
No, it’s not an FPS drop. The FPS was constantly jumping from 40 fps to 20 fps on lowest graphics throughout the gameplay session.</p>
<p>(Also, as a map developer for other games I am aware of the difference between map optimizations and that the game is in early access… But feedback is not bad, right?)<br>
<div class="lightbox-wrapper"><a class="lightbox" href="https://images.akamai.steamusercontent.com/ugc/34119782387372510/5731A7F8832BEABEC9A2DA131F2F0587D3B0D431/" title="" rel="nofollow noopener"><img src="https://images.akamai.steamusercontent.com/ugc/34119782387372510/5731A7F8832BEABEC9A2DA131F2F0587D3B0D431/" alt="" width="690" height="388"><div class="meta"><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-far-image svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#far-image"></use></svg><span class="filename"></span><span class="informations">1600×900</span><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-discourse-expand svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#discourse-expand"></use></svg></div></a></div></p>
<p>In this picture you can see that I’m running on lowest graphics settings, here’s my computer specs.</p>
<p>Again, keep in mind that my computer still gets decent framerate on many new games, so that’s definitely not the specs related issue.</p>
<div class="spoiler">
<ul>
<li>Windows 8, 64bit</li>
<li>Intel Core I5-3210M CPU @ 2.50 GHz</li>
<li>8 GB Ram</li>
</ul>
</div>
<p>So here’s all the things that MIGHT be affecting the performance.<br>
First of all, phong and envmap (or specular) reflections are still apparent even on lowest graphics settings. Normally, these things should be possible to be changed.<br>
The map is big, but that’s not the problem here. Many small and tiny details do not fade out in the distance as they normally should (fixable).<br>
There are some shrub models on top of the hills in Bounce map, they do not fade out even when you are on a corner of a map. They do fade out when you are out of bounds, which is something you will never access without noclip.<br>
Also, $detail on certain textures is still visible on lowest graphics settings. $detail and especially envmap reflections should not be used on very large bare surfaces (even though it looks better).<br>
Water is also very common troughout the maps (most of them). However, again, it still reflects even on lowest graphics settings. There should be a way to disable specular, envmap and world reflections independently, as right now I think it’s what is hindering my performance.</p>
<p>Anyways, I’m getting a new PC soon so I hope that might fix it for me. I do understand things are a subject of change, but I still want to report back here on how things go.</p>
<p>Thank you for taking your time!</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/some-thoughts-and-feedback-on-bm-dm/14022/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/some-thoughts-and-feedback-on-bm-dm/14022/6</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 14 May 2015 17:03:32 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14022-6</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/some-thoughts-and-feedback-on-bm-dm/14022.rss">Some thoughts and feedback on BM:DM.</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Some thoughts and feedback on BM:DM.</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[TextFAMGUY1]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="fury">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/f/3bc359/40.png" class="avatar"> fury:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I made a map feedback topic one or two days ago… So far I gave feedback on gasworks and stalkyard. I plan to give feedback about bounce, too… But making decent feedback takes a lot of time and atm I want to work on my HLDM map more… But what I can tell you is, that you have at least 4 LJ modules on bounce and also 3 gauss. I already thought about some changes that could be made to bounce, but I will give detailed feedback later. Still I think there is not much feedback about my suggestions on gasworks and stalkyard. So please check the topic out and give feedback if you have the time  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=9" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>We read your thread. I’m not going to comment on it as I’ve got way too much going on at the moment, but rest assured that we read it.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/some-thoughts-and-feedback-on-bm-dm/14022/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/some-thoughts-and-feedback-on-bm-dm/14022/5</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 14 May 2015 13:52:41 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14022-5</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/some-thoughts-and-feedback-on-bm-dm/14022.rss">Some thoughts and feedback on BM:DM.</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Some thoughts and feedback on BM:DM.</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[fury]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote group-black-mesa-devs" data-username="TextFAMGUY1">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/user_avatar/leakfree.org/textfamguy1/40/4294_2.png" class="avatar"> TextFAMGUY1:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>We’re working in visibility for weapon spawns. We used to have glowing weapon bases but they were super ugly so we canned them. We’ll find a solution.</p>
<p>The Glock is very far from useless, I promise you this - the primary fire is absolutely deadly if you can land headshots with it (that’s the intention). It does 16 damage with a 3x headshot multiplier, you can 3 shot enemies with the primary fire - and there is no damage falloff. Matchmaking is not in our plans currently, as we do not have the infrastructure for it or the manpower to look into it. The only map with an abundance of longjump is Bounce, which has 3 (I believe, I really should remember as I did the weapon placements for that map!). All the other maps have only a single module spawn, and it’s hard to get to on most maps. Full character customization will come in a future update. We have a bunch of features planned for it, including everything you requested. We had colour switching working a month or two ago but had to cut it because it had a lot of issues, but we will bring it back.</p>
<p>Thanks for the feedback, we appreciate it! Keep it coming if you find more things to comment on!</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I made a map feedback topic one or two days ago… So far I gave feedback on gasworks and stalkyard. I plan to give feedback about bounce, too… But making decent feedback takes a lot of time and atm I want to work on my HLDM map more… But what I can tell you is, that you have at least 4 LJ modules on bounce and also 3 gauss. I already thought about some changes that could be made to bounce, but I will give detailed feedback later. Still I think there is not much feedback about my suggestions on gasworks and stalkyard. So please check the topic out and give feedback if you have the time  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=9" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/some-thoughts-and-feedback-on-bm-dm/14022/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/some-thoughts-and-feedback-on-bm-dm/14022/4</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 14 May 2015 13:37:16 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14022-4</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/some-thoughts-and-feedback-on-bm-dm/14022.rss">Some thoughts and feedback on BM:DM.</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Some thoughts and feedback on BM:DM.</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[vamp]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="TheGuma">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/t/e56c9b/40.png" class="avatar"> TheGuma:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>In BM <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/smiley.png?v=9" title=":smiley:" class="emoji" alt=":smiley:"> M I’ve had struggle finding a revolver (again, I’m a noob, don’t hate me, just pointing out). I generally play on a decent resolution, my eyesight is also fine, but from time to time when taking the games pace into consideration, I don’t have time to stare at the ground looking for a weapon. Finding darker guns in dark environments is an big issue, so one of the ways to resolve that would be to actually make them highlighted when close to them or aiming at them.<br>
I know some hardcore players will be OUTRAGED by that. We won’t want “noobification” of the game, but I think that the gameplay shouldn’t be cluttered by graphics being a distraction (although I appreciate them), even if it’s foliage (which is quite abundant).</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I think the pro community wouldn’t mind about that  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=9" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:">  Infact probably want the same thing to happen about this subject.<br>
What they care the most about is movement. the rest is patatoes.<br>
so pretty easy   <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/smiley.png?v=9" title=":smiley:" class="emoji" alt=":smiley:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/some-thoughts-and-feedback-on-bm-dm/14022/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/some-thoughts-and-feedback-on-bm-dm/14022/3</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 14 May 2015 13:25:57 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14022-3</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/some-thoughts-and-feedback-on-bm-dm/14022.rss">Some thoughts and feedback on BM:DM.</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Some thoughts and feedback on BM:DM.</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[TextFAMGUY1]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>We’re working in visibility for weapon spawns. We used to have glowing weapon bases but they were super ugly so we canned them. We’ll find a solution.</p>
<p>The Glock is very far from useless, I promise you this - the primary fire is absolutely deadly if you can land headshots with it (that’s the intention). It does 16 damage with a 3x headshot multiplier, you can 3 shot enemies with the primary fire - and there is no damage falloff. Matchmaking is not in our plans currently, as we do not have the infrastructure for it or the manpower to look into it. The only map with an abundance of longjump is Bounce, which has 3 (I believe, I really should remember as I did the weapon placements for that map!). All the other maps have only a single module spawn, and it’s hard to get to on most maps. Full character customization will come in a future update. We have a bunch of features planned for it, including everything you requested. We had colour switching working a month or two ago but had to cut it because it had a lot of issues, but we will bring it back.</p>
<p>Thanks for the feedback, we appreciate it! Keep it coming if you find more things to comment on!</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/some-thoughts-and-feedback-on-bm-dm/14022/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/some-thoughts-and-feedback-on-bm-dm/14022/2</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 13 May 2015 21:36:29 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14022-2</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/some-thoughts-and-feedback-on-bm-dm/14022.rss">Some thoughts and feedback on BM:DM.</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Some thoughts and feedback on BM:DM.</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[TheGuma]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>So I’m quite new to the forums but I’ve been following Black Mesa for years. To be more specific, I saw the project 6 years ago, thought it was cool and moved on with my life.<br>
Now that it has been released on Steam, no matter how bad I am or was on Half Life series in general I still love playing it. I feel like my money was well spent, and I spent them specifically to support the developers and not just to buy the game.<br>
So why am I directing my feedback to BM <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/smiley.png?v=9" title=":smiley:" class="emoji" alt=":smiley:"> M?<br>
Well, because it has a lot of potential. Think of CS:GO.<br>
I know there’s a lot of people coming here with the same idea in mind, but I feel like it’s easy to direct feedback to Dev’s on these forums.<br>
So what am I talking about? First of all, my general gameplay feedback on multiplayer, and on the second part will be some feature requests.<br>
The first thing that I found awkward was the menu, it’s not related to BM <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/smiley.png?v=9" title=":smiley:" class="emoji" alt=":smiley:"> M but when you go to change video settings in the middle of the game it tends to glitch out, not being able to press the buttons you need to press Esc twice.<br>
Having to rejoin the game to change some graphical settings is also something I’m not used to, as in CS:GO when I normally change those same settings (graphics quality) I don’t have to leave the server.<br>
But these things are in somewhat different boundary of fixing whats necessary and whats not, obviously the bug should be squashed but it’s just a minor distraction having to rejoin most of the time.<br>
The next thing that I found pretty weird was finding weapons in multiplayer. Now, as stupid as it may sound I’ve never been or am an hardcore HL <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/smiley.png?v=9" title=":smiley:" class="emoji" alt=":smiley:"> M player. In fact, I suck (I don’t even know the spawns). But one thing that I do remember is that the weapons in original Half Life were VERY visible from long distance, they were bulky bold weapons.<br>
In BM <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/smiley.png?v=9" title=":smiley:" class="emoji" alt=":smiley:"> M I’ve had struggle finding a revolver (again, I’m a noob, don’t hate me, just pointing out). I generally play on a decent resolution, my eyesight is also fine, but from time to time when taking the games pace into consideration, I don’t have time to stare at the ground looking for a weapon. Finding darker guns in dark environments is an big issue, so one of the ways to resolve that would be to actually make them highlighted when close to them or aiming at them.<br>
I know some hardcore players will be OUTRAGED by that. We won’t want “noobification” of the game, but I think that the gameplay shouldn’t be cluttered by graphics being a distraction (although I appreciate them), even if it’s foliage (which is quite abundant).<br>
Longjumps for everybody! Cant hate it, right? Nuuh, it’s very bad. I can bail out of situations very easily even upon spawn just because I already have a LJ module. Everybody has one, so although it makes things more fast paced the LJ module doesn’t feel rewarded.<br>
I don’t care if it even takes to add killstreaks to the game to get the LJ module, but as long as it’s a spawned entity or not obtainable to everybody upon spawn I’ll be fine.<br>
I don’t know what others think about that, but in HL <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/smiley.png?v=9" title=":smiley:" class="emoji" alt=":smiley:"> M I had to go through egon and gauss gun lava just to get that one silly LJ module.<br>
The pistol was awkward (or glock, as you may call it), it really was. It felt like secondary fire was way too inaccurate while the primary fire was way too slow. I’m not saying buff the pistol, but primary fire is nearly useless in such a fast paced game. Maybe switching RMB to LMB would help?</p>
<p>Here’s some of my feature requests, besides the feedback. Interpret my feedback as you may, I may be wrong on some things but that’s just my feedback from noob’s POV.<br>
One thing that I would like to request is some sort of matchmaking. Ridiculous, right? But that’s one of the ways to help the game grow, as well as invite new players to the game a bit more engagingly. ALA CS:GO!<br>
I think that griefers, trolls and cheaters would be inevitable, but it would have it’s upside. BM <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/smiley.png?v=9" title=":smiley:" class="emoji" alt=":smiley:"> M truly is a game that could have a competitive scene (again, I might be retarded here but I would watch BM competitive matches over CS:GO any day).</p>
<p>Also, I think it would be really awesome if we could change our characters color (Hev suit, pants). Some sort of customization to make the game a bit more interactive would be cool.</p>
<p>So that’s about it! Take it easy on me guys, and have a respectful discussion. Feel free to disagree and counterpoint my feedback, correct me!  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/smiley.png?v=9" title=":smiley:" class="emoji" alt=":smiley:"></p>
<p>P.S - Are jihad suicide grenade bombers a feature or just something overlooked? I can easily LJ/bhop to an enemy with a premature grenade getting a few kills along a suicide.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/some-thoughts-and-feedback-on-bm-dm/14022/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/some-thoughts-and-feedback-on-bm-dm/14022/1</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 13 May 2015 21:22:04 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14022-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/some-thoughts-and-feedback-on-bm-dm/14022.rss">Some thoughts and feedback on BM:DM.</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
