<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Yet another &quot;Help me build a PC&quot; thread</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/yet-another-help-me-build-a-pc-thread/9116</link>
    <description>i know there&#39;s about a half dozen threads on the topic of building custom game PCs. There&#39;s at least one other on the top page of thisforum and at least two or more posted every few weeks. Every OP has their own specifications, budget, store preference, etc. So i apologize in advance for what is possibly the most posted question here not involving helmets and release dates.

Can you guys help me build a new PC?

My budget falls between $500 to $900, give or take a few bucks. i need specific recommendations on videocards; preferably nvidia. i need a mobo that supports plentiful and relatively inexpensive ram so i can add more down the road. CPU needs to run cool. i have no desire to overclock. i also might go 64 bit OS later but for now, a lot of my favorite apps require 32 bit XP. i might dualboot or use virtualbox some time later.

Cooling is a must. i live in the Pacific Northwest so climate isn&#39;t a problem, but the PC will also be used as a fileshare server around the clock, running 5 HDs and hosting the occasional Minecraft server.

The system will be used for gaming, mostly games like Skyrim, which is a resource hog, even without graphics mods. i&#39;d like to play more current gen games and need CPU, RAM and GPU to back them up. i&#39;m not a graphics whore, i play a lot of older and basic games and i don&#39;t typically turn up anti-aliasing but i DO work a lot in Photoshop, using lots of rasterized layers and effects. When GTA5 comes out, i&#39;d prefer to play it on PC as apposed to console. i was disappointed when i found GTA4 ran like garbage on my current setup.Also, as i posted in an earlier thread, i run multiple applications at
once like Photoshop and media player on separate screens. The videocard is probably the most expensive thing i&#39;ll be putting in, but if need be, i can use my current 8800GTS until i can afford something else.

is SLi worth it? Would i get a bigger boost out of hooking up two &lt;$100 cards instead of something &gt;$200? For that matter, what specs are most important when seeking out a videocard? i can honestly say i&#39;ve fallen behind as far as hardware goes. The last machine i built without help was back when AGP was the standard bus type for video. USB 3.0 was a distant pipedream and terabyte HDs were something only whispered about among file-swapping pirates in need of precious space for their warez.

Chassis, drives and the like are all taken care of unless anyone can share a great cooling system that requires a
heftier case. i&#39;d like to keep my CPU, RAM and mobo around 5-600. i&#39;m also curious if i should invest in a SSD for my new main C drive. Nothing too big, something just large enough for XP and program files.

if anyone has suggestions, questions or general advice, i&#39;m open to it!

-Kawai Tei-

By the way, i&#39;ve been posting all this with my ipod so please excuse the funky formatting if there is any.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 14 Aug 2012 19:03:56 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Help and Support</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/yet-another-help-me-build-a-pc-thread/9116.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Yet another &quot;Help me build a PC&quot; thread</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Daedalus193]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Hi guys. My brother is planning on buying a new computer and well I haven’t been much on this scene  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=9" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"></p>
<p>For the budget well between 600€ and 750€ I think it should be fine.</p>
<p>What I’ve chosen so far was (BTW all from <a href="http://Amazon.co.uk" rel="nofollow noopener">Amazon.co.uk</a>)</p>
<ul>
<li><a href="https://www.amazon.co.uk/Intel-Generation-i5-3570K-3-40GHz-Technology/dp/B007RUZKK6/ref=sr_1_1?s=computers&amp;ie=UTF8&amp;qid=1344968428&amp;sr=1-1" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Intel 3rd Generation Core i5-3570K CPU</a></li>
<li><a href="https://www.amazon.co.uk/Asus-DirectCU-Graphics-Express-4840MHz/dp/B007OYS4R6/ref=sr_1_1?s=computers&amp;ie=UTF8&amp;qid=1344968501&amp;sr=1-1" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Asus Radeon HD 7850 DirectCU II Graphics Card</a></li>
<li><a href="https://www.amazon.co.uk/GA-Z77X-UD3H-Graphics-CrossFireX-LucidLogix-DualBIOS/dp/B007R21JJK/ref=sr_1_3?ie=UTF8&amp;qid=1344969388&amp;sr=8-3" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">GA-Z77X-UD3H</a></li>
</ul>
<p>Are all those compatible?  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=9" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"></p>
<p>Also need help with the power supply, the cooling system, sound card and possibly a good case. If you could send me links from <a href="http://Amazon.co.uk" rel="nofollow noopener">Amazon.co.uk</a>, better.</p>
<p><a href="https://www.amazon.co.uk/b/ref=sa_menu_cc4?ie=UTF8&amp;node=428655031" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Main Page for computer components</a></p>
<p>Thanks</p>
<p>EDIT: Well the prices for those 3 is almost 650€…  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=9" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/yet-another-help-me-build-a-pc-thread/9116/10">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/yet-another-help-me-build-a-pc-thread/9116/10</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Aug 2012 19:03:56 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9116-10</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/yet-another-help-me-build-a-pc-thread/9116.rss">Yet another &quot;Help me build a PC&quot; thread</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Yet another &quot;Help me build a PC&quot; thread</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[amf66]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>If you’re not going to overclock get the <a href="https://www.newegg.com/Product/Product.aspx?Item=N82E16819116505" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">3550</a> instead of the 2500K. It’ll be faster.<br>
For the mobo, get a Z77 one. Either <a href="https://www.newegg.com/Product/Product.aspx?Item=N82E16813128544" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">this Gigabyte</a> or <a href="https://www.newegg.com/Product/Product.aspx?Item=N82E16813128544" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">this ASRock</a> are great choices.</p>
<p>Edit: Just looked at the SSD you linked to. I have that very one in my computer and it is wicked fast.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/yet-another-help-me-build-a-pc-thread/9116/9">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/yet-another-help-me-build-a-pc-thread/9116/9</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 12 Aug 2012 06:01:51 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9116-9</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/yet-another-help-me-build-a-pc-thread/9116.rss">Yet another &quot;Help me build a PC&quot; thread</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Yet another &quot;Help me build a PC&quot; thread</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Tei]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>i’ve had some terrible experiences with buying used hardware. Hell, even FREE hardware. There’s usually a hidden reason why people sell their hardware so it’s always a gamble. it’s just not worth the risk to me. But so long as people are willing to buy used parts, i’ll probably try selling my old PC build (minus the obviously toasted mobo) on craiglist. What i end up keeping will go into my new media/emulation PC for the living room.</p>
<p>-Kawai Tei-</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/yet-another-help-me-build-a-pc-thread/9116/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/yet-another-help-me-build-a-pc-thread/9116/8</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 09 Aug 2012 13:31:15 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9116-8</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/yet-another-help-me-build-a-pc-thread/9116.rss">Yet another &quot;Help me build a PC&quot; thread</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Yet another &quot;Help me build a PC&quot; thread</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[sersoft]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>on my craigslist people are still asking 200$ for their old Geforce 8800’s</p>
<p>on kijiji.ca there is one for 40$</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/yet-another-help-me-build-a-pc-thread/9116/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/yet-another-help-me-build-a-pc-thread/9116/7</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 08 Aug 2012 22:41:13 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9116-7</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/yet-another-help-me-build-a-pc-thread/9116.rss">Yet another &quot;Help me build a PC&quot; thread</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Yet another &quot;Help me build a PC&quot; thread</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Gasher]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>As I said before in another thread, I picked up GTX570 for $100 from some down-on-his-luck bloke on craigslist… you could easily save yourself hundreds by trying to snag some of this shit used. And if you call yourself <span class="bbcode-i">green</span> at all, this helps that cause too… If you are above using hand-me-downs, then that is another story…</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/yet-another-help-me-build-a-pc-thread/9116/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/yet-another-help-me-build-a-pc-thread/9116/6</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 08 Aug 2012 21:18:05 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9116-6</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/yet-another-help-me-build-a-pc-thread/9116.rss">Yet another &quot;Help me build a PC&quot; thread</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Yet another &quot;Help me build a PC&quot; thread</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Tei]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Katana">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/k/db5fbb/40.png" class="avatar"> Katana:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Random suggestion:</p>
<p><a href="https://www.newegg.com/Product/Product.aspx?Item=N82E16820227725" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://www.newegg.com/Product/Product.aspx?Item=N82E16820227725</a></p>
<p>I don’t own it, but that’s the one I’m eyeing.</p>
<p>I remember the days when 60 GB would be enough for your whole hard drive of stuff. And, if you find a way to move games’ install directories, you could put some of your most-played games on there to boot them up super-fast.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Actually, i think i may have found something <a href="https://www.newegg.com/Product/Product.aspx?Item=N82E16820233191" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">better</a>!<br>
After rebate and “instant savings” i can get twice the space for only 50% more. Better space to dollar ratio.</p>
<p>-Kawai Tei-</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/yet-another-help-me-build-a-pc-thread/9116/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/yet-another-help-me-build-a-pc-thread/9116/5</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 08 Aug 2012 20:38:05 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9116-5</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/yet-another-help-me-build-a-pc-thread/9116.rss">Yet another &quot;Help me build a PC&quot; thread</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Yet another &quot;Help me build a PC&quot; thread</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Katana]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Random suggestion:</p>
<p><a href="https://www.newegg.com/Product/Product.aspx?Item=N82E16820227725" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://www.newegg.com/Product/Product.aspx?Item=N82E16820227725</a></p>
<p>I don’t own it, but that’s the one I’m eyeing.</p>
<p>I remember the days when 60 GB would be enough for your whole hard drive of stuff. And, if you find a way to move games’ install directories, you could put some of your most-played games on there to boot them up super-fast.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/yet-another-help-me-build-a-pc-thread/9116/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/yet-another-help-me-build-a-pc-thread/9116/4</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 08 Aug 2012 19:38:18 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9116-4</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/yet-another-help-me-build-a-pc-thread/9116.rss">Yet another &quot;Help me build a PC&quot; thread</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Yet another &quot;Help me build a PC&quot; thread</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Tei]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>i wish i could post my NewEgg “wishlist” instead, but this is what i have so far.</p>
<p><a href="https://www.newegg.com/Product/Product.aspx?Item=N82E16813157271" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Mobo</a><br>
<a href="https://www.newegg.com/Product/Product.aspx?Item=N82E16819115072" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">CPU</a><br>
<a href="https://www.newegg.com/Product/Product.aspx?Item=N82E16820231314" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">RAM</a><br>
<a href="https://www.newegg.com/Product/Product.aspx?Item=N82E16817139028" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">PSU</a></p>
<p>…but i’m still burned out on what video card to go with. i want to stick with NVidia, but i have no idea where to start with chipset. i don’t want any CPU/GPU bottlenecking. i don’t plan on overclocking anything, so what do you guys recommend? SLi isn’t a must but i only plan on grabbing ONE card for now and maybe getting another of the same come Christmas.</p>
<p>i can’t wait to get back into Skyrim and i’m hoping to finally play GTA4; it ran like garbage on my last build. i credited that fuckup to a bad CPU/GPU combination.</p>
<p>EDiT : i’m also looking for a great SSD to boot from. Nothing special; just Windows and basic game and program files. i’ll still be running Skyrim from another drive because i add/remove so many mods. i plan on keeping my SSD pretty static since i have 4 other drives to store stuff.</p>
<p>-Kawai Tei-</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/yet-another-help-me-build-a-pc-thread/9116/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/yet-another-help-me-build-a-pc-thread/9116/3</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 08 Aug 2012 19:10:28 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9116-3</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/yet-another-help-me-build-a-pc-thread/9116.rss">Yet another &quot;Help me build a PC&quot; thread</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Yet another &quot;Help me build a PC&quot; thread</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[King_Kaddo]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I should have posted this a long time ago:<br>
<a href="https://www.computerbase.de/forum/showthread.php?t=215394" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://www.computerbase.de/forum/showthread.php?t=215394</a><br>
It’s in german but it shouldn’t bother you.</p>
<p>It’s basicly the perfect list for gaming pcs for a range of budgets with alternative suggestions and continued updates based on tests and opinions on the website. The prizes are for the german market but it shouldn’t be that much different. Take a look on that list, choose one configuration and post it here so we can tell you if it’s ok for you.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/yet-another-help-me-build-a-pc-thread/9116/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/yet-another-help-me-build-a-pc-thread/9116/2</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 02 Aug 2012 20:12:16 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9116-2</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/yet-another-help-me-build-a-pc-thread/9116.rss">Yet another &quot;Help me build a PC&quot; thread</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Yet another &quot;Help me build a PC&quot; thread</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Tei]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>i know there’s about a half dozen threads on the topic of building custom game PCs. There’s at least one other on the top page of thisforum and at least two or more posted every few weeks. Every OP has their own specifications, budget, store preference, etc. So i apologize in advance for what is possibly the most posted question here not involving helmets and release dates.</p>
<p>Can you guys help me build a new PC?</p>
<p>My budget falls between $500 to $900, give or take a few bucks. i need specific recommendations on videocards; preferably nvidia. i need a mobo that supports plentiful and relatively inexpensive ram so i can add more down the road. CPU needs to run cool. i have no desire to overclock. i also might go 64 bit OS later but for now, a lot of my favorite apps require 32 bit XP. i might dualboot or use virtualbox some time later.</p>
<p>Cooling is a must. i live in the Pacific Northwest so climate isn’t a problem, but the PC will also be used as a fileshare server around the clock, running 5 HDs and hosting the occasional Minecraft server.</p>
<p>The system will be used for gaming, mostly games like Skyrim, which is a resource hog, even without graphics mods. i’d like to play more current gen games and need CPU, RAM and GPU to back them up. i’m not a graphics whore, i play a lot of older and basic games and i don’t typically turn up anti-aliasing but i DO work a lot in Photoshop, using lots of rasterized layers and effects. When GTA5 comes out, i’d prefer to play it on PC as apposed to console. i was disappointed when i found GTA4 ran like garbage on my current setup.Also, as i posted in an earlier thread, i run multiple applications at<br>
once like Photoshop and media player on separate screens. The videocard is probably the most expensive thing i’ll be putting in, but if need be, i can use my current 8800GTS until i can afford something else.</p>
<p>is SLi worth it? Would i get a bigger boost out of hooking up two &lt;$100 cards instead of something &gt;$200? For that matter, what specs are most important when seeking out a videocard? i can honestly say i’ve fallen behind as far as hardware goes. The last machine i built without help was back when AGP was the standard bus type for video. USB 3.0 was a distant pipedream and terabyte HDs were something only whispered about among file-swapping pirates in need of precious space for their warez.</p>
<p>Chassis, drives and the like are all taken care of unless anyone can share a great cooling system that requires a<br>
heftier case. i’d like to keep my CPU, RAM and mobo around 5-600. i’m also curious if i should invest in a SSD for my new main C drive. Nothing too big, something just large enough for XP and program files.</p>
<p>if anyone has suggestions, questions or general advice, i’m open to it!</p>
<p>-Kawai Tei-</p>
<p>By the way, i’ve been posting all this with my ipod so please excuse the funky formatting if there is any.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/yet-another-help-me-build-a-pc-thread/9116/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/yet-another-help-me-build-a-pc-thread/9116/1</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 02 Aug 2012 19:10:33 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9116-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/yet-another-help-me-build-a-pc-thread/9116.rss">Yet another &quot;Help me build a PC&quot; thread</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
