<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Excessive Loading times, even loading same area</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/excessive-loading-times-even-loading-same-area/14189</link>
    <description>Long time source gamer, so I know that long loading times for map transitions are expected, anywhere from 3-15 seconds, and that&#39;s OK.

However, when I do a quick save and a quick load, it is consistently taking 7-15 seconds, depending on where I set my graphics. I&#39;ve seen that you&#39;ve tackled this issue for same-map loading, but I&#39;m hoping this isn&#39;t the &quot;fixed&quot; version I&#39;m feeling.


I&#39;m on a pretty high-end gaming laptop, and other source games quick-load in about two seconds, and about .5 if I&#39;m running Source Unpacked.
But thanks for such a nice source (AHAHAHAHA) port  :slight_smile: 


Also, please put ABH back.. If people speed run your game, more people will buy it, I promise. It doesn&#39;t affect the average player, since they don&#39;t know how to ABH, but no one will run your game without ABH (Or bunnyhopping, but you&#39;d have to really code that in there..)</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 11 Jun 2015 12:26:33 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>In-game Issues</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/excessive-loading-times-even-loading-same-area/14189.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Excessive Loading times, even loading same area</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Chrisazy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Long time source gamer, so I know that long loading times for map transitions are expected, anywhere from 3-15 seconds, and that’s OK.</p>
<p>However, when I do a quick save and a quick load, it is consistently taking 7-15 seconds, depending on where I set my graphics. I’ve seen that you’ve tackled this issue for same-map loading, but I’m hoping this isn’t the “fixed” version I’m feeling.</p>
<p>I’m on a pretty high-end gaming laptop, and other source games quick-load in about two seconds, and about .5 if I’m running Source Unpacked.<br>
But thanks for such a nice source (AHAHAHAHA) port  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=9" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
<p>Also, please put ABH back… If people speed run your game, more people will buy it, I promise. It doesn’t affect the average player, since they don’t know how to ABH, but no one will run your game without ABH (Or bunnyhopping, but you’d have to really code that in there…)</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/excessive-loading-times-even-loading-same-area/14189/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/excessive-loading-times-even-loading-same-area/14189/1</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jun 2015 12:26:33 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14189-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/excessive-loading-times-even-loading-same-area/14189.rss">Excessive Loading times, even loading same area</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
