<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>&quot;Fix it yourself&quot;?</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/fix-it-yourself/12284</link>
    <description>Wow, I don&#39;t know if this is the place to put this, but I can&#39;t think of anywhere else except maybe The Test Chamber.

Something I noticed about Black Mesa and complaints people have about the mod is the replies are rather rude. People say things along the lines of: &quot;If you don&#39;t like it, change it yourself!&quot; (Which I personally have been told before, even [i]after[/i] showing that I have been attempting to do just that) 

I want to touch upon why this is stupid. I&#39;ve said it once in a thread somewhere and I&#39;ll say it again, just because a person [i]can[/i] edit the files to whatever they want to doesn&#39;t mean they [i]should have to[/i]. Because then they are not playing the mod the way the developers intended. They are playing a mod of a mod. For example, let&#39;s say I change the weapon damage of the MP5. I just modded Black Mesa. It is a small mod, but I am not playing the same thing everyone else is anymore. If I were to play Black Mesa deathmatch, I would have to use the default values instead of my own because I can&#39;t play my mod with other people unless they have it as well. And not everyone does. Additionally, the jump height is something I have seen many people voice discontent with. If a large number of people say something is wrong, then it is wrong. They shouldn&#39;t be told to manually patch the game themselves to fix it. Imagine if Valve did this. Let&#39;s say Valve made a huge mistake with something in a game they made, and rather than fix it like they normally do, they just say (or they just let their fanboys say), &quot;Fix it yourself!&quot; See the problem? 

Also, not everyone is very good at &quot;fixing it themselves.&quot; Some people have no idea where to find the files to edit, some people get overwhelmed by all the lines of code and are too afraid to change values in fear of breaking something, and others just plain out don&#39;t know what to change the values to. I personally hate the jump height, but I don&#39;t know what number to set the thing to in order to get my desired effect. And I don&#39;t want to keep rebooting the game to test it in trial-and-error. The devs set up a game which by all accounts should be fun to play at install. Players shouldn&#39;t be forced to open up the mod&#39;s folder,look for a .txt file, and crunch numbers just to have a good time. 

Now some of you may say, &quot;Just press two buttons, noob!&quot; The problem with that is it may not be comfortable for me. I personally can jump-crouch with no problem, but not everyone can. Some people just don&#39;t have hands that flexible. Maybe they spend more time with consoles or other PC games instead of playing Half-Life. This leads into another issue which I will discuss later. Back on the topic of comfort however, some people just can&#39;t position their hands that way quickly and comfortably. While they can change the controls to something easier to press, it won&#39;t be comfortable crouching anymore. You are leaving players with three choices: break their hand, play with awful controls just to make a jump, or stop playing Black Mesa altogether. Option three is something nobody should want, because then why did anyone make the game? What was the point of spending all those years if only a select few are allowed to play? Another argument is &quot;Crouch-hopping was in Half-Life!&quot; So was bunny-hopping. Also, crouch-jumping wasn&#39;t in Half-Life as much as it is in Black Mesa. I should not have to make Gordon pull his legs up to his chest just to make him hop over an ankle-high wall. It is also rather annoying to get through a difficult firefight and then die immediately afterwards because I botched a crouch-jump. Maybe I don&#39;t want to quicksave every five seconds. Maybe I don&#39;t want to quicksave every time I have to jump. But anyways, now to transition to the other topic I promised to discuss later.

Some people feel way too entitled over playing Half-Life. They are the &#39;true-gamers&#39; and others outside the bubble are absolute scum. If someone doesn&#39;t play Half-Life, they are dirt. If someone plays on consoles, they are dirt. What does it matter? If anything, the community should be happy others are trying Black Mesa. Console players are saying, &quot;Hey! This game looks neat! I want to try it!&quot; They are so eager to try it they temporarily leave their platform of choice to play a mod they may know nothing about. And so what if they don&#39;t know? Let them try the game and enjoy it, that way they [i]can[/i] know. I&#39;ve seen Black Mesa community members get so angry at X-Box [i]Let&#39;s Play[/i]ers because they are trying Black Mesa. Why the anger? Black Mesa is attracting new people to the Half-Life fandom, and as these people who have little-to-no experience play the mod and get interested, they will [i]learn[/i] what Half-Life is. But the responses they receive only prompt them to say: &quot;Welp, I&#39;m not doing this again. I&#39;m sticking to X-Box.&quot; Nobody was born knowing everything about Half-Life and its mods. I still remember when I first heard of the series. But after playing the games I became so hooked that I tried to learn everything I could. And part of what made me like Valve was their updates. If something was wrong they would fix it. Nowadays it&#39;s debatable whether they succeed or not but at least they try. 

I&#39;ll stand firm in the belief that there is nothing wrong with making a few adjustments to suit one&#39;s personal tastes. The devs cannot please everyone, but my belief is that they should try to please as many people as they can. Some mods (NOT Black Mesa, thankfully) have developers with sticks shoved so far up their asses that they believe that [i]their[/i] way to make a game is the [i]only[/i] way to make a game. Whether there are bugs or annoyances galore, anything else is for &quot;stupid COD kids.&quot; Even if the suggested feature has nothing to do with Call of Duty at all. Trust me, I&#39;ve seen it. Additionally, some people get so incredibly hostile (you&#39;ve seen it yourselves during the Valvetime leak in regards to the .357) over something as simple as iron sights. Iron sights for crying out loud! And even developers will bash the shit out of the person suggesting the feature and rant over Call of Duty. Call of Duty did not even invent the iron sight mechanic, and in some ways iron sights can be traced back to Doom. The weapon was always in the center of the screen, and there was no crosshair, players aimed with the gun itself. Yet someone suggests iron sights and they get flammed to high hell over being a COD fag or something. 

Last thing I&#39;m going to say is that not everything can be fixed by players. At least, not without a buttload of work. The hitboxes in Black Mesa are absolute shit. I&#39;m not going to sugarcoat it. When I shoot at the Vortigaunts in Apprehension before fighting the Black Ops there are tubes wrapped around pieces of wood. Even though the geometry is shaped like an &#39;I&#39;, the hitbox is a big square. So my crossbow round gets caught in the air as if it hit a wall. And this happens multiple times, wasting my ammo. Not okay. The Humvees have a shitty hitbox. The entire space above the hood to the roof is considered a wall. That is a large space that can even be hopped onto in Surface Tension on the dam. I can float in the air because of that box problem, which is actually a bounding box issue. Also, in Surface Tension there is a turret hiding in a truck before the armory event. By all means the player should be able to shoot the turret through the tarp, yet the tarp is made of steel somehow. This forces the player to expose themselves to the turret&#39;s gun in order to attack it. The tarp could have been similar to the Combine force-field in Half-Life 2 in which the player couldn&#39;t pass through it but bullets could. While these issues can be fixed by a player, they would have to get three or four different programs (some of which cost money, so much for a &#39;free&#39; modification) in order to decompile the model, edit the boxes, and then recompile. And that&#39;s assuming the programs don&#39;t crash. I cannot fix these issues myself because every compiling tool I find crashes when I try to use it. So in this case &quot;fix it yourself&quot; isn&#39;t even [i]possible[/i].

In conclusion, Black Mesa is not perfect. There are problems. These problems need to be fixed officially, rather than by the players. I am sick of seeing this come up over and over again, and would rather have a topic to link to rather than having to type it out every time someone tells me or some other person this. Also, give people a break! Not everyone uses a computer as much as you do, and that is okay. At least they are interested in Black Mesa enough to give PC Gaming a go. Don&#39;t make them regret that decision.

EDIT: Hooray! My first wall of text!</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 05 May 2013 21:04:24 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>In-game Issues (Mod)</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/fix-it-yourself/12284.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>&quot;Fix it yourself&quot;?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[sgtpieman]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="MSKyuuni">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/m/71c47a/40.png" class="avatar"> MSKyuuni:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I can see the problems with crouch jumping, but they’re not my own. I finished BM normally with no problems at all, but one day, my father tried to play and couldn’t finish Unforseen Consequences because he couldn’t crouch jump every single time. He has finished the entire HL series (including Gearbox expansions) with no difficulties at all, but he couldn’t finish chapter three in BM because of the jumping? It’s not that he can’t do it, but that he couldn’t do it all the time. Sure, I edited the scripts with help from some people here and he finished the whole thing, but my point is that there should be more accommodation for those with difficulties relating to this mechanic.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Exactly. That’s how I feel, only it’s my brother instead of my father. And I didn’t edit the mod in any way, he was able to beat it but very slowly and poorly with a lot of obscenities.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="miklkit">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/m/59ef9b/40.png" class="avatar"> miklkit:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Have you read this thread?  The fixes in there work for me.</p>
<p><a href="https://forums.blackmesasource.com/showthread.php?t=12678" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://forums.blackmesasource.com/showthread.php?t=12678</a></p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Yep! Even posted in it!  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/wink.png?v=9" title=":wink:" class="emoji" alt=":wink:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/fix-it-yourself/12284/62">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/fix-it-yourself/12284/62</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 05 May 2013 21:04:24 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12284-62</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/fix-it-yourself/12284.rss">&quot;Fix it yourself&quot;?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>&quot;Fix it yourself&quot;?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[MSKyuuni]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I can see the problems with crouch jumping, but they’re not my own. I finished BM normally with no problems at all, but one day, my father tried to play and couldn’t finish Unforseen Consequences because he couldn’t crouch jump every single time. He has finished the entire HL series (including Gearbox expansions) with no difficulties at all, but he couldn’t finish chapter three in BM because of the jumping? It’s not that he can’t do it, but that he couldn’t do it all the time. Sure, I edited the scripts with help from some people here and he finished the whole thing, but my point is that there should be more accommodation for those with difficulties relating to this mechanic.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/fix-it-yourself/12284/61">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/fix-it-yourself/12284/61</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 05 May 2013 07:16:48 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12284-61</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/fix-it-yourself/12284.rss">&quot;Fix it yourself&quot;?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>&quot;Fix it yourself&quot;?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Dr_Maxwell]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="sudpuzzer">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/user_avatar/leakfree.org/sudpuzzer/40/5871_2.png" class="avatar"> sudpuzzer:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I don’t understand the hate towards crouch jumping. Black Mesa is a recreation of Half-life. Half-life had crouch jumping. Half-life INVENTED crouch jumping. Therefore, Black Mesa has crouch jumping. It’s not that hard to stretch from Ctrl to the Spacebar, and people who claim that they cannot do it should probably not be playing PC games at all. I’d even call crouch jumping a base mechanic of the game. Half-life was part shooter and part platformer. If you take out crouch jumping, you are not really remaking Half-life anymore.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I don’t think it’s a criticism of the <span class="bbcode-i">existence</span> of crouch-jumping, at least not from those familiar with the original game.  I think it’s a criticism of the <span class="bbcode-i">frequency</span> of required crouch-jumping, and the ease of missing the training for it (I for one was stuck in the giant diagonal elevator room for about half an hour because it had been ages since I’d played a Source game and I’d forgotten about crouch-jumping).</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/fix-it-yourself/12284/60">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/fix-it-yourself/12284/60</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 05 May 2013 06:32:19 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12284-60</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/fix-it-yourself/12284.rss">&quot;Fix it yourself&quot;?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>&quot;Fix it yourself&quot;?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[miklkit]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Have you read this thread?  The fixes in there work for me.</p>
<p><a href="https://forums.blackmesasource.com/showthread.php?t=12678" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://forums.blackmesasource.com/showthread.php?t=12678</a></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/fix-it-yourself/12284/59">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/fix-it-yourself/12284/59</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 05 May 2013 05:14:39 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12284-59</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/fix-it-yourself/12284.rss">&quot;Fix it yourself&quot;?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>&quot;Fix it yourself&quot;?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[sgtpieman]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="miklkit">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/m/59ef9b/40.png" class="avatar"> miklkit:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>But walking means that one must manipulate 4 buttons with the left hand on every…single…jump.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Actually, the way it is now requires 4 buttons for almost every jump. There’s the ‘w’ key to ensure you don’t jump straight up, the ‘shift’ button for jumping across gaps (there are plenty of these), the ‘spacebar’ for jumping, and the ‘ctrl’ button for jump-crouching.</p>
<p>That means to make it over the plethora of jumping puzzles in Black Mesa (they were in Half-Life, so it’s not the Devs’ faults for including them) one must use the pinky for pressing two buttons, the thumb for pressing one, and the middle finger for one. Or if they are feeling risky then they must be able to quickly move the pinky right at the jump, making sure not to let it slip and press the ‘Windows’ key, and press the crouch button.</p>
<p>Not very comfortable for everyone, especially those who only/mostly use consoles and were actually interested enough in Black Mesa to try the PC.</p>
<p>EDIT: Or they could use their ring-finger for the ‘shift’ key. Again, not the best setup.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/fix-it-yourself/12284/58">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/fix-it-yourself/12284/58</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 05 May 2013 00:46:10 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12284-58</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/fix-it-yourself/12284.rss">&quot;Fix it yourself&quot;?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>&quot;Fix it yourself&quot;?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[bur]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Mr. Someguy">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Mr. Someguy:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>No, the sprint button is the sprint button, or the run button if always sprint is enabled. They removed the walk (alt) function.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Oh yeah, that’s right :retard:</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/fix-it-yourself/12284/57">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/fix-it-yourself/12284/57</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 05 May 2013 00:44:23 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12284-57</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/fix-it-yourself/12284.rss">&quot;Fix it yourself&quot;?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>&quot;Fix it yourself&quot;?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Mr_Someguy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>No, the sprint button is the sprint button, or the run button if always sprint is enabled. They removed the walk (alt) function.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/fix-it-yourself/12284/56">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/fix-it-yourself/12284/56</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 04 May 2013 22:55:15 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12284-56</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/fix-it-yourself/12284.rss">&quot;Fix it yourself&quot;?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>&quot;Fix it yourself&quot;?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[bur]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>They did, it’s the sprint button, I think. Either that or it was defective and someone fixed it (thread in leak-free).</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/fix-it-yourself/12284/55">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/fix-it-yourself/12284/55</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 04 May 2013 22:04:25 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12284-55</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/fix-it-yourself/12284.rss">&quot;Fix it yourself&quot;?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>&quot;Fix it yourself&quot;?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Mr_Someguy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I wish they kept the walking option in, I used it a lot.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/fix-it-yourself/12284/54">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/fix-it-yourself/12284/54</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 04 May 2013 20:47:55 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12284-54</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/fix-it-yourself/12284.rss">&quot;Fix it yourself&quot;?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>&quot;Fix it yourself&quot;?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[miklkit]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>In BMS walking = running and sprinting = rocketman.<br>
I prefer to walk.  But walking means that one must manipulate 4 buttons with the left hand on every…single…jump.  I can handle 3 buttons but not 4, and that is where key binding comes in.</p>
<p>In HL1 there is the option to press a button to walk.  My little pinkie gets so tired from holding that button down all the time.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/fix-it-yourself/12284/53">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/fix-it-yourself/12284/53</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 04 May 2013 17:52:28 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12284-53</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/fix-it-yourself/12284.rss">&quot;Fix it yourself&quot;?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>&quot;Fix it yourself&quot;?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[sgtpieman]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Half-Life 1 style movement makes it harder to appreciate one’s surroundings, due to always sprinting. In a mod where that’s a large part of the idea, turning on the HL1 style movement is not the best idea. Plus it’s kind of uncomfortable on the Source engine. I can’t even play Half-Life Source because the movement is so awkward for me, even though Half-Life Goldsource is fine.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/fix-it-yourself/12284/52">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/fix-it-yourself/12284/52</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 04 May 2013 15:24:53 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12284-52</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/fix-it-yourself/12284.rss">&quot;Fix it yourself&quot;?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>&quot;Fix it yourself&quot;?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Chickenprotector]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>A little late to the party. Check how you move forward with BM and how it works in HL2. There’s a slight boost to your speed when you do it in HL2 that isn’t there in BM. That’s the primary and <span class="bbcode-i">only</span> difference.</p>
<p>New players should develop a habit of sprinting before they jump, or turning on the HL1 style movement.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/fix-it-yourself/12284/51">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/fix-it-yourself/12284/51</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 04 May 2013 12:50:24 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12284-51</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/fix-it-yourself/12284.rss">&quot;Fix it yourself&quot;?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>&quot;Fix it yourself&quot;?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[D3lta]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Pettifogg">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/p/ebca7d/40.png" class="avatar"> Pettifogg:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I do, but most people who play Black Mesa aren’t going download the Hazard Course. Even if the devs were to include it in the final game, not everyone will want to play a tutorial before starting the game, so there’s still a reason to have the crouch jump better introduced into actual gameplay.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I dont think it’ll get integrated, there are to much new extra’s.And if it was, it could be an idea to show a message if the player clicks on “New Game”, that says something like:Are you sure you dont want to play the tutorial first (highly recommended).I agree with you though, only a few peoplea are going to download it.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/fix-it-yourself/12284/50">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/fix-it-yourself/12284/50</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2013 07:29:52 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12284-50</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/fix-it-yourself/12284.rss">&quot;Fix it yourself&quot;?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>&quot;Fix it yourself&quot;?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Mr_Someguy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>If there’s a tutorial and they don’t play it, that’s their fault. However there isn’t one.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/fix-it-yourself/12284/49">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/fix-it-yourself/12284/49</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2013 02:48:03 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12284-49</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/fix-it-yourself/12284.rss">&quot;Fix it yourself&quot;?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>&quot;Fix it yourself&quot;?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Pettifogg]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="TehBoxNoob">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 TehBoxNoob:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>^^You got 777 posts, how can you not know the Hazard Course remake?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I do, but most people who play Black Mesa aren’t going download the Hazard Course. Even if the devs were to include it in the final game, not everyone will want to play a tutorial before starting the game, so there’s still a reason to have the crouch jump better introduced into actual gameplay.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/fix-it-yourself/12284/48">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/fix-it-yourself/12284/48</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2013 00:05:50 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12284-48</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/fix-it-yourself/12284.rss">&quot;Fix it yourself&quot;?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>&quot;Fix it yourself&quot;?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[sgtpieman]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="miklkit">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/m/59ef9b/40.png" class="avatar"> miklkit:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>With a little help I was able to adjust crouch jumping so I make it slightly more often than not.  Going from 160 to 175 did it.  Adjusted the keys too. Now BMS is a nice game.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Great. What I’m wondering is why should the players have to do this? Why can’t it be done already? Or maybe for the Steam release this:<br>
[URL=‘<a href="https://forums.blackmesasource.com/showthread.php?t=13013" rel="nofollow noopener">https://forums.blackmesasource.com/showthread.php?t=13013</a>’]<br>
can be activated by one of the checkmarks in the menu. That would be a nicer gesture. Players can check “automatic crouch-jump” in the options instead of having to either go to the forums and read through threads of people flaming others for not being able to crouch jump, or having to go to the forums and download a mod for a mod and then install that mod into their mod by manually going into the folders and throwing the file in/manually going into the folders, finding the correct file, finding the correct line of the file, and then finding the correct value for the line of the file.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/fix-it-yourself/12284/47">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/fix-it-yourself/12284/47</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2013 22:30:52 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12284-47</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/fix-it-yourself/12284.rss">&quot;Fix it yourself&quot;?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>&quot;Fix it yourself&quot;?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypt]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>It isn’t taught in a safe environment in <span class="bbcode-i">Black Mesa</span>. That crappy remake is irrelevant.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/fix-it-yourself/12284/46">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/fix-it-yourself/12284/46</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2013 21:51:39 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12284-46</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/fix-it-yourself/12284.rss">&quot;Fix it yourself&quot;?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>&quot;Fix it yourself&quot;?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[D3lta]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>^^You got 777 posts, how can you not know the Hazard Course remake?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/fix-it-yourself/12284/45">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/fix-it-yourself/12284/45</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2013 21:46:17 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12284-45</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/fix-it-yourself/12284.rss">&quot;Fix it yourself&quot;?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>&quot;Fix it yourself&quot;?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[imadoofus]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Pettifogg">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/p/ebca7d/40.png" class="avatar"> Pettifogg:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I think one thing that’d help with crouch-jumping is if the player was trained how to use it better. It’s currently introduced in the same area where you meet your first headcrab, so people are distracted and don’t take it in, <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=zs1IKZv8YyY" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">which leads to situations like this.</a></p>
<p>If it were introduced earlier in more low-stress environments, players would get the hang of it more quickly, so when it’s needed in higher stress environments they remember what to do.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Agreed. There’s a team remaking the Hazard Course as a BMS mod that shows you the basics without getting eaten by a headcrab if you’re not a fast enough learner.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/fix-it-yourself/12284/44">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/fix-it-yourself/12284/44</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2013 20:46:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12284-44</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/fix-it-yourself/12284.rss">&quot;Fix it yourself&quot;?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>&quot;Fix it yourself&quot;?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Pettifogg]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I think one thing that’d help with crouch-jumping is if the player was trained how to use it better. It’s currently introduced in the same area where you meet your first headcrab, so people are distracted and don’t take it in, <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=zs1IKZv8YyY" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">which leads to situations like this.</a></p>
<p>If it were introduced earlier in more low-stress environments, players would get the hang of it more quickly, so when it’s needed in higher stress environments they remember what to do.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/fix-it-yourself/12284/43">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/fix-it-yourself/12284/43</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2013 19:03:54 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12284-43</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/fix-it-yourself/12284.rss">&quot;Fix it yourself&quot;?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>&quot;Fix it yourself&quot;?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[bur]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Nah, they just changed the jumping mechanics. The only thing that’s really changed is the distance, I think.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/fix-it-yourself/12284/42">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/fix-it-yourself/12284/42</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2013 17:50:15 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12284-42</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/fix-it-yourself/12284.rss">&quot;Fix it yourself&quot;?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>&quot;Fix it yourself&quot;?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[miklkit]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>With a little help I was able to adjust crouch jumping so I make it slightly more often than not.  Going from 160 to 175 did it.  Adjusted the keys too. Now BMS is a nice game.<br>
Methinks perhaps the gravity got changed. When breaking boxes they float around instead of flying around.</p>
<p>Do the scientist models look somehow a little bit off to anyone else?  The just don’t look quite right to me.  Are their legs too long, or their bodies too short?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/fix-it-yourself/12284/41">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/fix-it-yourself/12284/41</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2013 16:38:26 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12284-41</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/fix-it-yourself/12284.rss">&quot;Fix it yourself&quot;?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>&quot;Fix it yourself&quot;?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[imadoofus]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I completely agree with you about this. I for one have zero experience with coding above the most basic level, and I could never fix a code line or a model without weeks of learning and trial-and-error. I also agree on the crouch-jump thing; It took me three playthroughs to the end of Office Complex to get the hang of crouch-jumping.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/fix-it-yourself/12284/40">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/fix-it-yourself/12284/40</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2013 16:20:22 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12284-40</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/fix-it-yourself/12284.rss">&quot;Fix it yourself&quot;?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>&quot;Fix it yourself&quot;?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypt]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>People modifying the game to better suit how they wish it to be? Nonsense!</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/fix-it-yourself/12284/39">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/fix-it-yourself/12284/39</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2013 09:37:23 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12284-39</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/fix-it-yourself/12284.rss">&quot;Fix it yourself&quot;?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>&quot;Fix it yourself&quot;?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[D3lta]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><a href="https://forums.blackmesasource.com/showthread.php?t=13013" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Whats so hard about placing this in your BMS folder?</a><br>
Crouch jumping is in every Source/GoldenSource game.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/fix-it-yourself/12284/38">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/fix-it-yourself/12284/38</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2013 08:55:50 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12284-38</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/fix-it-yourself/12284.rss">&quot;Fix it yourself&quot;?</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
