<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>[BUG] Glitchy Collision on vent props in bm_c2a2c</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/bug-glitchy-collision-on-vent-props-in-bm-c2a2c/14695</link>
    <description>Let me preface this by saying that I&#39;ve been playing about with Hammer on bm_c2a2a - as a result, it doesn&#39;t link to c2a2b at the moment, so I have to use the map command directly to load anything else in OaR. I don&#39;t know if that would affect the issue or not, but I haven&#39;t modified c2a2b or c2a2c yet. Anyways.

In the missile launch area, on the right side when entering through the fence, there are two vents next to each other.
[img=&#39;https://i.imgur.com/25D0hQL.jpg&#39;,none,660][/img]

The vent grills have some... interesting collision detection.

By just pushing against them and jumping, it&#39;s possible to get stuck inside the vent&#39;s hitbox:
[img=&#39;https://i.imgur.com/uKRbbzS.jpg&#39;,none,654][/img]

And jumping on top of the grill will treat the player as if they&#39;re falling - once they move far enough away from the grill, they&#39;ll plummet to the ground and take fall damage depending on how long they were floating.

I haven&#39;t been able to recreate it so far, but I also managed to turn [i]myself[/i] into a rocket by getting stuck on the vent and using explosives to kill myself:
[img=&#39;https://i.imgur.com/ZFLmsNQ.jpg&#39;,none,653][/img]

Video of the fall damage bug [url=&#39;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=dPqziRUjskE&#39;]here[/url].</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 25 Feb 2016 20:01:08 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>In-game Issues</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/bug-glitchy-collision-on-vent-props-in-bm-c2a2c/14695.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>[BUG] Glitchy Collision on vent props in bm_c2a2c</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[KyuuGryphon]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Let me preface this by saying that I’ve been playing about with Hammer on bm_c2a2a - as a result, it doesn’t link to c2a2b at the moment, so I have to use the map command directly to load anything else in OaR. I don’t know if that would affect the issue or not, but I haven’t modified c2a2b or c2a2c yet. Anyways.</p>
<p>In the missile launch area, on the right side when entering through the fence, there are two vents next to each other.<br>
<img alt=""></p>
<p>The vent grills have some… interesting collision detection.</p>
<p>By just pushing against them and jumping, it’s possible to get stuck inside the vent’s hitbox:<br>
<img alt=""></p>
<p>And jumping on top of the grill will treat the player as if they’re falling - once they move far enough away from the grill, they’ll plummet to the ground and take fall damage depending on how long they were floating.</p>
<p>I haven’t been able to recreate it so far, but I also managed to turn <span class="bbcode-i">myself</span> into a rocket by getting stuck on the vent and using explosives to kill myself:<br>
<img alt=""></p>
<p>Video of the fall damage bug <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=dPqziRUjskE" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">here</a>.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/bug-glitchy-collision-on-vent-props-in-bm-c2a2c/14695/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/bug-glitchy-collision-on-vent-props-in-bm-c2a2c/14695/1</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 25 Feb 2016 20:01:08 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14695-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/bug-glitchy-collision-on-vent-props-in-bm-c2a2c/14695.rss">[BUG] Glitchy Collision on vent props in bm_c2a2c</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
