<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Unique Black Mesa Embroidered Patch</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/unique-black-mesa-embroidered-patch/13517</link>
    <description>Hello.  I have a mystery, that&#39;s needing to be solved.  I was searching Ebay for a cool Black Mesa embroidered patch.  When I found one it looked very weird.  I just had to buy it.  I tried to message the seller and try to find out how he got his hands on this patch.  He told me that he knew nothing about it, except that it was about 3-4 inches long.  From the digging that I did do, I was able to turn up that the patch was made, because of the remake of the original Half-life game using the &quot;Source Engine&quot;.  That is why it has the &quot;S&quot; in the upper right section of the patch.  But the question I have is..... How did the public get a hold of such a patch.  Did it ship with some hard copy of the game?.  Or was this patch part of an event that was being held by Valve, or like a swag item from E3?.  Was this something that only the people who worked on the game had access to?  Either way I was hoping you might be able to shed some light on this matter.  I&#39;m having trouble placing a JPEG picture here in this post.  Thank you very much for your time.

  Cut and paste this into the Ebay search line............. PARCHE-HALF-LIFE-BLACK-MESA-G-PATCH</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2014 02:21:26 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Help!</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/unique-black-mesa-embroidered-patch/13517.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Unique Black Mesa Embroidered Patch</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Agent_722]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I found the store now.  Thank you for the help.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/unique-black-mesa-embroidered-patch/13517/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/unique-black-mesa-embroidered-patch/13517/5</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2014 02:21:26 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13517-5</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/unique-black-mesa-embroidered-patch/13517.rss">Unique Black Mesa Embroidered Patch</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Unique Black Mesa Embroidered Patch</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Agent_722]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Thank you very much.  You said that there is a store?.  I cannot seem to find the link to get to it.  I wouls like to see what they have for sale.  Being so new here, I’m sorry for not being able to find it.  Could you please direct me to it.</p>
<p>Thank you for your time.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/unique-black-mesa-embroidered-patch/13517/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/unique-black-mesa-embroidered-patch/13517/4</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 18 Oct 2014 04:39:06 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13517-4</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/unique-black-mesa-embroidered-patch/13517.rss">Unique Black Mesa Embroidered Patch</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Unique Black Mesa Embroidered Patch</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Flatline]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>If you look at this store, there’s a whole range. I doubt any of these are official.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/unique-black-mesa-embroidered-patch/13517/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/unique-black-mesa-embroidered-patch/13517/3</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2014 09:28:15 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13517-3</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/unique-black-mesa-embroidered-patch/13517.rss">Unique Black Mesa Embroidered Patch</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Unique Black Mesa Embroidered Patch</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Orpheon]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>It’s possible it was a promo item but it’s just as likely that it’s fan-made. It’s not like it would be hard to make. There are replicas and fan-made items of all sorts of things floating around on the internet - I’ve found multiple ROM-hack SNES games on ebay while searching for the original games.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/unique-black-mesa-embroidered-patch/13517/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/unique-black-mesa-embroidered-patch/13517/2</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2014 04:16:26 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13517-2</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/unique-black-mesa-embroidered-patch/13517.rss">Unique Black Mesa Embroidered Patch</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Unique Black Mesa Embroidered Patch</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Agent_722]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Hello.  I have a mystery, that’s needing to be solved.  I was searching Ebay for a cool Black Mesa embroidered patch.  When I found one it looked very weird.  I just had to buy it.  I tried to message the seller and try to find out how he got his hands on this patch.  He told me that he knew nothing about it, except that it was about 3-4 inches long.  From the digging that I did do, I was able to turn up that the patch was made, because of the remake of the original Half-life game using the “Source Engine”.  That is why it has the “S” in the upper right section of the patch.  But the question I have is… How did the public get a hold of such a patch.  Did it ship with some hard copy of the game?.  Or was this patch part of an event that was being held by Valve, or like a swag item from E3?.  Was this something that only the people who worked on the game had access to?  Either way I was hoping you might be able to shed some light on this matter.  I’m having trouble placing a JPEG picture here in this post.  Thank you very much for your time.</p>
<p>Cut and paste this into the Ebay search line… PARCHE-HALF-LIFE-BLACK-MESA-G-PATCH</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/unique-black-mesa-embroidered-patch/13517/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/unique-black-mesa-embroidered-patch/13517/1</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2014 03:47:41 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13517-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/unique-black-mesa-embroidered-patch/13517.rss">Unique Black Mesa Embroidered Patch</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
