<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Self Identity (friendly)debate thread</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/self-identity-friendly-debate-thread/14609</link>
    <description>Okay, I accidentally this whole thing in the YLYL so here we have a dedicated place for it. you all know the rules:

Don&#39;t be a douche
Don&#39;t be a baby
Know you aren&#39;t going to convince anyone on the internet
Realize people have different views and that is probably actually okay



Okay, so I&#39;ll start this out with my two bits that I want to get out, I think the whole thing is a load of tripe. If your dingle dangles you are a boy, if it doesn&#39;t, you are a girl. Gender identity stems from assumptions that boys (with dangly dingles) should act one way and that girls (no dangle)  should act another. It then attempts to make people who don&#39;t conform to these set guidelines by giving them the opposite identity, which is quite frankly retarded beyond all words. Because mentally, people are people and not boys and girls, there is no simple designation that will account for everyone so they started making new extra-retarded designations for people who don&#39;t fall neatly into any particular category. Fast-forward to today, the system which was meant to make people feel better about themselves is making every insecure idget question their self identity rather than dealing with the REAL issues in their lives, essentially making gender identity a self fulfilling prophecy. The proper way to deal with the issue would be to disassociate mentality from gender.

TLDR: The western crisis that is &quot;gender identity&quot; is only a thing because some well meaning fucktard started spewing nonsense instead of using their brain for half a minute, and the masses jumped on board because &quot;why should I think when other people can do that for me&quot;</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 23 Jan 2016 09:08:32 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Off Topic</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/self-identity-friendly-debate-thread/14609.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Self Identity (friendly)debate thread</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[_rot_fodder]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>At this point, it just comes down to philosophy I think, at least we are all on the same page.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/self-identity-friendly-debate-thread/14609/31">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/self-identity-friendly-debate-thread/14609/31</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 23 Jan 2016 09:08:32 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14609-31</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/self-identity-friendly-debate-thread/14609.rss">Self Identity (friendly)debate thread</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Self Identity (friendly)debate thread</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[garrthbarrttinn]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="(rot)(fodder">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 (rot)(fodder:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>So where do you draw the line then? Men are allowed to call themselves female and vice versa but the people who don’t like either identity must be shunned because it is unreasonable?</p>
<p>Certainly it makes more sense to base scociety on something with solid boundries rather than basing it on what feels right and what feels like it has gone “too far”?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I don’t think anyone should be shunned. And honestly I don’t even know what side I take on people who claim not to be affiliated with either gender, haven’t really worked that out yet.</p>
<p>I think that in so many things including gender there are cases that don’t conform to solid boundaries and so really in the end for some many things we do just have to rely on what feels like it’s gone “too far”. It’s I’d argue better than the two alternatives of believing everyone should identify as their biological sex and letting anyone say they’re anything.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/self-identity-friendly-debate-thread/14609/30">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/self-identity-friendly-debate-thread/14609/30</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 23 Jan 2016 08:44:34 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14609-30</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/self-identity-friendly-debate-thread/14609.rss">Self Identity (friendly)debate thread</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Self Identity (friendly)debate thread</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[_rot_fodder]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>So where do you draw the line then? Men are allowed to call themselves female and vice versa but the people who don’t like either identity must be shunned because it is unreasonable?</p>
<p>Certainly it makes more sense to base scociety on something with solid boundries rather than basing it on what feels right and what feels like it has gone “too far”?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/self-identity-friendly-debate-thread/14609/29">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/self-identity-friendly-debate-thread/14609/29</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 23 Jan 2016 08:25:15 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14609-29</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/self-identity-friendly-debate-thread/14609.rss">Self Identity (friendly)debate thread</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Self Identity (friendly)debate thread</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[garrthbarrttinn]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I absolutely disagree that gender is only a social construct.</p>
<p>Men and women have significant and universal behavioral/psychological differences that cannot be explained away as solely social construct. You could win the argument on hormones alone, though I’m sure there’s more at play. We know that testosterone and estrogen have a significant impact on behavior (such as testosterone being associated with aggression). We know that biological males and biological females as a trend have very different levels of these hormones. Ergo, biological men and biological women have significantly different behavior (as a trend).</p>
<p>Biological men have higher rates of suicide, higher rates of schizophrenia and a number of other mental illnesses, commit more crimes, etc. etc. Of course all of this has a degree of contribution from social factors, but the gaps are so wide you couldn’t possibly argue that it’s social alone. Not to mention, if you concede that life experience contributes to personality and character, the physical components of gender must also undeniably contribute to experience and thus indirectly to personality and character (ie men are significantly larger and stronger than women, don’t have periods, don’t undergo childbirth). I think it’d be pretty hard to argue that this difference isn’t a significant contribution to life experience with or without societal influence.</p>
<p>The way I see it is that society acts as a magnifying class for biological driven variation. Men and women are both physically and psychologically different and society magnifies the the difference that was there to begin with.</p>
<p>The concept of two genders, male and female, are just labels we apply to the general trend we see in people who are biologically male and people who are biologically female. In the end though, as with all such generalizations and labels, they only describe trends and there are always outliers who don’t fit the trend well. These are trans people, and there’s nothing wrong with that and their identification should be accepted.</p>
<p>It gets much more muddled when you go on tumblr and people argue that there are 25 million different genders and everyone should be allowed to identify as whatever they please. You can’t really let people invent whatever they want and call themselves that because then terms and categories lose all meaning as they are whatever the person wishes them to be. The gender binary emerged because it is a powerful descriptor of real trends observed across those who are biologically male and biologically female. At the same time, you can’t disregard anything but a shallow interpretation of the situation and say that those with male genitalia must identify as male and those with female genitalia must identify as female. The only tenable solution is a reasonable compromise between a person’s own invented or otherwise identification and the general consensus of society. Of course this system can only be as progressive as society, but in reality that is true of so many things and in many ways a pretty fundamental compromise and the way to fix it is to be an active participant in society and shift that compromise in the direction you see fit.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/self-identity-friendly-debate-thread/14609/28">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/self-identity-friendly-debate-thread/14609/28</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 23 Jan 2016 07:55:40 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14609-28</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/self-identity-friendly-debate-thread/14609.rss">Self Identity (friendly)debate thread</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Self Identity (friendly)debate thread</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Chickenprotector]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Fair enough.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/self-identity-friendly-debate-thread/14609/27">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/self-identity-friendly-debate-thread/14609/27</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 22 Jan 2016 00:39:55 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14609-27</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/self-identity-friendly-debate-thread/14609.rss">Self Identity (friendly)debate thread</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Self Identity (friendly)debate thread</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[_rot_fodder]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Oh very slim, very very slim. Doesn’t mean we shouldn’t call it out though.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/self-identity-friendly-debate-thread/14609/26">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/self-identity-friendly-debate-thread/14609/26</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 22 Jan 2016 00:36:27 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14609-26</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/self-identity-friendly-debate-thread/14609.rss">Self Identity (friendly)debate thread</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Self Identity (friendly)debate thread</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Chickenprotector]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="(rot)(fodder">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 (rot)(fodder:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>What I’m saying is we should be removing the notion of gender identity instead of empowering it.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I completely agree, but what do you think the chances are of that actually happening in modern western society?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/self-identity-friendly-debate-thread/14609/25">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/self-identity-friendly-debate-thread/14609/25</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jan 2016 18:05:09 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14609-25</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/self-identity-friendly-debate-thread/14609.rss">Self Identity (friendly)debate thread</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Self Identity (friendly)debate thread</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[_rot_fodder]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Exactly! Gender identity is only a problem because someone decided it <span class="bbcode-i">could</span> be.</p>
<p>What I’m saying is we should be removing the notion of gender identity instead of empowering it.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/self-identity-friendly-debate-thread/14609/24">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/self-identity-friendly-debate-thread/14609/24</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jan 2016 18:01:38 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14609-24</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/self-identity-friendly-debate-thread/14609.rss">Self Identity (friendly)debate thread</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Self Identity (friendly)debate thread</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Chickenprotector]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><a href="https://www.google.com/search?num=100&amp;site=&amp;source=hp&amp;q=placebo+effect&amp;oq=placibo+&amp;gs_l=hp.3.0.0i10l10.333.1573.0.2871.8.8.0.0.0.0.112.713.3j4.7.0....0...1c.1.64.hp..1.7.709.LAUnBkj5Mzw" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Placebo Effect</a>. Apply it to a mental state.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/self-identity-friendly-debate-thread/14609/23">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/self-identity-friendly-debate-thread/14609/23</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jan 2016 17:51:46 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14609-23</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/self-identity-friendly-debate-thread/14609.rss">Self Identity (friendly)debate thread</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Self Identity (friendly)debate thread</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[_rot_fodder]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>So if the only difference is physical, how can you have the brain of the opposite gender?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/self-identity-friendly-debate-thread/14609/22">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/self-identity-friendly-debate-thread/14609/22</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jan 2016 17:44:46 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14609-22</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/self-identity-friendly-debate-thread/14609.rss">Self Identity (friendly)debate thread</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Self Identity (friendly)debate thread</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Chickenprotector]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="(rot)(fodder">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 (rot)(fodder:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>What are some of these differences?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>That is just that, there <span class="bbcode-i">are</span> differences between the genders. Physically, one can have functional milk-producing boobs, it’s just easier for women to have them since their body makeup intends them for use. Men have them too, but it takes coaxing to produce the milk from the gland(s) (don’t ask me the exact details I am <span class="bbcode-i">not a biology major</span>).</p>
<p>Mentally, both men and women are one and the same, background gives you your personality and your values, there are some physical differences (boobs, your bits, brain chemistry), but over all they’re the same. As such, there is no such thing as being “transgender” physically, it’s a purely psychological condition.</p>
<p>And a woman may look like a guy depending on how she dresses and vise-versa, but that’s achieved artificially. Biologically, you’re still the original gender you were given even if you have the brain of the opposite gender.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/self-identity-friendly-debate-thread/14609/21">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/self-identity-friendly-debate-thread/14609/21</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jan 2016 17:30:08 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14609-21</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/self-identity-friendly-debate-thread/14609.rss">Self Identity (friendly)debate thread</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Self Identity (friendly)debate thread</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[_rot_fodder]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>And this is exactly why the entire concept of “Gender Identity” is rediculous.</p>
<p>Here, so there is no fundamental difference between whites and blacks (I agree) but you are saying there are fundamental differences between men and women. What are some of these differences?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/self-identity-friendly-debate-thread/14609/20">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/self-identity-friendly-debate-thread/14609/20</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jan 2016 17:09:51 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14609-20</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/self-identity-friendly-debate-thread/14609.rss">Self Identity (friendly)debate thread</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Self Identity (friendly)debate thread</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[danielsangeo]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Except that race is a social classification that we apply according to one’s skin color.  Gender identity is not skin color.  It is something much more personal than that.  It’s one’s own brain.  And the term “transgender” is the term we use to describe that certain trait where one’s physical appearance, gender-wise, does not match their gender identity.  Many people have been made aware of the term “transgender” without themselves becoming transgender (one cannot “become transgender”).</p>
<p><a href="https://s-media-cache-ak0.pinimg.com/236x/d1/20/04/d12004e5a3a447c17e6fb1ecc1d7fce2.jpg" data-bbcode="true">This person</a> can self-identify as a woman even if she doesn’t act in what one my stereotypically call “female behavior”.  Even the most butch, flannel-shirted, short-haired, tattooed lesbian is still a woman if she self-identifies as such.  The most effeminate, metrosexual, primped and yuppified <a href="https://s3.drafthouse.com/images/made/cabin_boy_2a2r7nk_758_426_81_s_c1.jpg" data-bbcode="true">man</a> is still a man if he self-identifies as such.</p>
<p>Transgender is not a state of behavior.  It’s a state of mind and rests in the brain.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/self-identity-friendly-debate-thread/14609/19">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/self-identity-friendly-debate-thread/14609/19</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jan 2016 10:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14609-19</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/self-identity-friendly-debate-thread/14609.rss">Self Identity (friendly)debate thread</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Self Identity (friendly)debate thread</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[_rot_fodder]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>^ Honestly it’s because my mind flies through what I’m thinking at 100MPH and when I try to talk out what I’m thinking, it comes out as nonsense most of the time, so I’m going to try and keep my posts in here short to avoid confusion.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="danielsangeo">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/user_avatar/leakfree.org/danielsangeo/40/4347_2.png" class="avatar"> danielsangeo:</div>
<blockquote>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="(rot)(fodder">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 (rot)(fodder:</div>
<blockquote></blockquote>
</aside>
<p>That’s a hypothetical question that cannot be answered because that would require a fundamental change in tree of life. You seem to assume that transgender is just something someone heard about from someone else they thought it was a good idea. Well, where did the <span class="bbcode-i">first</span> transgender person come from?</p>
<p>No.  People are transgender even if they’ve never heard of the concept before.  For example, a close family member of mine is like that, despite never prior knowing of its existence.  So, where did THAT come from?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Okay, so I think I see where we are not seeing eye to eye here. So first off, that is EXACTLY what I am assuming, but I am talking about “transgender” the term, not the people.</p>
<p>I’m going to risk taking this off topic to make a point.<br>
When you fight against the notions of racism, you are trying to disassociate stereotypes from physical features. With “Gender identity” we do the EXACT opposite. It would be retarded if we started re-designating people or making more categories for race, can you imagine meeting an African-American businessman who self identifies as “white” because he is successful? It’s complete madness, but that is how they try to deal with gender stereotypes.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/self-identity-friendly-debate-thread/14609/18">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/self-identity-friendly-debate-thread/14609/18</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jan 2016 07:01:07 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14609-18</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/self-identity-friendly-debate-thread/14609.rss">Self Identity (friendly)debate thread</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Self Identity (friendly)debate thread</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[geekofalltrades]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="(rot)(fodder">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 (rot)(fodder:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Gender identity stems from assumptions that boys (with dangly dingles) should act one way and that girls (no dangle)  should act another. It then attempts to make people who don’t conform to these set guidelines by giving them the opposite identity, which is quite frankly retarded beyond all words. Because mentally, people are people and not boys and girls, there is no simple designation that will account for everyone so they started making new extra-retarded designations for people who don’t fall neatly into any particular category.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Now this is an interesting perspective, and one I’ll have to consider. It did not come through at all in your posts in YLYL, FYI.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/self-identity-friendly-debate-thread/14609/17">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/self-identity-friendly-debate-thread/14609/17</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jan 2016 05:56:44 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14609-17</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/self-identity-friendly-debate-thread/14609.rss">Self Identity (friendly)debate thread</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Self Identity (friendly)debate thread</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Chickenprotector]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="danielsangeo">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/user_avatar/leakfree.org/danielsangeo/40/4347_2.png" class="avatar"> danielsangeo:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Except this did not happen with my family member.  There was no trauma, “deep” or otherwise.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I said “generally,” this means its open-ended. It’s not always the case. My point still stands, it doesn’t need to be an object or a substance to change your body’s chemistry. Case and point: placebos are used consistently in medicine, and nine times out of ten unless the subject has the actual illness, their conditions improve. One can apply this to one’s mental state, eventually a physical change occurs if you believe something long enough and/or strongly enough.</p>
<p>I think you missed the joke Tiki was trying to get at…</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/self-identity-friendly-debate-thread/14609/16">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/self-identity-friendly-debate-thread/14609/16</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jan 2016 00:42:34 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14609-16</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/self-identity-friendly-debate-thread/14609.rss">Self Identity (friendly)debate thread</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Self Identity (friendly)debate thread</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[danielsangeo]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="(rot)(fodder">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 (rot)(fodder:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Of course their brains are different, they use them differently. Okay, let us go back to the starting question, we will work out way up through this.</p>
<p>What would gender identity be, if we didn’t designate a mental state to a specific gender in the first place?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>That’s a hypothetical question that cannot be answered because that would require a fundamental change in tree of life.  You seem to assume that transgender is just something someone heard about from someone else they thought it was a good idea.  Well, where did the <span class="bbcode-i">first</span> transgender person come from?</p>
<p>No.  People are transgender even if they’ve never heard of the concept before.  For example, a close family member of mine is like that, despite never prior knowing of its existence.  So, where did THAT come from?</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Chickenprotector">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/user_avatar/leakfree.org/chickenprotector/40/5653_2.png" class="avatar"> Chickenprotector:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Anyway, these behaviors are generally routed from deep trauma, often times from childhood.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Except this did not happen with my family member.  There was no trauma, “deep” or otherwise.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Tiki">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/user_avatar/leakfree.org/tiki/40/4392_2.png" class="avatar"> Tiki:</div>
<blockquote>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="danielsangeo">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/user_avatar/leakfree.org/danielsangeo/40/4347_2.png" class="avatar"> danielsangeo:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>How should people respond to this?  How would YOU respond to these terms being applied to you?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Excuse me, I find the term '<span class="bbcode-i">people’</span>  to be really <span class="bbcode-i"><span class="bbcode-b">problematic</span></span>.<br>
I’m a <span class="bbcode-b"><span class="bbcode-i">gender-fluid, nonbinary, pansexual horsekin</span></span> and I don’t identify as a <span class="bbcode-b"><span class="bbcode-i">person</span></span><span class="bbcode-i">.</span><a href="https://terminallance.com/2016/01/08/terminal-lance-new-corps/" data-bbcode="true">*</a></p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Transgender, in conversational English, does not apply to those identities.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/self-identity-friendly-debate-thread/14609/15">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/self-identity-friendly-debate-thread/14609/15</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jan 2016 23:59:36 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14609-15</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/self-identity-friendly-debate-thread/14609.rss">Self Identity (friendly)debate thread</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Self Identity (friendly)debate thread</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Tiki]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="danielsangeo">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/user_avatar/leakfree.org/danielsangeo/40/4347_2.png" class="avatar"> danielsangeo:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>How should people respond to this?  How would YOU respond to these terms being applied to you?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Excuse me, I find the term '<span class="bbcode-i">people’</span>  to be really <span class="bbcode-i"><span class="bbcode-b">problematic</span></span>.<br>
I’m a <span class="bbcode-b"><span class="bbcode-i">gender-fluid, nonbinary, pansexual horsekin</span></span> and I don’t identify as a <span class="bbcode-b"><span class="bbcode-i">person</span></span><span class="bbcode-i">.</span><a href="https://terminallance.com/2016/01/08/terminal-lance-new-corps/" data-bbcode="true">*</a></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/self-identity-friendly-debate-thread/14609/14">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/self-identity-friendly-debate-thread/14609/14</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jan 2016 23:31:19 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14609-14</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/self-identity-friendly-debate-thread/14609.rss">Self Identity (friendly)debate thread</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Self Identity (friendly)debate thread</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Chickenprotector]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="danielsangeo">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/user_avatar/leakfree.org/danielsangeo/40/4347_2.png" class="avatar"> danielsangeo:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>That actually don’t make sense.  The physical brain is different in transgender people than their cisgender counterparts.  And there appears to be other differences as well.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>… Must… Ignore… Grammatical… Error… Grammar… Nazi… Mode… Contained…</p>
<p>Anyway, these behaviors are generally routed from deep trauma, often times from childhood. It make sense that the chemistry inside of their brain would change. If you believe something long enough, your brain will eventually adapt it and make the appropriate changes. A bad thyroid would cause a hormonal imbalance for instance, or a developing male child who eventually considers themselves a girl in a guys body for whatever reason. In some ways it is similar to addiction.</p>
<p>Over a long time of exposure, a substance can change your brain chemistry, in a similar way, if you believe something long enough, your brain will change its chemistry gradually over time, especially if you’re still developing. You don’t truly finish growing up until about the age of 24, possibly later in some instances. In any case my point stands.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="(rot)(fodder">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 (rot)(fodder:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>What would gender identity be, if we didn’t designate a mental state to a specific gender in the first place?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Good question.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/self-identity-friendly-debate-thread/14609/13">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/self-identity-friendly-debate-thread/14609/13</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jan 2016 22:07:15 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14609-13</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/self-identity-friendly-debate-thread/14609.rss">Self Identity (friendly)debate thread</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Self Identity (friendly)debate thread</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[_rot_fodder]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>So I’m an asshole. Moving on.</p>
<p>Of course their brains are different, they use them differently. Okay, let us go back to the starting question, we will work out way up through this.</p>
<p>What would gender identity be, if we didn’t designate a mental state to a specific gender in the first place?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/self-identity-friendly-debate-thread/14609/12">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/self-identity-friendly-debate-thread/14609/12</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jan 2016 21:15:27 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14609-12</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/self-identity-friendly-debate-thread/14609.rss">Self Identity (friendly)debate thread</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Self Identity (friendly)debate thread</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[danielsangeo]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="(rot)(fodder">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 (rot)(fodder:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>The reason is because these people have been duped into believing in an imaginary issue.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>That actually don’t make sense.  The physical brain is different in transgender people than their cisgender counterparts.  And there appears to be other differences as well.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>EDIT: Missed you post on my phone Dansan the first time. I thin you missed my point, you are saying identity is a mental state, and I am saying I agree 100%.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>It’s NOT a mental state, though.  It’s a physical state.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>P.S. If I offended you try reading it again in a different tone. I think that’s also covered in the rules somewhere too</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Oh,  you’d have to go a long way to offend me.</p>
<p>Also:<br>
“extra-retarded”<br>
“insecure idget”<br>
“fucktard”<br>
These are all terms you used directly out of the gate to describe transgender people.  How should people respond to this?  How would YOU respond to these terms being applied to you?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/self-identity-friendly-debate-thread/14609/11">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/self-identity-friendly-debate-thread/14609/11</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jan 2016 21:05:09 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14609-11</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/self-identity-friendly-debate-thread/14609.rss">Self Identity (friendly)debate thread</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Self Identity (friendly)debate thread</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Chickenprotector]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I think we can all agree on that. It’s just apart of the times, I also think it shouldn’t even be an issue either. Yet here we are.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/self-identity-friendly-debate-thread/14609/10">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/self-identity-friendly-debate-thread/14609/10</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jan 2016 17:57:20 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14609-10</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/self-identity-friendly-debate-thread/14609.rss">Self Identity (friendly)debate thread</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Self Identity (friendly)debate thread</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypt]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Yes, there’s no arguing that it genuinely affects people. It’s just ridiculous that it’s an issue because it really shouldn’t be.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/self-identity-friendly-debate-thread/14609/9">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/self-identity-friendly-debate-thread/14609/9</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jan 2016 17:51:09 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14609-9</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/self-identity-friendly-debate-thread/14609.rss">Self Identity (friendly)debate thread</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Self Identity (friendly)debate thread</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[_rot_fodder]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Crypt just said exactly what I am trying to get at.</p>
<p>And yes, gender identity really affects people, but the only reason that is true is because people believed it could. It’s a self made issue, it didn’t exist until someone said it did.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/self-identity-friendly-debate-thread/14609/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/self-identity-friendly-debate-thread/14609/8</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jan 2016 17:48:22 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14609-8</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/self-identity-friendly-debate-thread/14609.rss">Self Identity (friendly)debate thread</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Self Identity (friendly)debate thread</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Chickenprotector]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><a href="https://forums.blackmesasource.com/index.php/User/606-rot-fodder/" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">@(rot)(fodder</a> I thought my view was controversial… though that’s only a snippet on how I really feel about the entire fiasco known as Identity Politics, I didn’t want to get to the nitty gritty and be too offensive, so I trimmed it down.</p>
<p>I agree with transgenderism being a mental state and it being an imaginary issue like the “gender wage gap” in the United States.</p>
<p>That doesn’t mean it doesn’t exist. Hatred for gay people or any person for what they are will always exist, you can’t farm it out of society, it’ll always exist on the fringe. Sexism also isn’t as large of a problem as millennials think it is, yes it does exist, but it isn’t as wide spread as they’re claiming. Essentially, the issue DOES exist, but it isn’t as wide spread as they’re claiming it is.</p>
<p>Edit: If you were trying to iterate something other than what I thought you said, then you should explain a little further.</p>
<p>Edit <span class="hashtag">#2:</span> It occurs to me that I wasn’t entirely clear: 9 times out of 10 transgenderism will always be a purely mental issue. Having a troubled background/history and having that feeling reinforced over the years can hammer that into a persons mental state and even change their brain chemistry later down the line. Sometimes it could be a hormonal imbalance, but that’s a whole other can of worms.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/self-identity-friendly-debate-thread/14609/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/self-identity-friendly-debate-thread/14609/7</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jan 2016 17:36:59 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14609-7</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/self-identity-friendly-debate-thread/14609.rss">Self Identity (friendly)debate thread</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
