<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>de_jokey</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/de-jokey/224</link>
    <description>I made this years ago as an official enemydown map for their tournaments, but due to lack of time I couldn&#39;t finish it. The timings to get to the bombsites were timed to perfection; there were hidden noises like creaking floorboards etc for players who master every map, and plenty of nice awping spots.

The story for the map was that a group of arm dealers found the derelict hotel and knocked through walls etc, to use it as a depot. The two bombsites have a nearby alley way to the main road for exporting the goods. Anyway, the police got a lead on where they were hiding the illegal weaponry and that&#39;s why the CT&#39;s are there (they came through a sewer drain just outside their spawn point). It&#39;s up to the CT&#39;s to kill the terrorists or defuse any bombs planted to secure the evidence and it&#39;s up to the terrorists to kill, or get rid of as much of the weaponry they couldn&#39;t take away in time by blowing it up.

[url=&#39;https://tistin.co.uk/album/index.php/hammer/de_cuba&#39;][u]Here&#39;s the link for the pics.[/u][/url] ^_^

Edit - Just to add a bit more info. I would of liked to put more detail into the map but this was meant to be fps friendly (for those CS players who say CSS is just eye candy etc), but I also wanted it to look nice though of course. Bombsite A is the lobby area of the hotel, with clockroom etc, the middle of the map is an indoor seating area, same as Bombsite B which would of been an outside seating area, with nearby homes and their back gardens.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 10 May 2009 22:32:36 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Show Off</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/de-jokey/224.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>de_jokey</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Chris]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Thanks Zerego.  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=9" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
<p>I have some other things I’ve done in hammer but de_cuba is my best work. I might upload pics of other stuff if I think they’re good enough.  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=9" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/de-jokey/224/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/de-jokey/224/3</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 10 May 2009 22:32:36 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-224-3</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/de-jokey/224.rss">de_jokey</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>de_jokey</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Zerego]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Woah. That looks really good :o</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/de-jokey/224/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/de-jokey/224/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 10 May 2009 17:00:52 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-224-2</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/de-jokey/224.rss">de_jokey</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>de_jokey</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Chris]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I made this years ago as an official enemydown map for their tournaments, but due to lack of time I couldn’t finish it. The timings to get to the bombsites were timed to perfection; there were hidden noises like creaking floorboards etc for players who master every map, and plenty of nice awping spots.</p>
<p>The story for the map was that a group of arm dealers found the derelict hotel and knocked through walls etc, to use it as a depot. The two bombsites have a nearby alley way to the main road for exporting the goods. Anyway, the police got a lead on where they were hiding the illegal weaponry and that’s why the CT’s are there (they came through a sewer drain just outside their spawn point). It’s up to the CT’s to kill the terrorists or defuse any bombs planted to secure the evidence and it’s up to the terrorists to kill, or get rid of as much of the weaponry they couldn’t take away in time by blowing it up.</p>
<p><a href="https://tistin.co.uk/album/index.php/hammer/de_cuba" data-bbcode="true" rel="noopener nofollow ugc"><span class="bbcode-u">Here’s the link for the pics.</span></a> <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=9" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
<p>Edit - Just to add a bit more info. I would of liked to put more detail into the map but this was meant to be fps friendly (for those CS players who say CSS is just eye candy etc), but I also wanted it to look nice though of course. Bombsite A is the lobby area of the hotel, with clockroom etc, the middle of the map is an indoor seating area, same as Bombsite B which would of been an outside seating area, with nearby homes and their back gardens.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/de-jokey/224/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/de-jokey/224/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 10 May 2009 13:13:23 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-224-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/de-jokey/224.rss">de_jokey</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
