<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>PS3 vs. Xbox 360</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/ps3-vs-xbox-360/4567</link>
    <description>I&#39;m surprised there isn&#39;t already a thread about this.

Console war between PS3 and the Xbox 360 goes here!

What do you like with your console?</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 24 Jun 2010 00:58:31 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Off Topic</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/ps3-vs-xbox-360/4567.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>PS3 vs. Xbox 360</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Android11x]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Very well! I declare this thread over!</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/ps3-vs-xbox-360/4567/120">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/ps3-vs-xbox-360/4567/120</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jun 2010 00:58:31 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-4567-120</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/ps3-vs-xbox-360/4567.rss">PS3 vs. Xbox 360</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>PS3 vs. Xbox 360</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Mr.Shadow]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Me neither. It was just a question.</p>
<p>And like Jerry said: Everyone has different preferences. I see it as half finished, but that’s just IMO. You love the xbox, but that’s your opinion.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/ps3-vs-xbox-360/4567/119">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/ps3-vs-xbox-360/4567/119</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jun 2010 20:38:34 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-4567-119</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/ps3-vs-xbox-360/4567.rss">PS3 vs. Xbox 360</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>PS3 vs. Xbox 360</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Android11x]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><a class="mention" href="/u/shadow">@Shadow</a></p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Android11x">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/a/b9bd4f/40.png" class="avatar"> Android11x:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>This means MOVEH NIGHT in the family room! Oh, and slide shows to cry and laugh at. ORITE, and some dance parties while I’m the DJ.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>My PC is in the basement. Plus the TV has HD and surround sound and it’d be stupid to watch movie on my PC when I can on something so much better.</p>
<p>SO! Xbox is great for gaming and delivers a pretty decent media center.</p>
<p>I don’t see the problem.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/ps3-vs-xbox-360/4567/118">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/ps3-vs-xbox-360/4567/118</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jun 2010 20:30:58 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-4567-118</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/ps3-vs-xbox-360/4567.rss">PS3 vs. Xbox 360</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>PS3 vs. Xbox 360</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Surplus]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Play music while playing games.  It’s what I did.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/ps3-vs-xbox-360/4567/117">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/ps3-vs-xbox-360/4567/117</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jun 2010 20:28:57 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-4567-117</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/ps3-vs-xbox-360/4567.rss">PS3 vs. Xbox 360</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>PS3 vs. Xbox 360</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Mr.Shadow]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>But, like you said: if you only care about games, then what would be the point of that. And what advantage could you possibly have to connect it to your PC, instead of using your PC for all that crap?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/ps3-vs-xbox-360/4567/116">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/ps3-vs-xbox-360/4567/116</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jun 2010 20:24:46 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-4567-116</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/ps3-vs-xbox-360/4567.rss">PS3 vs. Xbox 360</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>PS3 vs. Xbox 360</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Android11x]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>BluRay/Wi-Fi &lt; connect directly to your PC and stream all of your music, videos, pictures, etc. Using Netflix, Last.fm and Instant Messengers. Strong online support and easy in-game interface. And… moar games.</p>
<p>Plus it’s like $5 to buy a 50 foot Ethernet cable so you can just run it to the your router and/or modem.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Jeannotvb">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/j/90ced4/40.png" class="avatar"> Jeannotvb:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>You haven’t really shown me that it’s cheaper. But ok.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>The point I tried to make is that online is free until you want to make the jump to Gold. And if you purchase an Xbox you get one month free to test it out.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/ps3-vs-xbox-360/4567/115">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/ps3-vs-xbox-360/4567/115</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jun 2010 20:18:35 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-4567-115</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/ps3-vs-xbox-360/4567.rss">PS3 vs. Xbox 360</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>PS3 vs. Xbox 360</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[jerry]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Everyone has different standards.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/ps3-vs-xbox-360/4567/114">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/ps3-vs-xbox-360/4567/114</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jun 2010 20:03:27 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-4567-114</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/ps3-vs-xbox-360/4567.rss">PS3 vs. Xbox 360</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>PS3 vs. Xbox 360</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Mr.Shadow]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Thank you… I think.</p>
<p>And the reason I bought xbox is because I thought it would go by my standards.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/ps3-vs-xbox-360/4567/113">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/ps3-vs-xbox-360/4567/113</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jun 2010 15:25:39 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-4567-113</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/ps3-vs-xbox-360/4567.rss">PS3 vs. Xbox 360</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>PS3 vs. Xbox 360</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[jerry]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Mr. Shadow: oh, i see you are not banned anymore. congratulations.</p>
<p>the reason why i bought xbox over ps3 is that xbox is more focusing on gaming, if i had the ps3, i would hack it, surf, install linux, and never play. as for rrod/rdod i think microsoft didnt fix it because if it wasnt there, more people would open it, and they wouldnt have that much to lose voiding their warranty. if you void you warranty on a console with rrod/rdod, microsoft would never fix it free.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/ps3-vs-xbox-360/4567/112">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/ps3-vs-xbox-360/4567/112</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jun 2010 15:22:01 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-4567-112</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/ps3-vs-xbox-360/4567.rss">PS3 vs. Xbox 360</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>PS3 vs. Xbox 360</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Mr.Shadow]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Android11x">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/a/b9bd4f/40.png" class="avatar"> Android11x:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I’d like Shadow to spit out the proof to why the PS3 is all around better because I dunno about you, but I like my console to play games. Not just shitty BluRays. I also like to connect with people over a community.</p>
<p>And there’s always room for improvement with anything, including consoles. The Xbox is upgrading, woohoo. It’s not half-finished, jackass. It’s shipping out a new unit. I’m pretty sure if I were to choose a company to work for that can please it’s customers and reap in profit I would choose Microsoft because they’re doing just that. And by opening up with Kinect they are spreading out to casuals as I’ve stated before which can only be good.</p>
<p>I love how most PS3 owners just yell about how they can play BluRays like it’s the best thing. If you take away the BluRay, what else is there? No, seriously. And don’t say Wi-Fi because NOW! Xbox is going to have it.</p>
<p>Oh, and Daedalus: My apologizes for offending you with my language, but you don’t have to resort to bashing people who are Xbox biased.</p>
<p>[COLOR=‘Red’]EDIT:</p>
<p>I do believe the Xbox Pro costs roughly $180 while the PS3 80GB is $270. Cheaper you say?<br>
Wait, the new Xbox Slim (250GB) is $300 with the Wi-Fi. My bad.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>But the fact it’s upgrading so much, makes me believe it was half finished.</p>
<p>I like to be able to do multiple things on my consoles. If you don’t like it, fine. We are not forcing you. As for Blue - ray: It’s going to be the next DVD. Y’know, like the video - DVD stuff that happen’d years ago. If you buy it now, you won’t have to buy a blue - ray player in the future.</p>
<p>And yes, it is infact cheaper, because you don’t have to buy everything for it.</p>
<p>And yes, I will say wi-fi, because the xbox is only getting it, while ps3 already has it, has free intarwebz which is , while slightly lower quality, simpy better 'cause it’s cheap. Not that I care that much for it, because I barely play multiplayers. So IMO, ps3 is better.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/ps3-vs-xbox-360/4567/111">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/ps3-vs-xbox-360/4567/111</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jun 2010 12:42:57 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-4567-111</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/ps3-vs-xbox-360/4567.rss">PS3 vs. Xbox 360</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>PS3 vs. Xbox 360</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[jerry]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Android11x">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/a/b9bd4f/40.png" class="avatar"> Android11x:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Well, the Xbox is quite the media fanatic as well, I’ll have you know.</p>
<p>IN FACT!</p>
<p>The thing that’s awesome is the fact the 360 can connect directly to your PC (unless your a Mac :meh <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=9" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:">  and stream all of your music, videos, pictures, etc. This may also be the reason piracy is possible on the Xbox. Oh, and using Netflix, Last.fm and my Instant Messanger is awesome.</p>
<p>THAT SAID! This means MOVEH NIGHT in the family room! Oh, and slide shows to cry and laugh at. ORITE, and some dance parties while I’m the DJ.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Yep, xbox is awesome as a media center.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/ps3-vs-xbox-360/4567/110">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/ps3-vs-xbox-360/4567/110</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jun 2010 09:16:19 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-4567-110</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/ps3-vs-xbox-360/4567.rss">PS3 vs. Xbox 360</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>PS3 vs. Xbox 360</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Jeannotvb]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Android11x">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/a/b9bd4f/40.png" class="avatar"> Android11x:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>You’d think so, but you’d be wrong. Lemme get things straight with Xbox Live.</p>
<p>There are two kinds of Live membership:</p>
<p>[COLOR=‘Silver’]Silver: Free, need internet connection + these perks</p>
<ul>
<li>Go online free of charge.</li>
<li>Register a unique gamertag and set up your individual gamer card to keep track of your gaming accomplishments.</li>
<li>Engage in one-on-one Voice Over Internet Protocol (VOIP) and chat with your friends via the Xbox 360 Headset.</li>
<li>Access Xbox Live Marketplace, download and view demos, trailers, and purchase classic and casual games over Xbox Live Arcade using Microsoft Points.</li>
<li>Preview Xbox Live Gold during free weekend trials.</li>
<li>Download auto updates and free downloads for your Xbox 360 games.</li>
<li>Access Xbox Live Message Center where you can send and receive voice and text messages from other members.</li>
<li>Compare gaming stats and achievements against other Xbox Live members.</li>
<li>Use your friends list to see who’s online.<br>
[COLOR=‘Gold’]<br>
Gold: $50 annual free, need internet connect + these perks</li>
<li>Play your Xbox 360 multiplayer games online with the premiere online gaming service.</li>
<li>Use the brand new TrueSkill Matchmaking system to play against opponents with similar skills, personalities, and gaming tastes.</li>
<li>Give player feedback to rate your teammates and opponents on their sportsmanship, abilities, and conduct to influence matchmaking.</li>
<li>Play select original Xbox games online (the Xbox 360 Hard Drive is required).</li>
<li>Get access to exclusive Gold Member content.</li>
<li>Engage in video chat.</li>
<li>Enjoy all the Xbox Live Silver features (above).</li>
</ul>
<p>And I’m not bashing the PS3… much. This is a versus thread and I’m giving information that could essentially help someone make the decision on purchasing a console. I believe the Xbox has “more bang for your buck” if you’re looking for gaming (for both casuals and hardcores, media viewing, user-friendliness, and a fulfilling online experience.</p>
<p>Xbox is just as much, if not, more a home entertainment center than the PS3. What it boils down to is what <span class="bbcode-i">you are</span> looking for in a console. I find that Xbox caters to the majority of mine and many others’ needs. Also, Microsoft has been nothing, but nice to me since I got the “[COLOR=‘Red’]Red Ring Of Death” after having the 360 for 3 years. Sent me a new one, free of charge even though I had surpassed my warranty.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>You haven’t really shown me that it’s cheaper. But ok.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/ps3-vs-xbox-360/4567/109">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/ps3-vs-xbox-360/4567/109</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jun 2010 07:03:52 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-4567-109</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/ps3-vs-xbox-360/4567.rss">PS3 vs. Xbox 360</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>PS3 vs. Xbox 360</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Android11x]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Well, the Xbox is quite the media fanatic as well, I’ll have you know.</p>
<p>IN FACT!</p>
<p>The thing that’s awesome is the fact the 360 can connect directly to your PC (unless your a Mac :meh <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=9" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:">  and stream all of your music, videos, pictures, etc. This may also be the reason piracy is possible on the Xbox. Oh, and using Netflix, Last.fm and my Instant Messanger is awesome.</p>
<p>THAT SAID! This means MOVEH NIGHT in the family room! Oh, and slide shows to cry and laugh at. ORITE, and some dance parties while I’m the DJ.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/ps3-vs-xbox-360/4567/108">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/ps3-vs-xbox-360/4567/108</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jun 2010 23:30:31 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-4567-108</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/ps3-vs-xbox-360/4567.rss">PS3 vs. Xbox 360</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>PS3 vs. Xbox 360</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Surplus]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I have a 360 I wish I hadn’t have bought it not that I wish I had bought a PS3.  Really this generation of consoles is total garbage.  Don’t feed me that motion control is innovation bullshit.  Its a new form of input instead of pressing a button I wave my arm.  The increase in immersion can be likened to better graphics, in the end its still all about the game design.</p>
<p>The big problem here is that consoles are bottle necking themselves with such strict regulation.  Microsoft is a total ass-face about it but at least Sony shows improvements with the allowing Steam.  With CoD:MW 2 (I thought about removing the face but I feel it is appropriate) not allowing dedicated server support or mods for PC just makes me more angry.  Consoles need to find a way to allow all that great custom content and freedom that PC games have;  if they don’t do that it won’t take people long to realize the illusion of a low price and simplicity that a console supplies and they will switch to PC.</p>
<p>My point being consoles all suck, pick your poison.  There is very little improvement from the last generation of consoles in terms of the platform.  The only thing that has really changed is a wider software support of online play.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/ps3-vs-xbox-360/4567/107">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/ps3-vs-xbox-360/4567/107</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jun 2010 23:25:10 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-4567-107</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/ps3-vs-xbox-360/4567.rss">PS3 vs. Xbox 360</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>PS3 vs. Xbox 360</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Daedalus]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Yeah that is pretty cool, but don’t you think it should’ve been from the start? I like the fact that they’re being so cool about the customer service, but with a console that gets defects that often, you don’t have much choice. If they’d created a console with 90% failure rate and then just be assholes in customer service too they’d probably been sued till the clothes were taken from their bodies.</p>
<p>Anywho, I can see why you prefer the XBOX though. I’m a mediawhore myself so therefore I prefer the PS3 (And of course cause of aforementioned reasons). But if you’re soley a gamer, don’t give a crap about movies etc, and alot about online gameplay that’s nice and streamlined, then the XBOX is the better choice. The reliability issues remain bad, but atleast they’re being cool about it.</p>
<p>But yeah like Maxey said it probably bit them in the butt pretty hard.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/ps3-vs-xbox-360/4567/106">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/ps3-vs-xbox-360/4567/106</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jun 2010 23:22:50 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-4567-106</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/ps3-vs-xbox-360/4567.rss">PS3 vs. Xbox 360</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>PS3 vs. Xbox 360</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Maxey]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I’m willing to bet MS spent more money with the whole RROD thing than all the money they spent on creating, launching and marketing the console.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/ps3-vs-xbox-360/4567/105">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/ps3-vs-xbox-360/4567/105</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jun 2010 23:19:17 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-4567-105</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/ps3-vs-xbox-360/4567.rss">PS3 vs. Xbox 360</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>PS3 vs. Xbox 360</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Android11x]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Daedalus, yeah. About that reliability thing with the 360. You are right. I mean I’ve had my PS2 since… probably 2000-- A VERY LONG TIME and never had a problem although sometimes it doesn’t like to read games.</p>
<p>I’ve had my first 360 back in '07 and 3 years later and E74 popped up. I do like, however, the way Microsoft treated me. I was passed my warranty and shipped it in, regardless to see if they could fix it. They could not and just shipped be a new unit with a month of Gold free.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/ps3-vs-xbox-360/4567/104">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/ps3-vs-xbox-360/4567/104</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jun 2010 23:16:04 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-4567-104</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/ps3-vs-xbox-360/4567.rss">PS3 vs. Xbox 360</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>PS3 vs. Xbox 360</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Daedalus]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Yeah, I think it’s just to blame on Sony’s strategy at first. They should’ve focussed more on the gaming part. But in the end, I do think it is the better console, has been from the start, and will be till the end.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/ps3-vs-xbox-360/4567/103">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/ps3-vs-xbox-360/4567/103</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jun 2010 23:13:19 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-4567-103</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/ps3-vs-xbox-360/4567.rss">PS3 vs. Xbox 360</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>PS3 vs. Xbox 360</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Maxey]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Maxey">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/user_avatar/leakfree.org/maxey/40/4358_2.png" class="avatar"> Maxey:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>edit: even with all the reliability issues, the 360 still managed to top the PS3 for a long time. That gotta mean that Microsoft made something very right.<br>
edit2: 360 games have better texture filtering and generally sharper textures than the PS3, but the PS3 compensates for that with more complex effects and higher poly-counts.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>In case you didn’t see the edits.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/ps3-vs-xbox-360/4567/102">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/ps3-vs-xbox-360/4567/102</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jun 2010 23:11:27 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-4567-102</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/ps3-vs-xbox-360/4567.rss">PS3 vs. Xbox 360</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>PS3 vs. Xbox 360</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Daedalus]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Maxey">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/user_avatar/leakfree.org/maxey/40/4358_2.png" class="avatar"> Maxey:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Anyway, since then Sony has improved the online component and changed their marketing strategy to focus on the gaming component only. Game developers have also learned how to code better for the Cell, so most multiplat games perform exactly the same on the two systems.</p>
<p>All that has helped the PS3 to regain some of the lost leadership they had with the PS2.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>And it also proves that they don’t mind spending a little more and sacrificing some to create a very good console. That’s how it should be.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/ps3-vs-xbox-360/4567/101">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/ps3-vs-xbox-360/4567/101</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jun 2010 23:06:31 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-4567-101</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/ps3-vs-xbox-360/4567.rss">PS3 vs. Xbox 360</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>PS3 vs. Xbox 360</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Chrillen]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Android11x">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/a/b9bd4f/40.png" class="avatar"> Android11x:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Oh, and Chrillen: get with the program.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I’m obviously not able to do that so I’ma just stay out.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/ps3-vs-xbox-360/4567/100">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/ps3-vs-xbox-360/4567/100</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jun 2010 23:05:12 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-4567-100</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/ps3-vs-xbox-360/4567.rss">PS3 vs. Xbox 360</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>PS3 vs. Xbox 360</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Maxey]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Anyway, since then Sony has improved the online component and changed their marketing strategy to focus on the gaming component only. Game developers have also learned how to code better for the Cell, so most multiplat games perform exactly the same on the two systems.</p>
<p>All that has helped the PS3 to regain some of the lost leadership they had with the PS2.</p>
<p>edit: even with all the reliability issues, the 360 still managed to top the PS3 for a long time. That gotta mean that Microsoft made something very right.<br>
edit2: 360 games have better texture filtering and generally sharper textures than the PS3, but the PS3 compensates for that with more complex effects and higher poly-counts.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/ps3-vs-xbox-360/4567/99">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/ps3-vs-xbox-360/4567/99</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jun 2010 23:03:59 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-4567-99</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/ps3-vs-xbox-360/4567.rss">PS3 vs. Xbox 360</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>PS3 vs. Xbox 360</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Daedalus]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Yeah you do have a good point there man. And I probably would if I wasn’t also a mediawhore. Except for one thing. Which remains the huge reliability issue. It just put me off so badly that even if the roles were turned around, and the xbox had a bluray etc, I would’nt have bought it just cause of that.<br>
I think it’s just bad ethics really. Bringing something completely immature on the market just to make more money. Completely disregarding the problems that it had, and thus the needs of us, the customers. That thing should’ve been tested far longer.</p>
<p>And it’s soley because of that I’d have bought the PS3. I just have good experiences with Playstation. My PS 1 is over 10 years old and still functions fine. Neither have my PS2 or PSP ever broken down or even shown hickups. They’re just solid electronic devices. Well built and decent, as they should be.</p>
<p>Of course the new xbox has hopefully taken care of the old problems, but it’s just too late. The new xbox is how it should have been when it was first released, instead of a half finished nearly surely to crash console. And not only that, also have I lost all trust in XBOX in the first place, and I’ll never be buying one. Not until Microsoft has once again truely proven it can create a decent, well functioning console, that doesn’t have a 90% failure rate in the first batch. That’s just unacceptable.</p>
<p>EDIT: Also, the PS3 indeed has an inferior graphics card but a far superior CPU. And they’re pretty much the same visual and performance wise so I’d say they cancel eachother out nicely.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/ps3-vs-xbox-360/4567/98">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/ps3-vs-xbox-360/4567/98</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jun 2010 22:59:48 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-4567-98</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/ps3-vs-xbox-360/4567.rss">PS3 vs. Xbox 360</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>PS3 vs. Xbox 360</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Android11x]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I like my strong online support, huge game selection, cheap prices and Xenos GPU which has far more computing power than the RSX GPU that resides in the PS3.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/ps3-vs-xbox-360/4567/97">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/ps3-vs-xbox-360/4567/97</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jun 2010 22:55:52 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-4567-97</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/ps3-vs-xbox-360/4567.rss">PS3 vs. Xbox 360</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>PS3 vs. Xbox 360</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Maxey]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Microsoft focused on the gaming part of the 360 more than Sony with their PS3.</p>
<p>When Sony launched the PS3, their marketing logic was to announce it as a multimedia system, rather than just a game console that also plays blu ray movies. That ended up alienating consumers, thinking that Sony downplayed the console gaming part. Add to that a weak online component on launch, a selection of multiplatform titles that performed better on the 360 because the PS3’s architecture is tricky to program for and a really steep price tag, and you end up with a system that suffers from identity crisis and ended up disappointing gamers.</p>
<p>The 360, however, was marketed from the start as a straight gaming machine, with a strong online support, far easier to program for and cheaper to buy.</p>
<p>If you’re a straight up gamer and look at them in that perspective, which system you end up getting?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/ps3-vs-xbox-360/4567/96">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/ps3-vs-xbox-360/4567/96</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jun 2010 22:48:51 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-4567-96</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/ps3-vs-xbox-360/4567.rss">PS3 vs. Xbox 360</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
