<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Replacing i3 to i5 in a laptop</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/replacing-i3-to-i5-in-a-laptop/7564</link>
    <description>I&#39;m using an Acer Aspire 7741g, and i was wondering, can i replace my i3 Dual-core whit an i5 Quad-core. CPU-Z tells me that my motherboard has an 989 rPGA socket, but i haven&#39;t found an i5 whit that socket. All i5 i have found, were whit LGA1155 sockets. Can i plug i5 into my laptop, or should i just save an extra 150€ and buy i7? (And can i use that also?)

Current system:
Win 7 Home Premium 64-bit
i3-370M 2.4 GHz
ATI Mobility Radeon HD 5470
4 GB Ram</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 27 Jul 2011 05:23:01 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Help and Support</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/replacing-i3-to-i5-in-a-laptop/7564.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Replacing i3 to i5 in a laptop</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[russilker]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>While neither upgrade will net you much in performance, IMO the processor upgrade will give you absolutely 0 benefit. The 4 to 8gb upgrade will at least allow you to multitask more and will help futureproof your system.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/replacing-i3-to-i5-in-a-laptop/7564/12">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/replacing-i3-to-i5-in-a-laptop/7564/12</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 27 Jul 2011 05:23:01 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7564-12</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/replacing-i3-to-i5-in-a-laptop/7564.rss">Replacing i3 to i5 in a laptop</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Replacing i3 to i5 in a laptop</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[FinlandGamer]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Thanks for the information. I’ve ruled out i7 as an possible upgrade to my laptop, and currently searching for an i5-580M. (0.26 GHz upgrade)</p>
<p>While this thread is active, which upgrade is more important, i3 to i5, or 4GB of RAM to 8GB, (2x4GB DDR3). I already know, that RAM upgrade is possible on this computer.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/replacing-i3-to-i5-in-a-laptop/7564/11">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/replacing-i3-to-i5-in-a-laptop/7564/11</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 27 Jul 2011 05:12:01 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7564-11</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/replacing-i3-to-i5-in-a-laptop/7564.rss">Replacing i3 to i5 in a laptop</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Replacing i3 to i5 in a laptop</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[russilker]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Ah alright just wanted to point that out, I just think Intel’s naming scheme is incredibly confusing at times. IMO an i3 should be dual core no hyperthreading and limited features (i.e. how celeron used to be), i5 should be dual core with hyperthreading and have a few more features, and i7 should be four core with hyperthreading and a full feature list. But I digress.</p>
<p>If he does buy that i7 it would be… well, I’m not going to insult his intelligence by suggesting he’d do such a thing. Paying hundreds of dollars for a boost of a few hundred megahertz and unneeded features (for the average consumer anyway) of virtualization technology et al is incredibly retarded.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/replacing-i3-to-i5-in-a-laptop/7564/10">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/replacing-i3-to-i5-in-a-laptop/7564/10</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jul 2011 23:25:09 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7564-10</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/replacing-i3-to-i5-in-a-laptop/7564.rss">Replacing i3 to i5 in a laptop</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Replacing i3 to i5 in a laptop</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[mental2k]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="russilker">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/r/bbce88/40.png" class="avatar"> russilker:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>The i7 640m is only a dual core like his i3 and is really not worth the upgrade at all. Anything with just an M at the end rather than a QM is a dual core, like I said in my last post.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I did agree with you lol.  But he does seem intent on doing it he might as well have a better processor than he already has.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/replacing-i3-to-i5-in-a-laptop/7564/9">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/replacing-i3-to-i5-in-a-laptop/7564/9</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jul 2011 23:18:50 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7564-9</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/replacing-i3-to-i5-in-a-laptop/7564.rss">Replacing i3 to i5 in a laptop</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Replacing i3 to i5 in a laptop</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[calhoun_freeman]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>damn, this brings back memories of buying LGA 1156 mobo when I had LGA 1155 i5.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/replacing-i3-to-i5-in-a-laptop/7564/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/replacing-i3-to-i5-in-a-laptop/7564/8</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jul 2011 22:55:33 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7564-8</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/replacing-i3-to-i5-in-a-laptop/7564.rss">Replacing i3 to i5 in a laptop</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Replacing i3 to i5 in a laptop</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[russilker]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>The i7 640m is only a dual core like his i3 and is really not worth the upgrade at all. Anything with just an M at the end rather than a QM is a dual core, like I said in my last post.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/replacing-i3-to-i5-in-a-laptop/7564/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/replacing-i3-to-i5-in-a-laptop/7564/7</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jul 2011 22:42:59 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7564-7</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/replacing-i3-to-i5-in-a-laptop/7564.rss">Replacing i3 to i5 in a laptop</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Replacing i3 to i5 in a laptop</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[mental2k]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>You could stick an i7-640M in it lol.  They’re pin compatable, BIOS compatable? Thats anyones guess.  Intel might know.  Or check out an overclockers forum.  They love a bit of this stuff.</p>
<p>If money is no limit it is an interesting project, but little more than academic really.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/replacing-i3-to-i5-in-a-laptop/7564/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/replacing-i3-to-i5-in-a-laptop/7564/6</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jul 2011 22:29:02 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7564-6</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/replacing-i3-to-i5-in-a-laptop/7564.rss">Replacing i3 to i5 in a laptop</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Replacing i3 to i5 in a laptop</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[russilker]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>All of those are dual core chips just like your own, so they would give you little to no improvement in performance. There’s also no way anyone fit a mobile i3 or i5 onto a LGA 1156 socket as those processors are intended for mobile sockets and that is a desktop socket; you have your facts confused. He probably had a custom high-end Clevo laptop that had a desktop-class motherboard and processor; even then there’s no way it had a mobile processor like the i3 or i7 you mentioned.</p>
<p>The fact of the matter is that you may not even be able to upgrade to a quad core. Check to see if your laptop model has a BIOS update that allows for Clarksfield processors to be installed; your i3 is an Arrandale. There are no quad core Arrandale processors. Even if the BIOS update is available, there are no quad core Clarksfield processors that clock as high as your i3 does. This means that in demanding single threaded applications, performance will be hurt, VERY significantly depending on which processor you go with (even the most expensive i7-940xm is only clocked at 2.13ghz, the “cheapest” option is the i7-720qm which comes in at 1.6ghz and costs anywhere from $150 to $250 usd). I repeat, unless you have some highly multithreaded applications that are completely CPU dependent and dont care about the GPU, you’re only DOWNGRADING (demanding game performance will suffer, for instance). Lastly, Clarksfield processors have a TDP 10 watts higher than your Arrandale, which means that your laptop will run hotter and your fans will spin louder; that is, if your cooling solution can even handle it.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Read the above paragraph very carefully before you make a potentially idiotic decision</span>.</p>
<p>P.S. Quad core mobile processors end in a “qm”, dual cores just end in “m”. Q stands for Quad, M stands for Mobile.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/replacing-i3-to-i5-in-a-laptop/7564/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/replacing-i3-to-i5-in-a-laptop/7564/5</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jul 2011 19:37:55 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7564-5</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/replacing-i3-to-i5-in-a-laptop/7564.rss">Replacing i3 to i5 in a laptop</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Replacing i3 to i5 in a laptop</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[FinlandGamer]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I know that <a href="https://forum.notebookreview.com/acer/547838-acer-aspire-7741g-soldered-cpu.html" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">someone</a> has replaced his i3-370m whit an i7-720QM , but his laptop has an 1156 LGA socket.</p>
<p>And i’ll take a look on those CPU’s, mental2k.</p>
<p>EDIT: i5-580M has a higher clocking rate (2.66GHz vs 2.6GHz), but i5-2540M has better system bus, and higher max memory bandwitch.<br>
<a href="https://ark.intel.com/compare/50072,49652" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Source</a><br>
I think going for i5-580M, but i’m still not sure, will it fit into 989 rPGA socket.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/replacing-i3-to-i5-in-a-laptop/7564/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/replacing-i3-to-i5-in-a-laptop/7564/4</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jul 2011 16:59:46 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7564-4</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/replacing-i3-to-i5-in-a-laptop/7564.rss">Replacing i3 to i5 in a laptop</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Replacing i3 to i5 in a laptop</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[mental2k]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Right the 989 rPGA is one form of the Intel Socket G.  From what I can glean it would appear some of these sockets are compatible with intel SocketG 988A/B chips.  The main problem you’re having at the minute is LGA1155 is a socket H2 which is for desktop processors. So maybe looking for mobile processors would be a start.</p>
<p>Have you considered the potential for increased heating inside the laptop? Can your current cooling system cope?  Thirdly will your motherboard drivers be happy with the upgrade?  Does the FSB match on any of these chips?</p>
<p>It’s possibly doable, but laptops are not as easy as desktops to upgrade.  Search and see if anyone else has done it with your laptop.  I have heard stories of others doing it with other laptops, but thats no guarantee, laptop hardware is more bespoke than desktop.</p>
<p>ninja’d</p>
<p>There are a range of Arrandale mobile i5s that use Socket G1<br>
Core i5-580M is the fastest of them.</p>
<p>There’s also Sandy Bridge they use Socket G2<br>
Core i5-2540M is the fastest of them.</p>
<p>Russilker is of course correct they’re dual core.</p>
<p>If you wanna know how they perform then get the model number of your processor and go on a benchmark site and see how they performs</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/replacing-i3-to-i5-in-a-laptop/7564/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/replacing-i3-to-i5-in-a-laptop/7564/3</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jul 2011 16:29:52 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7564-3</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/replacing-i3-to-i5-in-a-laptop/7564.rss">Replacing i3 to i5 in a laptop</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Replacing i3 to i5 in a laptop</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[russilker]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>As far as I know there are no quad core i5 processors that fit the G1 socket. An i7 720qm or 740qm should fit the bill quite nicely, just keep in mind that it has a higher TDP than the i5 processor you have so temperatures will be elevated… plus there’s the issue of BIOS compatibility, and are two additional lower-clocked cores really something you need? Games that aren’t multithreaded will drop in performance due to the lower clock speed, and most likely any modern game that is multithreaded will just be bottlenecked by your GPU, so unless you run some highly CPU dependent multithreaded applications I wouldn’t recommend upgrading to an i7.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/replacing-i3-to-i5-in-a-laptop/7564/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/replacing-i3-to-i5-in-a-laptop/7564/2</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jul 2011 16:13:15 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7564-2</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/replacing-i3-to-i5-in-a-laptop/7564.rss">Replacing i3 to i5 in a laptop</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Replacing i3 to i5 in a laptop</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[FinlandGamer]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I’m using an Acer Aspire 7741g, and i was wondering, can i replace my i3 Dual-core whit an i5 Quad-core. CPU-Z tells me that my motherboard has an 989 rPGA socket, but i haven’t found an i5 whit that socket. All i5 i have found, were whit LGA1155 sockets. Can i plug i5 into my laptop, or should i just save an extra 150€ and buy i7? (And can i use that also?)</p>
<p>Current system:<br>
Win 7 Home Premium 64-bit<br>
i3-370M 2.4 GHz<br>
ATI Mobility Radeon HD 5470<br>
4 GB Ram</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/replacing-i3-to-i5-in-a-laptop/7564/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/replacing-i3-to-i5-in-a-laptop/7564/1</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jul 2011 15:54:04 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7564-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/replacing-i3-to-i5-in-a-laptop/7564.rss">Replacing i3 to i5 in a laptop</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
