<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Game Icons not appearing</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/game-icons-not-appearing/5360</link>
    <description>the following games have somehow replaced their shortcut icons with that funny image of a piece of paper with a folded corner that you sometimes see:
blue shift,
opposing force,
half-life 2, lost coast &amp; episode one,
portal,
nightmare house 2 
source sdk base 

I&#39;ve had this issue for a while, and mostly ignored it, but when nightmare house appeared with no Icon I became a little concerned, so does anyone know how to fix this?

help is appreciated.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 13 Sep 2010 05:41:42 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Help and Support</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/game-icons-not-appearing/5360.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Game Icons not appearing</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[kewl]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Glad I wasnt the only person having this, i was afraid i might have a virseszeus</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/game-icons-not-appearing/5360/22">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/game-icons-not-appearing/5360/22</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 13 Sep 2010 05:41:42 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-5360-22</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/game-icons-not-appearing/5360.rss">Game Icons not appearing</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Game Icons not appearing</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[megavolt]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Had the same problem after moving my steam program files and game data to my D drive (so I could share with win 7 and vista)</p>
<p>The existing icons can be brought back to life by simply copying the folder<br>
D:\Program Files\Steam\steam\games<br>
to<br>
C:\Program Files\Steam\steam\games</p>
<p>On my XP installation that was the folder that the icons by default were pointing to.<br>
after I copied the steam files to D: it was the only thing that did not get sorted apart from the steam icon that needed the drive letter changing too.</p>
<p>(BTW: It won’t be taking up loads of space as it only contains game icons for steam)</p>
<p>Hope that helps someone, as I was not fancying manually re-doing all my games icons  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=9" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/game-icons-not-appearing/5360/21">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/game-icons-not-appearing/5360/21</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 12 Sep 2010 21:16:30 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-5360-21</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/game-icons-not-appearing/5360.rss">Game Icons not appearing</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Game Icons not appearing</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Sampdel]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Yeah my Steam games have been doing this for a while also</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/game-icons-not-appearing/5360/20">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/game-icons-not-appearing/5360/20</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 04 Sep 2010 21:40:21 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-5360-20</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/game-icons-not-appearing/5360.rss">Game Icons not appearing</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Game Icons not appearing</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[sersoft]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>yes I can navigate to all of my XP machines but the files I want to access are on my main PC (windows 7)</p>
<p>btw it also works if I enter the IP “\192.168.2.12\SharedDocs”</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/game-icons-not-appearing/5360/19">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/game-icons-not-appearing/5360/19</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 04 Sep 2010 18:27:48 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-5360-19</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/game-icons-not-appearing/5360.rss">Game Icons not appearing</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Game Icons not appearing</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[BaTz281]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="sersoft">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/user_avatar/leakfree.org/sersoft/40/5837_2.png" class="avatar"> sersoft:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>yeah I meant file types, in XP you used to be able to manage every file type and the various ways to open them, or change the icon, try to find that in windows 7</p>
<p>Also HomeGroup pisses me off on an entirely different level, I used to enter MSHOME and copy files to SharedDocs to access on any PC, now I have to use VNC file transfers. I mean it’s the same issue with the term steamID, the original meaning is a string of numbers that can ID your account on any server, the new meaning is your steam community profile page. The original meaning of homegroup is the name of the folder where your PC shares files on the network, new meaning is the name of the windows 7 file sharing system that I still haven’t managed to get working on my PC.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>As I mentioned, the Default Programs panel (Control Panel --&gt; Programs --&gt; Default Programs) allows you to edit what file extension opens with which program, which in turn determines the file icon (I never mess with default icons for program types i.e. mpegs, so I can’t direct you on that).</p>
<p>As for the Homegroup sharing issue, the way I share between XP and Windows 7 is just creating a folder and sharing it to Everyone.  I mean, if you’re familiar with UNC terminology, you can still navigate to your XP machine from Win7 by sticking \DesiredXPName\SharedDocs in Explorer’s address bar, or go a step further with \DesiredXPName\c$ or d$, etc.  You shouldn’t need VNC at all for any machine on your LAN - let me know what your situation is if you’re having problems with that.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/game-icons-not-appearing/5360/18">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/game-icons-not-appearing/5360/18</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 04 Sep 2010 16:00:09 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-5360-18</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/game-icons-not-appearing/5360.rss">Game Icons not appearing</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Game Icons not appearing</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[sersoft]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>yeah I meant file types, in XP you used to be able to manage every file type and the various ways to open them, or change the icon, try to find that in windows 7</p>
<p>Also HomeGroup pisses me off on an entirely different level, I used to enter MSHOME and copy files to SharedDocs to access on any PC, now I have to use VNC file transfers. I mean it’s the same issue with the term steamID, the original meaning is a string of numbers that can ID your account on any server, the new meaning is your steam community profile page. The original meaning of homegroup is the name of the folder where your PC shares files on the network, new meaning is the name of the windows 7 file sharing system that I still haven’t managed to get working on my PC.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/game-icons-not-appearing/5360/17">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/game-icons-not-appearing/5360/17</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 Sep 2010 23:33:35 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-5360-17</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/game-icons-not-appearing/5360.rss">Game Icons not appearing</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Game Icons not appearing</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[BaTz281]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="sersoft">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/user_avatar/leakfree.org/sersoft/40/5837_2.png" class="avatar"> sersoft:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I hate the library feature because they are forcing people to use it, you can’t open my documents anymore nooo it’s called libraries now…</p>
<p>I also hate how they totally fucked up the search feature, in XP it can search using any part of the filename but in 7 you must start the keyword with the beginning of the filename otherwise you won’t find shit.</p>
<p>Also in XP they had a perfectly good system for checking your file extensions in the control panel, now you must resort to registry hax and such/rant</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I couldn’t agree more with the search feature.  I like Windows7 on the whole, but MAN did they screw some stuff up.  Namely, homegroups are a joke, search is terrible, the audio engine / surround sound support in games is awful…</p>
<p>I hate desktop search clients but I may actually resort to one so I can functionally search my computer.</p>
<p>Which system for checking file extensions?  You mean the File Types tab, where you can associate a file type with a program?  If so, that’s still around - it’s called Default Programs (which, to me, seems different than XP’s Default Programs).  If not, I’m not sure what you mean  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/smiley.png?v=9" title=":smiley:" class="emoji" alt=":smiley:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/game-icons-not-appearing/5360/16">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/game-icons-not-appearing/5360/16</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 Sep 2010 21:21:56 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-5360-16</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/game-icons-not-appearing/5360.rss">Game Icons not appearing</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Game Icons not appearing</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[E-Nelson]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="BaTz281">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/user_avatar/leakfree.org/batz281/40/4503_2.png" class="avatar"> BaTz281:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>What program did you download to fix the icons?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Stardoc Icon Packager ftw.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="BaTz281">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/user_avatar/leakfree.org/batz281/40/4503_2.png" class="avatar"> BaTz281:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Not sure what “Owner” you’re referring to in your hard drive list.  Is your profile called Owner?  I know some Win7 installations default to Owner (and if that’s the list of C:\Users on your system, then this applies to you).  Thus, YOU are Owner.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>double click on my computer, and then in the left pane collapse <span class="bbcode-u">everything</span>.  The list you see is NOT correctly representing the layout of your computer.  You will see desktop, libraries, homegroup, owner, my computer, network, recycle bin… etc. (see pic below).  MY main issue is that ALL OF THAT IS TECHNICALLY UNDER <span class="bbcode-i">MY COMPUTER</span> somewhere. (c drive? F drive? who knows cuz it isnt showing!) Yet in this sweatheart of a list, it is listed outside of the <span class="bbcode-i">My Computer</span> directory.  Most folks dont have a problem with this. I <span class="bbcode-b">do</span>.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="BaTz281">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/user_avatar/leakfree.org/batz281/40/4503_2.png" class="avatar"> BaTz281:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>You CAN NOT!!! delete the other folders.  Well, I take that back - you can do whatever you want to them, but it can pretty much hose your system.  Windows uses Public and Default User to store information for certain programs, as well as storing shortcuts and certain files there - varies system to system.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Yep. For some secret reason, Mr. Gates insists on mucking up the directory listing with more crap rules making it that much difficult for me to spot check superfluous files that are safe to clean out.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="BaTz281">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/user_avatar/leakfree.org/batz281/40/4503_2.png" class="avatar"> BaTz281:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>As for libraries, it’s a new feature in Windows 7 that allows you to easily categorize folders all over your system into 1 virtual location.  Example - I have a Windows Home Server where I store ripped DVDs and TV shows.  I have a personal folder on my D drive where I store smaller personal videos, from concerts and the like.  And I have a temporary downloads folder on C: where I keep randomly downloaded stuff that I may just watch once and delete, or move permanently to one of the other 2 locations.</p>
<p>Now, back to libraries - I have added all 3 of those locations (Server, C: and D) to my Videos library (click on the Add Location link in the library).  Now I can just open that library link and have immediate access to all 3 locations, without having to browse specifically to them.  Give it a try, I just started using them 3 weeks ago and I love the feature.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Hm. I am not convinced I like the idea. But I will poke at it with a stick a bit to see if I can get it to the point where I am more agreeable to it.<br>
<img src="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/original/1X/6157896f983cac2d6b04b3d2751a12c68b041bb0.jpeg" alt="Clipboard01.jpg" data-base62-sha1="dT7RpyYCLQ0lWaqpaqmWWwxbYPK" width="194" height="337"></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/game-icons-not-appearing/5360/15">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/game-icons-not-appearing/5360/15</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 Sep 2010 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-5360-15</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/game-icons-not-appearing/5360.rss">Game Icons not appearing</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Game Icons not appearing</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[sersoft]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I hate the library feature because they are forcing people to use it, you can’t open my documents anymore nooo it’s called libraries now…</p>
<p>I also hate how they totally fucked up the search feature, in XP it can search using any part of the filename but in 7 you must start the keyword with the beginning of the filename otherwise you won’t find shit.</p>
<p>Also in XP they had a perfectly good system for checking your file extensions in the control panel, now you must resort to registry hax and such/rant</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/game-icons-not-appearing/5360/14">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/game-icons-not-appearing/5360/14</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 Sep 2010 19:48:20 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-5360-14</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/game-icons-not-appearing/5360.rss">Game Icons not appearing</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Game Icons not appearing</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[BaTz281]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="E-Nelson">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/e/34f0e0/40.png" class="avatar"> E-Nelson:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I had the icon issue too and had to download a program to force it to fix some of the icons. And it wasnt just icons on my desktop that got screwy, it was icons in my start / programs area that got goofy.  I like windows 7 and all, but there are a couple things wonky with it, the icon mystery being only one of them.</p>
<p>Like what exactly is the purpose and reasoning of separating files all over the place?  Such as <span class="bbcode-b">E:\Steam</span> vs <span class="bbcode-b">C:\ProgramData\Steam(game)\userdata</span>? wth? Why is it so hard to want to have everything to do with abc game in one directory area?</p>
<p>Or how about programs that I install under C:\Program Files (x86) sometimes show up in my start/programs list and other times they dont? Now I have to search to find my skype exe. why?</p>
<p>And why and what exactly is “Owner” showing up outside of the hard drive list and how does it relate to the <span class="bbcode-b">real </span>areas of the computer? You know, like the C:\Users area?  (example… there are installed programs under “owner” that arent installed under the c or e drive?)  That said, what exactly is the “Libraries” for and can I get rid of this seeing how my working drive is E and not C?</p>
<p>OH and I know that 99% of the population require many users on the same computer each with their own stupid settings (/sarcasm) but I prefer to keep it all clean and have only ONE profile on the computer.  And surprize surprize, I would like that one profile person to own / have access / have permission to EVERYTHING on the computer.  (dern locked icons keep showing up everywhere!) So how safe is it to make only ONE user and get rid of:<br>
C:\Users\all users,<br>
C:\Users\default,<br>
C:\Users\default user,<br>
C:\Users\owner,<br>
C:\Users\public.</p>
<p>Yeah. I got issues with windows 7.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>What program did you download to fix the icons?</p>
<p>Not sure what “Owner” you’re referring to in your hard drive list.  Is your profile called Owner?  I know some Win7 installations default to Owner (and if that’s the list of C:\Users on your system, then this applies to you).  Thus, YOU are Owner.</p>
<p>You CAN NOT!!! delete the other folders.  Well, I take that back - you can do whatever you want to them, but it can pretty much hose your system.  Windows uses Public and Default User to store information for certain programs, as well as storing shortcuts and certain files there - varies system to system.</p>
<p>As for libraries, it’s a new feature in Windows 7 that allows you to easily categorize folders all over your system into 1 virtual location.  Example - I have a Windows Home Server where I store ripped DVDs and TV shows.  I have a personal folder on my D drive where I store smaller personal videos, from concerts and the like.  And I have a temporary downloads folder on C: where I keep randomly downloaded stuff that I may just watch once and delete, or move permanently to one of the other 2 locations.</p>
<p>Now, back to libraries - I have added all 3 of those locations (Server, C: and D) to my Videos library (click on the Add Location link in the library).  Now I can just open that library link and have immediate access to all 3 locations, without having to browse specifically to them.  Give it a try, I just started using them 3 weeks ago and I love the feature.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/game-icons-not-appearing/5360/13">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/game-icons-not-appearing/5360/13</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 Sep 2010 18:22:35 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-5360-13</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/game-icons-not-appearing/5360.rss">Game Icons not appearing</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Game Icons not appearing</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[E-Nelson]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I had the icon issue too and had to download a program to force it to fix some of the icons. And it wasnt just icons on my desktop that got screwy, it was icons in my start / programs area that got goofy.  I like windows 7 and all, but there are a couple things wonky with it, the icon mystery being only one of them.</p>
<p>Like what exactly is the purpose and reasoning of separating files all over the place?  Such as <span class="bbcode-b">E:\Steam</span> vs <span class="bbcode-b">C:\ProgramData\Steam(game)\userdata</span>? wth? Why is it so hard to want to have everything to do with abc game in one directory area?</p>
<p>Or how about programs that I install under C:\Program Files (x86) sometimes show up in my start/programs list and other times they dont? Now I have to search to find my skype exe. why?</p>
<p>And why and what exactly is “Owner” showing up outside of the hard drive list and how does it relate to the <span class="bbcode-b">real </span>areas of the computer? You know, like the C:\Users area?  (example… there are installed programs under “owner” that arent installed under the c or e drive?)  That said, what exactly is the “Libraries” for and can I get rid of this seeing how my working drive is E and not C?</p>
<p>OH and I know that 99% of the population require many users on the same computer each with their own stupid settings (/sarcasm) but I prefer to keep it all clean and have only ONE profile on the computer.  And surprize surprize, I would like that one profile person to own / have access / have permission to EVERYTHING on the computer.  (dern locked icons keep showing up everywhere!) So how safe is it to make only ONE user and get rid of:<br>
C:\Users\all users,<br>
C:\Users\default,<br>
C:\Users\default user,<br>
C:\Users\owner,<br>
C:\Users\public.</p>
<p>Yeah. I got issues with windows 7.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/game-icons-not-appearing/5360/12">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/game-icons-not-appearing/5360/12</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 Sep 2010 16:39:48 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-5360-12</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/game-icons-not-appearing/5360.rss">Game Icons not appearing</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Game Icons not appearing</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[jerry]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>i had that issue too. it just sorted out over time.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/game-icons-not-appearing/5360/11">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/game-icons-not-appearing/5360/11</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 Sep 2010 15:22:03 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-5360-11</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/game-icons-not-appearing/5360.rss">Game Icons not appearing</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Game Icons not appearing</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[johnyo]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Check file format associations and reapply maybe?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/game-icons-not-appearing/5360/10">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/game-icons-not-appearing/5360/10</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 Sep 2010 14:49:32 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-5360-10</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/game-icons-not-appearing/5360.rss">Game Icons not appearing</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Game Icons not appearing</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[BaTz281]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Slightly related to this issue (since it involves the icon cache, which I’ve researched for my problem) - has anyone ever experienced the “Windows 7 Office 2007 icons missing” issue?  The Office program executables all have the correct icons, but any related files to be opened (.doc, .xls, etc.) have the above noted, folded-corner-with-dos-window looking default icons.</p>
<p>If this seems like a hijack, let me know and I shall apologize and back away from the thread  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/smiley.png?v=9" title=":smiley:" class="emoji" alt=":smiley:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/game-icons-not-appearing/5360/9">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/game-icons-not-appearing/5360/9</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 Sep 2010 14:43:41 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-5360-9</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/game-icons-not-appearing/5360.rss">Game Icons not appearing</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Game Icons not appearing</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[FireTime]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Usually that has to do with windows and the icon cache. Rebuilding that will usually work unless the programs icon was removed or unregistered for some reason.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/game-icons-not-appearing/5360/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/game-icons-not-appearing/5360/8</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 Sep 2010 14:05:27 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-5360-8</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/game-icons-not-appearing/5360.rss">Game Icons not appearing</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Game Icons not appearing</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[E-Nelson]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>yeah, I dont know why either, but when I create a steam shortcut on the desktop, I always have to change the icon from the system default to the real icon.  rather silly if you ask me.  I think it is cuz steam is not installed on the c drive?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/game-icons-not-appearing/5360/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/game-icons-not-appearing/5360/7</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 Sep 2010 13:41:56 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-5360-7</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/game-icons-not-appearing/5360.rss">Game Icons not appearing</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Game Icons not appearing</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[blackout]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>will give it a try. thanks.</p>
<p>Edit: yep it works, much appreciated.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/game-icons-not-appearing/5360/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/game-icons-not-appearing/5360/6</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 Sep 2010 13:27:55 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-5360-6</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/game-icons-not-appearing/5360.rss">Game Icons not appearing</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Game Icons not appearing</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[johnyo]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <ol>
<li>click “properties”</li>
<li>“change icon”</li>
<li>select the icon you want</li>
<li>???</li>
<li>Profit!</li>
</ol>
<p>[EDIT] Aw, shit, I don’t know if it works with steam shortcuts, they’re different.<br>
[ANOTHER EDIT] Just checked, it does work. Protip: the icons are usually in the “resource” folder.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/game-icons-not-appearing/5360/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/game-icons-not-appearing/5360/5</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 Sep 2010 12:41:55 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-5360-5</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/game-icons-not-appearing/5360.rss">Game Icons not appearing</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Game Icons not appearing</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[JeffMOD]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>But not ripped? Hmm… Either it’s missing from your installation of the game files, or Steam has to load it from the internet.<br>
Maybe you should file a bug report with a printscreen of the error with Valve.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/game-icons-not-appearing/5360/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/game-icons-not-appearing/5360/4</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 Sep 2010 12:06:03 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-5360-4</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/game-icons-not-appearing/5360.rss">Game Icons not appearing</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Game Icons not appearing</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[blackout]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>it’s folded in the top right-hand corner.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/game-icons-not-appearing/5360/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/game-icons-not-appearing/5360/3</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 Sep 2010 11:56:30 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-5360-3</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/game-icons-not-appearing/5360.rss">Game Icons not appearing</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Game Icons not appearing</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[JeffMOD]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Missing/Unloaded image?<br>
Is the piece of paper ripped, or full?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/game-icons-not-appearing/5360/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/game-icons-not-appearing/5360/2</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 Sep 2010 11:38:32 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-5360-2</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/game-icons-not-appearing/5360.rss">Game Icons not appearing</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Game Icons not appearing</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[blackout]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>the following games have somehow replaced their shortcut icons with that funny image of a piece of paper with a folded corner that you sometimes see:<br>
blue shift,<br>
opposing force,<br>
half-life 2, lost coast &amp; episode one,<br>
portal,<br>
nightmare house 2<br>
source sdk base</p>
<p>I’ve had this issue for a while, and mostly ignored it, but when nightmare house appeared with no Icon I became a little concerned, so does anyone know how to fix this?</p>
<p>help is appreciated.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/game-icons-not-appearing/5360/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/game-icons-not-appearing/5360/1</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 Sep 2010 06:53:49 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-5360-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/game-icons-not-appearing/5360.rss">Game Icons not appearing</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
