<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Slow Motion in BM and other Source Games</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/slow-motion-in-bm-and-other-source-games/11945</link>
    <description>Hey, I&#39;ve got an issue, and I don&#39;t know where it came from.

I hadn&#39;t played BM in about a month, but yesterday, I saw that the &quot;Uplink Remake&quot; was finished, so I installed it.  But when I installed it, weird stuff happened.  Almost everything was 2x slower.  The opening titles: &quot;Gordon Freeman, Ph.D. ... Assignment..., etc.&quot; lasted way longer than I thought they should, and the when game itself started, I was moving like slow motion.  However, I could pivot at full speed, and the scientists who were talking talked and acted at full speed, just moved slowly.  FPS is smooth as ever, just everything happens slowly.

I checked, and this also happens in HL2, so I suspect it&#39;s not a BM-specific problem, but I&#39;m curious if anyone has experienced this before.

I&#39;ve tried uninstalling Uplink, deleting the .cfg files for both BM and HL2, removing the BM install, and uninstalling-reinstalling HL2.  Nothing has made a difference.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 06 Jan 2013 22:55:06 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Help!</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/slow-motion-in-bm-and-other-source-games/11945.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Slow Motion in BM and other Source Games</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Kenley]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Got it figured out.  All I had to do was update my drivers!</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/slow-motion-in-bm-and-other-source-games/11945/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/slow-motion-in-bm-and-other-source-games/11945/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 06 Jan 2013 22:55:06 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11945-2</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/slow-motion-in-bm-and-other-source-games/11945.rss">Slow Motion in BM and other Source Games</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Slow Motion in BM and other Source Games</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Kenley]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Hey, I’ve got an issue, and I don’t know where it came from.</p>
<p>I hadn’t played BM in about a month, but yesterday, I saw that the “Uplink Remake” was finished, so I installed it.  But when I installed it, weird stuff happened.  Almost everything was 2x slower.  The opening titles: “Gordon Freeman, Ph.D. … Assignment…, etc.” lasted way longer than I thought they should, and the when game itself started, I was moving like slow motion.  However, I could pivot at full speed, and the scientists who were talking talked and acted at full speed, just moved slowly.  FPS is smooth as ever, just everything happens slowly.</p>
<p>I checked, and this also happens in HL2, so I suspect it’s not a BM-specific problem, but I’m curious if anyone has experienced this before.</p>
<p>I’ve tried uninstalling Uplink, deleting the .cfg files for both BM and HL2, removing the BM install, and uninstalling-reinstalling HL2.  Nothing has made a difference.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/slow-motion-in-bm-and-other-source-games/11945/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/slow-motion-in-bm-and-other-source-games/11945/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 05 Jan 2013 17:08:23 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11945-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/slow-motion-in-bm-and-other-source-games/11945.rss">Slow Motion in BM and other Source Games</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
