<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>TF2 Mann-Conomy Update: Thoughts, Recipes, and New Items</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/tf2-mann-conomy-update-thoughts-recipes-and-new-items/5609</link>
    <description>So Valve has finally released the long-awaited Polycount Pack update, along with a number of other updates, in one giant bundle called the Mann-Conomy Update. If you haven&#39;t read up on it, check out the links below:

[url=&#39;https://www.teamfortress.com/mannconomy/&#39;]Main Update Page[/url]

[url=&#39;https://www.teamfortress.com/mannconomy/item_sets/&#39;]New Polycount Item Sets[/url]

[url=&#39;https://www.teamfortress.com/mannconomy/FAQ/&#39;]FAQ[/url]

[url=&#39;https://www.pcgamer.com/2010/09/30/team-fortress-2-now-selling-items-for-real-money-massive-update-just-launched/&#39;]PC Gamer article[/url]

So, TF2 players, what are your thoughts on this update? Sounds like the initial reception is split about 50/50 between horrible and awesome. 

Personally, I have no problem letting players who want new items, but don&#39;t have time to play for hours to find or craft them, be able to purchase them. It comes at the cost of being able to trade or craft them, but then such a player probably wouldn&#39;t want to do that anyway. It&#39;s doesn&#39;t break the game, since you can still find the items with gameplay attributes, or craft them from just 2 existing items. And Valve has already provided tremendous FREE support for a 3-year old game and continues to do so, so I can&#39;t understand why so many people are all &quot;omg Valve is teh suck and they&#39;ve lost my respect&quot;. That&#39;s just disgustingly ungrateful, and shows a bratty entitled attitude. They owe us nothing. Besides, if you can&#39;t respect Valve just because they allowed completely optional microtransactions in 1 game, who the hell can you respect? Also, item trading is a huge plus, but most of the new items seem a little underwhelming at first glance. 

That&#39;s my 2 cents, what do you think of it? Also, if you discover any recipes for new items or find out anything about any of the new Valve items/hats/mystery boxes, go ahead and post it here too.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 15 Oct 2010 18:13:31 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Technology and Gaming</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/tf2-mann-conomy-update-thoughts-recipes-and-new-items/5609.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>TF2 Mann-Conomy Update: Thoughts, Recipes, and New Items</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Katana]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Bluemen230">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Bluemen230:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>What does the Holy Mackerel even do?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>As far as I know, it does the same damage as the bat, but it shows in the kill box how many times someone has been hit by it, and somehow “alerts” everyone to a fish-kill.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/tf2-mann-conomy-update-thoughts-recipes-and-new-items/5609/137">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/tf2-mann-conomy-update-thoughts-recipes-and-new-items/5609/137</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Oct 2010 18:13:31 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-5609-137</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/tf2-mann-conomy-update-thoughts-recipes-and-new-items/5609.rss">TF2 Mann-Conomy Update: Thoughts, Recipes, and New Items</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>TF2 Mann-Conomy Update: Thoughts, Recipes, and New Items</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Someonerandm]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="AllYourCakeAreBelongToUs">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 AllYourCakeAreBelongToUs:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I’m tired of seeing ONLY Shortstops all the time… though I DO love the Holy Mackerel.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I haven’t seen that many. I guess I’m just lucky.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/tf2-mann-conomy-update-thoughts-recipes-and-new-items/5609/136">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/tf2-mann-conomy-update-thoughts-recipes-and-new-items/5609/136</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Oct 2010 18:05:45 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-5609-136</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/tf2-mann-conomy-update-thoughts-recipes-and-new-items/5609.rss">TF2 Mann-Conomy Update: Thoughts, Recipes, and New Items</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>TF2 Mann-Conomy Update: Thoughts, Recipes, and New Items</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Acristoff]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Be a fish.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/tf2-mann-conomy-update-thoughts-recipes-and-new-items/5609/135">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/tf2-mann-conomy-update-thoughts-recipes-and-new-items/5609/135</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Oct 2010 04:33:27 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-5609-135</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/tf2-mann-conomy-update-thoughts-recipes-and-new-items/5609.rss">TF2 Mann-Conomy Update: Thoughts, Recipes, and New Items</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>TF2 Mann-Conomy Update: Thoughts, Recipes, and New Items</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[DeleteThis]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>What does the Holy Mackerel even do?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/tf2-mann-conomy-update-thoughts-recipes-and-new-items/5609/134">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/tf2-mann-conomy-update-thoughts-recipes-and-new-items/5609/134</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Oct 2010 02:02:24 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-5609-134</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/tf2-mann-conomy-update-thoughts-recipes-and-new-items/5609.rss">TF2 Mann-Conomy Update: Thoughts, Recipes, and New Items</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>TF2 Mann-Conomy Update: Thoughts, Recipes, and New Items</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[AllYourCakeAreBelong]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I honestly didn’t like the Mann-Conomy update that much. Some weapons are overpowered (Shortstop anyone?) and I don’t like the idea of sets giving you bonuses. WHY SHOULD HAVING A SET MAKE YOU IMMUNE TO HEADSHOTS?! I’m tired of seeing ONLY Shortstops all the time… though I DO love the Holy Mackerel.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/tf2-mann-conomy-update-thoughts-recipes-and-new-items/5609/133">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/tf2-mann-conomy-update-thoughts-recipes-and-new-items/5609/133</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Oct 2010 00:48:57 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-5609-133</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/tf2-mann-conomy-update-thoughts-recipes-and-new-items/5609.rss">TF2 Mann-Conomy Update: Thoughts, Recipes, and New Items</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>TF2 Mann-Conomy Update: Thoughts, Recipes, and New Items</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[RabidMonkey]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Orpheon">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/o/6bbea6/40.png" class="avatar"> Orpheon:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Has anyone else’s hat drop rate skyrocketed since around the time of the update? At the very least, that’s 4 hats in about a month, or about 50 hours of gameplay, when in my previous 600 or so hours, over a year or so, I’ve only found a total of 2.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Pure luck, I don’t believe the drop rate has been adjusted since the update.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/tf2-mann-conomy-update-thoughts-recipes-and-new-items/5609/132">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/tf2-mann-conomy-update-thoughts-recipes-and-new-items/5609/132</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 14 Oct 2010 23:51:44 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-5609-132</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/tf2-mann-conomy-update-thoughts-recipes-and-new-items/5609.rss">TF2 Mann-Conomy Update: Thoughts, Recipes, and New Items</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>TF2 Mann-Conomy Update: Thoughts, Recipes, and New Items</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Surplus]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Katana">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/k/db5fbb/40.png" class="avatar"> Katana:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>A. You are admitting that TF2 is slowly beginning to die out, having “reached its saturation point”. Please keep in mind games like World of Warcraft have gone on since 2004 with no signs of slowing down, so this would be pretty disappointing.</p>
<p>B. There are two people just in this topic, common players, who are frustrated. I don’t know if you realize, but the vast majority of TF2 players don’t talk about it much on weekends, play enough to get 1 hat every 4 months, don’t read the blog, and are only somewhat good. These people, I think, have <span class="bbcode-i">always</span> been somewhat frustrated by the changes to the game they can’t get used to, but never bothered taking the time to voice themselves and just went to other games. One example is Yahtzee; he said the game was pretty awesome on release, but only commented on it later because people begged him to play. He pretty much had the concerns a year ago that we have now; it’s just way too complex.</p>
<p>You really have to be able to look at this game from the point of view of someone who plays on-and-off, usually just other games; and even then only when their work or social life or other activities aren’t in the way. That sort of person could entirely miss two massive weapon updates between play sessions.</p>
<p>PS. I only posted this because I just lost massively against a team of demomen that weren’t even using polycount weapons. durr</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>As far as public play is concerned TF2 has had a pretty long lifespan for a FPS.  The issue is, that if Valve wants to keep players playing for extended periods of time they need fresh content.  Both in new maps to learn and explore and tactics and weapons.  New maps and game modes will rarely frustrate players but it won’t keep players playing as long.  I think its come to Valve which do we support the hardcore tf2 players or the causal?  TF2’s updates have always been an experiment and with the item cap and certain other things Valve is playing with the idea of a long lasting fps for both audiences.  I don’t think TF2 at its core was built for this long of on going development and this is where some of the over saturation draws from.  The game just isn’t built to be added to so heavily while remaining intuitive.  It had a fairly tough skill curve for casuals to begin with anyways.</p>
<p>Valve is always experimenting with their on going development if you don’t pay attention you might just miss it but Valve is making efforts to make it easier for casuals to keep up with the hardcore.</p>
<ol>
<li>Blog integration into TF2 and L4D<br>
2  L4D’s dynamic training system based on what the player has proven they know<br>
3 TF2’s item cap someone helps casuals stay competitive<br>
4  DoTA 2 has plans for a couching system<br>
5  TF2 finally got a training and offline practice not to long ago</li>
</ol>
<p>Though all these may not be in TF2 I am more than certain they will find their way into TF3.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/tf2-mann-conomy-update-thoughts-recipes-and-new-items/5609/131">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/tf2-mann-conomy-update-thoughts-recipes-and-new-items/5609/131</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 14 Oct 2010 23:18:06 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-5609-131</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/tf2-mann-conomy-update-thoughts-recipes-and-new-items/5609.rss">TF2 Mann-Conomy Update: Thoughts, Recipes, and New Items</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>TF2 Mann-Conomy Update: Thoughts, Recipes, and New Items</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Katana]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Orpheon">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/o/6bbea6/40.png" class="avatar"> Orpheon:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I suppose it’s true that there’s a steeper learning curve for new players, however the game <span class="bbcode-i">has</span> been out for 3 years now. When they released this update they joked about being told to start “making some f$%<span class="hashtag">#ing</span> money already”, and I think there might be at least a bit of truth to that. By now the game is likely reaching it’s saturation point, and without new players to buy the game, incentive to continue spending time and money updating and supporting it dwindles. So Valve needs to consider more what will appeal to its experienced, long time players, and then make money from that.</p>
<p>Personally, I have never felt that TF2 was too complicated, not even with this last update. I don’t feel that any (well, at least most) of the non-default weapons have ever changed the way I have to play so much that I can’t quickly adapt. Perhaps some players may feel that way, and if so that’s unfortunate. However, overall I have not seen a drop in player participation, on the contrary my favorite servers are more crowded than ever. And I have heard few if any people who I’ve played with recently complain about the complexity of the game or the abilities of the new weapons. (They’re still stuck on the same old “cuntsman - nade spam - spawn camp - FaN” complaints, as usual).</p>
<p>So I have to say that I am loving this update so far. TF2 is still my favorite and most-played game, and it’s only getting better as far as I’m concerned.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>A. You are admitting that TF2 is slowly beginning to die out, having “reached its saturation point”. Please keep in mind games like World of Warcraft have gone on since 2004 with no signs of slowing down, so this would be pretty disappointing.</p>
<p>B. There are two people just in this topic, common players, who are frustrated. I don’t know if you realize, but the vast majority of TF2 players don’t talk about it much on weekends, play enough to get 1 hat every 4 months, don’t read the blog, and are only somewhat good. These people, I think, have <span class="bbcode-i">always</span> been somewhat frustrated by the changes to the game they can’t get used to, but never bothered taking the time to voice themselves and just went to other games. One example is Yahtzee; he said the game was pretty awesome on release, but only commented on it later because people begged him to play. He pretty much had the concerns a year ago that we have now; it’s just way too complex.</p>
<p>You really have to be able to look at this game from the point of view of someone who plays on-and-off, usually just other games; and even then only when their work or social life or other activities aren’t in the way. That sort of person could entirely miss two massive weapon updates between play sessions.</p>
<p>PS. I only posted this because I just lost massively against a team of demomen that weren’t even using polycount weapons. durr</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/tf2-mann-conomy-update-thoughts-recipes-and-new-items/5609/130">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/tf2-mann-conomy-update-thoughts-recipes-and-new-items/5609/130</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 14 Oct 2010 21:39:30 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-5609-130</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/tf2-mann-conomy-update-thoughts-recipes-and-new-items/5609.rss">TF2 Mann-Conomy Update: Thoughts, Recipes, and New Items</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>TF2 Mann-Conomy Update: Thoughts, Recipes, and New Items</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Orpheon]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Has anyone else’s hat drop rate skyrocketed since around the time of the update? Just a little while prior to the update I found 2 hats in a few days. Then in the past week I’ve found another 3 (although there’s the possibility that one of those 3 was a craft that didn’t come through earlier on, still trying to find out about this). At the very least, that’s 4 hats in about a month, or about 50 hours of gameplay, when in my previous 600 or so hours, over a year or so, I’ve only found a total of 2. Not that I mind if I get more hats, but if they start dropping way more then they’re going to become a lot less valuable.</p>
<p>Also they need to make a way to smelt crates. If you don’t want to open them then it’s kind of a hassle trying to find people who will trade for them.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/tf2-mann-conomy-update-thoughts-recipes-and-new-items/5609/129">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/tf2-mann-conomy-update-thoughts-recipes-and-new-items/5609/129</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 14 Oct 2010 19:46:38 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-5609-129</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/tf2-mann-conomy-update-thoughts-recipes-and-new-items/5609.rss">TF2 Mann-Conomy Update: Thoughts, Recipes, and New Items</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>TF2 Mann-Conomy Update: Thoughts, Recipes, and New Items</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Chrillen]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Theevilpplz">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/t/cab0a1/40.png" class="avatar"> Theevilpplz:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Any reason why?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I don’t anymore, I thought it was a replacement for the pistol (and thus incredibly OP) but later realized that it’s actually a primary weapon.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/tf2-mann-conomy-update-thoughts-recipes-and-new-items/5609/128">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/tf2-mann-conomy-update-thoughts-recipes-and-new-items/5609/128</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 12 Oct 2010 14:40:17 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-5609-128</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/tf2-mann-conomy-update-thoughts-recipes-and-new-items/5609.rss">TF2 Mann-Conomy Update: Thoughts, Recipes, and New Items</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>TF2 Mann-Conomy Update: Thoughts, Recipes, and New Items</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Bravetriforcer]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>The packs overall</p>
<p>Scout:  Makes Scout a more Supportive class but with enough firepower to handle things himself.</p>
<p>Soldier: While it may seem like a Defensive set, this really makes him a fantastic Offensive/Supportive class.  The Black box makes him self-sufficient and Sentry resistance makes him great for pushes.  In fact, the Backup fills up so quickly that it seems much more useful and reliable than the Buff Banner.</p>
<p>Pyro: From what I can see, this outright perfects the Pyro and what he was meant to do.  The powerjack in itself is useful enough, but the overheal plus just kicks the fire axe to the curb (As if the axetinguisher didn’t already).  Degreaser makes using the Powerjack more efficient.  And the extra speed makes him good for actual flanking.  The extra bullet damage just balances out all the volatile awesome coming from Pyro now.</p>
<p>Spy:  It actually makes the Spy think like (le gasp) a spy and be sneaky.  Your Eternal Reward, while needed to be earned at first, is much more interesting to use, and is actually safer to use sentries with autodisguise.  The L’Etranger is nice, makes the C&amp;D fill up even faster.  Fez, while ridiculous looking, is worth it for quieter cloak.</p>
<p>Sniper: Danger Shield = Meh, I won’t complain.</p>
<pre><code>      Sydney Sleeper =  Good, but needs a little extra something to make it less "Noob/Newb Sniper" only.

       Bushwacka = Paradoxical in that the set benefit requires you to use the Danger Shield, which replaces Jarate.  Yes, you still have the Piss Gun, but close Range benefits don't work well when you only get them from a Long Range Rifle.
  
      'Ol Snaggletooth = Fuck yes.</code></pre>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/tf2-mann-conomy-update-thoughts-recipes-and-new-items/5609/127">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/tf2-mann-conomy-update-thoughts-recipes-and-new-items/5609/127</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 09 Oct 2010 00:56:04 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-5609-127</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/tf2-mann-conomy-update-thoughts-recipes-and-new-items/5609.rss">TF2 Mann-Conomy Update: Thoughts, Recipes, and New Items</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>TF2 Mann-Conomy Update: Thoughts, Recipes, and New Items</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Acristoff]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>It’s what the FaN should have been.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/tf2-mann-conomy-update-thoughts-recipes-and-new-items/5609/126">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/tf2-mann-conomy-update-thoughts-recipes-and-new-items/5609/126</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Oct 2010 22:49:56 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-5609-126</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/tf2-mann-conomy-update-thoughts-recipes-and-new-items/5609.rss">TF2 Mann-Conomy Update: Thoughts, Recipes, and New Items</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>TF2 Mann-Conomy Update: Thoughts, Recipes, and New Items</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Theevilpplz]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Any reason why?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/tf2-mann-conomy-update-thoughts-recipes-and-new-items/5609/125">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/tf2-mann-conomy-update-thoughts-recipes-and-new-items/5609/125</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Oct 2010 20:39:02 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-5609-125</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/tf2-mann-conomy-update-thoughts-recipes-and-new-items/5609.rss">TF2 Mann-Conomy Update: Thoughts, Recipes, and New Items</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>TF2 Mann-Conomy Update: Thoughts, Recipes, and New Items</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Chrillen]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I hate the shortstop</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/tf2-mann-conomy-update-thoughts-recipes-and-new-items/5609/124">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/tf2-mann-conomy-update-thoughts-recipes-and-new-items/5609/124</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Oct 2010 20:33:24 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-5609-124</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/tf2-mann-conomy-update-thoughts-recipes-and-new-items/5609.rss">TF2 Mann-Conomy Update: Thoughts, Recipes, and New Items</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>TF2 Mann-Conomy Update: Thoughts, Recipes, and New Items</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Orpheon]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Door">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/d/b4bc9f/40.png" class="avatar"> Door:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>The Polycount update was too much; five class updates in one is just too much for someone to keep up with.<br>
The hats are a nice bit of fun, and the original class updates were interesting to an extent, but the amount of weapons now is insane. It makes it far harder for a new player, or a player who hasn’t played for a while to get into it.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I suppose it’s true that there’s a steeper learning curve for new players, however the game <span class="bbcode-i">has</span> been out for 3 years now. When they released this update they joked about being told to start “making some f$%<span class="hashtag">#ing</span> money already”, and I think there might be at least a bit of truth to that. By now the game is likely reaching it’s saturation point, and without new players to buy the game, incentive to continue spending time and money updating and supporting it dwindles. So Valve needs to consider more what will appeal to its experienced, long time players, and then make money from that.</p>
<p>Personally, I have never felt that TF2 was too complicated, not even with this last update. I don’t feel that any (well, at least most) of the non-default weapons have ever changed the way I have to play so much that I can’t quickly adapt. Perhaps some players may feel that way, and if so that’s unfortunate. However, overall I have not seen a drop in player participation, on the contrary my favorite servers are more crowded than ever. And I have heard few if any people who I’ve played with recently complain about the complexity of the game or the abilities of the new weapons. (They’re still stuck on the same old “cuntsman - nade spam - spawn camp - FaN” complaints, as usual).</p>
<p>So I have to say that I am loving this update so far. TF2 is still my favorite and most-played game, and it’s only getting better as far as I’m concerned.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/tf2-mann-conomy-update-thoughts-recipes-and-new-items/5609/123">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/tf2-mann-conomy-update-thoughts-recipes-and-new-items/5609/123</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 06 Oct 2010 22:26:39 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-5609-123</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/tf2-mann-conomy-update-thoughts-recipes-and-new-items/5609.rss">TF2 Mann-Conomy Update: Thoughts, Recipes, and New Items</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>TF2 Mann-Conomy Update: Thoughts, Recipes, and New Items</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Door]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>The Polycount update was too much; five class updates in one is just too much for someone to keep up with.<br>
The hats are a nice bit of fun, and the original class updates were interesting to an extent, but the amount of weapons now is insane. It makes it far harder for a new player, or a player who hasn’t played for a while to get into it.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/tf2-mann-conomy-update-thoughts-recipes-and-new-items/5609/122">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/tf2-mann-conomy-update-thoughts-recipes-and-new-items/5609/122</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 06 Oct 2010 20:37:26 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-5609-122</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/tf2-mann-conomy-update-thoughts-recipes-and-new-items/5609.rss">TF2 Mann-Conomy Update: Thoughts, Recipes, and New Items</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>TF2 Mann-Conomy Update: Thoughts, Recipes, and New Items</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Acristoff]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Katana">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/k/db5fbb/40.png" class="avatar"> Katana:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I think I’d even be pissed if I had every single weapon. The game is just way too complicated now; there are essentially something like 50 classes based on what someone might potentially have.<br>
Meet the Scottish Warrior (who doesn’t explode things)<br>
Meet the Fire Scout<br>
Meet the Archer<br>
Meet the Slightly Different Archer (ie, Soldier with Direct Hit)<br>
Meet the Combat Engineer (gunslinger)<br>
Meet the Identity-Stealer (Spy, working completely differently)</p>
<p>I just feel like all these weapons change each class’s dynamic so much that it’s becoming difficult to keep track of, and respond to them all, at once. I think when the game started with 9 classes, it was a challenge to keep them balanced but they did it successfully. 17+ classes? No one can balance that.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Actually I think they’re doing a good job of it really, maybe I’m a dumb tasteless waste of space but I find it interesting and fun.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/tf2-mann-conomy-update-thoughts-recipes-and-new-items/5609/121">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/tf2-mann-conomy-update-thoughts-recipes-and-new-items/5609/121</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 06 Oct 2010 16:35:11 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-5609-121</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/tf2-mann-conomy-update-thoughts-recipes-and-new-items/5609.rss">TF2 Mann-Conomy Update: Thoughts, Recipes, and New Items</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>TF2 Mann-Conomy Update: Thoughts, Recipes, and New Items</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Katana]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I think I’d even be pissed if I had every single weapon. The game is just way too complicated now; there are essentially something like 50 classes based on what someone might potentially have.<br>
Meet the Scottish Warrior (who doesn’t explode things)<br>
Meet the Fire Scout<br>
Meet the Archer<br>
Meet the Slightly Different Archer (ie, Soldier with Direct Hit)<br>
Meet the Combat Engineer (gunslinger)<br>
Meet the Identity-Stealer (Spy, working completely differently)</p>
<p>I just feel like all these weapons change each class’s dynamic so much that it’s becoming difficult to keep track of, and respond to them all, at once. I think when the game started with 9 classes, it was a challenge to keep them balanced but they did it successfully. 17+ classes? No one can balance that.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/tf2-mann-conomy-update-thoughts-recipes-and-new-items/5609/120">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/tf2-mann-conomy-update-thoughts-recipes-and-new-items/5609/120</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 06 Oct 2010 16:22:53 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-5609-120</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/tf2-mann-conomy-update-thoughts-recipes-and-new-items/5609.rss">TF2 Mann-Conomy Update: Thoughts, Recipes, and New Items</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>TF2 Mann-Conomy Update: Thoughts, Recipes, and New Items</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Someonerandm]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>^That</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/tf2-mann-conomy-update-thoughts-recipes-and-new-items/5609/119">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/tf2-mann-conomy-update-thoughts-recipes-and-new-items/5609/119</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 06 Oct 2010 16:12:54 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-5609-119</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/tf2-mann-conomy-update-thoughts-recipes-and-new-items/5609.rss">TF2 Mann-Conomy Update: Thoughts, Recipes, and New Items</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>TF2 Mann-Conomy Update: Thoughts, Recipes, and New Items</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[DiePoente]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Not really</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/tf2-mann-conomy-update-thoughts-recipes-and-new-items/5609/118">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/tf2-mann-conomy-update-thoughts-recipes-and-new-items/5609/118</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 06 Oct 2010 12:39:42 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-5609-118</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/tf2-mann-conomy-update-thoughts-recipes-and-new-items/5609.rss">TF2 Mann-Conomy Update: Thoughts, Recipes, and New Items</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>TF2 Mann-Conomy Update: Thoughts, Recipes, and New Items</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Nerdguy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Just realized that this has turned to a WOW-esque trade chat</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/tf2-mann-conomy-update-thoughts-recipes-and-new-items/5609/117">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/tf2-mann-conomy-update-thoughts-recipes-and-new-items/5609/117</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 06 Oct 2010 10:37:17 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-5609-117</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/tf2-mann-conomy-update-thoughts-recipes-and-new-items/5609.rss">TF2 Mann-Conomy Update: Thoughts, Recipes, and New Items</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>TF2 Mann-Conomy Update: Thoughts, Recipes, and New Items</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Scrue]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>boxes have now gone.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/tf2-mann-conomy-update-thoughts-recipes-and-new-items/5609/116">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/tf2-mann-conomy-update-thoughts-recipes-and-new-items/5609/116</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 05 Oct 2010 14:46:38 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-5609-116</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/tf2-mann-conomy-update-thoughts-recipes-and-new-items/5609.rss">TF2 Mann-Conomy Update: Thoughts, Recipes, and New Items</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>TF2 Mann-Conomy Update: Thoughts, Recipes, and New Items</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[RabidMonkey]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I’d give you something equally as valuable for it, but I don’t have a DH to my name.</p>
<p>Although my crate drops have been disappointing so far…</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/tf2-mann-conomy-update-thoughts-recipes-and-new-items/5609/115">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/tf2-mann-conomy-update-thoughts-recipes-and-new-items/5609/115</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 05 Oct 2010 13:36:23 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-5609-115</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/tf2-mann-conomy-update-thoughts-recipes-and-new-items/5609.rss">TF2 Mann-Conomy Update: Thoughts, Recipes, and New Items</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>TF2 Mann-Conomy Update: Thoughts, Recipes, and New Items</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Scrue]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Someonerandm">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/s/d78d45/40.png" class="avatar"> Someonerandm:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>TF2 and COD have completely different play styles, and CoD has a substantially lesser emphasis on teamwork. We need more teamwork oriented people in TF2, and getting rid of CoD people helps with that.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Team work orientated people help, but nerfing natascha would also be a big help.</p>
<p>But then again i haven’t played CoD apart from the first one which i thought was awesome.</p>
<p>And i got a crate if any one wants to give me a direct hit for it. Feels like deal or no deal.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/tf2-mann-conomy-update-thoughts-recipes-and-new-items/5609/114">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/tf2-mann-conomy-update-thoughts-recipes-and-new-items/5609/114</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 05 Oct 2010 13:26:26 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-5609-114</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/tf2-mann-conomy-update-thoughts-recipes-and-new-items/5609.rss">TF2 Mann-Conomy Update: Thoughts, Recipes, and New Items</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>TF2 Mann-Conomy Update: Thoughts, Recipes, and New Items</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Someonerandm]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>TF2 and COD have completely different play styles, and CoD has a substantially lesser emphasis on teamwork. We need more teamwork oriented people in TF2, and getting rid of CoD people helps with that.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/tf2-mann-conomy-update-thoughts-recipes-and-new-items/5609/113">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/tf2-mann-conomy-update-thoughts-recipes-and-new-items/5609/113</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 05 Oct 2010 12:46:36 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-5609-113</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/tf2-mann-conomy-update-thoughts-recipes-and-new-items/5609.rss">TF2 Mann-Conomy Update: Thoughts, Recipes, and New Items</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
