<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Earthbound Chit-Chat Thread</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/earthbound-chit-chat-thread/61975</link>
    <description>_*NOTE*: With the potential for the first 14 chapters to receive another pass following Xen’s release, I thought it might be a good idea to create this thread as a companion to the Xen Chit-chat thread. This is simply meant to be a discussion of the current shortcomings of the Earthbound levels, and how certain aspects of them could be improved. Though it has been suggested by the developers multiple times as a potential future project, there is no guarantee that it will happen. My hope is that this thread can be a source of ongoing discussion and generate realistic, well-articulated ideas that could be used as some kind of reference were anything along these lines to occur._ 

Since the release of the mod back in 2012, there have been a number of improvements made to the Earthbound levels, be it through updated assets, as a side effect of engine improvements, or most obviously the expansion of Surface Tension. However, when viewing the released Xen media and comparing Surface Tension Uncut’s maps to the rest of the game, there is a clear disparity in quality even with said enhancements. This isn’t to say that the existing levels don’t hold up, as they still look excellent in many ways, however their design and visual fidelity are clearly not on the same level. This is to be expected when a project has a development cycle as long as Black Mesa’s, with some of these maps (in some similar form) dating back to far earlier builds of the game. 

My question to the community is: What kind of (realistic in scope) changes would you make to the first 14 chapters in order to bring them up to this much higher standard? They can be as specific as a model/texture/effect/etc. improvement, or as broad as changes to the design of a level to facilitate better gameplay or atmosphere. 

I will give an example: I have never found that the Anomalous Materials labs give the impression of a real worked-in environment due to its extremely strict linearity. Past the meta-remake-commentary room, the sequence more or less follows a series of hallways directly connected to one another with little deviation or even a hint of alternate paths, making it seem that much of Sector C lies along a singular hallway rather than part of a sprawling complex. Were adjacent hallways/rooms/elevators/etc. to be added at various points along the route to the test chamber simply as visual indicators of a much larger Sector C (which the player would be unable to access), it would lend a better sense of expansiveness and realism to the environment that just isn’t present at the moment.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 31 Aug 2019 18:17:09 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>The Cafeteria</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/earthbound-chit-chat-thread/61975.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Earthbound Chit-Chat Thread</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Ronster]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Yeah it’s a nice idea for helping that guy out.</p>
<p>As promised Cutscene Demo (Rough idea)… I actually did this ages ago but anyway I did’nt upload sooner because I realised that the HEV startup sequence audo times perfectly with the music and ends exactly when the song ends if you delay the getting the suit moment until the drums. Actual Music cue? It’s not in the Video but take my word on it.</p>
<p><a href="https://www.mediafire.com/file/0puu5xyokyguod9/Black_Mesa_Cutscene_Concept.mp4/file" class="onebox" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">https://www.mediafire.com/file/0puu5xyokyguod9/Black_Mesa_Cutscene_Concept.mp4/file</a></p>
<p>A few thoughts on HEV chamber sequence… Held inside HEV chamber briefly before allowed to move… Steam and so on Glass retracts… Then Free to run. Red Light once out the chamber like the other 2…</p>
<p>Audio quite busy with other characters lines… It would be ideal if you only made it a small way down the corridor before the music and speech end simultaneously. I thought about perhaps an extra room with a helmet Racked on the right of the suit chargers just to delay the player… Also mirror in the wash room shows change of player skin another delay tactic.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/earthbound-chit-chat-thread/61975/16">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/earthbound-chit-chat-thread/61975/16</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 31 Aug 2019 17:46:37 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-61975-16</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/earthbound-chit-chat-thread/61975.rss">Earthbound Chit-Chat Thread</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Earthbound Chit-Chat Thread</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Viewer]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Personally, I would like to see an acknowledgement of trying to help the injured guard in the control booth in Power Up - after turning on the track power, a section opens up with a number of medkits, and you’re able to throw them through the broken window. Maybe a voiced “hey…thanks” or something, and an achievement like the Brownian Motion one - perhaps “Blue Shift”? <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=9" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/earthbound-chit-chat-thread/61975/15">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/earthbound-chit-chat-thread/61975/15</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 31 Aug 2019 16:50:12 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-61975-15</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/earthbound-chit-chat-thread/61975.rss">Earthbound Chit-Chat Thread</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Earthbound Chit-Chat Thread</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Ronster]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Some Jokes I Liked…</p>
<p><img src="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/original/2X/c/c6f490ec8a397345e13bb75f0d823603817705e8.jpeg" alt="" data-base62-sha1="so2wdqmwlheHfBYvZU0SDT6YHVe" width="620" height="496"></p>
<p><div class="lightbox-wrapper"><a class="lightbox" href="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/original/2X/c/c0d48df8d2b540388760594278c38abc7d7055d6.jpeg" data-download-href="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/c0d48df8d2b540388760594278c38abc7d7055d6" title=""><img src="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/original/2X/c/c0d48df8d2b540388760594278c38abc7d7055d6.jpeg" alt="" data-base62-sha1="rvR4mEvoUDBdI62doN2woaenB1s" width="690" height="431" data-small-upload="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/optimized/2X/c/c0d48df8d2b540388760594278c38abc7d7055d6_2_10x10.png"><div class="meta"><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-far-image svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#far-image"></use></svg><span class="filename"></span><span class="informations">1440×900 103 KB</span><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-discourse-expand svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#discourse-expand"></use></svg></div></a></div></p>
<p><div class="lightbox-wrapper"><a class="lightbox" href="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/original/2X/b/b862e488902ae94cd0e57301a98b451e44b68c4d.jpeg" data-download-href="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/b862e488902ae94cd0e57301a98b451e44b68c4d" title=""><img src="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/optimized/2X/b/b862e488902ae94cd0e57301a98b451e44b68c4d_2_690x460.jpeg" alt="" data-base62-sha1="qj9JkMMlqOh0KdvRoQaX3DP1Jp3" width="690" height="460" srcset="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/optimized/2X/b/b862e488902ae94cd0e57301a98b451e44b68c4d_2_690x460.jpeg, https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/optimized/2X/b/b862e488902ae94cd0e57301a98b451e44b68c4d_2_1035x690.jpeg 1.5x, https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/optimized/2X/b/b862e488902ae94cd0e57301a98b451e44b68c4d_2_1380x920.jpeg 2x" data-small-upload="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/optimized/2X/b/b862e488902ae94cd0e57301a98b451e44b68c4d_2_10x10.png"><div class="meta"><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-far-image svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#far-image"></use></svg><span class="filename"></span><span class="informations">1440×960 207 KB</span><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-discourse-expand svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#discourse-expand"></use></svg></div></a></div></p>
<p><img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=9" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji only-emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/earthbound-chit-chat-thread/61975/14">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/earthbound-chit-chat-thread/61975/14</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 31 Aug 2019 15:57:49 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-61975-14</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/earthbound-chit-chat-thread/61975.rss">Earthbound Chit-Chat Thread</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Earthbound Chit-Chat Thread</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Ronster]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="CPU" data-post="12" data-topic="61975">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/user_avatar/leakfree.org/cpu/40/4349_2.png" class="avatar"> CPU:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Little bit of trivia for you about the original “The Thing From Another World” (1951 film):<br>
This film introduced, for the first time in movie history, the ‘boo’ scene. A moment in a film where all of a sudden someone or something suddenly appears that makes you jump. It had never happened before in movie history.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I read that it was a bit of controversy over who directed it but I can’t say i ever seen it unfortunately. The John Carpenter remake is superior from what I understand and I saw it when I was about 8 years old… It was pretty scary for me and certainly left an impression. It is one of the best horror films ever still to this day because of the character interactions not because of the alien. You could say the same for the Original 1979 Alien by Ridley scott also characters rule the roost.</p>
<p>Anyway the point is that scene with the defibrillator the aliens head falls off, that I think is enojgh to understand the feature set of what the half life 2 zombie is meant to be. So it is probably a feature not implemented in Half life but in Half life 2 it is bugged. The detachment is the step before the Gibb and Skull Spawn or that is how I am calling it a bug in Half Life 2.</p>
<p>Zombies have an unused drag body animation in Half life not sure when or what or where but it is perhaps drag body out of sight and gibb victim off screen?</p>
<p>The only other thought I have right now is if the Adrenaline pick up module was bullet time or slow motion effect? I don’t think the rest really matter. On the wiki it says revival 3 seconds after death… But it is infinite lives anyway. does not add up that.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/earthbound-chit-chat-thread/61975/13">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/earthbound-chit-chat-thread/61975/13</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 05 May 2019 19:43:52 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-61975-13</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/earthbound-chit-chat-thread/61975.rss">Earthbound Chit-Chat Thread</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Earthbound Chit-Chat Thread</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[CPU]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Ronster" data-post="11" data-topic="61975">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/r/5f9b8f/40.png" class="avatar"> Ronster:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I then started thinking about the mouth in the middle of the body and realized ok this is John Carpenters “The Thing”… Remember that scary defibrillator scene?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Little bit of trivia for you about the original “The Thing From Another World” (1951 film):<br>
This film introduced, for the first time in movie history, the ‘boo’ scene. A moment in a film where all of a sudden someone or something suddenly appears that makes you jump. It had never happened before in movie history.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/earthbound-chit-chat-thread/61975/12">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/earthbound-chit-chat-thread/61975/12</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 05 May 2019 15:37:15 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-61975-12</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/earthbound-chit-chat-thread/61975.rss">Earthbound Chit-Chat Thread</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Earthbound Chit-Chat Thread</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Ronster]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I just came to a bit of a startling conclusion about mechanics of the Zombie and how it is not correct in the original game Half Life.</p>
<p>I was looking at the Headshot and Headcrab detachment problem in Black Mesa and I think it ties in to the Scientist Skull Gibb and the fact that Headcrabs can not be Gibbed.</p>
<p>If we Look at the Fan room in Office Complex Headcrabs Gibb on contact with the Fan and they Gibb also when explosions occur. This could be a reason why Black Mesa have removed Headcrabs being able to be picked up?</p>
<p>Anyway… The effect I think is missing for the Zombie is as follows.</p>
<p>Shotgun or 357 Headshot on zombie = Headcrab Gibbs and spawns Broken Skull Gibb but Ragdolls Headless Zombie Corpse. (Crossbow does not do this)</p>
<p>Explosions  = Gibbs the Lot including Skull and Headcrab Fragments.</p>
<p>I then started thinking about the mouth in the middle of the body and realized ok this is John Carpenters “The Thing”… Remember that scary defibrillator scene?</p>
<p>So then I also remember the CPR scene as soon as you emerge from the Test Chamber!!!</p>
<p>Oh my god, well perhaps that was meant to be a bit more Gory or there was a second use for CPR on a Zombie or perhaps even their was to be a Joke where a Zombie is getting electrocuted on a stretcher with a defibrillator stuck inside him with a scientist with no Hands Left <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=9" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
<p>But yeah it all ties in so a Headcrab is a cross between a face hugger from Aliens and the Decapitated head Spider from “The Thing”.</p>
<p>Saw this thought it was Brilliant.</p>
<div class="onebox lazyYT lazyYT-container" data-youtube-id="K34eEnj-qA8" data-youtube-title="Fully Animated Health Charger (Black Mesa/Half Life)" data-parameters="feature=oembed&amp;wmode=opaque">
  <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=K34eEnj-qA8" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">
    <img class="ytp-thumbnail-image" src="https://i.ytimg.com/vi/K34eEnj-qA8/maxresdefault.jpg" title="Fully Animated Health Charger (Black Mesa/Half Life)" width="690" height="388">
  </a>
</div>

<p>Also this scripted scene seems like it is meant to go instead of the Duplicated scene of being pulled into the Vents actually is it 3 times? Anyway It is a good Alternative for Office Complex and Very Funny <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=9" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
<div class="onebox lazyYT lazyYT-container" data-youtube-id="1rF8ozBl5Ro" data-youtube-title="Half-Life Beta: Cut &quot;Pepsi&quot; Scripted Sequence" data-parameters="feature=oembed&amp;wmode=opaque">
  <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=1rF8ozBl5Ro" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">
    <img class="ytp-thumbnail-image" src="https://i.ytimg.com/vi/1rF8ozBl5Ro/maxresdefault.jpg" title="Half-Life Beta: Cut &quot;Pepsi&quot; Scripted Sequence" width="690" height="388">
  </a>
</div>

<p>I also think Office complex could do with the Broken Elevator from PS2 Version upon entering the Level. In fact Office Complex Feels Content light overall. I thought also about the Glass Atrium that Shatter above the Cafeteria from the Alpha might be also a nice touch. The Zombie Bashing the Vending Machine to get food out of it is also Absent and the Coffee machines before the Freezer Room.</p>
<p>A Comment I came across on the Character Mods for “Inbound” and “Anomalous Materials” suggested Dr. Breen should Be with the G-Man in that Room in as you enter past reception. I thought this was actually an excellent Idea. But to expand it a bit Further.</p>
<p><img src="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/original/2X/f/f833ea2dfc70b5caa4f691b27ec1f7729dcd2261.png" width="283" height="380"></p>
<p>G-man Briefcase on the Table open showing the Gun and Paperwork.</p>
<p><div class="lightbox-wrapper"><a class="lightbox" href="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/original/2X/2/2f5f335f6f4e50201d1a1c42c59e71a400c51e92.jpeg" data-download-href="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/2f5f335f6f4e50201d1a1c42c59e71a400c51e92" title="1327845844615.jpg"><img src="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/original/2X/2/2f5f335f6f4e50201d1a1c42c59e71a400c51e92.jpeg" width="690" height="487" data-small-upload="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/optimized/2X/2/2f5f335f6f4e50201d1a1c42c59e71a400c51e92_2_10x10.png"><div class="meta"><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-far-image svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#far-image"></use></svg><span class="filename">1327845844615.jpg</span><span class="informations">850×600 230 KB</span><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-discourse-expand svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#discourse-expand"></use></svg></div></a></div></p>
<p>Include Crystal in the Handler Machine in the Background (Re-Skin). I think that would really be a massive step up from the Original in terms of Setting up the Half Life 2.</p>
<p>Anyway this was a couple of things I had thoughts on and at the end of the day it’s all a bit of fun nods and winks and fulfilling <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=9" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
<p>I will be preparing a video of how cut-scenes can work in Inbound and Anomalous Materials… I will post it later.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/earthbound-chit-chat-thread/61975/11">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/earthbound-chit-chat-thread/61975/11</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 05 May 2019 10:11:04 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-61975-11</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/earthbound-chit-chat-thread/61975.rss">Earthbound Chit-Chat Thread</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Earthbound Chit-Chat Thread</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Ronster]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Ok I few more things I noticed and in no way do I mean this in a pessimistic way I just want to see the game be the best it can be. It’s actually going to be fairly short this post but I had a small collection of extra ideas and I want to put them for the earthbound part.</p>
<p>Going to start with the Satchel on this post. I think the C4 Satchel weapon needs not only it’s own distinct explosion sound but also it’s own particles different from regular explosions and more fire or flammable orientated. But other than that it’s just a way to give it a unique feel and different from say the grenade and rocket launcher.</p>
<p>The Destructible walkways in blast pit should be re-implemented as it’s just not the same without blowing them up by accident then making life harder by having to jump across if you blow them up by accident.</p>
<p>The section in questionable ethics which contains a canteen and some offices should go… It’s ok but I don’t think it fits the rest of the area. It should be a mini version of the Alien Research Labs… Here are some ideas.</p>
<ol>
<li>Alien Autopsy - Dead Vort on a operating Table</li>
<li>Dissected Headcrab</li>
<li>Zombie in a Catscan tunnel</li>
<li>Alien Grunt x-ray on a viewer (the one from the magazine)</li>
<li>Bullsquid Spit extraction (Decay)</li>
<li>Morgue? Or Leech Tank?</li>
<li>Scientists in Hazmat suits not normal science uniforms at the Death trap machine with blades.</li>
</ol>
<p>I think Questionable Ethics is actually better than the original game in Black Mesa so no bother but I also think it could basically wipe the floor on that level.</p>
<p>That would do to be honest even if only aesthetic it would fit the rest of the areas… Now although I said about a botanical garden earlier I don’t think this is needed but you should do more to make some areas have some more Plant life like the mapping contest Mod OASIS by Maki.</p>
<p>Ok I said this would be short and I thought about this and I don’t think this will be a popular opinion but I will say it… In forget about Freeman for the Tank Battle, there is too much going on. I think that it’s too busy and also the music does not represent the action. I think the focus needs to be put on the actual tank battle and then have some soldiers come out after the Tank is destroyed to mop up. The music should feel like you are going up against a Tank a slow Lumbering powerhouse.</p>
<p>I really like the music here but I have to say it would be great to keep it but it does not go here I would put it in the Apache battle instead on Clifftop, it’s too fast and does not represent a Tank Battle. I would also say the whole focus of the fight needs to be centered around the Tank perhaps the Rocks in the middle being destroyed by shell fire or something having to run for cover and hit and run rocket attacks.</p>
<p>Make Red Damage Indicators smaller they are too big. Scale them down quite a bit so they will not obscure the HUD so much.</p>
<p>Inbound. I like the Unreal Engine take in that you get scanned by Laser at the Security office. I don’t think it’s worth stopping the Tram for as it would mess up the timing for music and so on, but having a static Laser scan the Tram Drives through is good sci-fi.</p>
<p>Include 0 Days since last injury in “We got Hostiles”</p>
<p>Include Ichy poster by the Shark Tank describing what it is.</p>
<p>Leeches and cockroaches If you now have the entity count to add them back in a bit of atmosphere can be regained by there re-inclusion. I agree they are not needed but they add that Earth Mutated creatures element into the mix and it is good, shame they are not properly in as they were in the original game but entity limits are obviously a factor.</p>
<p>That is really all I can perhaps think of… Not to say it is something Black Mesa should implement but just thoughts or ideas and perhaps could be improvement but I would not be bothered or fussed if none of it happened either.</p>
<p>EDIT.</p>
<p>Forgot to add… Mortar shells only going whistle - bang.</p>
<p>Should be going whistle - whoosh - bang. Chech HL1 &amp; 2 set-up.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/earthbound-chit-chat-thread/61975/10">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/earthbound-chit-chat-thread/61975/10</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2019 18:50:35 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-61975-10</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/earthbound-chit-chat-thread/61975.rss">Earthbound Chit-Chat Thread</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Earthbound Chit-Chat Thread</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Ronster]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Sieben I agree with the office complex rundown also of note towards the end of chapter the scientist who falls down the shaft is triggered at a different time… I even heard a developer on a play through saying “it worked better in the original” and the scientist falls when you go upnear him rather than him just falling before you go in the shaft.</p>
<p>I Like the Idea of the Magnum with Laser attachment underneath more than the iron sights which is in game. Nice ideas for extra boosts or bonus abilities. It’s a bit like putting the deathmarch model in Single player but actually adding the feature of it having laser sight even with iron sights aswell. I think this would be really cool…</p>
<p>Glock with Silencer? this might also be an interesting attachment so you can use stealth with Glock conserving the crossbow ammo.</p>
<p>Re-animating the crowbar weapon to be much more like the original is very important it just looks wrong. It’s always been inferior. I think this is more important than map content.</p>
<p>The crossbow scope also seems to be one of those ongoing sagas it’s average that it is alright but it has never really worked properly or had some sort of issue with the scope. It looks better than it ever had done before now but it seems to be cursed. Ah well one day it will be fixed without breaking other stuff.</p>
<p>The Female Assassin is also another one of those things not working properly. I like the HL2 Beta combine Assassin Version… I was hoping the team would be able to use that as a replacement (reskin) once it was green-lit but anyway never happened but this is perhaps worst NPC in game kick should be a roundhouse kick and cloaking device not working also. This one could do with being redone as it is worst one of all npc.</p>
<p>I wish it was like HL2 Beta combine assassin… Should they Land in a Black Hawk rather than the Apache? Well it’s a potentially brilliant introduction to that enemy! Actually let me re-iterate this Black ops kills security guard then we hear the sound of rotor blades spinning up… as we turn the corner the Black Hawk is lifting off through the large opening in the roof from helipad once the helicopter is clear two doors slide across closing the Helipad off from the outside world. So there you have it very cool sequence that would be…</p>
<p>Another Introduction this time for the HECU -  the first encounter should have them rappelling down walls of elevator shaft (or Outside elevator shaft)  in we got hostiles rather than one riding down in the lift…before you fight them first time. this is the same room you get mp5 first time.</p>
<p>Been thinking quite a bit about introduction sequences and introduction of a new enemy via a scripted animation on first contact so as it has more punch and if you like more impressive introductions to new enemy types.</p>
<p>Bullsquid is alright but it could do with a re-skin…perhaps it’s mouth could be animated better but it looks nothing like headcrabs or houdeyes skin. Bullsquid looks more cartoon like rather than alien flesh.</p>
<p><div class="lightbox-wrapper"><a class="lightbox" href="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/original/2X/c/cb954d6d222539ca0ca693de3876bd00240a93a2.jpeg" data-download-href="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/cb954d6d222539ca0ca693de3876bd00240a93a2" title="k5wm1ltahrt11.jpg"><img src="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/optimized/2X/c/cb954d6d222539ca0ca693de3876bd00240a93a2_2_690x388.jpeg" width="690" height="388" srcset="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/optimized/2X/c/cb954d6d222539ca0ca693de3876bd00240a93a2_2_690x388.jpeg, https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/optimized/2X/c/cb954d6d222539ca0ca693de3876bd00240a93a2_2_1035x582.jpeg 1.5x, https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/optimized/2X/c/cb954d6d222539ca0ca693de3876bd00240a93a2_2_1380x776.jpeg 2x" data-small-upload="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/optimized/2X/c/cb954d6d222539ca0ca693de3876bd00240a93a2_2_10x10.png"><div class="meta"><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-far-image svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#far-image"></use></svg><span class="filename">k5wm1ltahrt11.jpg</span><span class="informations">1920×1080 107 KB</span><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-discourse-expand svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#discourse-expand"></use></svg></div></a></div></p>
<p>more like this…but mouth not as red more dark</p>
<p>Been thinking about bullsquid introduction I would remove the two zombies in the freezer room and have the woman run away screaming from a bullsquid chasing her… This would be an adequete introduction. I would also place another one feasting on a carcus in this room.</p>
<p>I also wanted to add a bit about the trash compactor scene… Now this seems quite buggy with floating crates and the trash compactor walls are doors that start and stop which messes up the sound… I think the only way to do the trash compactor escape justice is with cinematic physics for the rubbish being crushed and to avoid all the physics bugging out. This would also potentially sort out the stuttering sound of the compactor also. Not looking for anything particularly flash but it might be a better way to deal with this part rather than rely on the physics engine freaking out.</p>
<p>I have actually just seen the latest updated version on youtube and it is much better now than it was before on trash compactor  but the sound is still stop /start. I think the latest update looks very good but I think there are small instances of improvement to be found. Apart from crowbar and crossbow scope.</p>
<p>I saw someone modded Inbound with a suggestion of commercial helicopter swap for apache and construction workers… It is good.</p>
<p>In terms of Anormolous materials I will add the ideas for this chapter.</p>
<p>Put mirror in the changing rooms so player can see world model of themselves and change of costume.</p>
<p>Improve HEV suit chamber opening sequence with either video cutscene or dynamic lights and smoke on chamber. If done via cut-scene spawn player into suit after cut-scene.</p>
<p>Make test chamber / Resonance cascade more cinematic through either cut-scenes or scripted animation. Remove env_shake until Crystal goes in the beam. Start shaking on insertion.</p>
<p>When Gordon comes up out the elevator in Unforeseen consequences have a scripted animation sequence to introduce zombies. Have Barney Calhoun save you and be the character to escort you back to reception from where you are on your own.</p>
<p>EDIT:</p>
<p>Couple More things for Inspiration.</p>
<p><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=l-U1i7FA_34" class="onebox" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=l-U1i7FA_34</a></p>
<p>Add head humping animation to idle zombies… No need for Degenerate a corpse but Idle head humping is a very good one.</p>
<p>Add Particle effects similar to HL2 EP1 Flare (Red Light Sprite and smoke) Like Below</p>
<p><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=occMRdCAb7Q" class="onebox" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=occMRdCAb7Q</a></p>
<p>Add Particle Effect to Head crab Burrow (Dust puff Kick ups) This would Hide model clipping through the floor.</p>
<p>Add Legless Torso of this scientist where you pick up Tau Cannon</p>
<p><div class="lightbox-wrapper"><a class="lightbox" href="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/original/2X/4/4848ee8ca3ef89bec9e386be959f9dec92ac56c9.png" data-download-href="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/4848ee8ca3ef89bec9e386be959f9dec92ac56c9" title="grargh.png"><img src="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/optimized/2X/4/4848ee8ca3ef89bec9e386be959f9dec92ac56c9_2_407x500.png" width="407" height="500" srcset="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/optimized/2X/4/4848ee8ca3ef89bec9e386be959f9dec92ac56c9_2_407x500.png, https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/original/2X/4/4848ee8ca3ef89bec9e386be959f9dec92ac56c9.png 1.5x, https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/original/2X/4/4848ee8ca3ef89bec9e386be959f9dec92ac56c9.png 2x" data-small-upload="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/optimized/2X/4/4848ee8ca3ef89bec9e386be959f9dec92ac56c9_2_10x10.png"><div class="meta"><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-far-image svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#far-image"></use></svg><span class="filename">grargh.png</span><span class="informations">597×733 250 KB</span><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-discourse-expand svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#discourse-expand"></use></svg></div></a></div></p>
<p>Comedy Gold… Zombie Torso run over by Abrams Tank Tracks</p>
<p>Update Tau Canon particles for the Beam like Hlaf Life 2 Buggy Tau Canon</p>
<p><a href="https://youtu.be/OKIrFlUVp2A?t=42" class="onebox" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">https://youtu.be/OKIrFlUVp2A?t=42</a></p>
<p>Give Tau Canon Particles on hit like this video below for the Metal Sparks no matter what it Hits.</p>
<p><a href="https://youtu.be/DYxitb71M7o?t=11" class="onebox" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">https://youtu.be/DYxitb71M7o?t=11</a></p>
<p>Houndeyes need to be programmed to Simultaneously Attack at the Same time (Damage Amplifier) So the player has to run away rather than cannon fodder kill them. And also Houndeye not being afraid to attack at greater Distance as the Hound eye will only attack when directly in front of the player.</p>
<p><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Lqxag2TDqtQ" class="onebox" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Lqxag2TDqtQ</a></p>
<p>Took a look at the code (Valve made the source code public on Github). The formula for a houndeye’s sonic attack damage if the squad size is more than 1 is:</p>
<p>BaseDamage + BaseDamage * (SquadBonus * (SquadSize - 1))</p>
<p>Base damage is determined by difficulty and/or cvar settings. SquadBonus is hard coded to be 1.1</p>
<p>That means a base damage of 10 and a squad size of 4 would be: 10 + 10 * (1.1 * 3) = 43</p>
<p>Also, the game checks if the houndeye has direct line of sight with the player, and will deal half damage if the player is behind an obstacle. This does not apply to other monsters; they take no damage if they are obscured.</p>
<p>Not bothered about Color Change but re-add Particles for Sonic Attack from HL2 Beta or Similar</p>
<p>Obviously these are all just ideas or ideas inspired from other media but take em or leave em</p>
<p>I see the orb teleport flashes fixed in latest update too <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/wink.png?v=9" title=":wink:" class="emoji" alt=":wink:"> two thumbs up.</p>
<p>I think I have said all I have to say now It’s been nice seeing the latest version and looking forward to playing again soon.</p>
<p>Edit 2</p>
<p>Ok a couple more things I have thought of and these are mostly also quite small in scale sorry about this but I am getting these ideas out in the wild as potential changes / improvements / modifications.</p>
<p>Add Camera Bob to certain movement namely Crouch walking and Ladder Strafing… And perhaps, a slight bob to initial strafe movement like Deathmatch movement.</p>
<p>Make Crystal Cart a Vehicle with view model Hands on the Prop. Forward backward movement only enter and exit animations.</p>
<p>Make Barnacles Deadly for the player that once bitten it is game over… upon Bite trigger animated overlay on screen of interior of Barnacles mouth / stomach then fade to Red. The rules are the same then for both NPC and player.</p>
<p>I read about a sequence that consisted of using the power Loader under the players control (Via a control station or Levers) to defeat a Gargantua. This sounded an excellent Idea and I felt this was obviously teasing a vehicle in Inbound for the player and it is a shame this is not in the actual game. The Loader is such a good homage to aliens the movie it is a shame the feature to control a Loader in any shape or form does not exist and even the fact we never really see them used because it was by and large an unfinished idea. This sequence happened apparently by an abrams tank bursting through a door. There was to be a crate Puzzle also in which would be similar to opposing force crate puzzle. Even if not under player control it would be nice to see them included somewhere especially near at the Lambda complex part of the game. They feel like such a waste and they look really good.</p>
<p>Create Model for Commando Rocket Launcher for on a Rail Marines rocket outpost.<br>
<img src="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/original/2X/f/fdbfff61d4b74c64e47eabebd1bfbc9e0986160d.jpeg" width="400" height="317"></p>
<p>Add Impact sound for Crossbow Dart Hit Npc and world (can be the same sound or different)</p>
<p>In The Test Chamber on First Teleport in the original Half Life we have Green Lightning Flashes and Helmet Breathing sounds then black screen (something missing)?!? On this debate it seems to me Gordon Wears a Helmet going in to the Test Chamber but Losses it somewhere on Xen. This opens up a prospect of Having a cracked Glass overlay on the Helmet during the accident and having the Breathing Sound effects added. We could also find the Helmet again later on xen with cracked glass it also re-enforces it is not a dream. Using HL2 teleport effects would also be cool for continuity.</p>
<p>One more thing that has become a realization about the black ops assassins is that When Gordan is Apprehended in the room it is possible that it was Originally Planned that a Black Ops would have shot him with the crossbow (nero-toxic dart) to knock him out as their introduction would have been in conjunction with his apprehension. This is neither really here nor there but it is an interesting take on how he might of been apprehended before they got the silenced pistols as default. To complete the Cut-scene show Gordan being dropped from crane Magnet into Trash.</p>
<p>Put dead Assassin in the water where you first get the crossbow with shark cage if associated with assassins.</p>
<p>On Retinal Scanners Add texture Image of Retinal Scan on a screen / panel by the reader Goggles when used. Then Return to default texture. Perhaps remove number buttons or  Black Mesa Logo and replace with screen on model. Seems Retinal scanner also meant to have blue light for goggles when activated.<br>
<img src="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/original/2X/2/2e796fb5a47a47b4c0ce515cfe0e7a792288b722.jpeg" width="263" height="191"></p>
<p>Add Diamond shape around crosshair for the Visully impaired similar to PS2 HD port.</p>
<p>Fix Guargantua footstomp attack.</p>
<p>Add secondary fire to Gluon gun seeing as Hivehand now has cut secondary attack… Looked at the combineguard gun attack and like the darkmatter energy ball this could be added to the current spin up of the Gluon. Not sure what the seconday attack was meant to be honestly. combineguard attack too slmilar to tau canon attack perhaps it was meant to be like fast laser gun? Black hole gun?</p>
<p>Show Rifts occurring using code and effects for cut Blackhole grenade weapon EP1. Have Props and human npc’s being sucked into another dimension in various areas to explain the resonance cascade effects. Yellow Orange Lightning before the rifts</p>
<p>Once agin just Ideas and I really am done now :)<img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/smile.png?v=9" title=":smile:" class="emoji" alt=":smile:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/earthbound-chit-chat-thread/61975/9">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/earthbound-chit-chat-thread/61975/9</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2019 14:11:20 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-61975-9</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/earthbound-chit-chat-thread/61975.rss">Earthbound Chit-Chat Thread</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Earthbound Chit-Chat Thread</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Sieben]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>If I could ask for new features in earthbound chapters, that would be the details that was in original Half-Life and not included in BM. Puzzles, secrets, traps, etc.<br>
A few examples, in Office Complex:</p>
<ul>
<li>At the beginning of the chapter, unlike in the original game, the left path in the air duct is not a secret, since you can access to the supplies even if electricity is still on.</li>
<li>A moment later, behind the front desk, the zombie used to destroy the door in the original game. It brought <em>a lot</em> to the atmosphere. Also, it was kind of a secret area, since you couldn’t access the room if you killed the zombie too quickly.</li>
<li>Then, in the flooded room, the switch doesn’t bring anything to the game in BM. there is no need to turn it off because the air duct is available by climbing onto the furnitures, and there is no secret armour battery.</li>
<li>Then, in the air duct, there is no fan that would chop Gordon’s head off if not careful enough.</li>
<li>After that, in the corridor, the ventilation shaft is already available in BM,while in the original HL you needed to solve a small puzzle, with crates.</li>
<li>In the main office hub, the secret passage leading to the automated turret is already visible in the ceiling. It makes it too easy to find. Just a hint would have been nice, instead of revealing completely the secret.</li>
</ul>
<p>All these little details were so important to the spirit and atmosphere of Half-Life. BM is an awesome, awesome game. However, as a re-creation of a classic, I think it should be as faithful as possible to it. I’m glad when more original content is added, but not when legacy content is removed. I would be delighted if we were granted some more puzzles, secrets and traps: those that was in the original game, and some more! <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=9" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
<p>I also agree with what many people stated in this thread and elsewhere. On a Rail doesn’t feel like a trip like it did in HL. I understand that the devs are happy the way it is now, but it really misses something.<br>
The vent maze at the end of We Got Hostiles in painfully missing as well.<br>
I agree about the OP’s view on Anomalous Material. I would also like some doors, corridors, elevators here and there to indicate that this is a large place and not just a big corridor.<br>
About the original locations of weapons (crowbar, shotgun, magnum…): why not making it available as an optional feature? That way, everybody is happy, and it brings more to game replayability.</p>
<p>About the game difficulty. Marines are hard, and they should be. The main problem is that the MP5 is very bad in BM. And why not adding some randomized marine difficulty? Just like in real life, all people don’t have exactly the same abilities, right? All marines would have random characteristics (health and firing accuracy). Some marines would have 80 HP, some 100, and a few of them would have 120. Some would be very good at throwing grenades, some would be less good. Some would be good at firing with MP5, some would be less good… Etc. Of course, none of them would totally suck at anything, they are heavily trained soldiers for god’s sake! <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=9" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"> This feature would add more surprise and replayability, as the skill of each single marines wouldn’t be the same in every game, and it would bring more realism.<br>
Also, I haven’t played the game in a long time, but last time I did (it was the mod, not the steam game), choppers were a hell of a nightmare. They deal a lot of damage, and, more importantly, they are way too accurate when firing at poor Gordon. In real life, firing with accuracy from a flying vehicle must be extremely hard.</p>
<p>Finally, one thing that would improve the game (but would deviate quite a bit from the original game): giving Gordon enhancing bonuses. Sometimes, I find it very frustrating when I find a secret but I’m full of ammo (especially since the maximum amount of ammo is much lower in BM) or full HP and energy. I have no need of that secret then. So, why not putting some rare bonuses in some secret areas? These would be items that improve weapons or the HEV suit. For example:</p>
<ul>
<li>A new helmet with a scope, to allow zooming (which wouldn’t be a feature that Gordon originally has, of course)</li>
<li>A bonus to slightly increase the time under water without dying</li>
<li>A bonus to increase the speed of healing / recharging energy from the machines</li>
<li>A bonus to slightly reduce damage from radiactive sources</li>
<li>A laser, to help aiming with the Magnum</li>
<li>A bonus to increase the flashlight durability, effectiveness, range…</li>
<li>Etc!<br>
These bonuses wouldn’t be absolutely necessary to complete the game, but they would be a pleasant addition and would bring more interest to some supply caches.</li>
</ul>
<p>To conclude, I am wondering what the devs have in mind for the time after Xen is released. Will they just drop the game? Add new details? Improve the overall graphics quality? Add new game content? Would they consider using some content made by modders?<br>
For example, I would love to have more rooms to visit, more secrets, puzzles and traps, some alternative routes to choose… Anyway, it would be great that earthbound levels were improved, so the game is more faithful to the original HL (nostalgia brought so many of us here!) and, at the same time, so the game has more features, more original content, allowing the team to express their own creativity.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/earthbound-chit-chat-thread/61975/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/earthbound-chit-chat-thread/61975/8</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 05 Jan 2019 22:27:06 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-61975-8</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/earthbound-chit-chat-thread/61975.rss">Earthbound Chit-Chat Thread</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Earthbound Chit-Chat Thread</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Ronster]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I was directed here by Darkone.</p>
<p>Pretty much agree with what has been said also especially in terms of weapon introduction. On a rail expainsion and We Got hostilea Surface Tension also. We got hostiles outdoor area needs visual update for skybox and ciffs and background.<br>
office Complex that air duct Fan Room needs update also.</p>
<p>It would be great to have the parts missing put into game including Hazzard course. Although I agree with remix and remaster rather than straight up remake.</p>
<p>I always felt Questionable ethics needed a Earth Garden like botanical garden under glass roof just for aesthetics to break up the constant industrialness.</p>
<p>scientist pulled through crack in the wall is a missing scene.<br>
Alien Grunt pulling open doors should be put back to original placement.<br>
Forget about Freeman blowing doors open with the Tank turret under player control.<br>
Tentacle in the desert.<br>
There is also a unit which I think should appear before taking the lift down into Lambda core - Mini-Gun armoured HECU Boss fight well he is just dangerous.<img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=9" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
<p>That is it really but most of these things already have base maps uncut and other mods so it should not be too much to attempt.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/earthbound-chit-chat-thread/61975/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/earthbound-chit-chat-thread/61975/7</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 10 Dec 2018 06:51:18 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-61975-7</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/earthbound-chit-chat-thread/61975.rss">Earthbound Chit-Chat Thread</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Earthbound Chit-Chat Thread</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[darkone]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="9seed" data-post="5" data-topic="61975">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/user_avatar/leakfree.org/9seed/40/4371_2.png" class="avatar"> 9seed:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>You can quote a post by highlighting part of it and clicking the quote button.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>oh cool thanks. Also apparently there is a 20 character min for these forums now <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/frowning.png?v=9" title=":frowning:" class="emoji" alt=":frowning:"> And I can’t disable emojies.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/earthbound-chit-chat-thread/61975/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/earthbound-chit-chat-thread/61975/6</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 10 Dec 2018 02:58:57 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-61975-6</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/earthbound-chit-chat-thread/61975.rss">Earthbound Chit-Chat Thread</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Earthbound Chit-Chat Thread</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[9seed]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="darkone" data-post="4" data-topic="61975">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/user_avatar/leakfree.org/darkone/40/4296_2.png" class="avatar"> darkone:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Ok no clue how to quote with the new forms.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>You can quote a post by highlighting part of it and clicking the quote button.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/earthbound-chit-chat-thread/61975/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/earthbound-chit-chat-thread/61975/5</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 10 Dec 2018 00:36:03 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-61975-5</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/earthbound-chit-chat-thread/61975.rss">Earthbound Chit-Chat Thread</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Earthbound Chit-Chat Thread</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[darkone]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Ok no clue how to quote with the new forms. But I agree its new form clashes a lot and yeah the A2 uncut map would work well really well actually easy to splice in… well not really splice it would have to be re imagined to fit, but it would fit.</p>
<p>IT also has a place where military C4 can be introduced as we only see that used in the uncut part of surface tension. With a few props of it in tunnels.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/earthbound-chit-chat-thread/61975/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/earthbound-chit-chat-thread/61975/4</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 09 Dec 2018 23:36:46 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-61975-4</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/earthbound-chit-chat-thread/61975.rss">Earthbound Chit-Chat Thread</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Earthbound Chit-Chat Thread</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[KCKI113R]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="darkone" data-post="2" data-topic="61975">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/user_avatar/leakfree.org/darkone/40/4296_2.png" class="avatar"> darkone:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Another thing I think they need to do is add some more to on a rail not make it a long ass maze like it was before but add a single new map that just makes it feel like a trip.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I feel like an adaptation of the A2 map from Uncut would serve this perfectly. It’s not a sprawling maze, nor is it a linear rail section, and it gives an interesting alternative take on the office sections. Right now, the design of the chapter totally clashes with the narrative purpose it is supposed to serve, being a journey to launch the rocket. Certainly doesn’t feel like much of a journey in its current state.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/earthbound-chit-chat-thread/61975/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/earthbound-chit-chat-thread/61975/3</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 22:10:36 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-61975-3</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/earthbound-chit-chat-thread/61975.rss">Earthbound Chit-Chat Thread</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Earthbound Chit-Chat Thread</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[darkone]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I would like a small restructure of the vent maze that was in we got hostiles. I miss that. Sure the main path should be easy and all that. But there should be a few side paths that lead to goodies.</p>
<p>That and fixing the fact that the shotgun is gained by killing a soldier first, it should be in that armory that you get it as we have a good level to learn the pros and cons of the mp5 annoying to have to juggle both game play wise.</p>
<p>They also really need to add a distinguishing factor between shotgun soldiers and normal. Like Maybe give the shotgun soldiers a ballistic mask with orange reflective eye holes, something minor that makes sense to help make the shotgunners stand out. Cause even half life two had to go back and fix that.</p>
<p>Another thing I think they need to do is add some more to on a rail not make it a long ass maze like it was before but add a single new map that just makes it feel like a trip. Also I miss that rocket launcher in the tunnel scene where they miss. IT could easily be done with a small above ground area or something.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/earthbound-chit-chat-thread/61975/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/earthbound-chit-chat-thread/61975/2</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 20:14:29 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-61975-2</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/earthbound-chit-chat-thread/61975.rss">Earthbound Chit-Chat Thread</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Earthbound Chit-Chat Thread</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[KCKI113R]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><em><em>NOTE</em>: With the potential for the first 14 chapters to receive another pass following Xen’s release, I thought it might be a good idea to create this thread as a companion to the Xen Chit-chat thread. This is simply meant to be a discussion of the current shortcomings of the Earthbound levels, and how certain aspects of them could be improved. Though it has been suggested by the developers multiple times as a potential future project, there is no guarantee that it will happen. My hope is that this thread can be a source of ongoing discussion and generate realistic, well-articulated ideas that could be used as some kind of reference were anything along these lines to occur.</em></p>
<p>Since the release of the mod back in 2012, there have been a number of improvements made to the Earthbound levels, be it through updated assets, as a side effect of engine improvements, or most obviously the expansion of Surface Tension. However, when viewing the released Xen media and comparing Surface Tension Uncut’s maps to the rest of the game, there is a clear disparity in quality even with said enhancements. This isn’t to say that the existing levels don’t hold up, as they still look excellent in many ways, however their design and visual fidelity are clearly not on the same level. This is to be expected when a project has a development cycle as long as Black Mesa’s, with some of these maps (in some similar form) dating back to far earlier builds of the game.</p>
<p>My question to the community is: What kind of (realistic in scope) changes would you make to the first 14 chapters in order to bring them up to this much higher standard? They can be as specific as a model/texture/effect/etc. improvement, or as broad as changes to the design of a level to facilitate better gameplay or atmosphere.</p>
<p>I will give an example: I have never found that the Anomalous Materials labs give the impression of a real worked-in environment due to its extremely strict linearity. Past the meta-remake-commentary room, the sequence more or less follows a series of hallways directly connected to one another with little deviation or even a hint of alternate paths, making it seem that much of Sector C lies along a singular hallway rather than part of a sprawling complex. Were adjacent hallways/rooms/elevators/etc. to be added at various points along the route to the test chamber simply as visual indicators of a much larger Sector C (which the player would be unable to access), it would lend a better sense of expansiveness and realism to the environment that just isn’t present at the moment.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/earthbound-chit-chat-thread/61975/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/earthbound-chit-chat-thread/61975/1</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 13:00:18 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-61975-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/earthbound-chit-chat-thread/61975.rss">Earthbound Chit-Chat Thread</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
