<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Linux issues</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/linux-issues/14967</link>
    <description>So first thing&#39;s first, thank you for the continuous development of BM. I was very pleasantly surprised that I finally needn&#39;t booting to Windows anymore to play the game.

So far I&#39;m mostly enjoying the run. There are, however, two issues I&#39;d like to point out. I&#39;m focusing on &quot;retail&quot; (Steam - &quot;opt out of beta&quot;) release as, for most part even cu3 had them when I tried them.

Bug #1: I noticed it&#39;s been mentioned before but I&#39;m not sure if this is the same bug - and it is player being stuck to non-horizontal/curved surfaces, like pipes, ledges or ramps. Most notable/annoying are bm_c1a4* (where you can get stuck that only reloading from save helps - but only if you haven&#39;t save WHILE being stuck), c2a2* (makes jumping on tracks very tedious, and often causes the player to be thrown out of the &quot;locomotive&quot;). Nothing is thrown on the console.

Bug #2: Vortigaunts throw bolts everywhere but you (even commit suicide) - this usually gets fixed by saving and reloading.
Bug #2b: on reload, certain NPC enemies &quot;forget&quot; where you were if you are not in line of sight - and therefore are easy to kill.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2016 20:40:10 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>In-game Issues</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/linux-issues/14967.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Linux issues</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[tremby]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="ItsMeOnly">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/i/ba9def/40.png" class="avatar"> ItsMeOnly:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Bug <span class="hashtag">#1:</span> I noticed it’s been mentioned before but I’m not sure if this is the same bug - and it is player being stuck to non-horizontal/curved surfaces, like pipes, ledges or ramps. Most notable/annoying are bm_c1a4* (where you can get stuck that only reloading from save helps - but only if you haven’t save WHILE being stuck), c2a2* (makes jumping on tracks very tedious, and often causes the player to be thrown out of the “locomotive”). Nothing is thrown on the console.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I’ve come up against this multiple times too.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/linux-issues/14967/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/linux-issues/14967/2</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2016 20:40:10 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14967-2</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/linux-issues/14967.rss">Linux issues</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Linux issues</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[ItsMeOnly]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>So first thing’s first, thank you for the continuous development of BM. I was very pleasantly surprised that I finally needn’t booting to Windows anymore to play the game.</p>
<p>So far I’m mostly enjoying the run. There are, however, two issues I’d like to point out. I’m focusing on “retail” (Steam - “opt out of beta”) release as, for most part even cu3 had them when I tried them.</p>
<p>Bug <span class="hashtag">#1:</span> I noticed it’s been mentioned before but I’m not sure if this is the same bug - and it is player being stuck to non-horizontal/curved surfaces, like pipes, ledges or ramps. Most notable/annoying are bm_c1a4* (where you can get stuck that only reloading from save helps - but only if you haven’t save WHILE being stuck), c2a2* (makes jumping on tracks very tedious, and often causes the player to be thrown out of the “locomotive”). Nothing is thrown on the console.</p>
<p>Bug <span class="hashtag">#2:</span> Vortigaunts throw bolts everywhere but you (even commit suicide) - this usually gets fixed by saving and reloading.<br>
Bug <span class="hashtag">#2b:</span> on reload, certain NPC enemies “forget” where you were if you are not in line of sight - and therefore are easy to kill.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/linux-issues/14967/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/linux-issues/14967/1</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2016 21:39:46 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14967-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/linux-issues/14967.rss">Linux issues</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
