<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Attack after movement</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/attack-after-movement/15036</link>
    <description>I have noticed that I cannot use the left mouse button to attack after I have been moving or are moving when using the keyboard. The first press of the left mouse button does nothing, the second press works fine. Subsequent presses of the left mouse button do attack, but once I move using the W,S,A,D keys, I cannot get attack to work. If I hold down the left and right mouse buttons and move at the same time I can keep the crowbar attacking all the time the two mouse buttons are held. I wondered why I was dying so quickly!

In addition, navigating the main menu to save a game using the keyboard results in the game not accepting input until the escape key is pressed, then two lots of the &quot;overwrite game&quot; dialogs appear. Sometimes the navigation of the main menu is then corrupted where multiple menu items can be highlighted at once and pressing enter causes the multiplayer server setup window to appear in the game.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 30 Dec 2016 14:23:27 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>In-game Issues</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/attack-after-movement/15036.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Attack after movement</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[LordDz]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>This sounds more of an issue on your part than the game.</p>
<p>Are you perhaps using an old keyboard / mouse?<br>
Old drivers? Anything that can take over the input of the game?<br>
Does this happen in other games too?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/attack-after-movement/15036/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/attack-after-movement/15036/2</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 30 Dec 2016 14:23:27 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-15036-2</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/attack-after-movement/15036.rss">Attack after movement</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Attack after movement</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[bouncingboffin]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I have noticed that I cannot use the left mouse button to attack after I have been moving or are moving when using the keyboard. The first press of the left mouse button does nothing, the second press works fine. Subsequent presses of the left mouse button do attack, but once I move using the W,S,A,D keys, I cannot get attack to work. If I hold down the left and right mouse buttons and move at the same time I can keep the crowbar attacking all the time the two mouse buttons are held. I wondered why I was dying so quickly!</p>
<p>In addition, navigating the main menu to save a game using the keyboard results in the game not accepting input until the escape key is pressed, then two lots of the “overwrite game” dialogs appear. Sometimes the navigation of the main menu is then corrupted where multiple menu items can be highlighted at once and pressing enter causes the multiplayer server setup window to appear in the game.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/attack-after-movement/15036/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/attack-after-movement/15036/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 24 Dec 2016 01:33:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-15036-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/attack-after-movement/15036.rss">Attack after movement</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
