<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>How do I replace sounds?</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/how-do-i-replace-sounds/14044</link>
    <description>Hi, I&#39;m relatively new to the modding scene as far as Half Life 2/Source goes...

I played the game and loved it, but I prefered the feel of the original Half Life soundtrack... I wanted to replace the music, and followed various guides on valve&#39;s &quot;how to VPK&quot; or &quot;how to replace sounds&quot; but keep getting stuck

I have all the files ready to replace in OGG format and they are right down to the name of the music files in the VPKs but no matter where I put them, be it the steamapps\common\black mesa\bms\sound directory (in their respective music folder) or even creating a custom folder where they could work.

Am I missing something? If anybody could help me out here, I&#39;d really appreciate it


(BTW, sorry if I got the wrong area to post this in, I assumed this was the correct one since this isn&#39;t an issue of the regular game not working on its own)

[u][b]EDIT:[/b][/u] Problem solved, apparently I wasn&#39;t using the VPK exe file right and my folder was supposed to me named &quot;addons&quot;</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 12 Jul 2015 20:29:18 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Black Mesa</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/how-do-i-replace-sounds/14044.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>How do I replace sounds?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Admiral_Sakai]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Currently, the file-replace system is extremely buggy, and may or may not work for any given asset or script. There is not a <span class="bbcode-i">lot</span> you can do about it other than wait for developer fixes, but hopefully since they were extremely prompt in releasing VMFs when asked about it, that shouldn’t take incredibly long.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/how-do-i-replace-sounds/14044/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/how-do-i-replace-sounds/14044/4</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jul 2015 20:29:18 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14044-4</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/how-do-i-replace-sounds/14044.rss">How do I replace sounds?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How do I replace sounds?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Aynekko]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Thes Jr.">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Thes Jr.:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I followed the exact procedure a dev told me in the Steam forums: In order to replace (for example) the Glock firing sound I should put the new sound file named single.wav in the bms/sound/weapons/glock folder, but it just won’t work. Does it have to be an .ogg, a .vpk, does it have to be a different folder? I just don’t get it <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/confused.png?v=9" title=":confused:" class="emoji" alt=":confused:"></p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Same here, it just doesn’t work. I extracted the files from VPK and put edited in the same folder (not inside the VPK), but as far as I know the files in the folders should override the ones in VPK. I wanted to try to rebuild audio cache from the console, but it just doesn’t have such command.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/how-do-i-replace-sounds/14044/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/how-do-i-replace-sounds/14044/3</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jul 2015 18:55:58 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14044-3</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/how-do-i-replace-sounds/14044.rss">How do I replace sounds?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How do I replace sounds?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Johnwalter]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I want to replace only the shotgun fire and reload sounds.<br>
But how do i do that?<br>
i see a bunch of VPK files and a sound cache file.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/how-do-i-replace-sounds/14044/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/how-do-i-replace-sounds/14044/2</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jun 2015 07:24:59 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14044-2</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/how-do-i-replace-sounds/14044.rss">How do I replace sounds?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How do I replace sounds?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[RageMaker]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Hi, I’m relatively new to the modding scene as far as Half Life 2/Source goes…</p>
<p>I played the game and loved it, but I prefered the feel of the original Half Life soundtrack… I wanted to replace the music, and followed various guides on valve’s “how to VPK” or “how to replace sounds” but keep getting stuck</p>
<p>I have all the files ready to replace in OGG format and they are right down to the name of the music files in the VPKs but no matter where I put them, be it the steamapps\common\black mesa\bms\sound directory (in their respective music folder) or even creating a custom folder where they could work.</p>
<p>Am I missing something? If anybody could help me out here, I’d really appreciate it</p>
<p>(BTW, sorry if I got the wrong area to post this in, I assumed this was the correct one since this isn’t an issue of the regular game not working on its own)</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-u"><span class="bbcode-b">EDIT:</span></span> Problem solved, apparently I wasn’t using the VPK exe file right and my folder was supposed to me named “addons”</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/how-do-i-replace-sounds/14044/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/how-do-i-replace-sounds/14044/1</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 May 2015 00:21:46 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14044-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/how-do-i-replace-sounds/14044.rss">How do I replace sounds?</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
