<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Surface Tension door glitch</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/surface-tension-door-glitch/10822</link>
    <description>Hello everyone!!

I noticed after I killed the gargantua that if I want to go back through the big bent door from where the alien came from, I can&#39;t. If you want to go through the giant hole that the gargantua made, you just can&#39;t pass (it&#39;s like the map ended there). Maybe the developers didn&#39;t want me to go back through the tunnel, but at least they must have put something on fire (like a military truck) to block my way, instead of leaving a huge opening which cannot be trespased. Here&#39;s the screenshot:

[img]https://cloud.steampowered.com/ugc/918989594544322795/4DB6C8F89D1FAA9E5DD350B20BFC382F0AA0183D/[/img]

I have some more bugs I will report later. Thanks for doing an excelent mod, maybe the best Half-Life 2 mod yet.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 19 Sep 2012 14:06:53 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>In-game Issues (Mod)</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/surface-tension-door-glitch/10822.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Surface Tension door glitch</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Holy_Crap]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Hello everyone!!</p>
<p>I noticed after I killed the gargantua that if I want to go back through the big bent door from where the alien came from, I can’t. If you want to go through the giant hole that the gargantua made, you just can’t pass (it’s like the map ended there). Maybe the developers didn’t want me to go back through the tunnel, but at least they must have put something on fire (like a military truck) to block my way, instead of leaving a huge opening which cannot be trespased. Here’s the screenshot:</p>
<p><span alt="" class="broken-image" title="This image is broken"><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-unlink svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#unlink"></use></svg></span></p>
<p>I have some more bugs I will report later. Thanks for doing an excelent mod, maybe the best Half-Life 2 mod yet.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/surface-tension-door-glitch/10822/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/surface-tension-door-glitch/10822/1</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 19 Sep 2012 14:06:53 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-10822-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/surface-tension-door-glitch/10822.rss">Surface Tension door glitch</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
