<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Buying a New Laptop</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/buying-a-new-laptop/12766</link>
    <description>So I&#39;m buying a new Laptop, planning to pick something up around Black Friday, hopefully on a good sale. I&#39;ll be using it for gaming and school, and I&#39;d rather have a 15 inch than a 17 inch, however portability is not a major concern and 17 inch is not a deal breaker. I&#39;ll be doing most of my gaming with a 2560x1440 screen as my primary, so being able to play games natively at that resolution is a must have, however I don&#39;t mind turning AA all the way off and dropping other settings to compensate. My budget is pretty wide, between 1000-2000, but preferably closer to around 1500. An SSD, preferably 128 gigs, with a secondary HDD is a must have. Outside of that I&#39;m not picky.

I&#39;m replacing an asus G55 which I had a very poor experience with, and the current G series laptops look really overpriced, so I&#39;d say they&#39;re off the table. Anyway, this is what I&#39;ve looked at in my research:

[url=&#39;https://www.ibuypower.com/Site/Valkyrie-Series&#39;]ibuypower[/url]
[url=&#39;https://www.newegg.com/Product/Product.aspx?Item=N82E16834198032&#39;]CyberpowerPC With 780m[/url]
[url=&#39;https://www.xoticpc.com/force-msi-1763-22001-780m-msi-gt70-barebones-p-5815.html&#39;]Sager with 780m[/url]
[url=&#39;https://www.xoticpc.com/force-msi-1763-22001-780m-msi-gt70-barebones-p-5815.html&#39;]MSI with 780M[/url]
[url=&#39;https://www.xoticpc.com/sager-np8235-clevo-p151sm1-p-5840.html&#39;]Sager with 770M[/url]

What do you guys think about these choices? Any other recommendations? I&#39;m feeling the 780m is probably overkill and I&#39;ll probably settle in the 770m price range. I&#39;ve heard some bad things about CyberpowerPC and Ibuypower so I&#39;m a little nervous to buy from them, but they seem to have the best prices. Except for perhaps that sager I put last on the list, that one looks pretty good and has a really low price point. Not to mention it&#39;s not absolutely garish like the Ibuypower/CyberpowerPC laptops.

Edit: Also found the [url=&#39;https://www.newegg.com/Product/Product.aspx?Item=N82E16834313584&#39;]Lenovo y510p[/url] which looks really powerful for the budget.

Edit2: [url=&#39;https://www.xoticpc.com/custom-gaming-laptops-notebooks-xotic-force-series-ct-95_51_245.html&#39;]These[/url] appear to be the best price per performance laptops with the 770 and 780, really tempted by that 780 model. Unfortunately I can&#39;t find too much info on the quality of these Xotic MSI Barebones models.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 17 Nov 2013 03:56:30 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Help and Support</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/buying-a-new-laptop/12766.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Buying a New Laptop</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Orpheon]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>My instinct would be to go with the Lenovo or the MSI, simply based on reputation/quality. Lenovo makes great laptops and MSI, while I don’t know much about their laptops in particular, generally makes good quality products. I do not know about ibuypower or CyberpowerPC, although I have heard of them at least. Sager I have never even heard of. But when in doubt, I just go by newegg and/or amazon reviews (if available). Never gotten a bum steer from them before.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/buying-a-new-laptop/12766/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/buying-a-new-laptop/12766/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 17 Nov 2013 03:56:30 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12766-2</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/buying-a-new-laptop/12766.rss">Buying a New Laptop</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Buying a New Laptop</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[garrthbarrttinn]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>So I’m buying a new Laptop, planning to pick something up around Black Friday, hopefully on a good sale. I’ll be using it for gaming and school, and I’d rather have a 15 inch than a 17 inch, however portability is not a major concern and 17 inch is not a deal breaker. I’ll be doing most of my gaming with a 2560x1440 screen as my primary, so being able to play games natively at that resolution is a must have, however I don’t mind turning AA all the way off and dropping other settings to compensate. My budget is pretty wide, between 1000-2000, but preferably closer to around 1500. An SSD, preferably 128 gigs, with a secondary HDD is a must have. Outside of that I’m not picky.</p>
<p>I’m replacing an asus G55 which I had a very poor experience with, and the current G series laptops look really overpriced, so I’d say they’re off the table. Anyway, this is what I’ve looked at in my research:</p>
<p><a href="https://www.ibuypower.com/Site/Valkyrie-Series" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">ibuypower</a><br>
<a href="https://www.newegg.com/Product/Product.aspx?Item=N82E16834198032" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">CyberpowerPC With 780m</a><br>
<a href="https://www.xoticpc.com/force-msi-1763-22001-780m-msi-gt70-barebones-p-5815.html" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Sager with 780m</a><br>
<a href="https://www.xoticpc.com/force-msi-1763-22001-780m-msi-gt70-barebones-p-5815.html" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">MSI with 780M</a><br>
<a href="https://www.xoticpc.com/sager-np8235-clevo-p151sm1-p-5840.html" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Sager with 770M</a></p>
<p>What do you guys think about these choices? Any other recommendations? I’m feeling the 780m is probably overkill and I’ll probably settle in the 770m price range. I’ve heard some bad things about CyberpowerPC and Ibuypower so I’m a little nervous to buy from them, but they seem to have the best prices. Except for perhaps that sager I put last on the list, that one looks pretty good and has a really low price point. Not to mention it’s not absolutely garish like the Ibuypower/CyberpowerPC laptops.</p>
<p>Edit: Also found the <a href="https://www.newegg.com/Product/Product.aspx?Item=N82E16834313584" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Lenovo y510p</a> which looks really powerful for the budget.</p>
<p>Edit2: <a href="https://www.xoticpc.com/custom-gaming-laptops-notebooks-xotic-force-series-ct-95_51_245.html" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">These</a> appear to be the best price per performance laptops with the 770 and 780, really tempted by that 780 model. Unfortunately I can’t find too much info on the quality of these Xotic MSI Barebones models.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/buying-a-new-laptop/12766/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/buying-a-new-laptop/12766/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 16 Nov 2013 23:14:50 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12766-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/buying-a-new-laptop/12766.rss">Buying a New Laptop</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
