<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>C1a2a = Hl2.exe not responding.</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/c1a2a-hl2-exe-not-responding/10226</link>
    <description>Hey guys, great game so far on what i&#39;ve played. I was making a lets play for this series and so far have only got one episode done. Now i&#39;m at the level thats named as c1a2a in my saves and for some reason every time i even tried moving to face the eletricity that was touching the water the game automatically crashed. Today i launched in the game in the hopes of it worked and this time i could see on the other end of the corridor and it was fine! Great i thought, now i can carry on making my lets play. So i get my fraps ready and audacity and starting recording. 

I get to the security guard who asks help to remove the headcrab that has got his friend, while his &#39;friend&#39; comes around the corner to kill him. The guard opens the gate once i killed the zombie and i make my way over the supplies. I turn around to head back out and i crash again! Dammit, now i wasted my time recording again. 

I know you guys have tons of other bugs to fix so i&#39;m in no hurry. Here&#39;s the file that is requested for glitches. I&#39;ll put one of the crash in the hall after getting out of elevator and one in the &#39;supply room&#39; that the guard opens.


1.
&lt;a class=&#39;attachment&#39; href=&#39;/uploads/default/original/2X/7/7788bec64e8299fdb520d08c0767b5722cdca079.mdmp&#39;&gt;hl2_4104_crash_2012_9_15T17_2_35C0.mdmp&lt;/a&gt; (92.1 KB)
&lt;a class=&#39;attachment&#39; href=&#39;/uploads/default/original/2X/6/6c9064a1157ff1fe5d632301e967369fd5eb41ea.mdmp&#39;&gt;hl2_4104_crash_2012_9_16T11_36_23C0.mdmp&lt;/a&gt; (93 KB)</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 16 Sep 2012 11:47:20 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>In-game Issues (Mod)</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/c1a2a-hl2-exe-not-responding/10226.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>C1a2a = Hl2.exe not responding.</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[MrPie]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Hey guys, great game so far on what i’ve played. I was making a lets play for this series and so far have only got one episode done. Now i’m at the level thats named as c1a2a in my saves and for some reason every time i even tried moving to face the eletricity that was touching the water the game automatically crashed. Today i launched in the game in the hopes of it worked and this time i could see on the other end of the corridor and it was fine! Great i thought, now i can carry on making my lets play. So i get my fraps ready and audacity and starting recording.</p>
<p>I get to the security guard who asks help to remove the headcrab that has got his friend, while his ‘friend’ comes around the corner to kill him. The guard opens the gate once i killed the zombie and i make my way over the supplies. I turn around to head back out and i crash again! Dammit, now i wasted my time recording again.</p>
<p>I know you guys have tons of other bugs to fix so i’m in no hurry. Here’s the file that is requested for glitches. I’ll put one of the crash in the hall after getting out of elevator and one in the ‘supply room’ that the guard opens.</p>
<ol>
<li>
</li></ol>
<p><a class="attachment" href="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/original/2X/7/7788bec64e8299fdb520d08c0767b5722cdca079.mdmp">hl2_4104_crash_2012_9_15T17_2_35C0.mdmp</a> (92.1 KB)<br>
<a class="attachment" href="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/original/2X/6/6c9064a1157ff1fe5d632301e967369fd5eb41ea.mdmp">hl2_4104_crash_2012_9_16T11_36_23C0.mdmp</a> (93 KB)</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/c1a2a-hl2-exe-not-responding/10226/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/c1a2a-hl2-exe-not-responding/10226/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 16 Sep 2012 11:47:20 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-10226-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/c1a2a-hl2-exe-not-responding/10226.rss">C1a2a = Hl2.exe not responding.</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
