<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Network Interface Issues</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/network-interface-issues/5992</link>
    <description>I got one for you guys to solve:

When I got my old computer, I put a wireless card in it due to being far from our internet modem in the house, so I never really had to use the onboard NIC before, but now with the new machine, I&#39;m trying to set it up as a movie / music / everything / Minecraft server. The only problem is that the onboard NIC will not link with the router. It will not link directly with the modem either.

Funny thing is, the router and modem show activity on the port that I connect it to, but the computer will not create a link. I plug the same patch cord in my laptop and there is an instant connection.

So, I updated drivers, installed Windows XP and Windows 7 multiple times, nothing. I could not get it to work. The closest I could get was a limited or no connectivity icon.

The next thing I tried was buying a cheap D-Link gigabit PCI NIC to put in it. That all went fine, installed drivers, no link. It shows that it&#39;s connected at 100 Mbs Full Duplex, but no data link. So, install Windows 7 and use it&#39;s built in drivers for the card. Still no dice.

Anyways, I think it&#39;s weird, I&#39;m suspecting that it might be some controller on the motherboard that I have neglected to install drivers for or it&#39;s screwed, which controls all network activity on the system (doesn&#39;t really make sense since a wireless card works fine).

Mobo: Biostar M7NCG, nForce2 chipset (old as balls), nForce Networking Controller is what comes up as installed properly in the Device Manager.

PCI card: D-Link DGE-530T (also installs successfully as advertised)

Any ideas?</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 10 Dec 2010 14:10:41 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Help and Support</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/network-interface-issues/5992.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Network Interface Issues</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[MaxTheLimit]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Does statically assigning your IP to one in the range of your router, and setting the DNS servers to something like open DNS’s free DNS server addresses have any impact?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/network-interface-issues/5992/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/network-interface-issues/5992/4</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Dec 2010 14:10:41 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-5992-4</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/network-interface-issues/5992.rss">Network Interface Issues</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Network Interface Issues</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Cameron_D]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Check that you are not manually setting the IP/DNS, let your router DHCP sort that out. (Unless of course you can confirm that the manual settings are correct)</p>
<p>EDIT: Oh never mind, read that you reinstalled OS</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/network-interface-issues/5992/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/network-interface-issues/5992/3</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Dec 2010 12:18:07 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-5992-3</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/network-interface-issues/5992.rss">Network Interface Issues</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Network Interface Issues</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[jerry]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Try using Ubuntu Server  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/wink.png?v=9" title=":wink:" class="emoji" alt=":wink:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/network-interface-issues/5992/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/network-interface-issues/5992/2</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Dec 2010 10:51:19 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-5992-2</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/network-interface-issues/5992.rss">Network Interface Issues</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Network Interface Issues</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[sudpuzzer]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I got one for you guys to solve:</p>
<p>When I got my old computer, I put a wireless card in it due to being far from our internet modem in the house, so I never really had to use the onboard NIC before, but now with the new machine, I’m trying to set it up as a movie / music / everything / Minecraft server. The only problem is that the onboard NIC will not link with the router. It will not link directly with the modem either.</p>
<p>Funny thing is, the router and modem show activity on the port that I connect it to, but the computer will not create a link. I plug the same patch cord in my laptop and there is an instant connection.</p>
<p>So, I updated drivers, installed Windows XP and Windows 7 multiple times, nothing. I could not get it to work. The closest I could get was a limited or no connectivity icon.</p>
<p>The next thing I tried was buying a cheap D-Link gigabit PCI NIC to put in it. That all went fine, installed drivers, no link. It shows that it’s connected at 100 Mbs Full Duplex, but no data link. So, install Windows 7 and use it’s built in drivers for the card. Still no dice.</p>
<p>Anyways, I think it’s weird, I’m suspecting that it might be some controller on the motherboard that I have neglected to install drivers for or it’s screwed, which controls all network activity on the system (doesn’t really make sense since a wireless card works fine).</p>
<p>Mobo: Biostar M7NCG, nForce2 chipset (old as balls), nForce Networking Controller is what comes up as installed properly in the Device Manager.</p>
<p>PCI card: D-Link DGE-530T (also installs successfully as advertised)</p>
<p>Any ideas?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/network-interface-issues/5992/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/network-interface-issues/5992/1</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Dec 2010 04:35:30 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-5992-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/network-interface-issues/5992.rss">Network Interface Issues</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
