<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>NPC Bug: Marines are &quot;good&quot; at throwing frags over railing</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/npc-bug-marines-are-good-at-throwing-frags-over-railing/14533</link>
    <description>So I just bought this game, and I have to say, these marines are really pro at throwing grenades-- they keep throwing grenades over railings towards me, only to have it hit the railing they&#39;re trying to throw it over, which makes it rebound off said railing and (usually) land next to the guy who threw it. They don&#39;t even try to run away from their own grenade, they just let it detonate next to them. Surprisingly their own grenade doesnt do any damage to them though, or they&#39;d all be dead by now because they can&#39;t throw grenades worth crud apparently.

Marines 2 pro for me

Other than that, really good Marine AI.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 25 Dec 2015 18:04:07 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>In-game Issues</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/npc-bug-marines-are-good-at-throwing-frags-over-railing/14533.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>NPC Bug: Marines are &quot;good&quot; at throwing frags over railing</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Coolz]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>So I just bought this game, and I have to say, these marines are really pro at throwing grenades-- they keep throwing grenades over railings towards me, only to have it hit the railing they’re trying to throw it over, which makes it rebound off said railing and (usually) land next to the guy who threw it. They don’t even try to run away from their own grenade, they just let it detonate next to them. Surprisingly their own grenade doesnt do any damage to them though, or they’d all be dead by now because they can’t throw grenades worth crud apparently.</p>
<p>Marines 2 pro for me</p>
<p>Other than that, really good Marine AI.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/npc-bug-marines-are-good-at-throwing-frags-over-railing/14533/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/npc-bug-marines-are-good-at-throwing-frags-over-railing/14533/1</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Dec 2015 18:04:07 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14533-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/npc-bug-marines-are-good-at-throwing-frags-over-railing/14533.rss">NPC Bug: Marines are &quot;good&quot; at throwing frags over railing</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
