<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Can&#39;t access email acount</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/cant-access-email-acount/13326</link>
    <description>Somebody tried to get into my email adress on outlook.com and now my account is blocked and I&#39;ve tried to get my account reset but I don&#39;t know my security question or my password. I also contacted them with another email adress and gave them as much information about my account as possible and they still won&#39;t reset my account. I&#39;m at my wits end what should I do? I also received an email saying they won&#39;t reset my account because I didn&#39;t give enough information but the amount of information I gave is something only the user would know wtf? What should I do now?</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 29 Jun 2014 19:08:05 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Help!</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/cant-access-email-acount/13326.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Can&#39;t access email acount</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[coldroll]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Somebody tried to get into my email adress on <a href="http://outlook.com" rel="nofollow noopener">outlook.com</a> and now my account is blocked and I’ve tried to get my account reset but I don’t know my security question or my password. I also contacted them with another email adress and gave them as much information about my account as possible and they still won’t reset my account. I’m at my wits end what should I do? I also received an email saying they won’t reset my account because I didn’t give enough information but the amount of information I gave is something only the user would know wtf? What should I do now?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/cant-access-email-acount/13326/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/cant-access-email-acount/13326/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 29 Jun 2014 19:08:05 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13326-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/cant-access-email-acount/13326.rss">Can&#39;t access email acount</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
