<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crash on touching Icthyosaur in Forget About Freeman</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/crash-on-touching-icthyosaur-in-forget-about-freeman/15142</link>
    <description>This is my first time posting a crash report, fingers crossed I&#39;m not missing any details. I also looked back a couple pages in the forum to make sure this hasn&#39;t been reported recently.
In the sewer area right at the start of Forget About Freeman, I experienced a crash while attempting the Nuclear Fishin&#39; achievement on the Icthyosaur in the water. It happened right as the Icthyosaur attacked me for the second time while I was charging the Tau cannon.

This engine error window appeared upon crashing.
[img]https://image.prntscr.com/image/a3b183d756d84fd58df36a2cd74edbd5.png[/img]

[url=&#39;https://www.mediafire.com/?iiwwbpejikimma4&#39;]And here&#39;s the crash report dump.[/url] I hope Mediafire is acceptable.
[s]I&#39;ll be back later and update if I&#39;m able to replicate the crash.[/s]
[s][/s]
I was unable to replicate it, strangely. The exact map is bm_c3a1a if you still plan on investigating.
Fun fact: I actually unlocked the Nuclear Fishin&#39; achievement at the exact moment of the crash.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 06 Apr 2017 01:01:24 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>In-game Issues</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/crash-on-touching-icthyosaur-in-forget-about-freeman/15142.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Crash on touching Icthyosaur in Forget About Freeman</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crawfish]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>This is my first time posting a crash report, fingers crossed I’m not missing any details. I also looked back a couple pages in the forum to make sure this hasn’t been reported recently.<br>
In the sewer area right at the start of Forget About Freeman, I experienced a crash while attempting the Nuclear Fishin’ achievement on the Icthyosaur in the water. It happened right as the Icthyosaur attacked me for the second time while I was charging the Tau cannon.</p>
<p>This engine error window appeared upon crashing.<br>
<img src="https://image.prntscr.com/image/a3b183d756d84fd58df36a2cd74edbd5.png" alt="" width="481" height="188"></p>
<p><a href="https://www.mediafire.com/?iiwwbpejikimma4" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">And here’s the crash report dump.</a> I hope Mediafire is acceptable.<br>
<span class="bbcode-s">I’ll be back later and update if I’m able to replicate the crash.</span><br>
<span class="bbcode-s"></span><br>
I was unable to replicate it, strangely. The exact map is bm_c3a1a if you still plan on investigating.<br>
Fun fact: I actually unlocked the Nuclear Fishin’ achievement at the exact moment of the crash.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/crash-on-touching-icthyosaur-in-forget-about-freeman/15142/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/crash-on-touching-icthyosaur-in-forget-about-freeman/15142/1</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 06 Apr 2017 01:01:24 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-15142-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/crash-on-touching-icthyosaur-in-forget-about-freeman/15142.rss">Crash on touching Icthyosaur in Forget About Freeman</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
