<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>wipEout 2048 and HD/Fury DLC?</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/wipeout-2048-and-hd-fury-dlc/8640</link>
    <description>(I believe this is the right place to post this...)
Wipeout 2048 is an amazing game. My only complaints are that the graphics are a bit too complex for the framerate, and controls aren&#39;t tight enough. I suppose the latter makes sense since it&#39;s supposed to be the early days of anti-gravity racing.

As far as I can tell, Wipeout HD and Fury going to be released in the Spring (so some time soon) on the Vita as DLC. It will allow for cross play between the two systems. I&#39;ve already had a taste of this on the limited cross play content included with the game- it&#39;s delicious! I&#39;m just really happy there will be seconds.  :slight_smile: 

I don&#39;t have a PS3, but I like Sony&#39;s &quot;buy it on one system and get it free on another&quot; approach. Even though I will have to pay for the DLC, I don&#39;t mind it, and I&#39;ve really wanted to play Wipeout HD for a long time. What bugs me is that I can&#39;t find anymore info on this.

I&#39;d really like to know when they will release the DLC and how much it will cost. Wipeout HD is 20 dollars, right? I&#39;m guessing it will be the same on the Vita. I&#39;m sold anyway, but I can&#39;t find info on a release date- it seems they haven&#39;t mentioned except &quot;this Spring.&quot; Well, it&#39;s Spring right now, so I would think they would give us a heads up at one point.

Does anyone have more information?</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 19 Apr 2012 15:35:27 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Technology and Gaming</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/wipeout-2048-and-hd-fury-dlc/8640.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>wipEout 2048 and HD/Fury DLC?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[somewhere_in_new_mex]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>If they are going to release it in the spring, I’d expect them to announce it in the spring. Right? They ought to at least let us know its on the way- even if they don’t have a release date. Sony, tell us you’re preparing it. Give us <span class="bbcode-i">something.</span></p>
<p>Unless of course, Sony’s banking on some sales made due to eager fans waiting with great anticipation for their game to be released. I just hope this trend doesn’t become the norm (cough, cough, valve, HL3/EP3, cough cough). Oh, excuse me, I just had to clear my throat for a second. Anyway, has anyone heard anything yet? Is everyone as uninformed about this as I am? Anyone have a friend or relative working at Studio Liverpool? Is there some weird software bug that they can’t pinpoint or fix and it’s driving them mad? Is it some kind of stupid licensing problem? Did someone spill coffee on the backup drives at the office?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/wipeout-2048-and-hd-fury-dlc/8640/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/wipeout-2048-and-hd-fury-dlc/8640/6</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 19 Apr 2012 15:35:27 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8640-6</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/wipeout-2048-and-hd-fury-dlc/8640.rss">wipEout 2048 and HD/Fury DLC?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>wipEout 2048 and HD/Fury DLC?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[BahamutBBob]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>On a side note, trying to unlock the Feisar prototype, I realize how bad my line is on Empire Climb.  (Feisar prototype is slow, but it’s top speed increases every time you hit a boost pad, and resets on crashing or starting a new lap)</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/wipeout-2048-and-hd-fury-dlc/8640/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/wipeout-2048-and-hd-fury-dlc/8640/5</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 10 Apr 2012 14:33:43 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8640-5</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/wipeout-2048-and-hd-fury-dlc/8640.rss">wipEout 2048 and HD/Fury DLC?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>wipEout 2048 and HD/Fury DLC?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[somewhere_in_new_mex]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="k3nny1550">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/user_avatar/leakfree.org/k3nny1550/40/4952_2.png" class="avatar"> k3nny1550:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I’ve had Wipeout HD+Fury for a while- damn fun game. The real question with the cross-platform is how they’ll compensate for the reduced Vita framerate- WO2048 runs at 30fps, while HD+Fury is a flat 60fps.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Like I said, they’ve already worked it out. The courses, even though they are a bit scaled down, look stunning! I’ve tried the four included courses.</p>
<p>Remember, Wipeout HD’s courses were taken from the PSP. I had a PSP (the screen broke… I’ve got to replace it at one point…) and Wipeout Pure was a ton of fun. It’s going to be cool to play some of those tracks on the Vita (in far greater detail). History repeating can be a good thing…</p>
<p>Wipeout 2048 is a great game, but as I said the controls are a bit loose. It will be nice to have some more traditional content with tight controls, a more futuristic environment, and courses which are more colorful. There’s nothing wrong with the graphics in 2048, but I need some variety!</p>
<p>Thank you Sony! Just give me a release date!</p>
<p>And announce a flight simulation game for the Vita! Ace Combat or something! Or maybe even a more traditional sim like FSX or X-plane! Imagine that on the Vita!<br>
Hey Valve- <span class="bbcode-i">I’d pay you</span> for Vita ports of HL2, EP1, EP2, and Portal 1 @ 2. I know you guys are all about the PC and home consoles- this is a portable home console! Orange Box Vita!!!<br>
[/SIZE]</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/wipeout-2048-and-hd-fury-dlc/8640/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/wipeout-2048-and-hd-fury-dlc/8640/4</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 08 Apr 2012 02:25:10 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8640-4</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/wipeout-2048-and-hd-fury-dlc/8640.rss">wipEout 2048 and HD/Fury DLC?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>wipEout 2048 and HD/Fury DLC?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[k3nny1550]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I’ve had Wipeout HD+Fury for a while- damn fun game. The real question with the cross-platform is how they’ll compensate for the reduced Vita framerate- WO2048 runs at 30fps, while HD+Fury is a flat 60fps.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/wipeout-2048-and-hd-fury-dlc/8640/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/wipeout-2048-and-hd-fury-dlc/8640/3</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 06 Apr 2012 07:11:37 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8640-3</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/wipeout-2048-and-hd-fury-dlc/8640.rss">wipEout 2048 and HD/Fury DLC?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>wipEout 2048 and HD/Fury DLC?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[BahamutBBob]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>It depends on where you live.  As far as I can tell, WipeOut HD disappeared from the US PSN store shortly after it was free for PS+ members. (didn’t bother me because I already owned it)</p>
<p>I think you’re right about the price, $20 for HD, and $10 for Fury.  I got Fury, but haven’t played it much.  It does add a lot of content to HD, though, since HD just had the eight tracks they remastered from Pure and Pulse.</p>
<p>If they stick with the “buy it once” thing for this, looks like I’ll be getting some free DLC for 2048  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=9" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"></p>
<p>I haven’t played 2048 too much yet, but that’s because I’ve been distracted both by other Vita games, and by other stuff IRL.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/wipeout-2048-and-hd-fury-dlc/8640/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/wipeout-2048-and-hd-fury-dlc/8640/2</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 06 Apr 2012 04:24:49 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8640-2</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/wipeout-2048-and-hd-fury-dlc/8640.rss">wipEout 2048 and HD/Fury DLC?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>wipEout 2048 and HD/Fury DLC?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[somewhere_in_new_mex]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>(I believe this is the right place to post this…)<br>
Wipeout 2048 is an amazing game. My only complaints are that the graphics are a bit too complex for the framerate, and controls aren’t tight enough. I suppose the latter makes sense since it’s supposed to be the early days of anti-gravity racing.</p>
<p>As far as I can tell, Wipeout HD and Fury going to be released in the Spring (so some time soon) on the Vita as DLC. It will allow for cross play between the two systems. I’ve already had a taste of this on the limited cross play content included with the game- it’s delicious! I’m just really happy there will be seconds.  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=9" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
<p>I don’t have a PS3, but I like Sony’s “buy it on one system and get it free on another” approach. Even though I will have to pay for the DLC, I don’t mind it, and I’ve really wanted to play Wipeout HD for a long time. What bugs me is that I can’t find anymore info on this.</p>
<p>I’d really like to know when they will release the DLC and how much it will cost. Wipeout HD is 20 dollars, right? I’m guessing it will be the same on the Vita. I’m sold anyway, but I can’t find info on a release date- it seems they haven’t mentioned except “this Spring.” Well, it’s Spring right now, so I would think they would give us a heads up at one point.</p>
<p>Does anyone have more information?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/wipeout-2048-and-hd-fury-dlc/8640/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/wipeout-2048-and-hd-fury-dlc/8640/1</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 05 Apr 2012 18:13:24 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8640-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/wipeout-2048-and-hd-fury-dlc/8640.rss">wipEout 2048 and HD/Fury DLC?</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
