<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>DayZ Standalone - Hold on to your cans</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/dayz-standalone-hold-on-to-your-cans/12920</link>
    <description>For the life of me, I thought we had an official thread on DayZ. Maybe it was before the forum reset.

Anyway, who here bought this game? I find it much better than the mod in its early alpha state and I even have fun just walking around looking for stuff.

Just this morning I was playing with Jack Freeman and samzala, trying to finding each other. I and Jack eventually found each other. We were both fucked up and seeing the world in monochrome, trying to find something sharp to open our cans of food. At some point my character succumbed to starvation and could only crawl around, so we decided it was better to kill ourselves. So we did.

When we respawned somewhere else, the first thing we found was a can opener.

That&#39;s DayZ for ya.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 01 Feb 2014 20:26:38 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Technology and Gaming</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/dayz-standalone-hold-on-to-your-cans/12920.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>DayZ Standalone - Hold on to your cans</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[samzala]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Firefights are intense. Too bad most of the time whoever is getting shot at doesn’t get to shoot back but anyway.<br>
Group of three people made contact with some bullets. First I heard was a mosin shot missing me so I break contact and run to the side, get hit by pistol rounds so go into cover to bandage. Rather than keep running away, doubled back a bit off to the side and cover the route I came in from (they never see that coming, recommend trying it out if you’re under fire) and nailed one guy who had an M4. At this point I still thought there were just the two of them, suddenly a shotgun blast and You are dead.<br>
That was fun, even if I died!</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/dayz-standalone-hold-on-to-your-cans/12920/51">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/dayz-standalone-hold-on-to-your-cans/12920/51</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 01 Feb 2014 20:26:38 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12920-51</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/dayz-standalone-hold-on-to-your-cans/12920.rss">DayZ Standalone - Hold on to your cans</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>DayZ Standalone - Hold on to your cans</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Serza]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>So I can call myself an idiot?</p>
<p>Nice.</p>
<p>Meeeh. Fuck it, I was a nice guy… And besides, that char DID die.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/dayz-standalone-hold-on-to-your-cans/12920/50">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/dayz-standalone-hold-on-to-your-cans/12920/50</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 25 Jan 2014 16:53:31 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12920-50</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/dayz-standalone-hold-on-to-your-cans/12920.rss">DayZ Standalone - Hold on to your cans</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>DayZ Standalone - Hold on to your cans</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[samzala]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>patch reversed characters to a status one week earlier, hive database issue with servers</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/dayz-standalone-hold-on-to-your-cans/12920/49">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/dayz-standalone-hold-on-to-your-cans/12920/49</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 25 Jan 2014 15:10:30 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12920-49</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/dayz-standalone-hold-on-to-your-cans/12920.rss">DayZ Standalone - Hold on to your cans</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>DayZ Standalone - Hold on to your cans</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Serza]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I got a bug today… I got back my character who’s been dead for 48 hours now…</p>
<p>In a position that was saved over a week ago!<br>
(That character who took part in the huge shootout I described earlier)</p>
<p>Being the fair play (and bored of have-everything) guy I’m… I decided to kill off the character.</p>
<p>Met a two player group however… And being the nice guy I am, I did a little give away of all my kit except for M4, pants and backpack - including my FNX45 pistol, which I made sure was out of ammo (and gave them the Magnum ammo I carried around, heh…). Then I went onto the nearest TALL building, hid the M4 and backpack on the highest spot… And took the leap.</p>
<p>As darkness embraced me, I felt at peace with my actions.</p>
<p>Also, why not the M4? One of my reasons to kill the character was because having everything was boring. Didn’t want to doom the guys to the same fate.<br>
That, and M4A1 with ACOG, bayonet, bipod and several 40/30 round magazines might make them enter the “Hunt players” phase early.</p>
<p>Also warned them that not everyone is as nice as I am - they claimed to have just bought the game. Lucky lads.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/dayz-standalone-hold-on-to-your-cans/12920/48">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/dayz-standalone-hold-on-to-your-cans/12920/48</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2014 16:09:39 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12920-48</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/dayz-standalone-hold-on-to-your-cans/12920.rss">DayZ Standalone - Hold on to your cans</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>DayZ Standalone - Hold on to your cans</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Bolteh]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I’m liking it a lot more than the mod at the moment. Not sure if it’s because of the surplus of lootable locations, the new gear system (including the new medical system) or the new combat system (melee works really well when you’re not inside a building)… But it’s really enjoyable.</p>
<p>I just hope they can fix the more serious problems such as:</p>
<ul>
<li>client side performance</li>
<li>lag (i.e. takes a minute for items to appear on the floor when you drop them)</li>
<li>the Zeds (they seem to spot you from anywhere within a certain radius (even if you’re crawling or crouching or even behind a wall), the animations are really unsynchronised and the pathfinding is still dodgy at best)</li>
<li>the hit detection (aiming way above the head and swinging a shovel (up-down swing) usually hits the knees)</li>
</ul>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/dayz-standalone-hold-on-to-your-cans/12920/47">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/dayz-standalone-hold-on-to-your-cans/12920/47</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2014 08:28:15 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12920-47</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/dayz-standalone-hold-on-to-your-cans/12920.rss">DayZ Standalone - Hold on to your cans</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>DayZ Standalone - Hold on to your cans</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[BendyBread]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Man I’m really tempted to get DayZ, it looks pretty rad. D:</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/dayz-standalone-hold-on-to-your-cans/12920/46">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/dayz-standalone-hold-on-to-your-cans/12920/46</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2014 07:57:01 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12920-46</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/dayz-standalone-hold-on-to-your-cans/12920.rss">DayZ Standalone - Hold on to your cans</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>DayZ Standalone - Hold on to your cans</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Shaddy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I was gonna buy it today, but then I didn’t.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/dayz-standalone-hold-on-to-your-cans/12920/45">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/dayz-standalone-hold-on-to-your-cans/12920/45</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2014 03:12:40 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12920-45</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/dayz-standalone-hold-on-to-your-cans/12920.rss">DayZ Standalone - Hold on to your cans</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>DayZ Standalone - Hold on to your cans</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[geekofalltrades]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>11 hrs logged, been exhaustively searching every structure I come across, and I still haven’t found a single firearm.  Everyone else I come across seems to be armed with an assault rifle and jonesing for my blood.  I spotted some guy peeking at me from around a corner and just ran behind a building and logged out because I didn’t want to get killed again.</p>
<p>I did experience the night for the first time, though.  It’s extremely well-done.  Too bad I only had one of those gas lights, and it was bugged and wouldn’t light anything up.  So I ran around in the dark for forty minutes or so and then gave up and switched to a different server.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/dayz-standalone-hold-on-to-your-cans/12920/44">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/dayz-standalone-hold-on-to-your-cans/12920/44</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2014 02:02:20 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12920-44</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/dayz-standalone-hold-on-to-your-cans/12920.rss">DayZ Standalone - Hold on to your cans</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>DayZ Standalone - Hold on to your cans</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[mankyman6]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Now, don’t be hasty. I’m not a bandit <span class="bbcode-i">all</span> the time. I’m actually gearing up a new guy to go help fresh-spawns along the coast.</p>
<p>EDIT: Gotta say, playing in first-person only servers is a lot more fun and intense.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/dayz-standalone-hold-on-to-your-cans/12920/43">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/dayz-standalone-hold-on-to-your-cans/12920/43</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 19 Jan 2014 15:55:09 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12920-43</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/dayz-standalone-hold-on-to-your-cans/12920.rss">DayZ Standalone - Hold on to your cans</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>DayZ Standalone - Hold on to your cans</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Serza]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Remind me to spawncamp you. God’amn bandits.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/dayz-standalone-hold-on-to-your-cans/12920/42">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/dayz-standalone-hold-on-to-your-cans/12920/42</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 19 Jan 2014 15:17:14 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12920-42</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/dayz-standalone-hold-on-to-your-cans/12920.rss">DayZ Standalone - Hold on to your cans</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>DayZ Standalone - Hold on to your cans</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[samzala]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>fancy words<br>
8/10</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/dayz-standalone-hold-on-to-your-cans/12920/41">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/dayz-standalone-hold-on-to-your-cans/12920/41</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 19 Jan 2014 11:05:46 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12920-41</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/dayz-standalone-hold-on-to-your-cans/12920.rss">DayZ Standalone - Hold on to your cans</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>DayZ Standalone - Hold on to your cans</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[mankyman6]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>A long-time DayZ friend and I got ourselves fully geared and were just mucking about at the NE Airfield for awhile, killing campers, bandits, and camper-bandits 'till we got bored; whereupon we decided to head down to Elektro, set up camp in and old abandoned loft and annihilate anyone who crossed our path.</p>
<p>After about five minutes of dead silence and dull stair watching, the square that we overlooked flooded with fresh spawns, ax-wielding-deviants-in-disguise, and other species of the genus that is DayZ.</p>
<p>We lit that small patch of social-order up like a Christmas tree. Panic ensued as the small ounce of trust they had begun to muster was shattered and tossed aside, along with their hopes of ever finding a true friend in the barren wastes of Chernarus.</p>
<p>The stragglers attempted a feat of bravery, making their way to our small base of operations, creeping up the stairs as their minds boiled in anger and frustration, yearning revenge for their fallen friends. But no such reward would be theirs as the stairs were painted red with their vital essence, axes and crowbars flailing in a last desperate attempt to cease our reign of anarchy. They, too, fell as the rest.</p>
<p>Later on, after picking off would-be grave robbers, two marksman would find their place among a hill not too far from our domain. These bandits-turned-white-knights took it upon themselves to protect the weak that wondered this filthy city, placing their sights squarely upon our Hoxtons. One knight would find his mark squarely upon my brow, bringing my fun to an abrupt, wholly irritating halt, whereupon my partner, having none of it, found his way around these saviors’ perch, drilling one of them to the ground and the other to a heated combat-log, never to return.</p>
<p>T’was a good day, that one.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/dayz-standalone-hold-on-to-your-cans/12920/40">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/dayz-standalone-hold-on-to-your-cans/12920/40</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 19 Jan 2014 06:32:27 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12920-40</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/dayz-standalone-hold-on-to-your-cans/12920.rss">DayZ Standalone - Hold on to your cans</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>DayZ Standalone - Hold on to your cans</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[samzala]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Met first random player in an airfield who didn’t shoot me. He wanted me to kill him instead. Said he had been alive for so long there was nothing left to do anymore. Shooting seemed too boring so I put cuffs on him and pushed him off the air traffic control tower roof.<br>
<img src="https://dl.dropboxusercontent.com/u/3592386/4/ten.jpg" alt="" width="" height=""></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/dayz-standalone-hold-on-to-your-cans/12920/39">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/dayz-standalone-hold-on-to-your-cans/12920/39</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 18 Jan 2014 23:47:45 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12920-39</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/dayz-standalone-hold-on-to-your-cans/12920.rss">DayZ Standalone - Hold on to your cans</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>DayZ Standalone - Hold on to your cans</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Bolteh]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Played a bit yesterday and today… Was remarkably enjoyable. Met a random guy whom I teamed up with, got some decent basic gear and a melee weapon.</p>
<p>The melee combat is slightly flawed indoors, but really effective outdoors. I like!</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/dayz-standalone-hold-on-to-your-cans/12920/38">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/dayz-standalone-hold-on-to-your-cans/12920/38</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2014 14:21:28 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12920-38</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/dayz-standalone-hold-on-to-your-cans/12920.rss">DayZ Standalone - Hold on to your cans</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>DayZ Standalone - Hold on to your cans</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[mankyman6]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I imagine large cities like Cherno and Elektro will be flooded with zombies. I would also hope that the military bases would be as well since those seem like the obvious places to go once the outbreak started.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/dayz-standalone-hold-on-to-your-cans/12920/37">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/dayz-standalone-hold-on-to-your-cans/12920/37</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2014 13:33:03 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12920-37</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/dayz-standalone-hold-on-to-your-cans/12920.rss">DayZ Standalone - Hold on to your cans</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>DayZ Standalone - Hold on to your cans</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Jack_Freeman]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I kinda like that there aren’t a huge number of zombies. The deserted cities and villages are pretty fucking creepy, even at day. I do hope they raise the number of zombies, just not with a whole lot.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/dayz-standalone-hold-on-to-your-cans/12920/36">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/dayz-standalone-hold-on-to-your-cans/12920/36</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2014 11:50:37 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12920-36</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/dayz-standalone-hold-on-to-your-cans/12920.rss">DayZ Standalone - Hold on to your cans</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>DayZ Standalone - Hold on to your cans</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Serza]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Mouse acceleration is surviveable. I guess that’s years (since 2007, actually…) of  continuous ArmA - every single one of them had fucking mouse acceleration.</p>
<p>But in good ol’ ArmA: Armed Assault (Combat Operations for you 'Muricans) I had my muscles specifically made for THAT sort of shit. So I guess it’s more manageable for me than any rest of you. Though no mouse acceleration still makes shit a whole lot easier.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/dayz-standalone-hold-on-to-your-cans/12920/35">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/dayz-standalone-hold-on-to-your-cans/12920/35</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2014 09:03:10 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12920-35</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/dayz-standalone-hold-on-to-your-cans/12920.rss">DayZ Standalone - Hold on to your cans</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>DayZ Standalone - Hold on to your cans</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[geekofalltrades]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Yeah, I played for a few hours yesterday.  The first time I spawned, it was right on top of a frickin’ zombie.  I spent a while running from it without a weapon (I hadn’t figured out that I could fight with my fists yet), then a couple good samaritans came along and killed it and bandaged me.</p>
<p>Later on I faced two zombies armed with a spanner and couldn’t seem to land a fucking hit on either of the things, and was knocked unconcious.  Then I spent about two hours running around in the hills (I found a fucking castle) and didn’t encounter a single zombie the whole time.  I only died again when I got caught in a crossfire armed only with a baseball bat.</p>
<p>It’s definitely an alpha.  At one point I found a canteen and was trying to figure out how to refill it at a water pump and the game destroyed it.  I also tried to drink a soda while armed with a hammer and ended up drinking the hammer instead.  But hey, it quenched my thirst?  And <span class="bbcode-i">that fucking mouse acceleration…</span>  Turning off smoothing made it a lot better, but I can’t stand mouse acceleration even when it works, and DayZ’s definitely does not work.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/dayz-standalone-hold-on-to-your-cans/12920/34">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/dayz-standalone-hold-on-to-your-cans/12920/34</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2014 23:08:56 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12920-34</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/dayz-standalone-hold-on-to-your-cans/12920.rss">DayZ Standalone - Hold on to your cans</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>DayZ Standalone - Hold on to your cans</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Serza]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Yeah, I personaly also hope for… MUCH MUCH MUCH higher number of zombies (Bad luck? Oh, here, have a horde!) upon release (or, hopefully, Beta). So far, a well playable experience. I’ve managed to die to Zombies twice out of seven lifes though, which is nowhere near the percentage I wish it to be…</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/dayz-standalone-hold-on-to-your-cans/12920/33">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/dayz-standalone-hold-on-to-your-cans/12920/33</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2014 14:25:30 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12920-33</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/dayz-standalone-hold-on-to-your-cans/12920.rss">DayZ Standalone - Hold on to your cans</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>DayZ Standalone - Hold on to your cans</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[JeffMOD]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I recall reading that the number of zombies was toned down because they’re really buggy at the moment - stuff like not colliding with buildings.<br>
I’d expect them to pop back up once they’re more functional.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/dayz-standalone-hold-on-to-your-cans/12920/32">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/dayz-standalone-hold-on-to-your-cans/12920/32</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2014 13:31:20 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12920-32</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/dayz-standalone-hold-on-to-your-cans/12920.rss">DayZ Standalone - Hold on to your cans</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>DayZ Standalone - Hold on to your cans</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[TheeGoatPig]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I haven’t played the game, but from what I have seen in Lets Plays there aren’t nearly enough zombies, and they are hardly a threat. I guess that is the kind of thing that kills network stability though?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/dayz-standalone-hold-on-to-your-cans/12920/31">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/dayz-standalone-hold-on-to-your-cans/12920/31</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2014 13:24:40 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12920-31</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/dayz-standalone-hold-on-to-your-cans/12920.rss">DayZ Standalone - Hold on to your cans</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>DayZ Standalone - Hold on to your cans</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Maxey]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>They mostly come out at night. Mostly.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/dayz-standalone-hold-on-to-your-cans/12920/30">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/dayz-standalone-hold-on-to-your-cans/12920/30</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2014 13:12:10 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12920-30</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/dayz-standalone-hold-on-to-your-cans/12920.rss">DayZ Standalone - Hold on to your cans</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>DayZ Standalone - Hold on to your cans</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[samzala]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>try out a night server at least once<br>
and try to make it so you see dusk or dawn happen<br>
top tip turn clouds off in Quality for moonlight visibility</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/dayz-standalone-hold-on-to-your-cans/12920/29">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/dayz-standalone-hold-on-to-your-cans/12920/29</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2014 13:09:06 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12920-29</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/dayz-standalone-hold-on-to-your-cans/12920.rss">DayZ Standalone - Hold on to your cans</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>DayZ Standalone - Hold on to your cans</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Maxey]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Yeah, that sucks but, while we wait for a solution to that, you can mitigate that a little bit by disabling mouse smoothing, maxing out mouse sensitivity and, if you have a mouse with a dpi selector, playing with one of the slowest mouse setting you have. Then move the mouse slowly and smoothly anyway, as this is not a twitch shooter.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/dayz-standalone-hold-on-to-your-cans/12920/28">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/dayz-standalone-hold-on-to-your-cans/12920/28</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2014 10:33:43 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12920-28</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/dayz-standalone-hold-on-to-your-cans/12920.rss">DayZ Standalone - Hold on to your cans</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>DayZ Standalone - Hold on to your cans</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[geekofalltrades]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Boom, purchased.  I was hoping I’d be able to get the mod version working as sort of a demo before I bought the standalone version, but honestly I’ve seen enough of the gameplay that I feel pretty comfortable just buying it without having tried it.</p>
<p>EDIT: Mouse acceleration can’t be disabled?  <span class="bbcode-i">Seriously?</span></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/dayz-standalone-hold-on-to-your-cans/12920/27">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/dayz-standalone-hold-on-to-your-cans/12920/27</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2014 05:18:18 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12920-27</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/dayz-standalone-hold-on-to-your-cans/12920.rss">DayZ Standalone - Hold on to your cans</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
