<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Win7 security virus makes Computer=DEAD</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/win7-security-virus-makes-computer-dead/7107</link>
    <description>Be wary of some rogue virus that claims to be a Win7 Security Program. I&#39;ve gotten rid of the easier ones but this virus buried itself deep in my registry and completely fucked it to hell. All my data and HD is fried. Damn computer won&#39;t even start. So until we come up with enough money to buy a new computer my PC gaming days are over. Good thing the PS2 still works. Well I&#39;m still able to get SOME of my pysical memory from the HD but I&#39;d need to buy an external...anyway...if anyone knows where to get good computers for decent prices don&#39;t hesitate to let me know...</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 13 May 2011 14:23:02 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Help and Support</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/win7-security-virus-makes-computer-dead/7107.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Win7 security virus makes Computer=DEAD</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[GuitarJim]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>The best way I have found for recovering windows is to:</p>
<ol>
<li>
<p>Download and burn <a href="https://www.ubuntu.com/" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Ubuntu Live CD</a>. Make sure you burn it correctly with an iso burning program like <a href="https://www.imgburn.com/" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">imgburn</a>. You need to have at least 256mb of RAM on the laptop to run the live CD.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Run the ubuntu live CD and select “Try Ubuntu”. This will give you a fully functional desktop that does not affect your HDD.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Mount your HDD by selecting “places” and clicking on your drive. Be sure to select the correct partition as you will be also be able to see the recovery partition (if you have one) here which you should not mess with.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Transfer any files you need onto an external hard drive or usb pen (if you have one large enough).</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Insert the recovery CD or windows install CD to format and reinstall. Be sure to select full format to make sure that virus is gone completely.<br>
MAKE SURE you have your product key before you format (if you are using a windows CD) as you will not be able to recover it after. If you do not have a sticker with the key on then you will need to extract it.</p>
</li>
</ol>
<p>How to extract:</p>
<p>Go to C:\WINDOWS\System32\ and copy the “config” folder to a usb drive with the same folder string i.e. place a folder on the root of the drive called WINDOWS, inside that a folder called System32 and place the config folder inside this folder.</p>
<p>Next on a windows machine download <a href="https://www.magicaljellybean.com/keyfinder/" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">keyfinder</a> and install. Depending on your security you may get some warnings. This is a safe program but needs to access sensitive parts of the system hence your firewall may flag it. Once installed go to tools &gt; load hive and point it to the WINDOWS folder on your usb drive. It should now be able to read the key from there.</p>
<p>Good luck.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/win7-security-virus-makes-computer-dead/7107/41">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/win7-security-virus-makes-computer-dead/7107/41</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 13 May 2011 14:23:02 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7107-41</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/win7-security-virus-makes-computer-dead/7107.rss">Win7 security virus makes Computer=DEAD</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Win7 security virus makes Computer=DEAD</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Metritutus]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Termo543, I believe what Hyperbyte said gives you the best chances of saving some of the data on the laptop.  I felt it necessary to add emphasis.</p>
<p>You shouldn’t need to try and modify the BIOS at all I don’t think.</p>
<p>I’m not as knowledgeable on these matters as some, but some people really are giving out terrible advice in this thread.  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/frowning.png?v=9" title=":frowning:" class="emoji" alt=":frowning:"></p>
<p>Good luck.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/win7-security-virus-makes-computer-dead/7107/40">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/win7-security-virus-makes-computer-dead/7107/40</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 13 May 2011 09:31:08 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7107-40</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/win7-security-virus-makes-computer-dead/7107.rss">Win7 security virus makes Computer=DEAD</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Win7 security virus makes Computer=DEAD</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[JayJay]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>You only need to flash the BIOS if you need to update it to a version that supports a new processor you want to fit. Thats the only time I’ve <span class="bbcode-i">ever</span>had to flash a BIOS, certainly <span class="bbcode-b">not </span>when fitting a HDD.</p>
<p>All it does it tell the computer how to talk to peripherals/components until the OS takes over.</p>
<p><em>edit</em> and store basic system settings etc</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/win7-security-virus-makes-computer-dead/7107/39">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/win7-security-virus-makes-computer-dead/7107/39</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 13 May 2011 08:48:08 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7107-39</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/win7-security-virus-makes-computer-dead/7107.rss">Win7 security virus makes Computer=DEAD</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Win7 security virus makes Computer=DEAD</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Angdraug]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>So, you’re telling me, that every time I change a HDD I need to update/reinstall BIOS, which is on a separate chip on the motherboad?<br>
Call me lazy, but I have <span class="bbcode-i">never</span> installed/updated my BIOS. I have had to change my HDD many times though.</p>
<p>Are you sure you understand what is the difference between an Operating System and Basic Input/Output System? You might want to read Hyperbyte’s reply. I’m too lazy to type it all again.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/win7-security-virus-makes-computer-dead/7107/38">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/win7-security-virus-makes-computer-dead/7107/38</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 13 May 2011 08:44:30 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7107-38</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/win7-security-virus-makes-computer-dead/7107.rss">Win7 security virus makes Computer=DEAD</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Win7 security virus makes Computer=DEAD</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Chickenprotector]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Angdraug">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/a/77aa72/40.png" class="avatar"> Angdraug:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Why?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I’m assuming he dumps everything onto his main drive. Getting a new HDD usually indicates the thing is EMPTY when you first install it. Put two and two together.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/win7-security-virus-makes-computer-dead/7107/37">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/win7-security-virus-makes-computer-dead/7107/37</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 12 May 2011 21:44:01 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7107-37</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/win7-security-virus-makes-computer-dead/7107.rss">Win7 security virus makes Computer=DEAD</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Win7 security virus makes Computer=DEAD</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[russilker]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Like I said, pop your Windows installation CD in and boot into it, then format your computer before the installation takes place. Unless you have some super valuable info on the drive there’s no need to do anything more complicated than that.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/win7-security-virus-makes-computer-dead/7107/36">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/win7-security-virus-makes-computer-dead/7107/36</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 12 May 2011 14:24:10 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7107-36</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/win7-security-virus-makes-computer-dead/7107.rss">Win7 security virus makes Computer=DEAD</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Win7 security virus makes Computer=DEAD</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[DaftMink]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>My parents got this virus, for me it was simple to remove.<br>
Run a full <a href="https://www.malwarebytes.org/" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">malwarebytes</a> scan, and a system restore.<br>
The virus stops .exe’s from running when not “run as administrator”.</p>
<p>Nice safety tip, get a good ad blocking plugin for you browser.<br>
<a href="https://addons.mozilla.org/en-US/firefox/addon/adblock-plus/" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Adblock Plus</a> if you use firefox, <a href="https://ie.microsoft.com/testdrive/Browser/TrackingProtectionLists/" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Easy List</a> if you use IE 9.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/win7-security-virus-makes-computer-dead/7107/35">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/win7-security-virus-makes-computer-dead/7107/35</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 12 May 2011 10:58:37 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7107-35</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/win7-security-virus-makes-computer-dead/7107.rss">Win7 security virus makes Computer=DEAD</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Win7 security virus makes Computer=DEAD</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Hyperbyte]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>My god, the sheer amount of bullshit in this thread is amazing.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Chickenprotector</span>, could you please go back to protecting chickens and stay away from this thread?  You’re giving really bad advice and posting incorrect things as facts.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Chickenprotector">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/user_avatar/leakfree.org/chickenprotector/40/5653_2.png" class="avatar"> Chickenprotector:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Selectively extracting files from your directories is not the best of ideas. It can get on your other drives as a result.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>False.  You can copy, rename, move (et cetera) virus files all you want.  As long as you don’t open them or have your system generate a thumbnail view (which opens them), there is no danger.  A virus file can never do harm unless it is opened or executed.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Chickenprotector">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/user_avatar/leakfree.org/chickenprotector/40/5653_2.png" class="avatar"> Chickenprotector:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I would reformat without saving any files, doing a full purge is the only sure fire way in my personal opinion to avoid getting shit like that to begin with.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Ever heard of a virus scanner?  It’s a matter of plugging the harddisk into a computer which has a good and up-to-date virus scanner, make sure it doesn’t autoplay anything, and then scan away.  Again, as long as you don’t open anything…</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Chickenprotector">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/user_avatar/leakfree.org/chickenprotector/40/5653_2.png" class="avatar"> Chickenprotector:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>IF you get a new HDD you would need to re-install your BIOS (Base operating system for the computer, it should come with your Motherboard)</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>This is the dumbest statement I’ve ever read about modern computers.  If a BIOS comes with the motherboard, why would you need to reinstalled it when you plug in a new harddisk?  In the 80’s or early 90’s sometimes the BIOS setup tool was saved on the harddisk, but never the BIOS itself as that would be impossible.  Also, BIOS is a Basic Input/Output System.  It tells your operating system what hardware there is and how to communicate with it.  It is not dependant on an operating system and definitely isn’t an operating system by itself.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Termo543</span>, what you want to do is the following.  Firstly, you want to get an external USB case that fits your laptop’s harddisk.  There are lots of decent and very cheap 2.5" external harddisk cases out there.  Remove the harddisk from the laptop, put it in the case, plug the case with a USB cord into a computer that has a decent virus scanner and run a full scan on the drive, deleting any files that are found dangerous.  After that, backup your documents and other files you want to keep to the computer the laptop disk is plugged in to.  If you don’t care about recovering your files, you could skip this step.</p>
<p>Next, put the harddisk back in the laptop and search for your recovery CD’s.  Laptop usually come with restore CD’s which can restore the laptop software to it’s original state.  Just put in the first CD, boot the laptop, and the software should boot.  Sometimes there is a key you need to press during startup to boot from CD, like one of the F-keys.  Once the CD boots, the rest is explained on-screen.  Formatting the harddisk is automatically done by recovery CD’s.  Voila.  Now, if you don’t have these anymore, don’t worry.  It just makes things a little bit more difficult.</p>
<p>You could as well restore your system with a Windows installation CD.  Just insert the CD, boot your computer from the CD and the Windows installer will start.  Make sure you start a new, clean installation (not recovery, not reinstallation, not upgrade) and select that it should format your harddisks.  Next it will install an all new, clean Windows.  After that, go on a PC which has internet and download all drivers for your laptop (found on the manufacturers website).  Put the drivers on a USB stick, put it in the laptop and install them all.  You should then be ready to go again.</p>
<p>Of course, you’ll have to start over with installing all programs again et cetera, but you should have a clean and fresh PC again.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/win7-security-virus-makes-computer-dead/7107/34">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/win7-security-virus-makes-computer-dead/7107/34</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 12 May 2011 08:55:41 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7107-34</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/win7-security-virus-makes-computer-dead/7107.rss">Win7 security virus makes Computer=DEAD</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Win7 security virus makes Computer=DEAD</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[JayJay]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="garrthbarrttinn">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/g/977dab/40.png" class="avatar"> garrthbarrttinn:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>That’s not always enough, in fact, more often than not not enoguh. Who’s the derp now?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Yep, one of our users managed to get this virus even with AVG Business Edition installed :fffuuu:</p>
<p>Thing is I’m pretty sure they’re smart enough not to install random software on our machines…</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/win7-security-virus-makes-computer-dead/7107/33">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/win7-security-virus-makes-computer-dead/7107/33</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 12 May 2011 08:16:49 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7107-33</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/win7-security-virus-makes-computer-dead/7107.rss">Win7 security virus makes Computer=DEAD</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Win7 security virus makes Computer=DEAD</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[garrthbarrttinn]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="fx.">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 fx.:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>With an Anti virus, maybe?<br>
derp</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>That’s not always enough, in fact, more often than not that’s not enough. Who’s the derp now?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/win7-security-virus-makes-computer-dead/7107/32">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/win7-security-virus-makes-computer-dead/7107/32</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 12 May 2011 02:53:30 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7107-32</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/win7-security-virus-makes-computer-dead/7107.rss">Win7 security virus makes Computer=DEAD</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Win7 security virus makes Computer=DEAD</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Jim_DiGriz]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>If you can get into safe mode with networking, and if you can get your browser to run, try going to Trend Micro (<a href="https://www.trendmicro.com" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://www.trendmicro.com</a>) and run House Call. If and when it finds stuff, have it fix it if it can, quarantine the file if it can’t. Restart the scan when it finishes. Keep doing that until it comes up clean. It will probably take several tries. Reboot, and see what happens. If it still won’t boot into regular windows, try the safe mode scan again to make sure nothing was being masked with other viruses the first time through. Hopefully, you will be able to boot into windows. If you can, immediately get malwarebytes (<a href="https://www.malwarebytes.org" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://www.malwarebytes.org</a>), update it, and run it. Clean anything it finds. Run it until it comes through clean. Hopefully, your system will be usable at this point. Make sure your AV/firewall software is up to date.</p>
<p>If Windows still can’t boot properly, find your windows install CD. Put it in the drive, and reboot. Most computers are set to boot off the CD first. If yours isn’t, then restart, and watch for the BIOS setup or boot order key (usually <del> or , sometimes different). Set the CD/DVD as the first boot device, save (if necessary), and reboot again. You might have to press a key to boot to the CD, it’ll prompt you if it does. Once the CD/DVD boots, you can try to repair the current windows installation, and install a new copy. If repairing the current installation doesn’t work, reboot to the cd/dvd again. If you have room, try installing windows in a new folder (windows1, or something). Do not format the partition for this part. This should get you a bootable version of your OS where you can try to make everything work correctly, or get an external drive, and copy your important files off. If you decide to keep using this install, make sure to do a thorough scan with both AV and anit malware software. It won’t guarantee that the virus won’t pop back up in the future, but it can work. If you don’t care about anything currently on the drive, then boot to the cd/dvd, format the drive, and install your OS on the fresh format.</del></p>
<p>If you have a Dell or other machine that has the install files in a small partition on the hard drive, then a fresh install is probably your only option unless you made disks the first time the machine was turned on.</p>
<p>Good luck!</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/win7-security-virus-makes-computer-dead/7107/31">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/win7-security-virus-makes-computer-dead/7107/31</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 12 May 2011 01:03:59 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7107-31</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/win7-security-virus-makes-computer-dead/7107.rss">Win7 security virus makes Computer=DEAD</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Win7 security virus makes Computer=DEAD</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[pyjamasbox]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>mfw retards think malware can effect hardware.</p>
<p>if your computer won’t start, it’s not the malware that did it. motherboards, ram, and all other components ware over time and eventually break entirely. If your computer isn’t starting at all(Power On Self Test isn’t happening) it’s because you either fried your mobo using some kind of liquid (or it just gave in from time) or your PSU is fucked up.</p>
<p>RAM could also be the problem, but it’s more likely that your computer would start and continuously restart before reaching post then not being able to start at all.</p>
<p>People who purchase new computers because they have a virus are fucking FULL BLOWN retarded.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/win7-security-virus-makes-computer-dead/7107/30">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/win7-security-virus-makes-computer-dead/7107/30</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 12 May 2011 00:29:03 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7107-30</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/win7-security-virus-makes-computer-dead/7107.rss">Win7 security virus makes Computer=DEAD</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Win7 security virus makes Computer=DEAD</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[K_amp_955_ON]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>My dad got hit with this virus, and as the extreme computer know-it-all he claims to be he barely saved his machine. I don’t recall his exact methods of getting rid of the virus, but I know he did some work arounds so he could access his virus/malware protection/removal programs which the virus initial blocks.</p>
<p>The virus did however mess with his registry and completely removed his ability to get windows updates on his computer. He tried every method he came across on windows sites/forums for restoring the update functionality but in the end he ended up reformatting his main drive.</p>
<p>Definitely a pain in the ass. Best of luck with your computer mate, hopefully it can be salvaged.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/win7-security-virus-makes-computer-dead/7107/29">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/win7-security-virus-makes-computer-dead/7107/29</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 11 May 2011 23:43:30 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7107-29</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/win7-security-virus-makes-computer-dead/7107.rss">Win7 security virus makes Computer=DEAD</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Win7 security virus makes Computer=DEAD</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[JayJay]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Oh, when you said command prompt I thought it booted far enough into Windows for you to access it, the command prompt and the boot into safe mode options are quite different. Fraid you’re boned dude.</p>
<p>You shouldn’t need to re-install your BIOS, its helpd on a standalone chip based on the motherboard and its not really accessible to viruses these days  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/smiley.png?v=9" title=":smiley:" class="emoji" alt=":smiley:"></p>
<p>It could be a culmination of viruses, the one I’m thinking of just copied a few files around the place and changed a few registry values, nothing crazy but not the easiest to remove, hence only removing select files. Yours however seems a bit worse.</p>
<p>If yours is that destroyed I’d highly recommend nuking the whole thing, just format the drive and install. You’ll lose everything but you won’t run the risk of it propagating. Unless you get an external drive, in that case copy the files and plug it into a system you won’t mind losing in case anything has come along for the ride :fffuuu:</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/win7-security-virus-makes-computer-dead/7107/28">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/win7-security-virus-makes-computer-dead/7107/28</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 11 May 2011 21:08:22 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7107-28</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/win7-security-virus-makes-computer-dead/7107.rss">Win7 security virus makes Computer=DEAD</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Win7 security virus makes Computer=DEAD</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Termo543]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I’m not dumb enough not to know what re-formatting and formatting is. Some of you people obviously don’t get the fact that I can’t run anything. nothing at all. My screen is solid black except for the “safe mode” titles. Everything is inaccessible. This damn virus ran right past all my security programs, fucked around with my registry, and deleted alot of my files. So please quit giving me shit and tell me something useful. Now, as for those of you actually helping, thanks. I’ll heed all of what you said. I’ll buy an external drive, extract all my needed files, format, and put everything the way it as. Thanks, the end.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/win7-security-virus-makes-computer-dead/7107/27">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/win7-security-virus-makes-computer-dead/7107/27</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 11 May 2011 20:36:30 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7107-27</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/win7-security-virus-makes-computer-dead/7107.rss">Win7 security virus makes Computer=DEAD</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Win7 security virus makes Computer=DEAD</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Couch-pilot]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I just went through a nasty MBR virus experience… I feel your pain…</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/win7-security-virus-makes-computer-dead/7107/26">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/win7-security-virus-makes-computer-dead/7107/26</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 11 May 2011 20:24:06 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7107-26</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/win7-security-virus-makes-computer-dead/7107.rss">Win7 security virus makes Computer=DEAD</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Win7 security virus makes Computer=DEAD</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[russilker]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Make sure you know what formatting is… it will delete your virus, but it will also remove Windows, all of your programs, etc. You need to be able to reinstall the operating system after you format it. For that you’ll probably need a Windows DVD/CD, and you can reformat your hard drive right from that disc before reinstalling the OS.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/win7-security-virus-makes-computer-dead/7107/25">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/win7-security-virus-makes-computer-dead/7107/25</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 11 May 2011 20:00:49 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7107-25</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/win7-security-virus-makes-computer-dead/7107.rss">Win7 security virus makes Computer=DEAD</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Win7 security virus makes Computer=DEAD</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Angdraug]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Chickenprotector">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/user_avatar/leakfree.org/chickenprotector/40/5653_2.png" class="avatar"> Chickenprotector:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>IF you get a new HDD you would need to re-install your BIOS</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Why?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/win7-security-virus-makes-computer-dead/7107/24">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/win7-security-virus-makes-computer-dead/7107/24</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 11 May 2011 18:01:47 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7107-24</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/win7-security-virus-makes-computer-dead/7107.rss">Win7 security virus makes Computer=DEAD</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Win7 security virus makes Computer=DEAD</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Chickenprotector]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="JayJay">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/j/35a633/40.png" class="avatar"> JayJay:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Copy NEEDED files across only (i.e. My Documents, Steam games). Format 2nd drive.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Selectively extracting files from your directories is not the best of ideas. It can get on your other drives as a result. Some viruses are crafty enough for that I’ve seen it happen before. The particularly nasty viruses are the self-replicating ones.</p>
<p>But in all reality, do what he said, just reformat your machine, or get a new HDD for the computer, unless you’re using a laptop. I would reformat without saving any files, doing a full purge is the only sure fire way in my personal opinion to avoid getting shit like that to begin with.</p>
<p>IF you get a new HDD you would need to re-install your BIOS (Base operating system for the computer, it should come with your Motherboard) then install your OS then work from there.</p>
<p>Next time don’t click links people or pop-ups give you… ever. <span class="bbcode-b">[i][u]Never ever ever</span>[/i][/u] download something unless you know <span class="bbcode-b">exactly</span> what it is. And last but not least, don’t randomly surf the web unless you know exactly what you’re after.</p>
<p>These are my general rules of thumb, I haven’t got a bad infection yet.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/win7-security-virus-makes-computer-dead/7107/23">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/win7-security-virus-makes-computer-dead/7107/23</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 11 May 2011 17:49:35 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7107-23</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/win7-security-virus-makes-computer-dead/7107.rss">Win7 security virus makes Computer=DEAD</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Win7 security virus makes Computer=DEAD</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[fx1]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>With an Anti virus, maybe?<br>
derp</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/win7-security-virus-makes-computer-dead/7107/22">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/win7-security-virus-makes-computer-dead/7107/22</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 11 May 2011 17:46:57 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7107-22</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/win7-security-virus-makes-computer-dead/7107.rss">Win7 security virus makes Computer=DEAD</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Win7 security virus makes Computer=DEAD</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[JayJay]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Exactly, well put garrthbarrttinn 8)</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/win7-security-virus-makes-computer-dead/7107/21">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/win7-security-virus-makes-computer-dead/7107/21</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 11 May 2011 14:26:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7107-21</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/win7-security-virus-makes-computer-dead/7107.rss">Win7 security virus makes Computer=DEAD</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Win7 security virus makes Computer=DEAD</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[garrthbarrttinn]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><span class="mention">@fx</span>. Don’t be too harsh to the guy. EVerybody starts somewhere and the best way to learn how to fix a problem is to run into the problem. Who’s going to google “How to fix a virus” before they have a virus?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/win7-security-virus-makes-computer-dead/7107/20">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/win7-security-virus-makes-computer-dead/7107/20</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 11 May 2011 14:22:25 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7107-20</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/win7-security-virus-makes-computer-dead/7107.rss">Win7 security virus makes Computer=DEAD</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Win7 security virus makes Computer=DEAD</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[JayJay]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="fx.">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 fx.:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>If your HDD dies, your whole computer gets broken!<br>
Seriously, “buy a new computer”, you’re joking right?</p>
<p>Bet you don’t even know what reformat is, and you’re just some casual PC user that doesn’t know how a PC works</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-i">(Offensive post? Getting rid of a virus should be something every computer user should know, and saying the whole computer gets broken when it’s only the HDD, is just…)</span></p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Slightly offensive, just because he uses a PC doesn’t mean he should know all the ins-and-outs. Thats like saying when you fly you should know how to pilot the plane. Just because you use the PC doesn’t mean you should know how to operate it entirely.</p>
<p>But the HDD thing, yeah bud I’m afraid that is a bit OTT  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/smiley.png?v=9" title=":smiley:" class="emoji" alt=":smiley:">  I was posting pretty late last night, but another thing you could do is buy a new HDD and install Windows (or Linux, but it seems you’d be better off with Windows  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/wink.png?v=9" title=":wink:" class="emoji" alt=":wink:"> ), using the bust one as a 2nd drive. Once its all ok, copy ONLY NON-EXECUTABLE FILES from the 2nd drive, then format it completely.</p>
<p>That explorer.exe thing worked when one of the users here at work got the virus (or a very similar one). The file is based in C:\Windows.</p>
<p>So options are:</p>
<ul>
<li>Boot into Windows, start explorer.exe, copy all files then format</li>
<li>Format and lose everything</li>
<li>Buy a new HDD, install Windows onto the new one, use old as 2nd drive. Copy NEEDED files across only (i.e. My Documents, Steam games). Format 2nd drive.</li>
</ul>
<p>Personally I use Microsoft Security Essentials and I’ve never had any problems. Performance and security wise Kaspersky was the best I’ve ever used, however you can’t get that version anymore  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/frowning.png?v=9" title=":frowning:" class="emoji" alt=":frowning:">  We use AVG at work and I hate it with a passion.</p>
<p>For home use, MSE is perfect. Just use a bit of common sense when on the internet anyway.</p>
<p>And don’t download random crap. It should be common sense now that any popup saying you have a virus, that you’re the 10,000th visitor or there are errors on your machine SHOULD BE AVOIDED.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/win7-security-virus-makes-computer-dead/7107/19">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/win7-security-virus-makes-computer-dead/7107/19</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 11 May 2011 12:38:55 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7107-19</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/win7-security-virus-makes-computer-dead/7107.rss">Win7 security virus makes Computer=DEAD</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Win7 security virus makes Computer=DEAD</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[fx1]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>If your HDD dies, your whole computer gets broken!<br>
Seriously, “buy a new computer”, you’re joking right?</p>
<p>Bet you don’t even know what reformat is, and you’re just some casual PC user that doesn’t know how a PC works</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-i">(Offensive post? Getting rid of a virus should be something every computer user should know, and saying the whole computer gets broken when it’s only the HDD, is just…)</span></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/win7-security-virus-makes-computer-dead/7107/18">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/win7-security-virus-makes-computer-dead/7107/18</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 11 May 2011 12:24:49 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7107-18</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/win7-security-virus-makes-computer-dead/7107.rss">Win7 security virus makes Computer=DEAD</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Win7 security virus makes Computer=DEAD</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[JayJay]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>If its the virus I’m thinking of it’ll boot, but what its done is changed the registry to look at the virus’ exe as the shell, not explorer.exe. So, when it boots up and displays the virus screen, press ctrl+alt+del, select RUN and type in explorer.exe.</p>
<p>This’ll start the Windows “shell” and give you access to your files, copy any important things to somewhere safe then format the machine. I think the virus resides in the users documents area, so don’t copy the entire directory, only the files you need.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/win7-security-virus-makes-computer-dead/7107/17">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/win7-security-virus-makes-computer-dead/7107/17</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 11 May 2011 08:09:27 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7107-17</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/win7-security-virus-makes-computer-dead/7107.rss">Win7 security virus makes Computer=DEAD</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
