<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>You can bypass sections of the Refuse Processing conveyor belt area [Fixed]</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/you-can-bypass-sections-of-the-refuse-processing-conveyor-belt-area-fixed/9886</link>
    <description>map     : bm_c2a4c at: 325 x, -466 y, 329 z
setpos 325.749268 -466.202820 329.757935;setang 33.823887 -177.572647 0.000000

Basically, conveyor belts that are supposed to be &quot;one way&quot; aren&#39;t. When you first enter the Refuse Processing area with the many levels of conveyor belts, there&#39;s a belt coming out of a wall with a sticky mine in it. There are numerous holes like this, with one that you can see the next section of the level though. You can&#39;t go into the hole the conveyor belt is coming out of because the hole is too small and you have to duck. If you duck, you move slower and so can&#39;t move fast enough to make progress against the belt. Instead, you have to go along the belt and into a control room where you move a hanging platform and open a gate to reach the other side of the mined belt.

You don&#39;t have to. Simply walk up to the &quot;small&quot; hole with a conveyor belt coming out of it, crouch and start jumping. You move forward faster while jumping and can thus make it through the wall, skipping a good third of that section. You can go into all of those conveyor belt holes, in fact, but the others don&#39;t lead anywhere important.

*edit*
No screenshot as my picture host is being difficult.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 15 Sep 2012 18:01:34 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>In-game Issues (Mod)</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/you-can-bypass-sections-of-the-refuse-processing-conveyor-belt-area-fixed/9886.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>You can bypass sections of the Refuse Processing conveyor belt area [Fixed]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[RiscIt]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Malidictus">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/m/7bcc69/40.png" class="avatar"> Malidictus:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>No screenshot as my picture host is being difficult.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Steam is your picture host. It is not being difficult. Shift-F12 in game. Shift-Tab to caption and upload.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/you-can-bypass-sections-of-the-refuse-processing-conveyor-belt-area-fixed/9886/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/you-can-bypass-sections-of-the-refuse-processing-conveyor-belt-area-fixed/9886/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 15 Sep 2012 18:01:34 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9886-2</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/you-can-bypass-sections-of-the-refuse-processing-conveyor-belt-area-fixed/9886.rss">You can bypass sections of the Refuse Processing conveyor belt area [Fixed]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>You can bypass sections of the Refuse Processing conveyor belt area [Fixed]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Malidictus]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>map     : bm_c2a4c at: 325 x, -466 y, 329 z<br>
setpos 325.749268 -466.202820 329.757935;setang 33.823887 -177.572647 0.000000</p>
<p>Basically, conveyor belts that are supposed to be “one way” aren’t. When you first enter the Refuse Processing area with the many levels of conveyor belts, there’s a belt coming out of a wall with a sticky mine in it. There are numerous holes like this, with one that you can see the next section of the level though. You can’t go into the hole the conveyor belt is coming out of because the hole is too small and you have to duck. If you duck, you move slower and so can’t move fast enough to make progress against the belt. Instead, you have to go along the belt and into a control room where you move a hanging platform and open a gate to reach the other side of the mined belt.</p>
<p>You don’t have to. Simply walk up to the “small” hole with a conveyor belt coming out of it, crouch and start jumping. You move forward faster while jumping and can thus make it through the wall, skipping a good third of that section. You can go into all of those conveyor belt holes, in fact, but the others don’t lead anywhere important.</p>
<p><em>edit</em><br>
No screenshot as my picture host is being difficult.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/you-can-bypass-sections-of-the-refuse-processing-conveyor-belt-area-fixed/9886/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/you-can-bypass-sections-of-the-refuse-processing-conveyor-belt-area-fixed/9886/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 15 Sep 2012 15:20:46 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9886-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/you-can-bypass-sections-of-the-refuse-processing-conveyor-belt-area-fixed/9886.rss">You can bypass sections of the Refuse Processing conveyor belt area [Fixed]</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
