<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Cornered by (respawning?) marines in Surface Tension</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/cornered-by-respawning-marines-in-surface-tension/10828</link>
    <description>i&#39;ve been working on this corridor FOR AN HOUR!
Shortly after the warehouse full of tripwire explosives and the weapons warehouse, there&#39;s a 3 story building with its interior destroyed. Once you find your way through a hole in the floor on the second floor, there&#39;s a short road that leads up to several shipping containers. This is where i&#39;m stuck.

i&#39;m corned at the starting end of this short tunnel behind a fence and piping. Every time i poke me head out, there&#39;s another 6 or 7 marines waiting for me. i keep popping my head out and taking shots at them until they&#39;re gone. As SOON AS i try to progress, 6 or 7 MORE show up and shove me back into my corner. i&#39;ve spent at least an hour fighting off these damn marines. i have NO AMMO left, A WHOPPiNG 3 HEALTH and i&#39;ve been quick-saving and quick-loading to the point that my fingers never leave the F5 and F9 keys.

Do these marines respawn? Even if i turn the difficulty down, the marine&#39;s aim is always perfect and i&#39;m killed the split second i try to leave my hiding spot. i can&#39;t even grab any of the medkits they drop because i can&#39;t move 2 inches before i&#39;m dead.

Peak left, pop off one round with the shotgun, hide, listen to see if somebody took damage, quicksave. Peak left, die, reload. Peak left, die, reload. Peak left, die, reload. Peak left, die, reload. Peak left, pop off one round with the shotgun, hide, listen to see if somebody took damage, quicksave. Peak left, pop off one round with the shotgun, hide, listen to see if somebody took damage, quicksave. Repeat.

-Kawai Tei-</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 19 Sep 2012 15:24:57 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>In-game Issues (Mod)</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/cornered-by-respawning-marines-in-surface-tension/10828.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Cornered by (respawning?) marines in Surface Tension</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Giazzo]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Yes, the cheats work.</p>
<p>I didn’t have too much problems: I shot the Vortigaunts, the Agrunt and took the marines there one at a time from distance. Then I shot the Osprey down to stop them from coming more.</p>
<p>Maybe <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=bvwza3M8iXk#at=66m39s" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">this</a> will help you.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/cornered-by-respawning-marines-in-surface-tension/10828/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/cornered-by-respawning-marines-in-surface-tension/10828/4</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 19 Sep 2012 15:24:57 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-10828-4</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/cornered-by-respawning-marines-in-surface-tension/10828.rss">Cornered by (respawning?) marines in Surface Tension</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Cornered by (respawning?) marines in Surface Tension</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Tei]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Giazzo">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/g/76d3ee/40.png" class="avatar"> Giazzo:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Destroy the Osprey (the hovering aircraft) with the Tau cannon or the rocket launcher. They will stop coming.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>LOL i WOULD but i’m stuck!<br>
Do the typical cheats work for BM? (sv_cheats 1, etc.)  i haven’t tried yet and i won’t be going back to the game for a little while.</p>
<p>EDiT : i haven’t even SEEN the Osprey. Like i said, i can’t even get out of the tunnel, let alone out from behind this pipe. i could hear it so i figured some kind of chopper was out. i don’t suppose there’s any way to delay the marine spawn until AFTER you get out of the tunnel instead of the moment the current wave of marines are defeated?</p>
<p>-Kawai Tei-</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/cornered-by-respawning-marines-in-surface-tension/10828/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/cornered-by-respawning-marines-in-surface-tension/10828/3</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 19 Sep 2012 15:03:04 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-10828-3</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/cornered-by-respawning-marines-in-surface-tension/10828.rss">Cornered by (respawning?) marines in Surface Tension</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Cornered by (respawning?) marines in Surface Tension</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Giazzo]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Destroy the Osprey (the hovering aircraft) with the Tau cannon or the rocket launcher. They will stop coming.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/cornered-by-respawning-marines-in-surface-tension/10828/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/cornered-by-respawning-marines-in-surface-tension/10828/2</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 19 Sep 2012 14:57:32 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-10828-2</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/cornered-by-respawning-marines-in-surface-tension/10828.rss">Cornered by (respawning?) marines in Surface Tension</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Cornered by (respawning?) marines in Surface Tension</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Tei]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>i’ve been working on this corridor FOR AN HOUR!<br>
Shortly after the warehouse full of tripwire explosives and the weapons warehouse, there’s a 3 story building with its interior destroyed. Once you find your way through a hole in the floor on the second floor, there’s a short road that leads up to several shipping containers. This is where i’m stuck.</p>
<p>i’m corned at the starting end of this short tunnel behind a fence and piping. Every time i poke me head out, there’s another 6 or 7 marines waiting for me. i keep popping my head out and taking shots at them until they’re gone. As SOON AS i try to progress, 6 or 7 MORE show up and shove me back into my corner. i’ve spent at least an hour fighting off these damn marines. i have NO AMMO left, A WHOPPiNG 3 HEALTH and i’ve been quick-saving and quick-loading to the point that my fingers never leave the F5 and F9 keys.</p>
<p>Do these marines respawn? Even if i turn the difficulty down, the marine’s aim is always perfect and i’m killed the split second i try to leave my hiding spot. i can’t even grab any of the medkits they drop because i can’t move 2 inches before i’m dead.</p>
<p>Peak left, pop off one round with the shotgun, hide, listen to see if somebody took damage, quicksave. Peak left, die, reload. Peak left, die, reload. Peak left, die, reload. Peak left, die, reload. Peak left, pop off one round with the shotgun, hide, listen to see if somebody took damage, quicksave. Peak left, pop off one round with the shotgun, hide, listen to see if somebody took damage, quicksave. Repeat.</p>
<p>-Kawai Tei-</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/cornered-by-respawning-marines-in-surface-tension/10828/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/cornered-by-respawning-marines-in-surface-tension/10828/1</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 19 Sep 2012 14:54:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-10828-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/cornered-by-respawning-marines-in-surface-tension/10828.rss">Cornered by (respawning?) marines in Surface Tension</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
