<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Workshop Issue</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/workshop-issue/14725</link>
    <description>There are a few problems with the workshop. Any addon that involves new sound effects (Like any added Vox messages) don&#39;t have sound. This could be a problem on my end, but that being said, the workshop also has caused problems for others (Specifically the Hazard Course mod cannot be uploaded to the workshop for a number of reasons).</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 31 Mar 2016 04:11:14 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>In-game Issues</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/workshop-issue/14725.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Workshop Issue</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[KevinJRattman]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I think in the description of the VOX mod you are trying to download would say to enter a console command to actually play the sound.</p>
<p>This shouldnt be the case though. Devs should fix it but I have not heard from them since. Last time I asked they said… nothing. But Im sure they are.</p>
<p>Workshop do indeed have too much problems in its current state. About Hazard Course devs said they will fix this.</p>
<p>About cubemaps, Im also having similar problems but in different manner. Cubemaps work perfectly fine on my end but when I gove the map file to others for testing, on one tester’s end cubemap was not working correctly. It was like buzzing all over the place (if thats even correct word). I also tried the same thing by putting it up on workshop but same. Not sure why that happens.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/workshop-issue/14725/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/workshop-issue/14725/3</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 31 Mar 2016 04:11:14 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14725-3</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/workshop-issue/14725.rss">Workshop Issue</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Workshop Issue</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Admiral_Sakai]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Also, uploading to the workshop from a “staging” folder in the main “bms” directory seems to be destroying my cubemaps. Is anyone else experiencing this problem, and is there a way around it?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/workshop-issue/14725/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/workshop-issue/14725/2</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 31 Mar 2016 02:19:33 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14725-2</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/workshop-issue/14725.rss">Workshop Issue</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Workshop Issue</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[THEButterFingerBatMa]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>There are a few problems with the workshop. Any addon that involves new sound effects (Like any added Vox messages) don’t have sound. This could be a problem on my end, but that being said, the workshop also has caused problems for others (Specifically the Hazard Course mod cannot be uploaded to the workshop for a number of reasons).</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/workshop-issue/14725/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/workshop-issue/14725/1</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 31 Mar 2016 00:27:39 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14725-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/workshop-issue/14725.rss">Workshop Issue</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
