<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>A Black Mesa Tale (revisited)</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/a-black-mesa-tale-revisited/13120</link>
    <description>A couple of forums ago I had created a story called &quot;A Black Mesa Tale&quot;. The story used forum member&#39;s names in its telling and everyone seemed to enjoy it. I was quickly forced to create another one for those who wanted to be included and eventually, a third story was created (the one I enjoyed the most because of its included links). [/SIZE] Since they were lost because of forum updates I&#39;ve had multiple requests to re-post them and today I&#39;m doing that.

These will be shown in order of their creation. Today&#39;s is the original story and the others will follow with a few days break between them. Looking over it it&#39;s funny how many former members are named that you don&#39;t see around here anymore but, I hope you enjoy the stories anyway!
[quote]
[align=center][b]A Black Mesa Tale Part 1[/b][/align]

jerry Siggs considered himself a geekofalltrades but was better known for just being an OldDirtyBastard. Fortunately, this was one time Lord Grievous Patonki didn&#39;t need his help. He figured GuitarJim could simply bring his Ibanez Raminator to his Mont_Blanc residence, since he had Houston Security Officers on hand, and could meet him on the second Level for lessons. He was a much better choice than just Someonerandm. 

Wearing his shifty PJAMA he went downstairs to clean up his Bloodshot eyes and grab something to eat. baconeggs, a Cup o Joe and raw_bean Soup sounded good as well as the new Frozen Cham treat his kids had told him about. Unfortunately, the brokenfridgehing prevented him from considering adding the Chocolate Milk that Da Milk Man had delivered so he passed on the extra treat. 

Turning on the stove he reached for The can of raw_bean Soup but mistakingly grabbed the Jethrosoup instead. What a mistake that would prove to be. Grabbing a RandomSpoon from the drawer, for use with TheSuperNova microwave he had just purchased, he noticed a bur and a-dot of Fungus on the handle. 

That was the last straw. If Luciel couldn&#39;t do a better job cleaning than this then she&#39;s just got to go! She&#39;s always watching that stupid animal channel CatzEyes93 with that sudpuzzer host JamesKane who thinks he&#39;s MrSnaztastic when in actuality he&#39;s just Mr. Someguy and a pfannkuchen_gesicht to top it off! If he was really smart he would have reached out to one of his own show&#39;s sponsors for help. Dr Perky and Dr. Karamazov could have gotten rid of that crudface condition without a problem. 

I&#39;ll deal with her later, he said to himself as he proceeded to turn the temperature on the microwave from FireTime all the way up to Omega_Absolute. This was, unfortunately, precisely opposite of what the Jethrosoup instructions called for and soon a cloud began to appear from the oven. In reality, it was MarshmallowRadiation filing the room and before he knew what was happening he was screaming Imonfire!!! just praying that Bathroom Security would hear him. 

GuitarJim had just arrived at the front Door. Hearing an ungodly scream he ran to the source only to find Lord Patonki&#39;s prize DiePoente cookware burned and on the floor and what appeared to be some type of a large fowl laying beside it. It was a darkone, not a Winged One, had a huge Ballsopt on the top of its head and lay motionless. 

Lord Grievous Patonki was off to eternalness. His Collision with fate brought him what he had searched for. 

A place to rest..... 

a place of solace......

and perhaps............


A resortforyou?
[/quote]
[url=https://forums.blackmesasource.com/showthread.php?t=17968]A Black Mesa Tale Part 2[/url]
[url=https://forums.blackmesasource.com/showthread.php?p=576097#post576097]A Multimedia Black Mesa Tale Part 3[/url]</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2014 21:48:48 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Show Off</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/a-black-mesa-tale-revisited/13120.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>A Black Mesa Tale (revisited)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Luciel]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Loving it though, you do realize I´m a guy and not a girl…right?  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/frowning.png?v=9" title=":frowning:" class="emoji" alt=":frowning:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/a-black-mesa-tale-revisited/13120/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/a-black-mesa-tale-revisited/13120/6</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2014 21:48:48 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13120-6</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/a-black-mesa-tale-revisited/13120.rss">A Black Mesa Tale (revisited)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>A Black Mesa Tale (revisited)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[_rot_fodder]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Ah yes, I remember this now!  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=9" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/a-black-mesa-tale-revisited/13120/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/a-black-mesa-tale-revisited/13120/5</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2014 20:41:42 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13120-5</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/a-black-mesa-tale-revisited/13120.rss">A Black Mesa Tale (revisited)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>A Black Mesa Tale (revisited)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Deathmonkey7]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Yeah, me too. Its like a memorial for lost members.  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=9" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"><br>
Great work!</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/a-black-mesa-tale-revisited/13120/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/a-black-mesa-tale-revisited/13120/4</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2014 19:38:37 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13120-4</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/a-black-mesa-tale-revisited/13120.rss">A Black Mesa Tale (revisited)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>A Black Mesa Tale (revisited)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypt]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I haven’t seen some of these names in a while.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/a-black-mesa-tale-revisited/13120/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/a-black-mesa-tale-revisited/13120/3</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2014 18:01:35 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13120-3</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/a-black-mesa-tale-revisited/13120.rss">A Black Mesa Tale (revisited)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>A Black Mesa Tale (revisited)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Jack_Freeman]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>yay this again</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/a-black-mesa-tale-revisited/13120/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/a-black-mesa-tale-revisited/13120/2</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2014 16:37:16 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13120-2</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/a-black-mesa-tale-revisited/13120.rss">A Black Mesa Tale (revisited)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>A Black Mesa Tale (revisited)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[CPU]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>A couple of forums ago I had created a story called “A Black Mesa Tale”. The story used forum member’s names in its telling and everyone seemed to enjoy it. I was quickly forced to create another one for those who wanted to be included and eventually, a third story was created (the one I enjoyed the most because of its included links). [/SIZE] Since they were lost because of forum updates I’ve had multiple requests to re-post them and today I’m doing that.</p>
<p>These will be shown in order of their creation. Today’s is the original story and the others will follow with a few days break between them. Looking over it it’s funny how many former members are named that you don’t see around here anymore but, I hope you enjoy the stories anyway!</p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>[align=center]<span class="bbcode-b">A Black Mesa Tale Part 1</span>[/align]</p>
<p>jerry Siggs considered himself a geekofalltrades but was better known for just being an OldDirtyBastard. Fortunately, this was one time Lord Grievous Patonki didn’t need his help. He figured GuitarJim could simply bring his Ibanez Raminator to his Mont_Blanc residence, since he had Houston Security Officers on hand, and could meet him on the second Level for lessons. He was a much better choice than just Someonerandm.</p>
<p>Wearing his shifty PJAMA he went downstairs to clean up his Bloodshot eyes and grab something to eat. baconeggs, a Cup o Joe and raw_bean Soup sounded good as well as the new Frozen Cham treat his kids had told him about. Unfortunately, the brokenfridgehing prevented him from considering adding the Chocolate Milk that Da Milk Man had delivered so he passed on the extra treat.</p>
<p>Turning on the stove he reached for The can of raw_bean Soup but mistakingly grabbed the Jethrosoup instead. What a mistake that would prove to be. Grabbing a RandomSpoon from the drawer, for use with TheSuperNova microwave he had just purchased, he noticed a bur and a-dot of Fungus on the handle.</p>
<p>That was the last straw. If Luciel couldn’t do a better job cleaning than this then she’s just got to go! She’s always watching that stupid animal channel CatzEyes93 with that sudpuzzer host JamesKane who thinks he’s MrSnaztastic when in actuality he’s just Mr. Someguy and a pfannkuchen_gesicht to top it off! If he was really smart he would have reached out to one of his own show’s sponsors for help. Dr Perky and Dr. Karamazov could have gotten rid of that crudface condition without a problem.</p>
<p>I’ll deal with her later, he said to himself as he proceeded to turn the temperature on the microwave from FireTime all the way up to Omega_Absolute. This was, unfortunately, precisely opposite of what the Jethrosoup instructions called for and soon a cloud began to appear from the oven. In reality, it was MarshmallowRadiation filing the room and before he knew what was happening he was screaming Imonfire!!! just praying that Bathroom Security would hear him.</p>
<p>GuitarJim had just arrived at the front Door. Hearing an ungodly scream he ran to the source only to find Lord Patonki’s prize DiePoente cookware burned and on the floor and what appeared to be some type of a large fowl laying beside it. It was a darkone, not a Winged One, had a huge Ballsopt on the top of its head and lay motionless.</p>
<p>Lord Grievous Patonki was off to eternalness. His Collision with fate brought him what he had searched for.</p>
<p>A place to rest…</p>
<p>a place of solace…</p>
<p>and perhaps…</p>
<p>A resortforyou?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p><a href="https://forums.blackmesasource.com/showthread.php?t=17968" data-bbcode="true">A Black Mesa Tale Part 2</a><br>
<a href="https://forums.blackmesasource.com/showthread.php?p=576097#post576097" data-bbcode="true">A Multimedia Black Mesa Tale Part 3</a></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/a-black-mesa-tale-revisited/13120/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/a-black-mesa-tale-revisited/13120/1</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2014 15:57:06 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13120-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/a-black-mesa-tale-revisited/13120.rss">A Black Mesa Tale (revisited)</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
