<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>New Gaming Rig</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/new-gaming-rig/13369</link>
    <description>Hello, i just happen to have 2000 pounds on my hands and i want a new gaming rig and since there are so many options and so many wrong ways to build a computer from parts that i thought it would be a good idea to ask you guys, what do you recommend me ? Just a few.. pointers, i want a maximum of 24 inch monitor and i am interested in crossfire/SLI
       And since im making a post anyway i was wondering has anyone here played any of the Half-Life games/mods with Oculus ?</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2014 14:41:54 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Help and Support</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/new-gaming-rig/13369.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>New Gaming Rig</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Fryymon]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I got a clear view of what i want now, thanks a lot for your replies guys, they’ve been helpful</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/new-gaming-rig/13369/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/new-gaming-rig/13369/5</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2014 14:41:54 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13369-5</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/new-gaming-rig/13369.rss">New Gaming Rig</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>New Gaming Rig</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Orpheon]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Over on Tom’s Hardware they have a lot of great guides for building computers, and how to get the best for your money. Also, I’ve personally never gone wrong trusting the reviews on newegg. Just go with anything rated 4 or 5 eggs, and if you really want to be sure, read at least the most helpful reviews to find out anything else you might need to know about the part before you buy it.</p>
<p>What I’d suggest:</p>
<p>CPU: Intel Core i5-4690K</p>
<p>Motherboard: The brands I trust the most are Gigabyte, ASUS, and ASRock. Just make sure it’s reviewed well and has everything you’ll need - if you’re gonna do Crossfire or SLI make sure it’s got support for that, make sure it’s got enough SATA and USB connections, etc.</p>
<p>GPU: I don’t know if you have any particular brand loyalty, but the best bang for your buck right seems to be AMD cards if you’re gonna go single card - try an R9 280X or an R9 290. If you’re gonna SLI/Crossfire, check out how the games you want to play do with multi-GPU setups. Not all games benefit all that much from SLI/Crossfire AFAIK.</p>
<p>Power supply: Corsair, Antec, and Cooler Master are good brands, not too sure about anything else. Again, newegg reviews can help here. Additionally, make sure the wattage is high enough to handle all your components, that you have enough amps on the 12v rails (in order to power your GPU), and that you have enough connectors to power all your devices.</p>
<p>Storage: I’ve gone with Western Digital, Samsung, and Seagate. All drives seem to perform well. I’ve had the most failures with Seagate, but most of the drives I work with are Seagate, so that may not mean anything. Also consider an SSD for your OS and games. It really makes a huge difference in boot and load times. Good brands are OCZ, Intel, Samsung, ADATA, Crucial, Sandisk.</p>
<p>RAM: Get at least 8GB, and make sure you get the right speed for your motherboard. G.Skill, Crucial, Mushkin, and Corsair are good brands, even ADATA or Kingston might do.</p>
<p>Monitors: ASUS and Acer make good monitors. You might notice some light bleed on some of the cheaper ones though.</p>
<p>Keyboard/Mouse: I’m a Logitech fanboy. The G9/G9x is still my favorite mouse ever.</p>
<p>Hopefully some of that helps.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/new-gaming-rig/13369/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/new-gaming-rig/13369/4</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2014 00:09:39 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13369-4</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/new-gaming-rig/13369.rss">New Gaming Rig</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>New Gaming Rig</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[sersoft]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Pentium anniversary edition G3258, it’s great for games and overclocks like a beast.</p>
<p>It’s only a dual core though, but with a cheaper CPU you can afford more powerful GPU(s) and 99.7% of games today are not optimized for more than 2 cores.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/new-gaming-rig/13369/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/new-gaming-rig/13369/3</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2014 21:57:37 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13369-3</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/new-gaming-rig/13369.rss">New Gaming Rig</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>New Gaming Rig</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Kairouseki]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I don’t know about the price since I’m not English, but I’d suggest an i5 4670k, a GTX 770 or above (maybe someone else could suggest AMD cards), and 8GB of RAM (Gskill and Corsair are good brands, others too). For power supply, Corsair is a good brand and I think Seasonic too. Get either Western Digital or Toshiba HDDs/SSDs as I’ve heard bad things about Seagate. I’m not really all that sure what to look for in a motherboard, just get one that has decent reviews, has all the features you want, and supports the rest of your hardware (enough PCI(-E) slots, right CPU slot type, etc).</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/new-gaming-rig/13369/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/new-gaming-rig/13369/2</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2014 16:55:08 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13369-2</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/new-gaming-rig/13369.rss">New Gaming Rig</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>New Gaming Rig</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Fryymon]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Hello, i just happen to have 2000 pounds on my hands and i want a new gaming rig and since there are so many options and so many wrong ways to build a computer from parts that i thought it would be a good idea to ask you guys, what do you recommend me ? Just a few… pointers, i want a maximum of 24 inch monitor and i am interested in crossfire/SLI<br>
And since im making a post anyway i was wondering has anyone here played any of the Half-Life games/mods with Oculus ?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/new-gaming-rig/13369/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/new-gaming-rig/13369/1</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2014 09:29:22 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13369-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/new-gaming-rig/13369.rss">New Gaming Rig</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
