<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Charity, yay or nay?</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/charity-yay-or-nay/3043</link>
    <description>So, I&#39;d figure I&#39;d make a serious post for good measure.

So I chose the subject of charity. Seeing as it&#39;s a trendy thing to do lately. What&#39;s your view on charity? Do you think charity is needed? Do you feel like you&#39;re supposed to participate in charity because your country/culture might have been involved in the current situations of a certain country?


I for one dislike everything about charity. The concept, the idea, the process, the goals, the means, everything.

I really do not care that there&#39;s people in Africa being hungry, that there&#39;s people on certain islands that lost everything they had. I do not care for people that lost their job (even if they couldn&#39;t help it). I do not care that certain species of animal are on the brink of extinction (despite being a massive animal lover).

And above all, I personally see no valid reason -at all- to give my money to those charities. And if I wish to do so at some point in time, I&#39;ll do so myself, and I do not need some people in the streets to tell me what charity I should support and what not.

To me, charity is a massive waste of money and resources, and for what exactly? To corrupt a corrupt country even further (Haiti, for example)? To make sure that a rare species of animal can only exist in zoos? To give certain people some food and water and medicine, just to keep them alive, while they&#39;re of no use to society in general?

I&#39;d rather keep my money to myself and support my family and friends when they need me, but I do not wish to waste it on things I do not know and have no desire of knowing.


I also don&#39;t expect total strangers to give me resources and/or money when I&#39;m in dire need of said resources and/or money (before I get shot down as a hypocrite)</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 28 Feb 2010 05:44:27 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Off Topic</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/charity-yay-or-nay/3043.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Charity, yay or nay?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[papernick]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Bolteh">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/b/ecae2f/40.png" class="avatar"> Bolteh:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Well probably not, but I wouldn’t think of them as useless and pointless anymore.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>The thing that shocks me the most about your posts is that you brand some people’s lives as ‘useless’ and ‘pointless’ just because YOU think they live without purpose. Who are you to say which life is or isn’t useful?</p>
<p>Also:</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Bolteh">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/b/ecae2f/40.png" class="avatar"> Bolteh:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Abuse is only a small fraction of what ChildLine does. Most of the other things are subjects I used to talk to my parents about. But ye, the abuse. Great, they talked to someone about how they got/get abused. ChildLine enlists someone to come and take the kid away from his family so he doesn’t get abused anymore. And what does it matter? Nothing at all. The kid still got mental/physical scars, damage has been done and can’t be undone. When a child gets abused, it’s already too late to help.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Would you prefer to be as far away as possible from the person who abuses you, or to keep getting abused?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/charity-yay-or-nay/3043/355">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/charity-yay-or-nay/3043/355</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 28 Feb 2010 05:44:27 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3043-355</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/charity-yay-or-nay/3043.rss">Charity, yay or nay?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Charity, yay or nay?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Brother_Shrike]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I just spent a week in Texas cleaning up after Ike and I have to say, it was the most meaningful thing I’ve ever done. Doing charity just… <em>cough</em> … feels good man.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/charity-yay-or-nay/3043/354">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/charity-yay-or-nay/3043/354</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 27 Feb 2010 22:24:04 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3043-354</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/charity-yay-or-nay/3043.rss">Charity, yay or nay?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Charity, yay or nay?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[noonem]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Boosts my likeability.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/charity-yay-or-nay/3043/353">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/charity-yay-or-nay/3043/353</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 27 Feb 2010 20:37:56 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3043-353</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/charity-yay-or-nay/3043.rss">Charity, yay or nay?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Charity, yay or nay?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[JohnKiller118]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username=":retard:">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 :retard::</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I’m surprised you even know the meaning of “irony” if you use that thread as an argument.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username=":retard:">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 :retard::</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Well, it’s thanks to people like me that the rest of the sane universe has these negative views about the human race.</p>
<p>“Charity sux!!”, “because that XX number of bad people are stealing and other bad shit in the destroyed country we should deny the entire country aid”, “it’s because of charity that 00 good thing things happen… even though that isn’t true… but fuk you im so awsum”, “Charity suxs!”, “I have a massive e-penis, I’m the best”, “I’m glad I don’t live in a shit cuntry that needs help, go help urselves!”, “Charity suxs!”, “duuurrrrrrrrrrrrr!”, “derp”</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>fix’d<br>
:retard:</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/charity-yay-or-nay/3043/352">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/charity-yay-or-nay/3043/352</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 27 Feb 2010 03:39:49 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3043-352</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/charity-yay-or-nay/3043.rss">Charity, yay or nay?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Charity, yay or nay?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[bur]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Bolteh">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/b/ecae2f/40.png" class="avatar"> Bolteh:</div>
<blockquote>
<ul>
<li>Most of Africa’s problems are because of their own institutions, governments and people</li>
</ul>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Most of those institutions and governments were set up by the west. The people have been suppressed and kept dumb by their corrupt governments and by the Catholic church.<br>
Corrupt leaders instated by the CIA come to mind as an example of shit that still goes on today.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Bolteh">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/b/ecae2f/40.png" class="avatar"> Bolteh:</div>
<blockquote>
<ul>
<li>The west may have jumpstarted it, but those countries rebelled and they wanted freedom. Well they can have their freedom, too bad they’re not doing anything with it and still expect help from the west.</li>
</ul>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>No. They were stripped of resources and all their independence and existing institutions were destroyed. The west then just abandoned them, when they had practically nothing left.</p>
<p>If some rich dude with a gun went out on the streets and robbed a random middle class person and then beat the shit out of him and left him lying on the floor, possibly with a friend of the rich dude watching over him so he can’t help himself, that would be about the same.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Bolteh">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/b/ecae2f/40.png" class="avatar"> Bolteh:</div>
<blockquote>
<ul>
<li>Africa’s always been centuries behind on the west. Even before the west started exploring the continent.</li>
</ul>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>That’s not true. There were rich cultures there before the west started pillaging the continent. The Egyptian culture comes to mind as an example. There’s more, but I can’t think of any off the top of my head.<br>
And even if it were true, does that justify all the suffering caused to them?</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Bolteh">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/b/ecae2f/40.png" class="avatar"> Bolteh:</div>
<blockquote>
<ul>
<li>No, I should not pay for King Leopold the Third’s slaughter of the Congolese people. Just like you shouldn’t go to prison for a murder your cousin committed. Just like you shouldn’t go to prison because your uncle is a scammer.</li>
</ul>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Yes, we should. Those people are <span class="bbcode-i">still</span> in dire straits because of things that happened a hundred years ago, just like we are still benefiting from the same events.<br>
They’re suffering so we can have the wealth we have.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/charity-yay-or-nay/3043/351">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/charity-yay-or-nay/3043/351</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 26 Feb 2010 13:39:13 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3043-351</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/charity-yay-or-nay/3043.rss">Charity, yay or nay?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Charity, yay or nay?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Bolteh]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="danielsangeo">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/user_avatar/leakfree.org/danielsangeo/40/4347_2.png" class="avatar"> danielsangeo:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>That’s okay, Bolteh.  When you’re in dire need for assistance, there’s someone out there that’ll want to help you even if they don’t know you.  They offer you more courtesy and maturity than you offer them.  They’re pretty stupid, huh?</p>
<p>And with that, I’m done with this this thread.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>And there will also be people that will laugh at me and do nothing to help me (SassyRobot comes to mind). So what’s your point? Maturity has nothing to do with it. As a matter of fact, I participated in more charities when I was a kid (granted, forced by schools) than now.</p>
<p>There are people that care and there are people that don’t.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/charity-yay-or-nay/3043/350">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/charity-yay-or-nay/3043/350</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 26 Feb 2010 12:55:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3043-350</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/charity-yay-or-nay/3043.rss">Charity, yay or nay?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Charity, yay or nay?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[danielsangeo]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>That’s okay, Bolteh.  When you’re in dire need for assistance, there’s someone out there that’ll want to help you even if they don’t know you.  They offer you more courtesy and maturity than you offer them.  They’re pretty stupid, huh?</p>
<p>And with that, I’m done with this this thread.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/charity-yay-or-nay/3043/349">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/charity-yay-or-nay/3043/349</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 26 Feb 2010 12:33:56 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3043-349</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/charity-yay-or-nay/3043.rss">Charity, yay or nay?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Charity, yay or nay?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Bolteh]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Well probably not, but I wouldn’t think of them as useless and pointless anymore.</p>
<p>Buy ye, you’re right, my complete lack of care for someone I don’t know comes into play as well.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/charity-yay-or-nay/3043/348">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/charity-yay-or-nay/3043/348</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 26 Feb 2010 10:22:59 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3043-348</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/charity-yay-or-nay/3043.rss">Charity, yay or nay?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Charity, yay or nay?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Soup]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>You obviously wouldn’t become supportive, judging by everything else you’ve said.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/charity-yay-or-nay/3043/347">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/charity-yay-or-nay/3043/347</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 26 Feb 2010 09:30:19 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3043-347</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/charity-yay-or-nay/3043.rss">Charity, yay or nay?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Charity, yay or nay?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Bolteh]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Well yes, both are necessary. Their leaders and institutions -should- help their people. problem is: they simply don’t and won’t. And while charity may make the lives of the people there slightly more bearable, it’s still pointless in the effort of getting Africa out of the pile of shit it’s buried in and back on the road of evolution.</p>
<p>And yes, I may be a bad person for not caring about those people enough to support them without a specific set goal, but the moment the red light turns green and everything is set for a straight line to a proper future with no hindrance, then I may just become supportive of charities with such goals. But until that day, I don’t see the use of supporting something that can’t develop.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/charity-yay-or-nay/3043/346">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/charity-yay-or-nay/3043/346</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 26 Feb 2010 08:58:06 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3043-346</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/charity-yay-or-nay/3043.rss">Charity, yay or nay?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Charity, yay or nay?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[danielsangeo]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Bolteh: Don’t you think that BOTH are necessary?  Get their leaders and institutions AND charity to help those hurt by theirs and other’s countries?  Or should we not do ANYTHING to help the victims while this crap is in place?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/charity-yay-or-nay/3043/345">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/charity-yay-or-nay/3043/345</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 26 Feb 2010 08:23:14 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3043-345</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/charity-yay-or-nay/3043.rss">Charity, yay or nay?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Charity, yay or nay?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Bolteh]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>No, I’m saying that it’s pointless in trying to get them going while their leaders and institutions stop them from moving on.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/charity-yay-or-nay/3043/344">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/charity-yay-or-nay/3043/344</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 26 Feb 2010 07:50:31 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3043-344</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/charity-yay-or-nay/3043.rss">Charity, yay or nay?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Charity, yay or nay?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Soup]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>So you think an entire continent should pay because of the actions of other countries and corrupt leaders of their own countries?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/charity-yay-or-nay/3043/343">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/charity-yay-or-nay/3043/343</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 26 Feb 2010 07:48:36 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3043-343</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/charity-yay-or-nay/3043.rss">Charity, yay or nay?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Charity, yay or nay?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Bolteh]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="JohnKiller118">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 JohnKiller118:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>It’s so ironic that it’s almost sad.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I’m surprised you even know the meaning of “irony” if you use that thread as an argument.</p>
<p><em>edit</em> FFFFFFFFUUU, I was typing a lengthy reply to Burbinator’s post, but then Firefox crashed.</p>
<p>Anyway, recap:</p>
<ul>
<li>Well, fair trade is charity then. I just see it as buying products I prefer over expensive brands. I’m not going to stop buying it just because I dislike charity.</li>
<li>Most of Africa’s problems are because of their own institutions, governments and people</li>
<li>The west may have jumpstarted it, but those countries rebelled and they wanted freedom. Well they can have their freedom, too bad they’re not doing anything with it and still expect help from the west.</li>
<li>Africa’s always been centuries behind on the west. Even before the west started exploring the continent.</li>
<li>No, I should not pay for King Leopold the Third’s slaughter of the Congolese people. Just like you shouldn’t go to prison for a murder your cousin committed. Just like you shouldn’t go to prison because your uncle is a scammer.</li>
</ul>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/charity-yay-or-nay/3043/342">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/charity-yay-or-nay/3043/342</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 26 Feb 2010 07:13:32 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3043-342</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/charity-yay-or-nay/3043.rss">Charity, yay or nay?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Charity, yay or nay?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[JohnKiller118]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="DansonDelta40">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/d/bbce88/40.png" class="avatar"> DansonDelta40:</div>
<blockquote>
<p><span class="mention">@Johnkiller</span>:</p>
<p>Your facepalm may be inappropriate here. There is an actual disorder called <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Trypanophobia" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Trypanophobia</a> or, simply put, “needle phobia”, which cannot be helped and is supposedly an inheritable genetic trait. My ex fiance suffers from that, too.</p>
<p>I once went donating blood, and caught an infection in the process, leaving me suffering from severe diarrhoea for two days. I was at the brink of lethal dehydration when it finally stopped. That was the first and last time I ever went donating blood.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Well, that was… informative. :FFFUUU:<br>
It just seemed like he was looking for any excuse to not help people.</p>
<p>Whatever, Bolteh’s still an ass.<br>
And to think he was the one who accused Americans of being assholes in the <span class="bbcode-i">“Ask an American”</span> thread. It’s so ironic that it’s almost sad.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/charity-yay-or-nay/3043/341">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/charity-yay-or-nay/3043/341</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 26 Feb 2010 02:38:11 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3043-341</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/charity-yay-or-nay/3043.rss">Charity, yay or nay?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Charity, yay or nay?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[bur]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I didn’t say the farmers didn’t get any money. I said you bought their goods, so do they obviously get money.<br>
And to the rest in that paragraph: without that organization that took upon them the burden of charity it wouldn’t be possible to buy, and you’re <span class="bbcode-i">donating money</span> by buying the products from them.<br>
I guess you could look at it as paying them for the service of making the products available to you.</p>
<p>Also, it’s not just mistakes done in the past. Those “mistakes” still go on today, and yes, you should try to make up for mistakes stillmade  by your own culture all the time.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/charity-yay-or-nay/3043/340">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/charity-yay-or-nay/3043/340</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 26 Feb 2010 01:57:29 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3043-340</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/charity-yay-or-nay/3043.rss">Charity, yay or nay?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Charity, yay or nay?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Soup]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Maybe you should care because it’s unfair? You were bitching about how we were just as rude as you (well, no, you left that part out) so surely unfairness is something of an issue with you?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/charity-yay-or-nay/3043/339">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/charity-yay-or-nay/3043/339</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 26 Feb 2010 00:42:08 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3043-339</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/charity-yay-or-nay/3043.rss">Charity, yay or nay?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Charity, yay or nay?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Bolteh]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Burbinator">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Burbinator:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>tl;dr: Africa can’t sell domestic products anywhere because of unfair conduct. The west can sell their products everywhere because of unfair conduct. Africa is in its current state largely because of the west.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>And as long as this keeps up, I see no point in wasting money on charity for anything in Africa.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Burbinator">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Burbinator:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>In other words, fairtrade <span class="bbcode-i">is</span> charity. You buy materials for your own needs, but the rest of your money goes to the organization that makes it possible for you to buy it.<br>
I donate €5 a month to Oxfam (a fairtrade organization), and I sometimes buy from them too.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>So you’re saying that the farmers don’t get any money (or material) from it, that it all goes to the organization? Then what’s the point of that fair trade business? Nono, farmers do get money/materials, and sure, that might be through an organization that took upon them the burden of charity, but the actual process doesn’t change. Person makes product, I buy product, person gets money/materials. So I actively paid for the service/product of someone, so that person can keep on doing what he does and make a living that way. I prefer that method over blindly giving money so they can stomp a water tap near a village, while its inhabitants remain a waste of space.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Burbinator">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Burbinator:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Your whole stance on Africa seems to be that they got themselves in this mess, so they don’t deserve any help. That simply isn’t true at all.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Sure, you can say “it’s the fault of the west”, and you’re right about that, but why should I make up for mistakes done in the past? I had nothing to do with it. It’s just how humanity has evolved. Natural selection. The strong survive. The strong west came in and ripped the weak Africa dry of its resources. Yes, it’s unfair, but why should I care? There’s no way we can undo it, most of Africa is dead land because of events in the past (whether you like it or not) and there’s nothing you can do about it, so I see no point in pumping money to attempt to develop Africa, while there’s little to no room for development.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/charity-yay-or-nay/3043/338">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/charity-yay-or-nay/3043/338</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 25 Feb 2010 21:58:13 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3043-338</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/charity-yay-or-nay/3043.rss">Charity, yay or nay?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Charity, yay or nay?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[bur]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Bolteh">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/b/ecae2f/40.png" class="avatar"> Bolteh:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Then why are people still wasting charity on Africa? Why don’t Africans “just go out and reap all the lovely fruits mother nature gave them”? The first humans did it, why can’t they?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Because European civilization stole their resources, destroyed their civilizations and suppressed their peoples?</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Bolteh">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/b/ecae2f/40.png" class="avatar"> Bolteh:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I’ll tell you why they can’t, because they can survive by charity, so they have no reason to produce their own food, collect their own water, develop their own civilization.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>No. They can’t even survive thanks to charity. Charity helps those that need it.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Bolteh">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/b/ecae2f/40.png" class="avatar"> Bolteh:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Also, gorillas in Africa:<br>
<a href="https://www.solarnavigator.net/animal_kingdom/animal_images/Gorilla_distribution_map_Africa.jpg" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://www.solarnavigator.net/animal_kingdom/animal_images/Gorilla_distribution_map_Africa.jpg</a></p>
<p>(Just to make it clear: the red bits are the habitat of the gorilla, massive amount of jungle indeed)</p>
<p>Besides, jungles aren’t the best areas to farm in, unless you put up a banana farm.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>My point was, Africa isn’t a barren wasteland, it has plenty of space to use productively.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Bolteh">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/b/ecae2f/40.png" class="avatar"> Bolteh:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Side note: I do buy fair trade, btw. But that can’t really be considered charity, since I buy materials for my own needs. Though I do like the idea that poor farmers who farmed those materials  get a decent price for it, even they still get a lot less than what their products go for. But at least they did something for it, rather than just sitting there being poor and hungry.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>You know what fairtrade is about? Poor farmers and such selling their goods at fair price around the world, which they simply can’t do <span class="bbcode-i">because of western companies and policies</span>.</p>
<p>One of the reasons why they can’t is that Europe and the US, mainly, produce more food than they can sell. They then dump it on Africa where they can sell it for less than local farmers and businesses can, because of which they can’t survive.</p>
<p>A second reason is import taxes. Europe (and other areas too, probably) have high import taxes on food, which forces African producers to sell their products for more than food that’s sold here, because of which they can’t sell anything.<br>
As soon as an African country tries to enforce import taxes, we extort them so they won’t. Many countries receive massive amounts of financial help which they absolutely need (which is because of us in the first place) from Europe, which gives us a lot of power over them.</p>
<p>tl;dr: Africa can’t sell domestic products anywhere because of unfair conduct. The west can sell their products everywhere because of unfair conduct. Africa is in its current state largely because of the west.</p>
<p>In other words, fairtrade <span class="bbcode-i">is</span> charity. You buy materials for your own needs, but the rest of your money goes to the organization that makes it possible for you to buy it.<br>
I donate €5 a month to Oxfam (a fairtrade organization), and I sometimes buy from them too.</p>
<p>Your whole stance on Africa seems to be that they got themselves in this mess, so they don’t deserve any help. That simply isn’t true at all.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/charity-yay-or-nay/3043/337">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/charity-yay-or-nay/3043/337</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 25 Feb 2010 20:46:15 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3043-337</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/charity-yay-or-nay/3043.rss">Charity, yay or nay?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Charity, yay or nay?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Deutscher_Scharfschu]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>If the Democratic republic of Congo was properly and efficiently farmed (like California), then they could feed the entirety of the African population. the problem is that:</p>
<p>A) the government and economy are shit.<br>
B) there is zero infrastructure to transport that food<br>
C) Even if the the country wasn’t royally fucked, they still have to transport materials through other war-torn African countries.</p>
<p>I wish there was a way to get their shit together.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/charity-yay-or-nay/3043/336">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/charity-yay-or-nay/3043/336</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 25 Feb 2010 20:09:35 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3043-336</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/charity-yay-or-nay/3043.rss">Charity, yay or nay?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Charity, yay or nay?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Bolteh]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Then why are people still wasting charity on Africa? Why don’t Africans “just go out and reap all the lovely fruits mother nature gave them”? The first humans did it, why can’t they? I’ll tell you why they can’t, because they can survive by charity, so they have no reason to produce their own food, collect their own water, develop their own civilization.</p>
<p>Also, gorillas in Africa:<br>
<span alt="" class="broken-image" title="This image is broken"><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-unlink svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#unlink"></use></svg></span></p>
<p>(Just to make it clear: the red bits are the habitat of the gorilla, massive amount of jungle indeed)</p>
<p>Besides, jungles aren’t the best areas to farm in, unless you put up a banana farm.</p>
<p>Side note: I do buy fair trade, btw. But that can’t really be considered charity, since I buy materials for my own needs. Though I do like the idea that poor farmers who farmed those materials  get a decent price for it, even they still get a lot less than what their products go for. But at least they did something for it, rather than just sitting there being poor and hungry.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/charity-yay-or-nay/3043/335">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/charity-yay-or-nay/3043/335</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 25 Feb 2010 20:05:38 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3043-335</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/charity-yay-or-nay/3043.rss">Charity, yay or nay?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Charity, yay or nay?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[bur]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Bolteh, Africa isn’t dead land. There’s plenty of possibility for farming and industry. There are even plenty of forests and jungles. Where do you think gorillas live?<br>
That’s the worst argument you’ve made so far.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/charity-yay-or-nay/3043/334">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/charity-yay-or-nay/3043/334</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 25 Feb 2010 19:34:42 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3043-334</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/charity-yay-or-nay/3043.rss">Charity, yay or nay?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Charity, yay or nay?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[mattemuse]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="koolkalang">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/k/45deac/40.png" class="avatar"> koolkalang:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Bolteh, you are now stuck in a shithole. You have been beat and shat and pissed on, stranded in the middle of the desert,  mutilated part of your body, and you are now being fried on a hot day on the desert sand.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>haha I thought you were talking about this thread at first when i read that  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/smiley.png?v=9" title=":smiley:" class="emoji" alt=":smiley:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/charity-yay-or-nay/3043/333">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/charity-yay-or-nay/3043/333</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 25 Feb 2010 19:09:34 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3043-333</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/charity-yay-or-nay/3043.rss">Charity, yay or nay?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Charity, yay or nay?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Bolteh]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Codgin">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/c/ba8739/40.png" class="avatar"> Codgin:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>so cleary human life doesnt matter as long as suffering still exsists, so by your logic a family who already lost a son, I should shoot their other son because hey theyll still be suffering, no gain, no loss, right? Makes all the sense in the world</p>
<p>Lost someone close? HA! Who cares? Here lose another, hahaha, what? your still suffering, your still miserable, whats different</p>
<p>Perhaps the fact you’ve just shot my kid</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Difference is that I won’t go to prison, you will.</p>
<p>And seriously, suffering or misery because you lost someone close? What kind of weak person are you if you actively suffer and feel miserable when someone close to you died? My grandfather died las year, I was sad, I cried, I lost someone dear. Was I suffering or feeling miserable? No not really, I tend to look back at the good times I had with him. I’m happy now, and I’m happy when I think back to my grandfather. Life went its way with him, life will get its way with all of us.</p>
<p>Onwards to the black continent!</p>
<p>As I said before, most parts of Africa will never become balanced compared to the rest of the world because it’s a dead land. Tens of thousands of years ago, humans left an area when it turned hostile, when it became impossible to live there. But what do we do these days? We gather around, throw some money together, put a damn tap next to their village and then hope that a big civilized nation will rise from it? The only thing that tap, those meds and those nets do, is keep them there for no reason at all. You keep them alive on that very spot, a spot where they have absolutely no business of being at, because it doesn’t offer them anything. The only things offered there, are frigging taps that people shoved in the ground before buggering off again.</p>
<p>You’re basically just keeping them on life support, hoping something comes along to magically boost the quality of the land (and thus the life) there.</p>
<p>So yes, it is pointless. You make sure that people exist there, but you don’t offer them lives.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/charity-yay-or-nay/3043/332">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/charity-yay-or-nay/3043/332</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 25 Feb 2010 18:36:03 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3043-332</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/charity-yay-or-nay/3043.rss">Charity, yay or nay?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Charity, yay or nay?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[X_Mastershot_X]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>The life doesn’t matter we should all die</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/charity-yay-or-nay/3043/331">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/charity-yay-or-nay/3043/331</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 25 Feb 2010 17:34:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3043-331</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/charity-yay-or-nay/3043.rss">Charity, yay or nay?</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
