<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Suicide</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/suicide/5734</link>
    <description>
[QUOTE=Silence@DV]
Suicide is one of the main problems in the modern day world. People blame mistreatment and emotion disorders on this fact but in all actuality it is the world that makes them want to end it. I believe that at least. If the world wasn&#39;t on its day routine then well people would do different things daily and have different experiences.

Heres an example, Jeff wakes up in the morning, takes a shower, eats breakfast, goes to school, learns the same subjects in 1st hour, 2nd hour, 3rd hour, ect...

Adult example, Mary wakes up has a cup of coffee and gets on the computer for a few minutes before she has to go to work, goes to work, spends her day in a cubical handling the issues of some product for the company she works for, saying the same old stuff every day, going home to do the same thing she usually does.

I think that this is a reason why people commit suicide, they get bored and sad and depressed, routine is one of those reasons because routine is not an instinct for humans we would do what it took to survive which means we would actually do something different every day if we lived in the wild. Routine IS DEPRESSION! 
[/QUOTE]
I, for one, dread the idea of non-existence. It&#39;s the fact it&#39;s just that- you&#39;re no longer &quot;there.&quot;

Final. Nothing. Nonexistence isn&#39;t peace because the peace can&#39;t coexist fore oneself with the nothingness created by death. Absolutely nothing, an end, everything will go on without you.

Death isn&#39;t a means to an end it is the end in itself and one cannot escape from it once one is already there.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 04 Nov 2010 11:24:46 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Off Topic</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/suicide/5734.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Suicide</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[gugamilare]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I guess everyone has its own limit when it comes to depression. While you are a happy (or not so happy) person it’s hard to imagine how you would behave in extreme depression situations.</p>
<p>From what has been said in this thread I concluded depression is different from having a hard time in your life like starving to death, it must be the feeling that your life is not what you expected. If you are starving but you are not expecting much else from your life, you won’t have a depression. However, if you have a job and plenty of food on the refrigerator and you are a simple workman but you expected to be, say, a doctor, that might cause you a depression unless you are able to say to yourself “Okay, I’m a simple workman, big deal, there is still plenty of things in my life that make me joy.” And depression can go deeper if you don’t deal with it.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/suicide/5734/57">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/suicide/5734/57</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 04 Nov 2010 11:24:46 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-5734-57</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/suicide/5734.rss">Suicide</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Suicide</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Gluckspirat]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Hm maybe it’s time to tell my story. I had a depression for nearly half a year and on it’s maximum I sometimes thougt of killig myself. When you are depressive you can’t see that everything will get better when your depression is over. For depressive people everything in their life is shit and they have no hope to be cured sometime. I never really wanted to kill myself but I didn’t know how to live on with my depression. I cried all the time, had the weirdest thoughts in my had and yes, depressive people don’t think in al logical way.  I never understood how people could kill theselves until I had my depression.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/suicide/5734/56">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/suicide/5734/56</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 04 Nov 2010 10:26:40 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-5734-56</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/suicide/5734.rss">Suicide</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Suicide</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[k3nny1550]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>That’s how many of my friends saw it, but thankfully they’re still with us.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/suicide/5734/55">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/suicide/5734/55</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 04 Nov 2010 09:39:42 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-5734-55</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/suicide/5734.rss">Suicide</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Suicide</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[CatzEyes93]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>In most of the instances where I hear of suicide, it is more of a “get me out of this place or feeling”.  Sometimes you hear of wanting to move forward to the next stage, but more often than not it seems it is as a result of simply wanting what is going on right now to STOP.  Feeling back, getting abused, getting picked on, feeling depressed or worthless… suicide to me seems to be more about running away from something you dont want in your world anymore rather than running towards something else.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/suicide/5734/54">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/suicide/5734/54</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 03 Nov 2010 23:23:17 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-5734-54</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/suicide/5734.rss">Suicide</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Suicide</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[bur]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>That’s not the same as a verbal insult though.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/suicide/5734/53">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/suicide/5734/53</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 03 Nov 2010 17:01:59 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-5734-53</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/suicide/5734.rss">Suicide</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Suicide</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Acristoff]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Fancy Pants">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Fancy Pants:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>i’ve considered it due to never really feeling anything but numbness<br>
but then i decided to stop being a fucking pussy and dealt with it</p>
<p>people have it worse than me and have made it through their shit, i feel like killing myself would be almost insulting to them</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Is that really it though? You don’t strike me as the type to care if you insult <span class="bbcode-i">anyone.</span></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/suicide/5734/52">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/suicide/5734/52</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 03 Nov 2010 16:59:45 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-5734-52</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/suicide/5734.rss">Suicide</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Suicide</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[bur]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Survival of the fittest goes beyond the individual, at least with social animals.<br>
There is an equation of sorts, which shows that an individual will help another at the cost of its own survival relative to how closely the other is related.</p>
<p>For example, an individual will sacrifice itself more for a sibling than for a cousin. I can’t remember what the equation (for lack of a better word) was called or anything though, or else I might be able to explain it better  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/frowning.png?v=9" title=":frowning:" class="emoji" alt=":frowning:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/suicide/5734/51">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/suicide/5734/51</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 31 Oct 2010 15:59:22 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-5734-51</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/suicide/5734.rss">Suicide</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Suicide</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Chrillen]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="gugamilare">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/g/f04885/40.png" class="avatar"> gugamilare:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Not necessarily. That does not explain why crows always tell their group when they find food. Or why human babies, contrary to most monkeys, have the habit of dividing their food with other babies when they are satisfied (not always, mind you, but many times).</p>
<p>I believe I could even find more examples if I looked at wikipedia.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Perhaps that behavior is because the group (or pack) is considered essential for the survival of the individual’s genes, but that doesn’t mean that the individual is interested in the survival of the entire species.</p>
<p>Do mind that I don’t actually know any facts about the matter, this is just what seems logical to me.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/suicide/5734/50">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/suicide/5734/50</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 31 Oct 2010 15:44:29 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-5734-50</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/suicide/5734.rss">Suicide</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Suicide</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[gugamilare]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Not necessarily. That does not explain why crows always tell their group when they find food. Or why human babies, contrary to most monkeys, have the habit of dividing their food with other babies when they are satisfied (not always, mind you, but many times).</p>
<p>I believe I could even find more examples if I looked at wikipedia.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/suicide/5734/49">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/suicide/5734/49</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 31 Oct 2010 15:35:51 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-5734-49</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/suicide/5734.rss">Suicide</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Suicide</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Chrillen]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Burbinator">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Burbinator:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I can think of an evolutionary explanation for suicide. When it appears to benefit the species, or at least close relatives, in some way, and sufficiently so, it can appear a viable option in evolutionary terms.</p>
<p>And that quote is simply incorrect. Chimpanzees, for example, are known to wage wars. Basically any territorial animal can act destructively towards its own species.</p>
<p>Self-destructive behaviour is often the result of a feeling of guilt or a lack of a sense of self-worth, which fits nicely with the explanation above.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Well, I always understood that it wasn’t so much about the survival of your species, but rather the survival of your own genes. So the chimpanzees wouldn’t care about killing the other chimpanzee groups, as long as it meant their group would survive.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/suicide/5734/48">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/suicide/5734/48</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 31 Oct 2010 15:22:57 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-5734-48</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/suicide/5734.rss">Suicide</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Suicide</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[gugamilare]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>There is also the Komodo Dragon.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="wikipedia">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 wikipedia:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Young Komodo dragons are vulnerable and therefore dwell in trees, safe from predators and cannibalistic adults.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p><a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Komodo_dragon" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Komodo_dragon</a></p>
<p>Oh, and many more:</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="wikipedia">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 wikipedia:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Another common form of cannibalism is filial cannibalism (a form of infanticide) where adults eat the young of their own species (sometimes even their own immediate offspring). Classical vertebrate examples include the <span class="bbcode-b">chimpanzee</span>s where groups of adult males have been observed to attack and consume conspecific infants,[9][10][11] and <span class="bbcode-b">cats,[12] elephants, dogs, baboons, bears, lions, and some types of fish,</span> where adult males commonly kill infants when they take over a new harem after replacing the previous dominant males.[13][14] In agricultural settings, <span class="bbcode-b">pigs</span> are known to eat their own young, accounting for a sizeable percentage of total piglet deaths.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p><a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Cannibalism_(zoology)" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Cannibalism_(zoology)</a></p>
<p>This idea that “animals don’t sin” because “only humans have free will” is just another irrational theory inflicted by religion.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/suicide/5734/47">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/suicide/5734/47</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 31 Oct 2010 15:21:02 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-5734-47</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/suicide/5734.rss">Suicide</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Suicide</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[bur]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I can think of an evolutionary explanation for suicide. When it appears to benefit the species, or at least close relatives, in some way, and sufficiently so, it can appear a viable option in evolutionary terms.</p>
<p>And that quote is simply incorrect. Chimpanzees, for example, are known to wage wars. Basically any territorial animal can act destructively towards its own species.</p>
<p>Self-destructive behaviour is often the result of a feeling of guilt or a lack of a sense of self-worth, which fits nicely with the explanation above.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/suicide/5734/46">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/suicide/5734/46</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 31 Oct 2010 14:45:41 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-5734-46</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/suicide/5734.rss">Suicide</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Suicide</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[k3nny1550]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Back on topic…</p>
<p>The truely sad part is that people wind up making it into a joke. Remember the “an hero” meme? Dear God was that tasteless.</p>
<p>Death is a topic no one is truly ready to discuss. About the closest I’ve been to it was being dehydrated in an amusement park and walking into someone else’s nine-iron mid-backswing. Suicide is equally difficult to discuss in pragmatic terms, since no rational organism would willingly wish to destroy itself.</p>
<p>And yet we get quotes like this:</p>
<p>“Man is free to choose not to be conscious, but not free to escape the penalty of unconsciousness: destruction. Man is the only living species that has the power to act as his own destroyer—and that is the way he has acted through most of his history.” - Ayn Rand</p>
<p>Of course, the above is more a socieo-economic example rather than that of a self-destructive individual. Unfortunately I know someone who has tried to commit suicide in real life. It is a very real, very serious problem, and merits mature, thoughtful discussion.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/suicide/5734/45">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/suicide/5734/45</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 31 Oct 2010 09:40:09 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-5734-45</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/suicide/5734.rss">Suicide</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Suicide</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[bur]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I think at the moment money and power are more selective traits than culture and morals.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/suicide/5734/44">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/suicide/5734/44</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 24 Oct 2010 03:45:26 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-5734-44</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/suicide/5734.rss">Suicide</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Suicide</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[gugamilare]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="X_Mastershot_X">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/x/c5a1d2/40.png" class="avatar"> X_Mastershot_X:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>It is kinda sad, though. None of your ancestors have failed to reproduce except you. by your ancestors I also mean your non-Human ancestors. Even your single-celled ancestors were more successful than you at reproducing.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Remember, though, that many living organisms also died or failed to reproduce in the process, and probably at least 10 times more. What you see today in society - many, many human surviving and reproducing - is very strange to nature.</p>
<p>I think the most important thing evolution-wise nowadays is selecting best culture and moral, not selecting individuals. And, in that sense, I believe society nowadays has great chance of changing for the best. The key is education, moral is a consequence.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/suicide/5734/43">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/suicide/5734/43</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 24 Oct 2010 02:15:54 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-5734-43</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/suicide/5734.rss">Suicide</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Suicide</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[sersoft]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I’m not gonna kill myself based on the same principle, I don’t want any of you to get a better chance of survival die bitches!</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/suicide/5734/42">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/suicide/5734/42</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 24 Oct 2010 01:10:10 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-5734-42</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/suicide/5734.rss">Suicide</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Suicide</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[bur]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I’m pretty sure suicide can also be explained in evolutionary terms, in some cases. Something about giving other members of your species/close relatives a better chance of survival. Or something. In some cases.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/suicide/5734/41">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/suicide/5734/41</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 24 Oct 2010 00:14:32 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-5734-41</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/suicide/5734.rss">Suicide</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Suicide</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Jeannotvb]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="X_Mastershot_X">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/x/c5a1d2/40.png" class="avatar"> X_Mastershot_X:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>It is kinda sad, though. None of your ancestors have failed to reproduce except you. by your ancestors I also mean your non-Human ancestors. Even your single-celled ancestors were more successful than you at reproducing.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>yea well, i still don’t give a shit.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/suicide/5734/40">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/suicide/5734/40</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 23 Oct 2010 22:10:28 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-5734-40</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/suicide/5734.rss">Suicide</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Suicide</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[sersoft]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Not true, your cells still divide as long as you are alive dip****.</p>
<p>Also **** you most likely I won’t have any children because women don’t find me attractive enough/too geeky.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/suicide/5734/39">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/suicide/5734/39</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 23 Oct 2010 20:51:09 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-5734-39</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/suicide/5734.rss">Suicide</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Suicide</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[X_Mastershot_X]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Jeannotvb">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/j/90ced4/40.png" class="avatar"> Jeannotvb:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Resist evolutionary instincts. FUCK YEAH.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>It is kinda sad, though. None of your ancestors have failed to reproduce except you. by your ancestors I also mean your non-Human ancestors. Even your single-celled ancestors were more successful than you at reproducing.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/suicide/5734/38">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/suicide/5734/38</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 23 Oct 2010 20:27:04 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-5734-38</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/suicide/5734.rss">Suicide</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Suicide</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[gugamilare]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>^ This forum is full of smart people  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=9" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
<p>The conclusion that I draw from this is that people should stop living hidden, afraid of trying different things: different ways of thinking, places, interacting with new people, etc. Give yourself an objective, a challenge, and pursue it with all our heart.</p>
<p>One of the most exciting things I’ve done lately is trying to say what I have on my mind. It doesn’t matter if I don’t know the person I’m are talking to, and I try not to be shy. The challenge I’ve given myself is to talk to strange people without feeling awkward and without having them think I’m weird or crazy. The more smiles I get back, the happier I get  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=9" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/suicide/5734/37">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/suicide/5734/37</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 23 Oct 2010 19:29:27 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-5734-37</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/suicide/5734.rss">Suicide</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Suicide</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[_rot_fodder]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>What we have to take into account, is that while there are people getting beaten and have illness and starvation, all those things provoke a natural, physical response to survive. So while physically they are way worse off than anyone over here, the constant adrenaline of just living keeps them from a suicidal state.</p>
<p>that is just my two cents.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/suicide/5734/36">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/suicide/5734/36</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 23 Oct 2010 17:45:49 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-5734-36</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/suicide/5734.rss">Suicide</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Suicide</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[blackout]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>my dad committed suicide 3.5 years ago, I was only 11 at the time.<br>
that pretty much summs up what suicide means to me.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/suicide/5734/35">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/suicide/5734/35</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 23 Oct 2010 16:54:58 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-5734-35</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/suicide/5734.rss">Suicide</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Suicide</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[gugamilare]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Chrillen">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/c/58956e/40.png" class="avatar"> Chrillen:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Suicide is the betrayal of your own genes.</p>
<p>I mean, for almost 4 billions years those genes have been competing for survival, probably against all odds, and then they come to an end because some dumbshit emo teenager think they’re having a hard time.</p>
<p>At least that’s just my primitive view of it.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>In the point of view of natural selection, suicidal people are just people that weren’t selected as the best prepared for life.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/suicide/5734/34">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/suicide/5734/34</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 23 Oct 2010 16:29:22 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-5734-34</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/suicide/5734.rss">Suicide</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Suicide</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Jeannotvb]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>That doesn’t just count for suicidal people, but also for people who don’t have children.<br>
I couldn’t give a shit whether my genes are passed on or not. Resist evolutionary instincts. FUCK YEAH.</p>
<p>It’s not like we’re short on human life anyway.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/suicide/5734/33">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/suicide/5734/33</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 23 Oct 2010 16:18:06 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-5734-33</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/suicide/5734.rss">Suicide</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
