<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Learn Spanish with Half Life 2</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/learn-spanish-with-half-life-2/63351</link>
    <description>I&#39;ve made a website for learning Spanish through video game dialogue. The website contains a collection of edited gameplay recordings that contain only character dialogues. Each video comes with two subtitle tracks, one with original Spanish text and the other with English translation. You can see what exactly each Spanish word means just by clicking on it. 

 

So far I&#39;ve made a 4 part series on Half Life 2 Episode One. More translations are coming soon. 

 

I&#39;d really appreciate your feedback. Check out the website using the link below: [https://supertitles.tv/](https://supertitles.tv/)</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 03 Jul 2020 01:06:23 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Show Off</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/learn-spanish-with-half-life-2/63351.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Learn Spanish with Half Life 2</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[spektrum]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I’ve made a website for learning Spanish through video game dialogue. The website contains a collection of edited gameplay recordings that contain only character dialogues. Each video comes with two subtitle tracks, one with original Spanish text and the other with English translation. You can see what exactly each Spanish word means just by clicking on it.</p>
<p>So far I’ve made a 4 part series on Half Life 2 Episode One. More translations are coming soon.</p>
<p>I’d really appreciate your feedback. Check out the website using the link below: <a href="https://supertitles.tv/" rel="nofollow noopener">https://supertitles.tv/</a></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/learn-spanish-with-half-life-2/63351/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/learn-spanish-with-half-life-2/63351/1</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jul 2020 01:06:23 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-63351-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/learn-spanish-with-half-life-2/63351.rss">Learn Spanish with Half Life 2</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
