<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Does anyone have the VMFs for the Xen levels?</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/does-anyone-have-the-vmfs-for-the-xen-levels/63373</link>
    <description>Not sure if this is the right place to post this, but I&#39;m not sure where else to ask. I&#39;m trying to make a mod and I need the VMFs for every level of the game. I have the earthbound levels (someone had them up for download), but I can&#39;t find the Xen ones. I would decompile them myself but I haven&#39;t been able to get BSPSource working for some reason (will try fighting with it more later if I have to), and I even tried rolling back to the public beta version to get the VMFs but I can&#39;t seem to find them.

Like I said, someone had put up the earthbound levels files in a repository online, so I was wondering if anyone might know where I could get the ones for the Xen levels. Whether that&#39;s a direct download of the VMFs, or tips on how to find the files, I don&#39;t care.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 27 Jul 2020 17:58:31 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Black Mesa</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/does-anyone-have-the-vmfs-for-the-xen-levels/63373.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Does anyone have the VMFs for the Xen levels?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[CPU]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>This site is in the process of closing down. The community has moved to Discord.</p>
<p>Join us here <a href="https://discord.gg/KpBDTqm">https://discord.gg/KpBDTqm</a></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/does-anyone-have-the-vmfs-for-the-xen-levels/63373/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/does-anyone-have-the-vmfs-for-the-xen-levels/63373/2</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 27 Jul 2020 17:58:31 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-63373-2</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/does-anyone-have-the-vmfs-for-the-xen-levels/63373.rss">Does anyone have the VMFs for the Xen levels?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Does anyone have the VMFs for the Xen levels?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Macclutcheon]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Not sure if this is the right place to post this, but I’m not sure where else to ask. I’m trying to make a mod and I need the VMFs for every level of the game. I have the earthbound levels (someone had them up for download), but I can’t find the Xen ones. I would decompile them myself but I haven’t been able to get BSPSource working for some reason (will try fighting with it more later if I have to), and I even tried rolling back to the public beta version to get the VMFs but I can’t seem to find them.</p>
<p>Like I said, someone had put up the earthbound levels files in a repository online, so I was wondering if anyone might know where I could get the ones for the Xen levels. Whether that’s a direct download of the VMFs, or tips on how to find the files, I don’t care.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/does-anyone-have-the-vmfs-for-the-xen-levels/63373/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/does-anyone-have-the-vmfs-for-the-xen-levels/63373/1</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 27 Jul 2020 16:55:05 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-63373-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/does-anyone-have-the-vmfs-for-the-xen-levels/63373.rss">Does anyone have the VMFs for the Xen levels?</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
