<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Help Me Make My New Song</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/help-me-make-my-new-song/12348</link>
    <description>The song is now finished, and It&#39;s AMAZING! Seriously check it out below.

[url]https://youtu.be/cW65UDlh37E[/url]

[u]Everything below this sentence is old (when I was working on the song)[/u]

LISTEN TO MY SONG PREVIEW USING THE LINK BELOW

[url]https://youtu.be/Rml_tbVxJ5A[/url]

Alright, so I&#39;ve been working super hard on my next song Till The Sun Sets, and if you don&#39;t by now I&#39;ve been making electronic music for over 3 years. I think this is my 45th song, but I could be wrong. Anyways,

I love feedback, and constructive criticism. Suggest something you&#39;d like to see in the song, and who knows maybe I&#39;ll put it in there. The genre I&#39;m specifically working in is Chip tune, Orchestral, and obviously dubstep (my fave XD). The Tempo is 124 bpm, which is actually kinda slow for usual dubstep, and some notable software I&#39;m using is Ni Massive, tb_peach, bunch of DSK synths, and GMS. Effects wise I&#39;m really just playing around with a bunch of stuff like Effector, dblue glitch, sumo distortion, camel audio crusher, bitcrushers, Tal chorus, Up stereo (This is seriously good for widening anything in your mix!) and hundreds of other effects I forgot.

Hope you like the song, and remember I love criticism. I&#39;ve posted on enough forums to be bombarded by trolls who just don&#39;t give a $hit, and know the difference between helpful and purely lathargic advice. Don&#39;t be that guy. Thanks for listening !!!</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2013 23:18:55 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Help and Support</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/help-me-make-my-new-song/12348.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Help Me Make My New Song</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[D3lta]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Brendon77">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Brendon77:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>If you have a hobby you first learn about basic music.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Why do you keep bumping old threads  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/frowning.png?v=9" title=":frowning:" class="emoji" alt=":frowning:"> ?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/help-me-make-my-new-song/12348/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/help-me-make-my-new-song/12348/6</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2013 23:18:55 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12348-6</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/help-me-make-my-new-song/12348.rss">Help Me Make My New Song</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Help Me Make My New Song</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[GilCMassey]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Well this thread was pretty dead I think.</p>
<p>Anyways, I do, in case you missed that. MOST of my learning is made through trial and error, yes. I may not know the name of everything I do, but I can explain it well enough. I am well aware of the basics of music. I have played several instruments for close to 10 years, but have stayed with guitar for the longest at 3.5 years and only carried over basic understanding of music and how it works through the instruments I’ve played.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/help-me-make-my-new-song/12348/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/help-me-make-my-new-song/12348/5</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2013 20:55:54 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12348-5</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/help-me-make-my-new-song/12348.rss">Help Me Make My New Song</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Help Me Make My New Song</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[GilCMassey]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>No problem. I tend to do the same thing when I write some of my own music. I have one case in particular that I’m fond of it haha when it’s finished I might show it off.</p>
<p>I’m still very early on in my music theory as well as my mixing/recording, so my suggestions are gonna be based off sound rather than numbers, letters, and such.</p>
<p>Though I’ve been playing for close to 4 years I don’t have much of an educational basis for my musical knowledge, but more of a working understanding and a feel for sound. Pick it up as I go. It’s hilarious watching me teach someone. I’m fond of thingy and whatchamacallit and then just saying “just do this. Don’t worry about terms.”</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/help-me-make-my-new-song/12348/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/help-me-make-my-new-song/12348/4</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2013 03:31:35 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12348-4</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/help-me-make-my-new-song/12348.rss">Help Me Make My New Song</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Help Me Make My New Song</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[GravityGun]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Yes, I wasn’t sure to put this in show off or help, but thinking its an unfinished product and I wanted people to offer advice I’d put it here. Thanks for taking a listen.</p>
<p>The particular part I think you’re talking about is the violin section, where it goes from E,E#,F, and G (just before the percussion), then repeats itself twice and for the rise I add an octave higher that keeps going up until the drop. I see what your saying by adding a little sweep of notes down the scale after the last note (G). Maybe like G,F, E#, E, B, G, F, E#, and E. I think that would be cool and give a smooth transition.</p>
<p>Nice suggestion I’ll see how it sounds when I get in the studio tonight (lol my bedroom).</p>
<p>Any more comments or feedback appreciated; I know there’s a lot of music production people on these forums so please do join in.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/help-me-make-my-new-song/12348/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/help-me-make-my-new-song/12348/3</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2013 22:38:19 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12348-3</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/help-me-make-my-new-song/12348.rss">Help Me Make My New Song</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Help Me Make My New Song</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[GilCMassey]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Sounds great really. I don’t have anything in the way of critique. Personally, I strongly dislike dubstep, but the rest is fantastic. Not that the DS part wasn’t, it’s just not something I generally like.</p>
<p>The only thing I can say is, and I’ll do my best to explain it, is when the orchestra (I think was it) goes up, where its like higher, higher, higher, higher I think a quick drop down from the highest note, back through the lower notes to the lowest would sound good. The first occurrence is at 0:23-0:27, so you know what I’m talking about.</p>
<p>Also, should this stuff be in help and support? I think it’s more misc than help and support. Oh well haha</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/help-me-make-my-new-song/12348/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/help-me-make-my-new-song/12348/2</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2013 18:28:54 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12348-2</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/help-me-make-my-new-song/12348.rss">Help Me Make My New Song</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Help Me Make My New Song</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[GravityGun]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>The song is now finished, and It’s AMAZING! Seriously check it out below.</p>
<p><a href="https://youtu.be/cW65UDlh37E" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://youtu.be/cW65UDlh37E</a></p>
<p><span class="bbcode-u">Everything below this sentence is old (when I was working on the song)</span></p>
<p>LISTEN TO MY SONG PREVIEW USING THE LINK BELOW</p>
<p><a href="https://youtu.be/Rml_tbVxJ5A" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://youtu.be/Rml_tbVxJ5A</a></p>
<p>Alright, so I’ve been working super hard on my next song Till The Sun Sets, and if you don’t by now I’ve been making electronic music for over 3 years. I think this is my 45th song, but I could be wrong. Anyways,</p>
<p>I love feedback, and constructive criticism. Suggest something you’d like to see in the song, and who knows maybe I’ll put it in there. The genre I’m specifically working in is Chip tune, Orchestral, and obviously dubstep (my fave XD). The Tempo is 124 bpm, which is actually kinda slow for usual dubstep, and some notable software I’m using is Ni Massive, tb_peach, bunch of DSK synths, and GMS. Effects wise I’m really just playing around with a bunch of stuff like Effector, dblue glitch, sumo distortion, camel audio crusher, bitcrushers, Tal chorus, Up stereo (This is seriously good for widening anything in your mix!) and hundreds of other effects I forgot.</p>
<p>Hope you like the song, and remember I love criticism. I’ve posted on enough forums to be bombarded by trolls who just don’t give a $hit, and know the difference between helpful and purely lathargic advice. Don’t be that guy. Thanks for listening !!!</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/help-me-make-my-new-song/12348/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/help-me-make-my-new-song/12348/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 23 Jun 2013 23:08:58 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12348-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/help-me-make-my-new-song/12348.rss">Help Me Make My New Song</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
