<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Steam Features</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/steam-features/8484</link>
    <description>Steam is adding a lot of cool stuff, from android and iphone apps to turning steam workshop into a mod manager. The question is, what do you want to see next?

First I&#39;d like to see a video recorder. IIRC, such a thing is in the works according to a Gaben interview. Also, as impractical as the controls would be, and as impractical as the whole concept would be, I think it&#39;d be pretty cool to see goldsrc (with mod support) ported to android/iphone and all the goldsrc games added to the steam app. Hell, if we wanted to go really impractical here, source and all it&#39;s games and mods too. 

On the more practical side, I&#39;d like to see the game &quot;recommendations&quot; system expanded to include comments and ratings and such. Also, perhaps a stat tracker tied to CS:GO, similar to origin&#39;s battlelog just more in-depth. What guns are you good at? What maps and what locations in maps give you the highest k/d? What guns kill you the most? And other things that could help you improve your skills. And CS:GO would be perfect for it, being an ultra-competitive game.

Usually when a program expands it&#39;s features, I go &quot;da fuck is dis shit? I don&#39;t want it.&quot; But with steam, so far I&#39;ve liked it.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2012 13:30:56 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Technology and Gaming</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/steam-features/8484.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Steam Features</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[striker]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <ul>
<li>tabbed browsing in the client</li>
<li>wishlist-/and purchase-button on every search result (not only on the game site itself)</li>
<li>possibility of listing all bought dlc in the library (not only in the game preference window)</li>
<li><span class="bbcode-b">Age-Verification feature to allow us poor Europeans (specifically Germans) to play adult games and not be treated as kids</span></li>
</ul>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/steam-features/8484/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/steam-features/8484/4</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2012 13:30:56 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8484-4</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/steam-features/8484.rss">Steam Features</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Steam Features</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[garrthbarrttinn]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="ChancyWancy">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/c/f05b48/40.png" class="avatar"> ChancyWancy:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Another thing that should be added to said menu, and I <span class="bbcode-i">really</span> want this, a Notepad feature — a place where I can write down console commands, game activation keys, cheat codes, general game notes, and other things.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I really like the notepad idea. And perhaps you could save different notepads to different games. So if you click shift+tab on HL1 and click notepads you have all your HL1 related notes right there. And game related bookmarks on the internet browser would be pretty cool too. Open the in-game web browser while playing Skyrim and it’d take you right to the Skyrim wiki.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/steam-features/8484/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/steam-features/8484/3</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2012 04:34:54 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8484-3</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/steam-features/8484.rss">Steam Features</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Steam Features</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[ChancyWancy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I think they should add a proprietary media player to the In-Game Overlay menu. When activated, in game sound is muted. I can see people using this on games like HL2 <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/smiley.png?v=9" title=":smiley:" class="emoji" alt=":smiley:"> M, especially people who don’t care for voice chat.</p>
<p>Another thing that should be added to said menu, and I <span class="bbcode-i">really</span> want this, a Notepad feature — a place where I can write down console commands, game activation keys, cheat codes, general game notes, and other things.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/steam-features/8484/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/steam-features/8484/2</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2012 03:57:53 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8484-2</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/steam-features/8484.rss">Steam Features</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Steam Features</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[garrthbarrttinn]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Steam is adding a lot of cool stuff, from android and iphone apps to turning steam workshop into a mod manager. The question is, what do you want to see next?</p>
<p>First I’d like to see a video recorder. IIRC, such a thing is in the works according to a Gaben interview. Also, as impractical as the controls would be, and as impractical as the whole concept would be, I think it’d be pretty cool to see goldsrc (with mod support) ported to android/iphone and all the goldsrc games added to the steam app. Hell, if we wanted to go really impractical here, source and all it’s games and mods too.</p>
<p>On the more practical side, I’d like to see the game “recommendations” system expanded to include comments and ratings and such. Also, perhaps a stat tracker tied to CS:GO, similar to origin’s battlelog just more in-depth. What guns are you good at? What maps and what locations in maps give you the highest k/d? What guns kill you the most? And other things that could help you improve your skills. And CS:GO would be perfect for it, being an ultra-competitive game.</p>
<p>Usually when a program expands it’s features, I go “da fuck is dis shit? I don’t want it.” But with steam, so far I’ve liked it.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/steam-features/8484/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/steam-features/8484/1</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2012 02:56:54 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8484-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/steam-features/8484.rss">Steam Features</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
