<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>[Linux] Game Crashes after altering graphical settings</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/linux-game-crashes-after-altering-graphical-settings/63252</link>
    <description>I&#39;m running on Arch Linux, and have an AMD Radeon 5600XT. Whenever I try to alter the graphical settings in any way, the game crashes soon after I hit &quot;apply&quot;. 

I have been unable to find any textual game logs, and I do not know where they are. Running the game from the command line also proved unsuccessful. As such, I can&#39;t provide those logs for you. However, I was able to get a coredump. The issue is a segfault somewhere in the UI code, and that&#39;s really about all I can say because I don&#39;t know anything else.

Minidump isn&#39;t a thing on Linux, so I can&#39;t give you one. I *can*, however, give you my coredump. Presumably, you have a copy of the executable with debugging symbols, which would render it useful. You can find it [here](https://drive.google.com/open?id=1U-qRQ4sUR0C3NYePG-RP6D0a4CEZypB9) 

I am aware that my system configuration is unsupported, and that you don&#39;t have any obligation to help me. I understand if you can&#39;t resolve the issue, but am appreciative of any help you can give me.

Thank you.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 13 May 2020 01:48:31 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>In-game Issues</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/linux-game-crashes-after-altering-graphical-settings/63252.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>[Linux] Game Crashes after altering graphical settings</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[ThothXV]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I’m running on Arch Linux, and have an AMD Radeon 5600XT. Whenever I try to alter the graphical settings in any way, the game crashes soon after I hit “apply”.</p>
<p>I have been unable to find any textual game logs, and I do not know where they are. Running the game from the command line also proved unsuccessful. As such, I can’t provide those logs for you. However, I was able to get a coredump. The issue is a segfault somewhere in the UI code, and that’s really about all I can say because I don’t know anything else.</p>
<p>Minidump isn’t a thing on Linux, so I can’t give you one. I <em>can</em>, however, give you my coredump. Presumably, you have a copy of the executable with debugging symbols, which would render it useful. You can find it <a href="https://drive.google.com/open?id=1U-qRQ4sUR0C3NYePG-RP6D0a4CEZypB9" rel="nofollow noopener">here</a></p>
<p>I am aware that my system configuration is unsupported, and that you don’t have any obligation to help me. I understand if you can’t resolve the issue, but am appreciative of any help you can give me.</p>
<p>Thank you.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/linux-game-crashes-after-altering-graphical-settings/63252/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/linux-game-crashes-after-altering-graphical-settings/63252/1</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 13 May 2020 01:48:31 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-63252-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/linux-game-crashes-after-altering-graphical-settings/63252.rss">[Linux] Game Crashes after altering graphical settings</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
