<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Team Fortress 2 (TF2) Tactics</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/team-fortress-2-tf2-tactics/7553</link>
    <description>TF2 tactic discussions occasionally rise, but I do not think an official thread has been started, I did try searching for one.

So it&#39;s basically like the title implies.  Let&#39;s discuss your usual TF2 class/tactics/play style.  Sorry if this reads like a &quot;how to&quot; guide.

Preferred game: CTF (2fort is always fun, flame if you must)
Preferred class: Pyro

I feel the pyro deserves more respect, the pryo&#39;s versatility is unmatched by other classes.  He may be a class noobs gravitate towards, but it takes time to master his skills.  One must be smart to know when to use which tactic, which sometimes mean retreating then ambushing.

Preferred weapons: Degreaser, axtinguisher, shotgun.

First, I will mention the importance of spy checking.  Always spy check with your thrower as you move from place to place.  I routinely find cloaked spies hiding in corners or running away.  My thrower of choice is the degreaser.  The degreaser&#39;s fast weapon switch more than makes up for the decreased damage.  When combined with the axtinguisher, one can single-handedly drop any class (including heavies) in close encounters/ambush.  To handle enemy pyros, I prefer the shotgun.  Give the pyro a good toasting, airblast him back, end it with the shotgun.  Also, don&#39;t forget to always spy check with your thrower as you move from place to place.  I routinely find cloaked spies hiding in corners or running away.

Shotgun is useful for finishing any class out of flame/melee range.  There is no need to uselessly flame a retreating, burning victim...just finish him with the shotgun.  I do occasionally use the flare gun as well, especially since they removed the distance requirements for crits.  Its fun to set an enemy on fire, airblast him back, crit him with a flare while hes airborne, rinse and repeat.  Oh and lets not forget counter-sniping with flares, that always gives me a good laugh.

Due to the slower weapon switch, I do not play with the regular flamethrower and the backburner is just a waste IMO.  The backburner&#39;s increased damage is only necessary in certain situations, like ambushing LARGE groups of people when it is difficult to take them out one at a time. Generally, depending on classes, one can efficiently ambush and drop a group of 3 enemies with degreaser+axtinguisher combos. They (unnecessarily) added airblast, but it uses too much ammo. Airblast is invaluable, IMO the most important tool in the pyro&#39;s arsenal.

Airblasting is something most players never take the time to practice.  There are too many W+M1 pyros out there, giving the rest of us a bad name.  Not only can you put out burning teammates (especially your pocket medic), you can effectively airblast any projectile or charging player.  My favorite kills come from reflected arrows, reflected stickies, and reflected sentry rockets.  Not only is reflecting projectiles important, but slowing ubers and stopping intel caps is crucial.  Thanks to the airblast, pyro is ideal for intel and sentry defense.

Although excellent at defense, capping intelligence is my primary focus.  Being the second fastest class with more health than a scout, pyro is a great capper.  Combined with his speed, the airblast is an effective tool for avoiding defenses such as sticky traps and sentry rockets, not to mention charging demos and any other projectile trying to stop your cap.  Due to the pyro&#39;s ability to effectively clear paths and put out flames with his airblast, he makes a good friend for any medic.

When combined with an uber medic, one can effectively clear entire defenses.  It is easy to destroy 2 closely positioned sentries, and any enemies, with a single uber.  Again, degreaser+axtinguisher makes quick work for victims who get in your way, of course you can always airblast them back to get to those sentries.  Unfortunately an enemy pyro can efficiently stop your uber rush with his airblast, but this just highlights how valuable pyros are.  If possible, I prefer ubering into the intel while my teammates follow and defend my way out.  Luckily the pyro&#39;s speed helps to get in and out quicker than most classes.

So what I just wrote is basically the life of a CTF pyro.  Overall Id say my kills are well distributed; half from flame kills and axe kills, the other half from  shotgun and reflection kills.  I try to have a diverse play style and keep the enemy on his toes, its nice when people don&#39;t know what you&#39;re gonna do next.

Sorry for the long post, I hope this gives some insight into the mind of a crazy pyromaniac.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 26 Jul 2011 04:15:51 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Technology and Gaming</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/team-fortress-2-tf2-tactics/7553.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Team Fortress 2 (TF2) Tactics</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Shinobi]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>As a sniper, never underestimate the jarate and bushwacka combo, it can generally beat any other close range enemies. If you are attacked by a pyro, especially one with a degreaser, jump at him and throw the jarate at your feet, and kill him with the bushwacka. Works about 50% of the time, esp if the pull out their axtinguisher in attempt to crit you. Conversely, if you get jarated as another class, stay away from snipers since they probably have the bushwacka and will focus on you.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/team-fortress-2-tf2-tactics/7553/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/team-fortress-2-tf2-tactics/7553/5</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jul 2011 04:15:51 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7553-5</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/team-fortress-2-tf2-tactics/7553.rss">Team Fortress 2 (TF2) Tactics</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Team Fortress 2 (TF2) Tactics</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[beejoo]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I only play games with a max of 18 players- smaller teams are much more fun IMO. I love Arena because it stops the mindless spam of bullets and becomes more about skill and trying to stay alive.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/team-fortress-2-tf2-tactics/7553/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/team-fortress-2-tf2-tactics/7553/4</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 25 Jul 2011 19:17:55 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7553-4</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/team-fortress-2-tf2-tactics/7553.rss">Team Fortress 2 (TF2) Tactics</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Team Fortress 2 (TF2) Tactics</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Ramirezoid]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>be Pyro, equip shotgun and backburner/degreaser.<br>
Preferably Backburner, because it has no drawbacks.</p>
<p>Roam around and torch anyone you see, even on your own team.<br>
If they ignite, either pour on the heat with even more flames, or whip out your chotgun and blow 'em to smitheroons.</p>
<p>Make sure to but into skirmishes between other players by torching the fuck out of the place.</p>
<p>If you see something flying at you, airblast it and get your axe slot out. If you’re cool, this is a vintage homewrecker. Smack some shit down</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/team-fortress-2-tf2-tactics/7553/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/team-fortress-2-tf2-tactics/7553/3</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 24 Jul 2011 22:16:24 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7553-3</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/team-fortress-2-tf2-tactics/7553.rss">Team Fortress 2 (TF2) Tactics</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Team Fortress 2 (TF2) Tactics</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Kaweebo]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>This should be a given but when playing as Medic, if there’s cover, always take it. If the Heavy or whatever is going out the door, heal him while staying behind cover until he’s too far out for you to heal anymore. Only then would you leave cover because by that time, he’s probably killed everybody anyway.</p>
<p>Never stop moving, and if your a sniper, stop only briefly to take the shot and then keep going, who knows what Spies are around. Also as a Sniper, after you kill someone, move from that spot immediately.</p>
<p>Stick with your teammates for the most part, going solo a lot of times means running into a whole bunch of the other team in a tight hallway, though there are exceptions such as the Spy.</p>
<p>Everyone is suspect to being a Spy as well. Almost always spy check everyone unless there’s obviously no spies on the other team. Be paranoid, look behind yourself every once in a while. I’ve saved myself from several backstab attempts by just looking around. Especially when you hear the Spie’s de-cloaking noise.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/team-fortress-2-tf2-tactics/7553/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/team-fortress-2-tf2-tactics/7553/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 24 Jul 2011 19:31:29 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7553-2</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/team-fortress-2-tf2-tactics/7553.rss">Team Fortress 2 (TF2) Tactics</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Team Fortress 2 (TF2) Tactics</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[rorriMAesU]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>TF2 tactic discussions occasionally rise, but I do not think an official thread has been started, I did try searching for one.</p>
<p>So it’s basically like the title implies.  Let’s discuss your usual TF2 class/tactics/play style.  Sorry if this reads like a “how to” guide.</p>
<p>Preferred game: CTF (2fort is always fun, flame if you must)<br>
Preferred class: Pyro</p>
<p>I feel the pyro deserves more respect, the pryo’s versatility is unmatched by other classes.  He may be a class noobs gravitate towards, but it takes time to master his skills.  One must be smart to know when to use which tactic, which sometimes mean retreating then ambushing.</p>
<p>Preferred weapons: Degreaser, axtinguisher, shotgun.</p>
<p>First, I will mention the importance of spy checking.  Always spy check with your thrower as you move from place to place.  I routinely find cloaked spies hiding in corners or running away.  My thrower of choice is the degreaser.  The degreaser’s fast weapon switch more than makes up for the decreased damage.  When combined with the axtinguisher, one can single-handedly drop any class (including heavies) in close encounters/ambush.  To handle enemy pyros, I prefer the shotgun.  Give the pyro a good toasting, airblast him back, end it with the shotgun.  Also, don’t forget to always spy check with your thrower as you move from place to place.  I routinely find cloaked spies hiding in corners or running away.</p>
<p>Shotgun is useful for finishing any class out of flame/melee range.  There is no need to uselessly flame a retreating, burning victim…just finish him with the shotgun.  I do occasionally use the flare gun as well, especially since they removed the distance requirements for crits.  Its fun to set an enemy on fire, airblast him back, crit him with a flare while hes airborne, rinse and repeat.  Oh and lets not forget counter-sniping with flares, that always gives me a good laugh.</p>
<p>Due to the slower weapon switch, I do not play with the regular flamethrower and the backburner is just a waste IMO.  The backburner’s increased damage is only necessary in certain situations, like ambushing LARGE groups of people when it is difficult to take them out one at a time. Generally, depending on classes, one can efficiently ambush and drop a group of 3 enemies with degreaser+axtinguisher combos. They (unnecessarily) added airblast, but it uses too much ammo. Airblast is invaluable, IMO the most important tool in the pyro’s arsenal.</p>
<p>Airblasting is something most players never take the time to practice.  There are too many W+M1 pyros out there, giving the rest of us a bad name.  Not only can you put out burning teammates (especially your pocket medic), you can effectively airblast any projectile or charging player.  My favorite kills come from reflected arrows, reflected stickies, and reflected sentry rockets.  Not only is reflecting projectiles important, but slowing ubers and stopping intel caps is crucial.  Thanks to the airblast, pyro is ideal for intel and sentry defense.</p>
<p>Although excellent at defense, capping intelligence is my primary focus.  Being the second fastest class with more health than a scout, pyro is a great capper.  Combined with his speed, the airblast is an effective tool for avoiding defenses such as sticky traps and sentry rockets, not to mention charging demos and any other projectile trying to stop your cap.  Due to the pyro’s ability to effectively clear paths and put out flames with his airblast, he makes a good friend for any medic.</p>
<p>When combined with an uber medic, one can effectively clear entire defenses.  It is easy to destroy 2 closely positioned sentries, and any enemies, with a single uber.  Again, degreaser+axtinguisher makes quick work for victims who get in your way, of course you can always airblast them back to get to those sentries.  Unfortunately an enemy pyro can efficiently stop your uber rush with his airblast, but this just highlights how valuable pyros are.  If possible, I prefer ubering into the intel while my teammates follow and defend my way out.  Luckily the pyro’s speed helps to get in and out quicker than most classes.</p>
<p>So what I just wrote is basically the life of a CTF pyro.  Overall Id say my kills are well distributed; half from flame kills and axe kills, the other half from  shotgun and reflection kills.  I try to have a diverse play style and keep the enemy on his toes, its nice when people don’t know what you’re gonna do next.</p>
<p>Sorry for the long post, I hope this gives some insight into the mind of a crazy pyromaniac.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/team-fortress-2-tf2-tactics/7553/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/team-fortress-2-tf2-tactics/7553/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 24 Jul 2011 19:14:13 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7553-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/team-fortress-2-tf2-tactics/7553.rss">Team Fortress 2 (TF2) Tactics</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
