<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Half-Life 1 registration problems</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/half-life-1-registration-problems/3647</link>
    <description>With all the drama with the Valve/Zyanga poll made me realize that I want to play Half-Life 1 again. I found a CD that I had of Half-Life 1 that I bought when I was in Russia. The only problem is that I live in America and because I bought it from Russia, I can&#39;t register it. I already tried contacting Steam Support, but all they said was to return it (I can&#39;t do that). So, I&#39;ve come to you all, hoping that someone could help. If anyone here lives in Russia, and is willing to help, add me to you friends list, so we could decide when to do this.

All I&#39;m asking is for you to download Team Viewer, and let me log in with my steam account on your computer and let me register Half-Life. I really hope that someone could help me.

Also, before someone says it&#39;s an illegal copy, I bought the Orange Box there too and and I was able to register it (It was early in the trip, while Half-Life was a last minute buy).

[url=&#39;https://www.teamviewer.com/index.aspx&#39;]Team Viewer[/url]

Thank you in advance.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Apr 2010 00:03:52 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Help and Support</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/half-life-1-registration-problems/3647.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Half-Life 1 registration problems</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Firebringer]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>With all the drama with the Valve/Zyanga poll made me realize that I want to play Half-Life 1 again. I found a CD that I had of Half-Life 1 that I bought when I was in Russia. The only problem is that I live in America and because I bought it from Russia, I can’t register it. I already tried contacting Steam Support, but all they said was to return it (I can’t do that). So, I’ve come to you all, hoping that someone could help. If anyone here lives in Russia, and is willing to help, add me to you friends list, so we could decide when to do this.</p>
<p>All I’m asking is for you to download Team Viewer, and let me log in with my steam account on your computer and let me register Half-Life. I really hope that someone could help me.</p>
<p>Also, before someone says it’s an illegal copy, I bought the Orange Box there too and and I was able to register it (It was early in the trip, while Half-Life was a last minute buy).</p>
<p><a href="https://www.teamviewer.com/index.aspx" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Team Viewer</a></p>
<p>Thank you in advance.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/half-life-1-registration-problems/3647/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/half-life-1-registration-problems/3647/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 04 Apr 2010 00:03:52 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3647-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/half-life-1-registration-problems/3647.rss">Half-Life 1 registration problems</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
