<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Favorite TFC Class</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/favorite-tfc-class/1530</link>
    <description>I&#39;ve seen at least three other people mention preferring an older TFC class in the [url=https://www.blackmesasource.com/forums/showthread.php?t=1744]TF2 class thread[/url]. Sure, the TF2 characters were given a little bit more personality to help with marketing, but the classes played very differently back in the day. They deserve their own thread.


I&#39;m a Pyro fan, of course. The player models both look perfect for the job of handling fire, and the weapons are easy to use but extremely difficult to master. A good enough pyro will begin to upset enemies by endlessly setting them on fire, obstructing their views. An [i]upset[/i] enemy is an [i]irrational[/i] enemy (if you can dig Zeno).

He&#39;s also usually the least selfish of classes, able to wound many enemies but having a harder time when it comes to killing. When somebody plays pyro, you know they&#39;re of noble character. ([url=https://www.vgcats.com/comics/?strip_id=46]Or maybe just bat-shit insane.[/url])

Finally, it&#39;s a very liberating class to play, because pyros don&#39;t get involved in a whole lot of ethics.* While medics are scorned for infecting-and-running, it&#39;s an accepted strategy as a pyro to ignite-and-flee.
* Demomen are bastards when they camp resupply rooms, but a naplm grenade is [i]supposed[/i] to sit outside of the enemy spawn.
* Heavy weapons guys are always whores, but when a pyro sets you on fire, it&#39;s your own damn fault no matter [i]how[/i] much he was spamming his rockets.
* Scouts and medics who are constantly bunnyhopping+concing don&#39;t deserve any respect, but IC-jumps are perfectly balanced, and 2Fort, I&#39;mma let you finish your round, but Badlands was one of the best CTF maps [u]of all time[/u] thanks to IC-jumping into the flag room.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 29 Sep 2009 11:01:38 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Technology and Gaming</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/favorite-tfc-class/1530.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Favorite TFC Class</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[JeffMOD]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Either sniper, engie, or civie.<br>
I like the laser pistol the engineer has. :3</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/favorite-tfc-class/1530/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/favorite-tfc-class/1530/3</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 29 Sep 2009 11:01:38 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-1530-3</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/favorite-tfc-class/1530.rss">Favorite TFC Class</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Favorite TFC Class</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Brother_Shrike]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Mmm, I suck at all of the classes, but I’m partial to the pyro (in the 3-4 times I’ve played it)</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/favorite-tfc-class/1530/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/favorite-tfc-class/1530/2</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 29 Sep 2009 10:53:11 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-1530-2</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/favorite-tfc-class/1530.rss">Favorite TFC Class</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Favorite TFC Class</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Comrade_Tiki]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I’ve seen at least three other people mention preferring an older TFC class in the <a href="https://www.blackmesasource.com/forums/showthread.php?t=1744" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">TF2 class thread</a>. Sure, the TF2 characters were given a little bit more personality to help with marketing, but the classes played very differently back in the day. They deserve their own thread.</p>
<p>I’m a Pyro fan, of course. The player models both look perfect for the job of handling fire, and the weapons are easy to use but extremely difficult to master. A good enough pyro will begin to upset enemies by endlessly setting them on fire, obstructing their views. An <span class="bbcode-i">upset</span> enemy is an <span class="bbcode-i">irrational</span> enemy (if you can dig Zeno).</p>
<p>He’s also usually the least selfish of classes, able to wound many enemies but having a harder time when it comes to killing. When somebody plays pyro, you know they’re of noble character. (<a href="https://www.vgcats.com/comics/?strip_id=46" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Or maybe just bat-shit insane.</a>)</p>
<p>Finally, it’s a very liberating class to play, because pyros don’t get involved in a whole lot of ethics.* While medics are scorned for infecting-and-running, it’s an accepted strategy as a pyro to ignite-and-flee.</p>
<ul>
<li>Demomen are bastards when they camp resupply rooms, but a naplm grenade is <span class="bbcode-i">supposed</span> to sit outside of the enemy spawn.</li>
<li>Heavy weapons guys are always whores, but when a pyro sets you on fire, it’s your own damn fault no matter <span class="bbcode-i">how</span> much he was spamming his rockets.</li>
<li>Scouts and medics who are constantly bunnyhopping+concing don’t deserve any respect, but IC-jumps are perfectly balanced, and 2Fort, I’mma let you finish your round, but Badlands was one of the best CTF maps <span class="bbcode-u">of all time</span> thanks to IC-jumping into the flag room.</li>
</ul>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/favorite-tfc-class/1530/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/favorite-tfc-class/1530/1</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 29 Sep 2009 06:29:39 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-1530-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/favorite-tfc-class/1530.rss">Favorite TFC Class</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
