<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>So Worth The Wait</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/so-worth-the-wait/10193</link>
    <description>I&#39;ve lurked the forums since the beginning, and this is my first post. I wanted to say how glad I am that the mod has finally released and that it couldn&#39;t have come at a better time. The count down and release has cheered me up through my break up with my girlfriend. I&#39;m about half way through the mod on Hard and it&#39;s been the most fun I&#39;ve had in a game in a long time.

So congratulations to the Black Mesa team. I hope you guys celebrated and are taking a much needed rest after your years of hard work. I know you won&#39;t be resting too long with bugs that need fixing and the final chapters being finished.

I wanted to comment on a few things, like everyone else is doing. I absolutely love the mod. The atmosphere is amazing, the details astonishing, it&#39;s like reliving the first play through Half-Life 1. 

I love the Glock. I&#39;ve seen a few comments about the clunkiness or certain details of the model being off. As a Glock owner and carrier I love the feel and sound of it in game. The sights are not the stock sights which I&#39;ve seen people complain about. But there are third-party read sights like the in-game model has. It&#39;s a blast to use.

The Python though has one flaw that bugs me. When you zoom in and fire, the cylinder cycles on it&#39;s own to the next chamber, but the hammer stays disengaged. This is not how a revolvers action works in real life. If I am firing my GP100, a similar revolver, I would pull the hammer back, which would cycle the cylinder and bring a new chamber into action, as well as setting the trigger. Not only is this how they work in real life but it makes more sense because the gun now has a lighter trigger and there is less moving parts that will set your aim off.

I would also like to know the reasoning behind giving the player the magnum prior to the shotgun. I liked how there was a lot more enemy engagements before you found the crowbar this time, but it seems like I could have done better with the shotgun instead of the magnum so early. Was it for balance purposes for to give the player more chances to use it? I am glad I get to use it more than in the original however.

Well that&#39;s it for now. I&#39;ve got to get to bed so I can play some more tomorrow. I&#39;ll leave you with a wallpaper I made from a photo I took last year.

![](upload://zO1T4iq7SzQtq1OZjyoSzUtcMXS.jpeg)</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 17 Sep 2012 10:47:53 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>The Cafeteria</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/so-worth-the-wait/10193.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>So Worth The Wait</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Flowers_Of_Naivety]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Ramirezoid">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/r/ba9def/40.png" class="avatar"> Ramirezoid:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I think the magnum was put in place of the shotgun because they wanted you to use it more. That, and seeing the shotgun hidden at the beginning and end security office of We’ve Got Hostiles makes acquiring it a sort of reward for completing that level, whereas the same thing in HL1 was just another shotgun pickup.</p>
<p>Great wallpaper though. I’m using it for my secondary monitor.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I’m thinking the same thing about the magnum. And thank you, I’m glad you like it!</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/so-worth-the-wait/10193/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/so-worth-the-wait/10193/3</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 17 Sep 2012 10:47:53 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-10193-3</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/so-worth-the-wait/10193.rss">So Worth The Wait</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>So Worth The Wait</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Ramirezoid]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I think the magnum was put in place of the shotgun because they wanted you to use it more. That, and seeing the shotgun hidden at the beginning and end security office of We’ve Got Hostiles makes acquiring it a sort of reward for completing that level, whereas the same thing in HL1 was just another shotgun pickup.</p>
<p>Great wallpaper though. I’m using it for my secondary monitor.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/so-worth-the-wait/10193/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/so-worth-the-wait/10193/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 16 Sep 2012 09:35:05 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-10193-2</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/so-worth-the-wait/10193.rss">So Worth The Wait</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>So Worth The Wait</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Flowers_Of_Naivety]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I’ve lurked the forums since the beginning, and this is my first post. I wanted to say how glad I am that the mod has finally released and that it couldn’t have come at a better time. The count down and release has cheered me up through my break up with my girlfriend. I’m about half way through the mod on Hard and it’s been the most fun I’ve had in a game in a long time.</p>
<p>So congratulations to the Black Mesa team. I hope you guys celebrated and are taking a much needed rest after your years of hard work. I know you won’t be resting too long with bugs that need fixing and the final chapters being finished.</p>
<p>I wanted to comment on a few things, like everyone else is doing. I absolutely love the mod. The atmosphere is amazing, the details astonishing, it’s like reliving the first play through Half-Life 1.</p>
<p>I love the Glock. I’ve seen a few comments about the clunkiness or certain details of the model being off. As a Glock owner and carrier I love the feel and sound of it in game. The sights are not the stock sights which I’ve seen people complain about. But there are third-party read sights like the in-game model has. It’s a blast to use.</p>
<p>The Python though has one flaw that bugs me. When you zoom in and fire, the cylinder cycles on it’s own to the next chamber, but the hammer stays disengaged. This is not how a revolvers action works in real life. If I am firing my GP100, a similar revolver, I would pull the hammer back, which would cycle the cylinder and bring a new chamber into action, as well as setting the trigger. Not only is this how they work in real life but it makes more sense because the gun now has a lighter trigger and there is less moving parts that will set your aim off.</p>
<p>I would also like to know the reasoning behind giving the player the magnum prior to the shotgun. I liked how there was a lot more enemy engagements before you found the crowbar this time, but it seems like I could have done better with the shotgun instead of the magnum so early. Was it for balance purposes for to give the player more chances to use it? I am glad I get to use it more than in the original however.</p>
<p>Well that’s it for now. I’ve got to get to bed so I can play some more tomorrow. I’ll leave you with a wallpaper I made from a photo I took last year.</p>
<p><div class="lightbox-wrapper"><a class="lightbox" href="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/original/3X/f/a/faf3e27cff9ec7b9ec90ac3ad5bf624492272b70.jpeg" data-download-href="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/faf3e27cff9ec7b9ec90ac3ad5bf624492272b70" title=""><img src="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/optimized/3X/f/a/faf3e27cff9ec7b9ec90ac3ad5bf624492272b70_2_690x388.jpeg" alt="" data-base62-sha1="zO1T4iq7SzQtq1OZjyoSzUtcMXS" width="690" height="388" srcset="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/optimized/3X/f/a/faf3e27cff9ec7b9ec90ac3ad5bf624492272b70_2_690x388.jpeg, https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/optimized/3X/f/a/faf3e27cff9ec7b9ec90ac3ad5bf624492272b70_2_1035x582.jpeg 1.5x, https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/optimized/3X/f/a/faf3e27cff9ec7b9ec90ac3ad5bf624492272b70_2_1380x776.jpeg 2x" data-small-upload="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/optimized/3X/f/a/faf3e27cff9ec7b9ec90ac3ad5bf624492272b70_2_10x10.png"><div class="meta"><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-far-image svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#far-image"></use></svg><span class="filename"></span><span class="informations">1920×1080 290 KB</span><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-discourse-expand svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#discourse-expand"></use></svg></div></a></div></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/so-worth-the-wait/10193/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/so-worth-the-wait/10193/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 16 Sep 2012 09:16:16 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-10193-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/so-worth-the-wait/10193.rss">So Worth The Wait</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
