<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Old Arcade Machine Repair</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/old-arcade-machine-repair/8850</link>
    <description>So my friend got a hold of this old arcade machine and it was working but now it just bluescreens on boot. He asked me to help fix it, but I don&#39;t know shit about arcade machines.  The arcade machine is called PGA Golf Tour. The company is GlobalVR. I was unable to find any other info on the machine.

Inside the thing is just an ordinary looking, albeit very old tower. The Bios appears on boot and it gets to the regular old &quot;windows shutdown incorrectly....start windows normally&quot; screen and it is only after waiting 20 seconds and auto starting that it bluescreens.

I tried plugging in a mouse and keyboard through two of its usb ports but that did not work presumably because it&#39;s not compatible. I&#39;ll have to try and get a hold of a ps/2 M+KB. I saw an os sticker on the front of the tower but didn&#39;t think to look at it for info, next chance I get I&#39;ll take a look and be back with that.

So to wrap this all up, I was thinking maybe I&#39;d try to replace the old tower with a slightly newer tower and pirating any software needed to make it run. Is that at all feasible or would it be a better idea to work with the pos that came with the system?

Edit: After posting this I realized it was a much better idea to go to a forum dedicated to arcade machines. I posted this there but I&#39;ll leave this here just in case any of you can help.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 06 Jun 2012 03:51:45 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Help and Support</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/old-arcade-machine-repair/8850.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Old Arcade Machine Repair</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[garrthbarrttinn]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>So my friend got a hold of this old arcade machine and it was working but now it just bluescreens on boot. He asked me to help fix it, but I don’t know shit about arcade machines.  The arcade machine is called PGA Golf Tour. The company is GlobalVR. I was unable to find any other info on the machine.</p>
<p>Inside the thing is just an ordinary looking, albeit very old tower. The Bios appears on boot and it gets to the regular old “windows shutdown incorrectly…start windows normally” screen and it is only after waiting 20 seconds and auto starting that it bluescreens.</p>
<p>I tried plugging in a mouse and keyboard through two of its usb ports but that did not work presumably because it’s not compatible. I’ll have to try and get a hold of a ps/2 M+KB. I saw an os sticker on the front of the tower but didn’t think to look at it for info, next chance I get I’ll take a look and be back with that.</p>
<p>So to wrap this all up, I was thinking maybe I’d try to replace the old tower with a slightly newer tower and pirating any software needed to make it run. Is that at all feasible or would it be a better idea to work with the pos that came with the system?</p>
<p>Edit: After posting this I realized it was a much better idea to go to a forum dedicated to arcade machines. I posted this there but I’ll leave this here just in case any of you can help.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/old-arcade-machine-repair/8850/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/old-arcade-machine-repair/8850/1</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 06 Jun 2012 03:51:45 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8850-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/old-arcade-machine-repair/8850.rss">Old Arcade Machine Repair</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
