<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Proper Installation of Black Mesa</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/proper-installation-of-black-mesa/10163</link>
    <description>I&#39;ve been reading through quite a few of these threads, and there seems to be a high number of bugs that are solved by a proper installation, and even questions on how to install it at all.  I figured this might help.

[b]Black Mesa: Installation Guide[/SIZE][/b]

[b][COLOR=&#39;SeaGreen&#39;]Forward:[/b] Before you start...

[b][COLOR=&#39;SeaGreen&#39;]Section 1:[/b] Downloading the Mod
[b][COLOR=&#39;SeaGreen&#39;]Section 1-1:[/b] Downloading a Torrent

[b][COLOR=&#39;SeaGreen&#39;]Section 2:[/b] Preparing Steam

[b][COLOR=&#39;SeaGreen&#39;]Section 3:[/b] Installing the Mod
[b][COLOR=&#39;SeaGreen&#39;]Section 3-1:[/b] With Executable File
[b][COLOR=&#39;SeaGreen&#39;]Section 3-2:[/b] Without Executable File

---------------------------------------------

[b][COLOR=&#39;SeaGreen&#39;]Forward:[/b] Before you start...[/SIZE]

A quick word before you go on.  This guide takes into account as many variables as I could think of while writing it.  For example, if you already have Steam installed, a few of the steps in Section 2 can be skipped.  Or if you&#39;ve downloaded torrents in the past, you can ignore Section 1-1.  However, this guide will work for absolutely anybody, regardless of whether they have ever used Steam at all.

Make sure your computer meets the specifications.  If you own Half-Life 2: Episode 2, and have trouble running it, then you WILL have trouble with Black Mesa.  If not, you can access your system specs by typing &quot;dxdiag&quot; into the Run program on your computer (or the Search bar in the Start menu of Windows 7).  Compare that to the specifications on the [url=&#39;https://www.blackmesasource.com/download.html&#39;]Download Page[/url].

Also, if you have anything to add, please add it as a comment to this thread!

--------------------
[b][COLOR=&#39;SeaGreen&#39;]Section 1:[/b] Downloading the Mod[/SIZE]

You have a plethora of choices here, but I highly recommend using one of the official mirrors listed on the [url=&#39;https://release.blackmesasource.com/&#39;][b]Home Page[/b][/url] of the official site.  I also highly recommend using the Torrent, as it can provide some of the fastest speeds, and it helps other people as well.  I&#39;ll provide instructions on downloading Torrents if you choose that.

Regardless of how you download the mod, instructions below will walk you through installing it.

[b][COLOR=&#39;SeaGreen&#39;]Section 1-1: Downloading a Torrent[/b]

If you&#39;ve never downloaded a torrent before, the first thing you&#39;ll need to do is grab a [b][url=&#39;https://www.google.com/search?q=torrent+client&amp;ie=utf-8&amp;oe=utf-8&amp;aq=t&amp;rls=org.mozilla:en-US:official&amp;client=firefox-a&#39;]Torrent Client[/url][/b], such as [b][url=&#39;https://www.utorrent.com/&#39;]uTorrent[/url][/b], or [b][url=&#39;https://www.bittorrent.com/&#39;]BitTorrent[/url][/b].

Find the client of your choice, and download it.  Install it (usually by running the file you downloaded, it&#39;s really straightforward) and launch the program.

At this point, you should be able to simply double-click on BlackMesaNewTrackers.torrent, and that should be that.  If it doesn&#39;t automatically show up in your torrent client, try drag-and-dropping the .torrent right into the client.

---------------------------------------------

[b][COLOR=&#39;SeaGreen&#39;]Section 2:[/b] Preparing Steam[/SIZE]

Alright, all you Steam users can skip to Step 4.  If you don&#39;t already have Steam, start right... here.

1) Go right on over to [b][url=&#39;https://store.steampowered.com/&#39;]Steam&#39;s Website[/url][/b] and click the little &quot;Install Steam&quot; button at the top of the site, far to the right of the Steam logo.
2) Save and run the file.  Once it&#39;s complete, you will be greeted with a Login screen.  Create a new (free) account, and log in.  As long as you have an e-mail address, you&#39;ll be fine.
3) Log in using your newly created Username and Password.
4) Go to the &quot;Library&quot; tab at the top of the Steam window.
5) To the right of the Search Bar in the Library, is a drop-down menu.  Access it and select &quot;Tools&quot;.
6) Scroll down the list to &quot;Source SDK Base 2007&quot;.  Follow the prompt to start the Installation.
7) Once the installation is complete, close exit Steam by opening the &quot;Steam&quot; menu at the top-left, and selecting &quot;Exit&quot; (this logs you out and closes the program entirely)

---------------------------------------------

[b][COLOR=&#39;SeaGreen&#39;]Section 3:[/b] Installing the Mod[/SIZE]

Alright, so you&#39;ve got Steam, the SDK Base 2007, and the mod is sitting there waiting to be installed.  Now, depending on how you downloaded the mod, you may or may not have an executable file (blackmesa-setup.exe) with the compressed archive.

[b][COLOR=&#39;SeaGreen&#39;]Section 3-1: With Executable File[/b]

Simply double-click on blackmesa-setup.exe.  That&#39;s it.  Restart Steam and Black Mesa will show up in your Library Games list!

[b][COLOR=&#39;SeaGreen&#39;]Section 3-2: Without Executable File[/b]

1) Open up a file browser, and navigate to the Steam folder inside of Program Files.  Usually this is C:\Program Files\Steam [or C:\Program Files (x86)\Steam if you have a 64-bit version of Windows].
2) Now open Steamapps and then SourceMods.  If that file is missing, make one.
3) Open the BlackMesa archive that you downloaded (use [url=&#39;https://www.win-rar.com/download.html?&amp;L=0&#39;]WinRar[/url] if you don&#39;t have something already).
4) Select &quot;Extract To&quot;.
5) Use the browser to navigate to ...\Steam\steamapps\SourceMods\.
6) Add &quot;BMS&quot; after the final backslash [The navigation bar should now end with this: ...\Steam\steamapps\SourceMods\BMS\]
7) Hit the &quot;Extract&quot; button!

Restart Steam and Black Mesa will show up in your Library Games list!</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 16 Sep 2012 06:24:51 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>In-game Issues (Mod)</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/proper-installation-of-black-mesa/10163.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Proper Installation of Black Mesa</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Madcat1030]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I’ve been reading through quite a few of these threads, and there seems to be a high number of bugs that are solved by a proper installation, and even questions on how to install it at all.  I figured this might help.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Black Mesa: Installation Guide[/SIZE]</span></p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">[COLOR=‘SeaGreen’]Forward:</span> Before you start…</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">[COLOR=‘SeaGreen’]Section 1:</span> Downloading the Mod<br>
<span class="bbcode-b">[COLOR=‘SeaGreen’]Section 1-1:</span> Downloading a Torrent</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">[COLOR=‘SeaGreen’]Section 2:</span> Preparing Steam</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">[COLOR=‘SeaGreen’]Section 3:</span> Installing the Mod<br>
<span class="bbcode-b">[COLOR=‘SeaGreen’]Section 3-1:</span> With Executable File<br>
<span class="bbcode-b">[COLOR=‘SeaGreen’]Section 3-2:</span> Without Executable File</p>
<hr>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">[COLOR=‘SeaGreen’]Forward:</span> Before you start…[/SIZE]</p>
<p>A quick word before you go on.  This guide takes into account as many variables as I could think of while writing it.  For example, if you already have Steam installed, a few of the steps in Section 2 can be skipped.  Or if you’ve downloaded torrents in the past, you can ignore Section 1-1.  However, this guide will work for absolutely anybody, regardless of whether they have ever used Steam at all.</p>
<p>Make sure your computer meets the specifications.  If you own Half-Life 2: Episode 2, and have trouble running it, then you WILL have trouble with Black Mesa.  If not, you can access your system specs by typing “dxdiag” into the Run program on your computer (or the Search bar in the Start menu of Windows 7).  Compare that to the specifications on the <a href="https://www.blackmesasource.com/download.html" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Download Page</a>.</p>
<p>Also, if you have anything to add, please add it as a comment to this thread!</p>
<hr>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">[COLOR=‘SeaGreen’]Section 1:</span> Downloading the Mod[/SIZE]</p>
<p>You have a plethora of choices here, but I highly recommend using one of the official mirrors listed on the <a href="https://release.blackmesasource.com/" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener"><span class="bbcode-b">Home Page</span></a> of the official site.  I also highly recommend using the Torrent, as it can provide some of the fastest speeds, and it helps other people as well.  I’ll provide instructions on downloading Torrents if you choose that.</p>
<p>Regardless of how you download the mod, instructions below will walk you through installing it.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">[COLOR=‘SeaGreen’]Section 1-1: Downloading a Torrent</span></p>
<p>If you’ve never downloaded a torrent before, the first thing you’ll need to do is grab a <span class="bbcode-b"><a href="https://www.google.com/search?q=torrent+client&amp;ie=utf-8&amp;oe=utf-8&amp;aq=t&amp;rls=org.mozilla:en-US:official&amp;client=firefox-a" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Torrent Client</a></span>, such as <span class="bbcode-b"><a href="https://www.utorrent.com/" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">uTorrent</a></span>, or <span class="bbcode-b"><a href="https://www.bittorrent.com/" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">BitTorrent</a></span>.</p>
<p>Find the client of your choice, and download it.  Install it (usually by running the file you downloaded, it’s really straightforward) and launch the program.</p>
<p>At this point, you should be able to simply double-click on BlackMesaNewTrackers.torrent, and that should be that.  If it doesn’t automatically show up in your torrent client, try drag-and-dropping the .torrent right into the client.</p>
<hr>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">[COLOR=‘SeaGreen’]Section 2:</span> Preparing Steam[/SIZE]</p>
<p>Alright, all you Steam users can skip to Step 4.  If you don’t already have Steam, start right… here.</p>
<ol>
<li>Go right on over to <span class="bbcode-b"><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Steam’s Website</a></span> and click the little “Install Steam” button at the top of the site, far to the right of the Steam logo.</li>
<li>Save and run the file.  Once it’s complete, you will be greeted with a Login screen.  Create a new (free) account, and log in.  As long as you have an e-mail address, you’ll be fine.</li>
<li>Log in using your newly created Username and Password.</li>
<li>Go to the “Library” tab at the top of the Steam window.</li>
<li>To the right of the Search Bar in the Library, is a drop-down menu.  Access it and select “Tools”.</li>
<li>Scroll down the list to “Source SDK Base 2007”.  Follow the prompt to start the Installation.</li>
<li>Once the installation is complete, close exit Steam by opening the “Steam” menu at the top-left, and selecting “Exit” (this logs you out and closes the program entirely)</li>
</ol>
<hr>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">[COLOR=‘SeaGreen’]Section 3:</span> Installing the Mod[/SIZE]</p>
<p>Alright, so you’ve got Steam, the SDK Base 2007, and the mod is sitting there waiting to be installed.  Now, depending on how you downloaded the mod, you may or may not have an executable file (blackmesa-setup.exe) with the compressed archive.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">[COLOR=‘SeaGreen’]Section 3-1: With Executable File</span></p>
<p>Simply double-click on blackmesa-setup.exe.  That’s it.  Restart Steam and Black Mesa will show up in your Library Games list!</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">[COLOR=‘SeaGreen’]Section 3-2: Without Executable File</span></p>
<ol>
<li>Open up a file browser, and navigate to the Steam folder inside of Program Files.  Usually this is C:\Program Files\Steam [or C:\Program Files (x86)\Steam if you have a 64-bit version of Windows].</li>
<li>Now open Steamapps and then SourceMods.  If that file is missing, make one.</li>
<li>Open the BlackMesa archive that you downloaded (use <a href="https://www.win-rar.com/download.html?&amp;L=0" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">WinRar</a> if you don’t have something already).</li>
<li>Select “Extract To”.</li>
<li>Use the browser to navigate to …\Steam\steamapps\SourceMods.</li>
<li>Add “BMS” after the final backslash [The navigation bar should now end with this: …\Steam\steamapps\SourceMods\BMS]</li>
<li>Hit the “Extract” button!</li>
</ol>
<p>Restart Steam and Black Mesa will show up in your Library Games list!</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/proper-installation-of-black-mesa/10163/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/proper-installation-of-black-mesa/10163/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 16 Sep 2012 06:24:51 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-10163-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/proper-installation-of-black-mesa/10163.rss">Proper Installation of Black Mesa</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
