<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>The Resident Evil Thread</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/the-resident-evil-thread/4832</link>
    <description>A thread for any Resident Evil disccusion. Love it, hate it, whatever. Post your thoughts here. Please try to keep posts legible and civil. Also, I&#39;m not quite sure if this is in the right place, if not please tell me.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 08 Aug 2010 19:17:25 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Technology and Gaming</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/the-resident-evil-thread/4832.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>The Resident Evil Thread</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[rorriMAesU]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>RE5 is too heavy on the action and light the survival, RE has historically been a survival/horror series. For instance, action elements include the waves of enemies, lots of ammo, and a real-time, limited-in-size backpack (cant upgrade size and cant pause the game to manage).  The only real survival element is the OCCASIONAL puzzle and inability to shoot while moving which is simply annoying because RE5 is so action oriented.  Also, they completely removed combining treasures, now you have one dimensional pickups for money.  Wheres the fun in that?</p>
<p>RE4 is the best blend between action and survival, while RE5 just took it over the edge with the action.  The earlier REs can be considered more horror/survival with their puzzles and treasures, lack of ammo, fewer numbers of enemies to fight at once, more startle/scare tactics, etc.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/the-resident-evil-thread/4832/50">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/the-resident-evil-thread/4832/50</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 08 Aug 2010 19:17:25 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-4832-50</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/the-resident-evil-thread/4832.rss">The Resident Evil Thread</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The Resident Evil Thread</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Surplus]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="BahamutBBob">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/b/e9bcb4/40.png" class="avatar"> BahamutBBob:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I want them to make the next game play like RE4 and 5</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Then I’ve got bad news for you, because its been said that RE5 was the last of “its kind”.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/the-resident-evil-thread/4832/49">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/the-resident-evil-thread/4832/49</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 08 Aug 2010 16:02:05 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-4832-49</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/the-resident-evil-thread/4832.rss">The Resident Evil Thread</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The Resident Evil Thread</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[BahamutBBob]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I like the Resident Evil series as a whole, but couldn’t stand to play through 4 more than once.  The story was just so bad in my opinion.  I don’t give a fuck about Leon’s vacation in Spain, since it has absolutely nothing to do with the rest of the games in the series.  RE5 was pretty dumb too, but at least they tried to tie it’s story to the other games.</p>
<p>I want them to make the next game play like RE4 and 5, but either have Zombies or other T-virus enemies only, or something new that isn’t as lame as the Plagas.  Also, drop the QTEs.  RE5 only had a small handful of cutscenes with QTEs, where it felt like RE4 had QTEs in every cutscene.  If I wanted to play a game where more than half of the combat takes place in QTEs, I would play Shenmue through again.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/the-resident-evil-thread/4832/48">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/the-resident-evil-thread/4832/48</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 08 Aug 2010 02:58:44 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-4832-48</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/the-resident-evil-thread/4832.rss">The Resident Evil Thread</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The Resident Evil Thread</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Bobikan00sh]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="bulbman">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/b/ee59a6/40.png" class="avatar"> bulbman:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>RE4 and RE5 are good games, just not Resident Evil, for me anyway. In my opinion RE5 would have been waaaay better without Sheva at all, less enemies, and why the FUCK can I not buy ammo at a fucking gun shop, and 5 rounds for each pickup? What the hell! It’s an ACTION game. All well hopefully the next one will be better.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>^this was the reason i hated re5.</p>
<p>it was a action game. not a horror. nice job capcom you ruined my love for resident evil<br>
:’(</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/the-resident-evil-thread/4832/47">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/the-resident-evil-thread/4832/47</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 07 Aug 2010 21:44:48 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-4832-47</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/the-resident-evil-thread/4832.rss">The Resident Evil Thread</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The Resident Evil Thread</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Surplus]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I don’t even understand what would be bad about the controls in RE4.  Tons of games emulated its style.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/the-resident-evil-thread/4832/46">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/the-resident-evil-thread/4832/46</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 07 Aug 2010 18:33:38 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-4832-46</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/the-resident-evil-thread/4832.rss">The Resident Evil Thread</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The Resident Evil Thread</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[DrGonzo]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>The controls in the originals were horrific. The story terrible and the acting hilarious. The best of those would be Code Veronica in my opinion. Then there was Resident Evil 4 and 5, who’s story was terrible and acting hilarious. And the controls were horrific in a new and original way.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/the-resident-evil-thread/4832/45">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/the-resident-evil-thread/4832/45</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 07 Aug 2010 16:58:20 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-4832-45</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/the-resident-evil-thread/4832.rss">The Resident Evil Thread</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The Resident Evil Thread</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[bulbman]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>RE4 and RE5 are good games, just not Resident Evil, for me anyway. In my opinion RE5 would have been waaaay better without Sheva at all, less enemies, and why the FUCK can I not buy ammo at a fucking gun shop, and 5 rounds for each pickup? What the hell! It’s an ACTION game. All well hopefully the next one will be better.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/the-resident-evil-thread/4832/44">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/the-resident-evil-thread/4832/44</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 07 Aug 2010 15:43:23 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-4832-44</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/the-resident-evil-thread/4832.rss">The Resident Evil Thread</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The Resident Evil Thread</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[GordonFreeman]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I would say that my enjoyment of RE1, RE Zero, and Code Veronica (the only “original-style” ones I’ve played) were hampered by the bad camera angles, weak weapons and the awkward controls. Getting eaten by an enemy that I didn’t see coming can be frustrating after the fifth time. Can still appreaciate the games for what they were. A new direction in gaming.<br>
RE4 for me is a blast. It does stray from the survival horror feel of the older Resident Evil games, but that makes it a refreshing change from the “silly-premise-taken-seriously” plot of the old ones. RE4 by no means takes itself too seriously. The characters are outrageously hammy, the plot is simple and the dialogue is hilariously absurd. And the way it’s executed is brilliant. I love it. Plus, the Mercaneries mode has fun gameplay and in-game benefits. The over-the-shoulder, rotating camera REALLY helps me enjoy it as well.<br>
Playing RE5 can be really unenjoyable if you take the game’s plot as seriously as it takes itself. I have thoroughly enjoyed RE5 past all it’s annoying gamplay aspects, the blatant rascism and frequent quick-time events for one reason. It’s HILARIOUSLY rediculous story. The dialogue, the characters, the settings (maybe not so much, except for the VOLCANO). All makes for one funny, absurd tale. It’s different from RE4 as RE4 was somewhat self-aware as to how silly it was. RE5 assumes you’ll take all the bullshit it gives, and that can be entertaining. The cutscenes with Albert Wesker (who’s been stealing clothes from JC Denton’s wardrobe) are side-splittingly hilarious. One scream of “CHRISSSSSSS!!!” makes me just crack up. They also keep the Mercaneries mode in this one too, which still maintains it’s awesomeness.</p>
<p>Final Personal Verdict:<br>
RE 1 -&gt; RE 4, Good games, frustrating controls and bad camera angles<br>
RE 4 +, Enjoyable parodies of survival horror games</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/the-resident-evil-thread/4832/43">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/the-resident-evil-thread/4832/43</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 06 Aug 2010 07:36:03 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-4832-43</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/the-resident-evil-thread/4832.rss">The Resident Evil Thread</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The Resident Evil Thread</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[player]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I’ve played 2, 3, 4, Code Veronica-X, Dead Aim, Outbreak, and Outbreak file 2.  RE3 was the most epic thing I had ever seen for ps1 when it first came out.   I didn’t get a chance to play 2 until a few years ago when I lucked into both discs for ps1, but the previous owner kept them out of the case.  So the Claire disc freezes and doesn’t load models at the end that are necessary to progress from a cut scene.  I’ve never seen a copy of 1 and I’m pretty sure it was out of print when I got 3 back around '98 or '99.  Does anyone know if they ported 1 and 2 to pc and if so, is there anywhere that it can legally be downloaded or purchased on disc?  Capcom’s site doesn’t have much of anything, but I have found the demo for 3 with the option of buying the full version before.  I’d love to be able to play the original and 2 without worrying about it freezing all the time.</p>
<p>Also, I’d have to say 2 and 3 are my favorites with Code Veronica-X at a close second.  Dead Aim was the worst because of the plot and dialog but was kind of cool for combining first and third person.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/the-resident-evil-thread/4832/42">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/the-resident-evil-thread/4832/42</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 06 Aug 2010 05:43:18 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-4832-42</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/the-resident-evil-thread/4832.rss">The Resident Evil Thread</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The Resident Evil Thread</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[daivonbee]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>First of all, the old Resident Evil games were survival horror games. This means that you were given weapons with limited amount of ammo to spare. This simple game mechanic influenced the way the you played the game. I almost have absolutely nothing good to say about this title, maybe that it bares the RE.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/the-resident-evil-thread/4832/41">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/the-resident-evil-thread/4832/41</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 05 Aug 2010 07:20:58 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-4832-41</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/the-resident-evil-thread/4832.rss">The Resident Evil Thread</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The Resident Evil Thread</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Thecromewriter]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="garthbartin">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 garthbartin:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Resident Evil 4 is one of my favorite games of all times, but it’s the only RE I’ve played much. The regenerators scared the piss out of me, they’re way scarier than anything in deadspace. Unfortunately RE4 wins the award for world’s shittiest port to pc.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I tried playing RE4, but it was on a friends Wii. I believe you when you say it was good, but the Wii version was just terrible trying to control it with Nintendo’s excuse for a more different controller.</p>
<p>Ugh, the N64 controller was my first and favorite controller, if only it wouldn’t have had the durability of a twig  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/frowning.png?v=9" title=":frowning:" class="emoji" alt=":frowning:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/the-resident-evil-thread/4832/40">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/the-resident-evil-thread/4832/40</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 05 Aug 2010 07:20:57 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-4832-40</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/the-resident-evil-thread/4832.rss">The Resident Evil Thread</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The Resident Evil Thread</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Bobikan00sh]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Morrussian">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/m/43a26b/40.png" class="avatar"> Morrussian:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I dunno, from talking to most of my friends, RE0 was one of the weaker ones overall, I enjoyed it, but RE will always be my favorite.  Especially once I got good at speed runs in it.</p>
<p>I’ll accept your issue with the race things, but about the “Supernatural Events” I’m gonna have to dispute you there.  I mean the “true” name of the game is Biohazard, it’s all meant to be grounded in a scientific explanation.  I don’t mean to be getting on YOUR case about it (so don’t hate me OP).  And if there was ANY fan service in that game, it was the lickers, they were really not needed.  First runner up fan service would be the El Gigante battle… dumbest thing ever…<br>
Also, I never had a problem with the lighting, in standard or HD, the lighting always seemed to fit perfectly, in regular and across all the filters.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>ok you have a valid point about</p>
<p>and katana does as well(however i don’t believe i mentioned fear. that game just was not anything-good or bad) because yes, kings quest 4 had some scary moments in it.( but i was like 10 playing that so i don’t know if they would hold up )but neither point excuses the fact that 5 was a overall bad game. 4 was on the edge for me but managed to stay good because it traded out slow building horror for fast paced oh-shit-i-gotta-run horror.</p>
<p>5 had none of these things. the lighting allowed for ganados to be easily found and made the game less scary overall</p>
<p>they need to seriously think about what makes a good game for 6. pumping out the same thing every couple years with a different title does not work anymore, espcially when most gamers i talk to agree that the economies status means we cant spend 60 bucks on the same shit being repackaged every year(cough cough final FUCKING fantasy)</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/the-resident-evil-thread/4832/39">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/the-resident-evil-thread/4832/39</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 05 Aug 2010 06:22:03 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-4832-39</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/the-resident-evil-thread/4832.rss">The Resident Evil Thread</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The Resident Evil Thread</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Morrussian]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Fnoigy">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/f/b5e925/40.png" class="avatar"> Fnoigy:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>My friend bought me Resident Evil Zero, even though I’ve expressed my disliking of Resident Evil for quite some time.</p>
<p>It was bad.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I dunno, from talking to most of my friends, RE0 was one of the weaker ones overall, I enjoyed it, but RE will always be my favorite.  Especially once I got good at speed runs in it.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Bobikan00sh">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/b/ad7895/40.png" class="avatar"> Bobikan00sh:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>5 sucked. to sum it up no horror just violence. there was no feeling of supernatural events like in 4 and being in brightly lit Africa just made 5 seem like it was fan service to all the Chris fans.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I’ll accept your issue with the race things, but about the “Supernatural Events” I’m gonna have to dispute you there.  I mean the “true” name of the game is Biohazard, it’s all meant to be grounded in a scientific explanation.  I don’t mean to be getting on YOUR case about it (so don’t hate me OP).  And if there was ANY fan service in that game, it was the lickers, they were really not needed.  First runner up fan service would be the El Gigante battle… dumbest thing ever…<br>
Also, I never had a problem with the lighting, in standard or HD, the lighting always seemed to fit perfectly, in regular and across all the filters.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="bulbman">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/b/ee59a6/40.png" class="avatar"> bulbman:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Have you played Code Veronica?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I just wanted to steal your quote to break up the thread…</p>
<p>CV was good, at some points it seems like they went far out of their way to be as inconvenient as possible.  How many people missed the revolver on their first play through because they didn’t have the fire extinguisher?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/the-resident-evil-thread/4832/38">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/the-resident-evil-thread/4832/38</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 05 Aug 2010 04:18:48 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-4832-38</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/the-resident-evil-thread/4832.rss">The Resident Evil Thread</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The Resident Evil Thread</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Surplus]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="felipedomaul">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/f/ba8739/40.png" class="avatar"> felipedomaul:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>why didn<code>t anyone mention outbreak,it</code>s characters are your regular everyman,each of the 8 with it`s own personality,embarking on well built scenarios that played unlike any RE,specially because there are 2 bots helping,while maintaining the core elements.i just ilegally downloaded it for my ps2 emulator and i highly recommend it.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Left 4 Dead is the game that RE Outbreak wanted to be.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/the-resident-evil-thread/4832/37">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/the-resident-evil-thread/4832/37</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 05 Aug 2010 03:22:22 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-4832-37</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/the-resident-evil-thread/4832.rss">The Resident Evil Thread</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The Resident Evil Thread</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[felipedomaul]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>why didn<code>t anyone mention outbreak,it</code>s characters are your regular everyman,each of the 8 with it`s own personality,embarking on well built scenarios that played unlike any RE,specially because there are 2 bots helping,while maintaining the core elements.i just ilegally downloaded it for my ps2 emulator and i highly recommend it.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/the-resident-evil-thread/4832/36">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/the-resident-evil-thread/4832/36</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 05 Aug 2010 02:37:23 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-4832-36</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/the-resident-evil-thread/4832.rss">The Resident Evil Thread</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The Resident Evil Thread</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Katana]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Bobikan00sh">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/b/ad7895/40.png" class="avatar"> Bobikan00sh:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>to sum it up no horror just violence.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>And? F.E.A.R. didn’t exactly have what it implied on the tin, but it was still pretty awesome.</p>
<p>I have my few games for actual true horror; and they ain’t Silent Hill. Heck, one’s an adventure game.</p>
<p>Ever played King’s Quest 4? Trust me, you do NOT want to walk to the next screen and hear the giant’s music. There’s also a cave where the monster of choice follows you between screens. And it is PITCH BLACK. EVEN WHEN YOU FIND A LANTERN.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/the-resident-evil-thread/4832/35">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/the-resident-evil-thread/4832/35</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 05 Aug 2010 01:40:25 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-4832-35</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/the-resident-evil-thread/4832.rss">The Resident Evil Thread</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The Resident Evil Thread</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[bulbman]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I heard that RE5 is the last RE game with the action packed gameplay. And<br>
<a class="mention" href="/u/bobikan00sh">@Bobikan00sh</a> One of the major reasons Sheva was in the game was to ease all the racism stuff. But really she just sucks.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/the-resident-evil-thread/4832/34">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/the-resident-evil-thread/4832/34</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 05 Aug 2010 01:16:51 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-4832-34</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/the-resident-evil-thread/4832.rss">The Resident Evil Thread</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The Resident Evil Thread</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Android11x]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>RE5 was a stupid fucking game.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/the-resident-evil-thread/4832/33">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/the-resident-evil-thread/4832/33</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 31 Jul 2010 04:06:14 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-4832-33</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/the-resident-evil-thread/4832.rss">The Resident Evil Thread</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The Resident Evil Thread</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Bobikan00sh]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>4 is my personal favorite because it got rid of clunky controls. 0-veronica x were puzzles in frustration and ammo conservation</p>
<p>i was not afraid in any of the games before 4 just frustrated. 4 made me scared. the supernatural and oppressive horror allowed for me to feel isolated in a remote are of spain with no hope for survival and knowing the only things keeping me alive were wits, the merchant, and a thin wooden door.</p>
<p>5 sucked. to sum it up no horror just violence. there was no feeling of supernatural events like in 4 and being in brightly lit Africa just made 5 seem like it was fan service to all the Chris fans. the lighting allow for absolutely NO scenes like the dark deary dungeons in the castle of re4 and the ganados that haunted my dreams after playing 4 felt washed up and lame after halfway through 5. Also as one of the few black gamers i know. i was personally invested on the side of “racism in re5 is bullshit” because i had seen the trailers involving white zombies in the game. then i got to chapter 5.<br>
In which you only fight black zombies.<br>
Wearing grass skirts and tribal masks from Zimbabwe.<br>
and throwing spears at you.<br>
that’s about when i took the disc in and sold it. can’t even describe how much that pissed me off<br>
and motorcycle riding zombies. stupid as shit.:fffuuu:</p>
<p>p.s.  all the reasons i disliked the resident evil series are reasons i loved the silent hill series. in those games the controls are ok because most of the time you run and SURVIVE instead of fight. the horror is physiological not physical.<br>
that’s why silent hill is a better game series In my opinion</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/the-resident-evil-thread/4832/32">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/the-resident-evil-thread/4832/32</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 31 Jul 2010 03:28:32 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-4832-32</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/the-resident-evil-thread/4832.rss">The Resident Evil Thread</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The Resident Evil Thread</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[rorriMAesU]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Katana">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/k/db5fbb/40.png" class="avatar"> Katana:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>…I’ve really taken advantage of the whole chapter-jumping thing to just replay my favorite parts.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>so true</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/the-resident-evil-thread/4832/31">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/the-resident-evil-thread/4832/31</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 31 Jul 2010 01:37:17 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-4832-31</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/the-resident-evil-thread/4832.rss">The Resident Evil Thread</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The Resident Evil Thread</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Katana]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>My first in the series was RE4, and I think I beat it about 3 or 4 times. I could probably beat the game using nothing but magnum ammo and grenades from all I saved up.</p>
<p>I’ve really been enjoying RE5 too; though I can’t count the number of times I’ve “beaten” it, since I’ve really taken advantage of the whole chapter-jumping thing to just replay my favorite parts.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/the-resident-evil-thread/4832/30">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/the-resident-evil-thread/4832/30</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jul 2010 22:42:45 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-4832-30</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/the-resident-evil-thread/4832.rss">The Resident Evil Thread</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The Resident Evil Thread</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Android11x]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>^ that and similar to what others said. I loved 1, 2 and 3. The GameCube remake did wonders for the original RE.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/the-resident-evil-thread/4832/29">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/the-resident-evil-thread/4832/29</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jul 2010 22:04:38 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-4832-29</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/the-resident-evil-thread/4832.rss">The Resident Evil Thread</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The Resident Evil Thread</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[nsane]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I loved the Resident Evil series, up until 4 that is. Don’t get me wrong, Resident Evil 4 is a good game, it’s just not a Resident Evil game. To me, the real series died after Code Veronica X. It’s a shame too.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/the-resident-evil-thread/4832/28">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/the-resident-evil-thread/4832/28</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jul 2010 21:56:10 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-4832-28</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/the-resident-evil-thread/4832.rss">The Resident Evil Thread</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The Resident Evil Thread</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Surplus]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Deathmonkey7">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/user_avatar/leakfree.org/deathmonkey7/40/5247_2.png" class="avatar"> Deathmonkey7:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Bought Resident Evil 0. I love that game, I’ve been looking for a good used one for a while. I’ve played 0, 1, 4, and 5. I’ve loved all of them thus far.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I think RE0 is my favorite, the 2 characters at once was interesting and fun.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/the-resident-evil-thread/4832/27">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/the-resident-evil-thread/4832/27</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jul 2010 06:11:49 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-4832-27</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/the-resident-evil-thread/4832.rss">The Resident Evil Thread</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The Resident Evil Thread</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[blackmesafan]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>i personally didn’t like the games that much. i can’t figure out what it was that made me not really like them though.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/the-resident-evil-thread/4832/26">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/the-resident-evil-thread/4832/26</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jul 2010 04:16:53 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-4832-26</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/the-resident-evil-thread/4832.rss">The Resident Evil Thread</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
