<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Screenshots from non Steam games disappearing</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/screenshots-from-non-steam-games-disappearing/11925</link>
    <description>So usually, I take screenshots through Steam but if I have a game that&#39;s not with Steam I usually add it as a non Steam game to use the screenshot function. After a little bit those screenshots disappear though, so when I highlight a game the screenshots that I&#39;ve already taken aren&#39;t there anymore. If I look in the place where screenshots are kept in Steam, they&#39;re still there in one of the folders, but taking any more will create a new folder for them, so some of the non Steam games I have added will have 2 or 3 different folders for screenshots. Anyone know why this is happening and if there&#39;s a way to fix it?</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2013 23:37:17 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Help and Support</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/screenshots-from-non-steam-games-disappearing/11925.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Screenshots from non Steam games disappearing</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Cpl.1nsane]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I’ve encountered a similar issue before, usually steam for what ever reason removing my non steam games. But making sure all the information matches when I add the shortcuts back seems to work (folder location etc) Though not always sadly, not sure if there is a proper fix for it.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/screenshots-from-non-steam-games-disappearing/11925/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/screenshots-from-non-steam-games-disappearing/11925/2</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2013 23:37:17 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11925-2</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/screenshots-from-non-steam-games-disappearing/11925.rss">Screenshots from non Steam games disappearing</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Screenshots from non Steam games disappearing</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Kairouseki]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>So usually, I take screenshots through Steam but if I have a game that’s not with Steam I usually add it as a non Steam game to use the screenshot function. After a little bit those screenshots disappear though, so when I highlight a game the screenshots that I’ve already taken aren’t there anymore. If I look in the place where screenshots are kept in Steam, they’re still there in one of the folders, but taking any more will create a new folder for them, so some of the non Steam games I have added will have 2 or 3 different folders for screenshots. Anyone know why this is happening and if there’s a way to fix it?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/screenshots-from-non-steam-games-disappearing/11925/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/screenshots-from-non-steam-games-disappearing/11925/1</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2013 18:58:40 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11925-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/screenshots-from-non-steam-games-disappearing/11925.rss">Screenshots from non Steam games disappearing</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
