<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Multiplayer first impressions</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/multiplayer-first-impressions/14042</link>
    <description>Hello guys,

Today I bought this game and played few maps. My first impressions are generally positive and i believe this game have a lot of potential to become really great fast paced multiplayer shooter.

Yes, i am one of those guys who think that bhop is core element of hldm. I believe game wont have any future as competitive game if it wont have bhop. For me this game will be perfect as long as there will be Gauss jumping and bunny hoping similar to hl1 and ag. So, primary thing to focus on for me is movement, everything else is secondary at the moment.  If there will be too many casual players who hates bhop and related to it stuff may be it is possible to set it to on/off feature.

Also, i have wrote about weapon placement in one of the threads :  &quot;Half life is not just reckless run and shot game in hl there always were important and unimportant areas of the map, mostly teams fight for controlling certain areas, if one team looses fight for area its not the end - team can start gathering resources from other areas and when they are ready they can attack important area again. You would need good teamplay and skill level to know when to hold, when to attack or maybe wait and get more stack for a few minutes. But by adding a lot of weapons to every area(like 4 gauss, 4 LJ and alot of other weapons for single map) makes fighting for them useless and gameplay very arcade and almost completely deletes any teamplay from the game and leads it to run and shoot type of play.&quot; I think that its enough to have one gauss and one LJ for every map and two gauss and two LJ at maximum for very large maps.

There are weapons that i feel is not working like they should do:

1. Crossbow for example don&#39;t have instant zoom, it makes this weapon too slow to use in fast combat or at close distances, its only good for long range shots and camping playstyle, Thats only my opinion and if you guys feel that its should be as it is i am fine with it.  
1. Gauss after secondary fire mode reloads too slow - delays after shots are too long, it spoils Gauss jumping and makes it harder to hit with secondary mode. Also there is minor gauss jumping issues but its not that important at current state.
1. MP5 shouldnt have recoil like it has now - crosshair shouldn&#39;t move while you shot like in cs go.  I feel that it moves game to incorrect direction, this game is not about recoil control but more about aiming while you are in action. So in my opinion you should worrying about hitting your opponent and dodging his shots, not about your recoil
Map design is fantastic and every else is fantastic too. Thanks for your attention.

Cheers,
ert</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 29 May 2015 23:12:54 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>The Cafeteria</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/multiplayer-first-impressions/14042.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Multiplayer first impressions</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[fury]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I very much agree about the MP5 and almost everything he said… I think the bow should definately be insta-zoom and the trace-line of zoomed crossbow-shots should be removed. I also think that a working voting system (like what AG has) is very important for the game… Atm you only have some public servers with lots of players in them (way too many players imo)… With a voting system players could organize proper, more organzied and competetive matches. It also makes things easier in public servers…</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/multiplayer-first-impressions/14042/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/multiplayer-first-impressions/14042/2</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 May 2015 23:12:54 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14042-2</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/multiplayer-first-impressions/14042.rss">Multiplayer first impressions</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Multiplayer first impressions</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[eriksonis6]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Hello guys,</p>
<p>Today I bought this game and played few maps. My first impressions are generally positive and i believe this game have a lot of potential to become really great fast paced multiplayer shooter.</p>
<p>Yes, i am one of those guys who think that bhop is core element of hldm. I believe game wont have any future as competitive game if it wont have bhop. For me this game will be perfect as long as there will be Gauss jumping and bunny hoping similar to hl1 and ag. So, primary thing to focus on for me is movement, everything else is secondary at the moment.  If there will be too many casual players who hates bhop and related to it stuff may be it is possible to set it to on/off feature.</p>
<p>Also, i have wrote about weapon placement in one of the threads :  “Half life is not just reckless run and shot game in hl there always were important and unimportant areas of the map, mostly teams fight for controlling certain areas, if one team looses fight for area its not the end - team can start gathering resources from other areas and when they are ready they can attack important area again. You would need good teamplay and skill level to know when to hold, when to attack or maybe wait and get more stack for a few minutes. But by adding a lot of weapons to every area(like 4 gauss, 4 LJ and alot of other weapons for single map) makes fighting for them useless and gameplay very arcade and almost completely deletes any teamplay from the game and leads it to run and shoot type of play.” I think that its enough to have one gauss and one LJ for every map and two gauss and two LJ at maximum for very large maps.</p>
<p>There are weapons that i feel is not working like they should do:</p>
<ol>
<li>Crossbow for example don’t have instant zoom, it makes this weapon too slow to use in fast combat or at close distances, its only good for long range shots and camping playstyle, Thats only my opinion and if you guys feel that its should be as it is i am fine with it.</li>
<li>Gauss after secondary fire mode reloads too slow - delays after shots are too long, it spoils Gauss jumping and makes it harder to hit with secondary mode. Also there is minor gauss jumping issues but its not that important at current state.</li>
<li>MP5 shouldnt have recoil like it has now - crosshair shouldn’t move while you shot like in cs go.  I feel that it moves game to incorrect direction, this game is not about recoil control but more about aiming while you are in action. So in my opinion you should worrying about hitting your opponent and dodging his shots, not about your recoil<br>
Map design is fantastic and every else is fantastic too. Thanks for your attention.</li>
</ol>
<p>Cheers,<br>
ert</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/multiplayer-first-impressions/14042/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/multiplayer-first-impressions/14042/1</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 14 May 2015 21:00:13 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14042-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/multiplayer-first-impressions/14042.rss">Multiplayer first impressions</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
