<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>&quot;On a Rail&quot; train bug [Fixed]</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/on-a-rail-train-bug-fixed/10953</link>
    <description>Hey guys, I have a posible glitch/bug. Im on the part of the level after you raise the bridge and the security door. After this there is a turn table thing that you have to raise your train with, but after I go up there I cant seem to find a switch or button to raise it. So, I countinue down the tracks untill the game says &quot;loading&quot;, and then I deside to turn back and head to the turn table and what do you know, the turn table had lifted up but the train is no loger on the turn table! I then went back down the ladder to find headlight/taillights from the train floating in the air. So now I have no train... :&#39;(</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 21 Sep 2012 01:05:44 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>In-game Issues (Mod)</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/on-a-rail-train-bug-fixed/10953.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>&quot;On a Rail&quot; train bug [Fixed]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Fopqwas]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Hey guys, I have a posible glitch/bug. Im on the part of the level after you raise the bridge and the security door. After this there is a turn table thing that you have to raise your train with, but after I go up there I cant seem to find a switch or button to raise it. So, I countinue down the tracks untill the game says “loading”, and then I deside to turn back and head to the turn table and what do you know, the turn table had lifted up but the train is no loger on the turn table! I then went back down the ladder to find headlight/taillights from the train floating in the air. So now I have no train… :’(</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/on-a-rail-train-bug-fixed/10953/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/on-a-rail-train-bug-fixed/10953/1</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 21 Sep 2012 01:05:44 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-10953-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/on-a-rail-train-bug-fixed/10953.rss">&quot;On a Rail&quot; train bug [Fixed]</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
