<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Small Feedback/Crashes</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/small-feedback-crashes/9797</link>
    <description>Wonderful job you guys did, but here are some small issues I noticed:

I had 2 crashes so far, but they did not seem to be reproduceable. They however happened, when my energy weapon (can&#39;t remember the name) reached full charge.

The helicopter boss seems to be a little too powerful at the moment. I&#39;m not talking about his health pool, but the amount of damage his MG does (The Rockets are fine, because you can somewhat dodge them). Since there is very little cover where you fight him, you are guaranteed to loose a major chunk of your health or die when you were low.

The second time the Gargantua shows up, it completely ignores the 2 soldiers that just shot you out of the ventilation shaft for nor apparent reason. I remember this back from the old Half-Life 1 and the short moment, where it dealt with the 2 guys, was the time I needed to get away safely in time (it also seems unlogical, why it would ignore the 2 guys). Right now I&#39;m always taking quite a lot of damage because it manages to catch up before I get on the tower.

Last thing, are the Leeches missing, because they were bloody annoying to fight against?</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 15 Sep 2012 12:18:47 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>In-game Issues (Mod)</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/small-feedback-crashes/9797.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Small Feedback/Crashes</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Stefan]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Since I forgot to upload my crashdump and it won’t let me add it to my previous post, I just made a new one.<br>
<a class="attachment" href="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/original/2X/3/34fc98428ae17a6227c37283f67859f19a3b047d.mdmp">hl2_4104_crash_2012_9_15T8_47_37C0.mdmp</a> (105 KB)</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/small-feedback-crashes/9797/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/small-feedback-crashes/9797/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 15 Sep 2012 12:18:47 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9797-2</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/small-feedback-crashes/9797.rss">Small Feedback/Crashes</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Small Feedback/Crashes</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Stefan]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Wonderful job you guys did, but here are some small issues I noticed:</p>
<p>I had 2 crashes so far, but they did not seem to be reproduceable. They however happened, when my energy weapon (can’t remember the name) reached full charge.</p>
<p>The helicopter boss seems to be a little too powerful at the moment. I’m not talking about his health pool, but the amount of damage his MG does (The Rockets are fine, because you can somewhat dodge them). Since there is very little cover where you fight him, you are guaranteed to loose a major chunk of your health or die when you were low.</p>
<p>The second time the Gargantua shows up, it completely ignores the 2 soldiers that just shot you out of the ventilation shaft for nor apparent reason. I remember this back from the old Half-Life 1 and the short moment, where it dealt with the 2 guys, was the time I needed to get away safely in time (it also seems unlogical, why it would ignore the 2 guys). Right now I’m always taking quite a lot of damage because it manages to catch up before I get on the tower.</p>
<p>Last thing, are the Leeches missing, because they were bloody annoying to fight against?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/small-feedback-crashes/9797/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/small-feedback-crashes/9797/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 15 Sep 2012 09:38:23 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9797-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/small-feedback-crashes/9797.rss">Small Feedback/Crashes</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
