<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Content Creator Request Thread</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/content-creator-request-thread/14660</link>
    <description>As I&#39;m sure you all already know, there&#39;s a lot of aspects involved with content creation and it can be difficult for Crowbar Collective to keep up with what&#39;s needed, broken or wished for. This thread will serve as a sort of modding request compendium for CC to look into for Black Mesa. This will help keep things more tidy and organized so that the developers can easily access what the modding community would like addressed.

So if you&#39;re a content creator and you&#39;ve got something you&#39;d like to bring to the attention of the developers to fulfill your modding needs, feel free to post about it here. What&#39;s asked is that you keep it reasonably specific (nothing like &quot;animations don&#39;t work&quot;) and relevant. [u][b]THIS IS NOT A GENERAL REQUEST THREAD.[/b][/u] This thread is for modding and content creation-related requests only.

To ensure that we get some content in right from the get-go, I&#39;ll start off with a couple things.
* Allow custom scripts/resource files: Black Mesa seems to ignore custom files located in the bms\scripts and bms\resource folders in favor of stock files. Problematic as it disallows a wealth of custom user content, such as closed captions, HUD modification, soundscapes, and more. Also ignored is the bms\particles folder.
* Enable tools mode: Tools mode is used most notably for creating particles and developer commentary. Currently when attempting to launch Black Mesa in tools mode, the game launches fine but the tools interface is nowhere to be seen.
* [s]Fix logic_playerproxy entity: Some functions of the entity seem to not be called. Confirmed ones so far are PlayerDied and FlashlightOn.[/s]</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2017 01:01:13 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Source 1</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/content-creator-request-thread/14660.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Content Creator Request Thread</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Admiral_Sakai]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I wonder how far ahead of the actual Xen update the engine update will be released?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/content-creator-request-thread/14660/35">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/content-creator-request-thread/14660/35</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2017 01:01:13 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14660-35</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/content-creator-request-thread/14660.rss">Content Creator Request Thread</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Content Creator Request Thread</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[JeffMOD]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>After a few experiments with various sound and dialog systems, I have a couple more requests for whenever your programmers are finished with Xen and general engine updates (and have had some time to rest, of course)</p>
<ol>
<li>Implement <a href="https://developer.valvesoftware.com/wiki/Ambient_generic:_stop_and_toggle_fix" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">this code</a> so that the Stop input works on sounds without loop points.</li>
<li>In addition to Sage J Fox’s suggestions on the previous page for custom per-map script files, per-map variants of <font face="Consolas,Courier New,Courier,monospace">sentences.txt</font>, <font face="Consolas,Courier New,Courier,monospace">response_rules.txt</font>, and, if at all possible, <font face="Consolas,Courier New,Courier,monospace">scenes.image</font> (though as a binary file and something generated by an engine tool I realize that one’s a tall order!) would be greatly appreciated so we can get some more in-depth dialog going beyond just giving ambient_generics files with phoneme data and making an NPC the audio source entity.</li>
</ol>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/content-creator-request-thread/14660/34">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/content-creator-request-thread/14660/34</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2017 00:52:04 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14660-34</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/content-creator-request-thread/14660.rss">Content Creator Request Thread</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Content Creator Request Thread</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Admiral_Sakai]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Three things I would like to see that are lighting-related, based on my recent… errrm… <span class="bbcode-i">experiences</span> with Office Complex.</p>
<ol>
<li>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">A way to make lights direct-only (i.e. not bouncing) without naming them.</span> Non-bouncing lights are useful for accent lighting and making the lighting in an area look ‘harsher’, and currently the only way to get lights not to bounce is to name them (the canon BM maps use this technique themselves for the shadow-generating lights in the stairwells in Office Complex, and possibly in other places as well). However, if you have a lot of named accent lights they can take out a sizeable chunk of the map’s entdata budget for something that <span class="bbcode-i">could</span> just be baked into the lightmap as usual and would have no reason to have IO properties, and they can interfere with the proper functioning of more conventional named lights that are actually turned on and off by taking up Source’s scarce lightmap “pages” unnecessarily.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">A functional “maximum distance” parameter:</span> In the FGD there is an option to cause lights to only cast a certain distance and then abruptly drop off to zero brightness, but it currently does not seem to have any effect at all. Having such a parameter would be very useful in preventing the “lighting pileup” problems that cause some surfaces to show up much brighter than others when multiple constant or nearly constant lights are placed in a room that is significantly longer or shorter in one dimension than in either or both of the the other two.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Support for negative RGB or brightness values in lights:</span> I am imagining this behavior as being about what you would expect. A negative value would make the relvant R, G, or B channel of the lightmap <span class="bbcode-i">darker</span>, and as the light bounced around and attenuated that value would get closer and closer to 0. This would cap at 0 so that no actual negative values could exist in the finished lightmap- a 0, 0, -255 light (or, depending on how the property was expressed, a 0, 0, 255 light with negative brightness) shining on a white lightmap could make it completely not-blue (i.e. yellow), but that’s it. My primary interest in this sort of light is to add colored accents to very bright areas without making them even brighter, but I imagine this would also be very useful for making certain specific areas look darker or more shadowy when they are in the immediate presence of brighter lights- like in an office area where the lighting is very even (constant attenuation), making a pool of darkness under one burnt-out bulb.</p>
</li>
</ol>
<p>I of course wouldn’t presume to <span class="bbcode-i">command</span> that these features be added, but I would very much appreciate at least some feedback on how feasible they would be.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/content-creator-request-thread/14660/33">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/content-creator-request-thread/14660/33</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 04 Jun 2017 14:17:51 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14660-33</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/content-creator-request-thread/14660.rss">Content Creator Request Thread</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Content Creator Request Thread</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Admiral_Sakai]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>You can actually do that through the character manifest, although sometimes the results can be a bit strange.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/content-creator-request-thread/14660/32">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/content-creator-request-thread/14660/32</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 24 Aug 2016 19:29:30 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14660-32</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/content-creator-request-thread/14660.rss">Content Creator Request Thread</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Content Creator Request Thread</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[LordDz]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>You could allow us to use custom models for the npcs in Hammer, selecting them like you do for prop_statics and such.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/content-creator-request-thread/14660/31">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/content-creator-request-thread/14660/31</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 24 Aug 2016 19:15:56 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14660-31</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/content-creator-request-thread/14660.rss">Content Creator Request Thread</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Content Creator Request Thread</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[bkdale86]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>The NPC bit will probably never happen. Our process so far involves lots of hacks to get things working with the old animation sets from HL2. It isn’t just plug in and works.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/content-creator-request-thread/14660/30">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/content-creator-request-thread/14660/30</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 24 Aug 2016 15:44:02 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14660-30</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/content-creator-request-thread/14660.rss">Content Creator Request Thread</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Content Creator Request Thread</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Snaiper]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Vscripting would be neat, or releasing <span class="bbcode-b"><span class="bbcode-i"><span class="bbcode-u">some</span></span></span> source files for us to modify would also be good.<br>
It would be nice if we could import custom NPCs, kind of like we can with HL2/HL2 Ep2, as well as easily modify the current ones.<br>
Custom weaponry, custom hands, etc. should all be a thing.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/content-creator-request-thread/14660/29">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/content-creator-request-thread/14660/29</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 19 Aug 2016 12:54:58 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14660-29</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/content-creator-request-thread/14660.rss">Content Creator Request Thread</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Content Creator Request Thread</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[dky.tehkingd.u]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Sage J. Fox">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Sage J. Fox:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Apologies for the bit of a bump, but one big thing I could see helping campaign creators would be allowing custom character/gib manifest files, soundscapes, etc. to be loaded per map.</p>
<p>e.g. examplemap.bsp would load examplemap_character_manifest.txt, examplemap_gib_manifest.txt, and/or examplemap_soundscapes.txt, were the file(s) to exist.</p>
<p>Figure per map would be the best way to avoid conflicts, and allow the loading to go automatically. Ideally, the files would be loaded on top of the default files, rather than instead of the defaults.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>So last night I just remembered that <a href="https://developer.valvesoftware.com/wiki/BSPZIP" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">BSPZIP</a> is a thing. I tried it out with Black Mesa, and it mostly works (other than the usual manifest/resource files). So, I think it would be pretty feasible to implement your idea if the BM programmers were to change the code to allow those files to be sourced from a BSPZIPped map.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/content-creator-request-thread/14660/28">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/content-creator-request-thread/14660/28</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 17 Jul 2016 02:35:19 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14660-28</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/content-creator-request-thread/14660.rss">Content Creator Request Thread</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Content Creator Request Thread</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Admiral_Sakai]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>One small thing that would be very useful would be a way to define what name a custom map gets in the saved game list- at the moment the canonical maps have their chapter titles displayed, but custom ones are stuck with their alphanumeric filenames.</p>
<p>There <span class="bbcode-i">might</span> be something that controls this already in the scripts directory, but since those files are themselves aggressively resistant to modding I have not looked at them in any detail.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/content-creator-request-thread/14660/27">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/content-creator-request-thread/14660/27</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 16 Jul 2016 13:28:03 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14660-27</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/content-creator-request-thread/14660.rss">Content Creator Request Thread</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Content Creator Request Thread</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[hscsguy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>oh wait so point_proximity_sensor will send it’s distance value to logic_compare without the need to actually call it? That is easier than I initially thought. I still think some sort of env_trigger or something would be beneficial, but I’ll stick w/ regular triggers and your suggested setup for now. Thanks for the tip!</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/content-creator-request-thread/14660/26">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/content-creator-request-thread/14660/26</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jul 2016 17:47:21 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14660-26</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/content-creator-request-thread/14660.rss">Content Creator Request Thread</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Content Creator Request Thread</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[dky.tehkingd.u]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>It wouldn’t be hard to program, but on the other hand it’s also not too difficult to just do it with standard entities. Plus, the benefit of using standard entities is that it’s more portable between other Source games. If you have a need to make a lot of these kinds of setups, that’s what prefabs are for.</p>
<p>Basically, prefer the standard entities whenever possible.</p>
<p>EDIT: To be clear, you don’t need a logic_timer. All you need to do is hook up the point_proximity_sensor’s “Distance” output to a logic_compare’s “SetValueCompare” input, and set the logic_compare’s “OnLessThan” output to whatever you want to trigger. This setup requires a grand total of two logic entities. That’s <span class="bbcode-i">nothing</span>.  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=9" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/content-creator-request-thread/14660/25">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/content-creator-request-thread/14660/25</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jul 2016 16:03:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14660-25</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/content-creator-request-thread/14660.rss">Content Creator Request Thread</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Content Creator Request Thread</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[hscsguy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="LordDz">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/l/d2c977/40.png" class="avatar"> LordDz:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>There is the <a href="https://developer.valvesoftware.com/wiki/Point_proximity_sensor" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">point_proximity_sensor</a> , that allows you to output the distance between two entities.</p>
<p>So set 1 entity to !player and the other to either itself or an info_target.</p>
<p>I guess in the outputs you could do something like “Distance 200” target “bla bla bla”</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>That’s true, but that would require a logic_compare to determine if the activator is within the appropriate distance and a logic_timer to keep testing the Distance from point_proximity_sensor. I figured something like an env_trigger would help avoid having to set something like that up, but I could be oversimplifying the requirements to add such an entity.   <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=9" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/content-creator-request-thread/14660/24">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/content-creator-request-thread/14660/24</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jul 2016 01:42:44 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14660-24</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/content-creator-request-thread/14660.rss">Content Creator Request Thread</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Content Creator Request Thread</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[LordDz]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>There is the <a href="https://developer.valvesoftware.com/wiki/Point_proximity_sensor" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">point_proximity_sensor</a> , that allows you to output the distance between two entities.</p>
<p>So set 1 entity to !player and the other to either itself or an info_target.</p>
<p>I guess in the outputs you could do something like “Distance 200” target “bla bla bla”</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/content-creator-request-thread/14660/23">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/content-creator-request-thread/14660/23</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jul 2016 21:26:59 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14660-23</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/content-creator-request-thread/14660.rss">Content Creator Request Thread</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Content Creator Request Thread</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[hscsguy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Sorry to bump an already bumped old thread, but I had an idea and wanted to run a question by the developers. I may just be called lazy for this, but I was curious if it would be possible and simple enough to add an entity that fired the same outputs as a trigger_once or a trigger_multiple, but operated as a point entity with a radial trigger like env_soundscape? It would be beneficial for setting up scripts quickly without having to create a brush volume every time you wish to add a new trigger and then recompile VBSP. Plus, a spherical trigger volume can be very useful in areas that don’t require the boxy precision of brushes. I know that you could create a spherical trigger_multiple, but hammer is notorious for messing up the vertices on spherical brushes and it still requires recompiling more than -onlyents.</p>
<p>It’s not a big request and is really more about convenience admittedly, rather than necessity. But it was an idea that I just wanted to throw out there, see what anyone else thought. Assuming an entity with this functionality doesn’t already exist in the editor and has somehow alluded me all this time.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/content-creator-request-thread/14660/22">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/content-creator-request-thread/14660/22</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jul 2016 20:17:42 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14660-22</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/content-creator-request-thread/14660.rss">Content Creator Request Thread</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Content Creator Request Thread</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[TextFAMGUY1]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>That would be pretty sweet, yes. I’ll run it by the team.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/content-creator-request-thread/14660/21">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/content-creator-request-thread/14660/21</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 May 2016 05:13:38 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14660-21</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/content-creator-request-thread/14660.rss">Content Creator Request Thread</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Content Creator Request Thread</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypt]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>That’s actually a pretty good idea. I don’t how deeply ingrained into the engine the current loading system is, but the idea itself sounds simple enough on everyone.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/content-creator-request-thread/14660/20">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/content-creator-request-thread/14660/20</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 May 2016 20:53:48 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14660-20</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/content-creator-request-thread/14660.rss">Content Creator Request Thread</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Content Creator Request Thread</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Sage_J_Fox]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Apologies for the bit of a bump, but one big thing I could see helping campaign creators would be allowing custom character/gib manifest files, soundscapes, etc. to be loaded per map.</p>
<p>e.g. examplemap.bsp would load examplemap_character_manifest.txt, examplemap_gib_manifest.txt, and/or examplemap_soundscapes.txt, were the file(s) to exist.</p>
<p>Figure per map would be the best way to avoid conflicts, and allow the loading to go automatically. Ideally, the files would be loaded on top of the default files, rather than instead of the defaults.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/content-creator-request-thread/14660/19">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/content-creator-request-thread/14660/19</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 May 2016 20:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14660-19</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/content-creator-request-thread/14660.rss">Content Creator Request Thread</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Content Creator Request Thread</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[bkdale86]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Please don’t report “bugs” here. They might get lost. This is for requests from content creators and as such if it’s a true bug it might not get added to the fix list for a while.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/content-creator-request-thread/14660/18">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/content-creator-request-thread/14660/18</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 07 Feb 2016 16:40:28 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14660-18</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/content-creator-request-thread/14660.rss">Content Creator Request Thread</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Content Creator Request Thread</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[KevinJRattman]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Maki">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/m/ba8739/40.png" class="avatar"> Maki:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I assume this is the post mentioned <a href="https://steamcommunity.com/app/362890/discussions/0/412446292753469778/" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">here</a>.</p>
<p>Okay, thanks on the Tentacles.</p>
<p>Like I said - it doesn’t have to be “smart” about making sure its head doesn’t hit collision or something.  Basically, I want a flag that disables its vertical ascent/descent while in its normal AI.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I wanted you to post about the Tentacles yourself since it was your idea, but I thought you weren’t going to see my reply (the one I directed you to here in Steam forum), and I also saw you were inactive for quite a long time so I thought I would make one myself along with mine. Feel free to keep suggest ideas or report bugs that would help your mapping journey, though.</p>
<p>Anyway, Chon has stated that the likelyhood of the Tentacles in newer Surface Tension is slim. He hasn’t talked about modding topic, though. It would be really, really nice if this were implemented, but as a modder I know how just somethings can’t be done. I’m not an AI coder so I don’t know a lot on this topic, and I even doubt if it’s really hard to make Tentacles bang only the base (it’s more of removing the AI code, actually), if it’s something impossible, I guess we’ll have to accept it.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b"><span class="bbcode-i"><span class="bbcode-u">EDIT:</span></span><span class="bbcode-u"> New bugs found</span>- The input UnholsterWeapon and HolsterWeapon do not work.</span> Since it’s only one line I just edited my previous post instead of making a new one. On input fire, this happens:</p>
<p>CBaseAnimatingOverlay::AddGesture:  model models/humans/guard_02.mdl missing activity ACT_DISARM</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/content-creator-request-thread/14660/17">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/content-creator-request-thread/14660/17</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2016 20:40:24 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14660-17</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/content-creator-request-thread/14660.rss">Content Creator Request Thread</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Content Creator Request Thread</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Maki]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I assume this is the post mentioned <a href="https://steamcommunity.com/app/362890/discussions/0/412446292753469778/" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">here</a>.</p>
<p>Okay, thanks on the Tentacles.</p>
<p>Like I said - it doesn’t have to be “smart” about making sure its head doesn’t hit collision or something.  Basically, I want a flag that disables its vertical ascent/descent while in its normal AI.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/content-creator-request-thread/14660/16">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/content-creator-request-thread/14660/16</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2016 19:54:01 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14660-16</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/content-creator-request-thread/14660.rss">Content Creator Request Thread</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Content Creator Request Thread</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Fr0z3n]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="KevinJRattman">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/k/53a042/40.png" class="avatar"> KevinJRattman:</div>
<blockquote>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Fr0z3n">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/f/f1d935/40.png" class="avatar"> Fr0z3n:</div>
<blockquote>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="KevinJRattman">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/k/53a042/40.png" class="avatar"> KevinJRattman:</div>
<blockquote></blockquote>
</aside>
<p>These are good. I’ll ask about the .50cal thing, and if it’s broke for sure I’ll make a report for it.Our music may be in the the wrong format for previewing in sound browser, so tha probably why it’s not show up. If it’s not showing up in game too, then it’s a bigger issue.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I was talking about since you can’t preview it in the browser you actually have to go into sounds.vpk and look for the name, and that’s a bad thing. Some other suggestions:<br>
<span class="bbcode-b">Modder-friendly Tentacle.</span> Currently they are heavily script based, especially with the heights they bang. They are always set to bang certain heights you see in Blast Pit which is a bad news for modders. So a way to specify heights they bang would be a good option. However I have no idea how this would work out with current animation system for Tentacle, which probably was pre-animated and therefore do not support this. In this case then, simply a sort of “bang only the first level” spawnflags would be a nice alternative, that is, will only attack this particular level checked, which would be a suitable option for most map makers. <a href="https://forums.blackmesasource.com/index.php/Thread/28691-Tentacles/" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">(Courtesy of Maki!)</a></p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">INVISMETAL textures don’t seem to work</span> - they still make non-metal sounds.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Is func_tank sort of broken for non-0-degrees?</span> If I want to make func_tank that is rotated like, 90 degrees, the steps required is a bit complicated. I first build the tank in non-rotated ways, that is in 0 degrees, and then specify the 90 degrees in its angles keyvalue. I do not remember having to do this in other games, I would just build the tank in a desired angle and done. The alternative seem to work OK, so I’d say this is just a minor issue. I just wanted to bring it up if anyone came across same obstacle as me.</p>
<p>A minor compliant, but <span class="bbcode-b">when you open Hammer it is recognized as the game in Steam</span>. This makes it frustrating to open both the game and the hammer together, as trying to open the game result in “The game is already running”. I can open the game first and then hammer, however this gives a temporal “video card has crashed” error (although the game runs fine)</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I can’t say anything about the tentacles right now, but I’ll pop the suggestion.</p>
<p>func_tank is a dash janky atm, and we know about it, but not sure when a fix will come through.</p>
<p>For hammer: No idea how that works programming side, so again, I shall confer with the magic programmers and see what they say.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/content-creator-request-thread/14660/15">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/content-creator-request-thread/14660/15</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2016 12:58:32 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14660-15</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/content-creator-request-thread/14660.rss">Content Creator Request Thread</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Content Creator Request Thread</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[KevinJRattman]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Fr0z3n">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/f/f1d935/40.png" class="avatar"> Fr0z3n:</div>
<blockquote>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="KevinJRattman">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/k/53a042/40.png" class="avatar"> KevinJRattman:</div>
<blockquote></blockquote>
</aside>
<p>These are good. I’ll ask about the .50cal thing, and if it’s broke for sure I’ll make a report for it.<br>
Our music may be in the the wrong format for previewing in sound browser, so tha probably why it’s not show up. If it’s not showing up in game too, then it’s a bigger issue.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I was talking about since you can’t preview it in the browser you actually have to go into sounds.vpk and look for the name, and that’s a bad thing. Some other suggestions:</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Modder-friendly Tentacle.</span> Currently they are heavily script based, especially with the heights they bang. They are always set to bang certain heights you see in Blast Pit which is a bad news for modders. So a way to specify heights they bang would be a good option. However I have no idea how this would work out with current animation system for Tentacle, which probably was pre-animated and therefore do not support this. In this case then, simply a sort of “bang only the first level” spawnflags would be a nice alternative, that is, will only attack this particular level checked, which would be a suitable option for most map makers. <a href="https://forums.blackmesasource.com/index.php/Thread/28691-Tentacles/" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">(Courtesy of Maki!)</a></p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">INVISMETAL textures don’t seem to work</span> - they still make non-metal sounds.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Is func_tank sort of broken for non-0-degrees?</span> If I want to make func_tank that is rotated like, 90 degrees, the steps required is a bit complicated. I first build the tank in non-rotated ways, that is in 0 degrees, and then specify the 90 degrees in its angles keyvalue. I do not remember having to do this in other games, I would just build the tank in a desired angle and done. The alternative seem to work OK, so I’d say this is just a minor issue. I just wanted to bring it up if anyone came across same obstacle as me.</p>
<p>A minor compliant, but <span class="bbcode-b">when you open Hammer it is recognized as the game in Steam</span>. This makes it frustrating to open both the game and the hammer together, as trying to open the game result in “The game is already running”. I can open the game first and then hammer, however this gives a temporal “video card has crashed” error (although the game runs fine)</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/content-creator-request-thread/14660/14">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/content-creator-request-thread/14660/14</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2016 12:47:21 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14660-14</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/content-creator-request-thread/14660.rss">Content Creator Request Thread</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Content Creator Request Thread</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypt]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <ul>
<li>The console command r_flushlod causes the engine to crash without error. The command quickly refreshes the models so you can view changes in-game immediately, but right now since it crashes, you have to manually restart the game to reload the models, which takes significantly longer.</li>
</ul>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/content-creator-request-thread/14660/13">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/content-creator-request-thread/14660/13</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2016 08:29:51 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14660-13</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/content-creator-request-thread/14660.rss">Content Creator Request Thread</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Content Creator Request Thread</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Fr0z3n]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="KevinJRattman">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/k/53a042/40.png" class="avatar"> KevinJRattman:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Oh, well. I should’ve known. Also, a few more things to suggest.</p>
<p>Some outputs are not working: <span class="bbcode-b">in func_50cal, the output OnAmmoDepleted doesn’t seem to work</span>. Now, no 50 cal guns in Black Mesa have ammunition limits, but since this is supposed to be a modding thread, and I was actually making a map with ammo limit 50 cal, I thought I should throw it in. I was trying to make the H.E.V. say “Ammunition depleted.” once it runs out of ammo, but the output doesn’t get called.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Barnacles do not have “Ambush Mode” spawnflag</span> - bug? In the original HL series, it was possible to make them ambush you by making them not have their toung stick out initially, and have them out when you call “DropToungue” input). The spawnflag seemed to be overriden by “Tougue never penetrates water”, which seems like an equally nice option, by the way.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Would it be possible to have reprogrammed turrets have no ammo limits using spawnflags, keyvalues, etc?</span> I was trying to somewhat recreate that scene from Nova Prospekt in Half-Life 2, using turrets to defend the ememies. But reprogrammed sentries have ammunition limits and generally low health. I can bypass the health via SetHealth input, but if they keep retract themselves after shooting 3 or more enemies, it doesn’t quite feel the same. They also would have to not die if they get knocked over too. Or better yet- maybe add keyvalue like func_50cal above, let mappers decide how much ammo the turret have. e.g. -1 for infinite ammo. This seems a much better option than spawnflag, but not sure how it could be worked out seeing how turrets are technically NPCs. I understand if this is something impossible.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">In Half-Life series, musics come up in sound browsers, but in </span><span class="bbcode-b">Black Mesa they do not.</span> Is it be possible to fix this?</p>
<p>About the alternate hand skin (guard hand skin, etc), it’s a nice feature, <span class="bbcode-b">but it would also have to disable the “Freeman lines”.</span> e.g. “Lead on, Gordon!” or “Squad, we’ve got Freeman!”. Marines have this function via spawnflags, but I don’t think guards/scientists do.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>These are good. I’ll ask about the .50cal thing, and if it’s broke for sure I’ll make a report for it.</p>
<p>Our music may be in the the wrong format for previewing in sound browser, so tha probably why it’s not show up. If it’s not showing up in game too, then it’s a bigger issue.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/content-creator-request-thread/14660/12">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/content-creator-request-thread/14660/12</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 04 Feb 2016 16:09:53 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14660-12</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/content-creator-request-thread/14660.rss">Content Creator Request Thread</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Content Creator Request Thread</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[dky.tehkingd.u]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Assuming that they fix the content mounting issues, you could edit the response rules file to simply not use any of the “Freeman” lines whenever a global context is present. That would be a viable alternative to the “Disable freeman lines” spawnflag (again, once they fix the content mounting/external file override issues).</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/content-creator-request-thread/14660/11">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/content-creator-request-thread/14660/11</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 03 Feb 2016 22:54:35 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14660-11</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/content-creator-request-thread/14660.rss">Content Creator Request Thread</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
