<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Creationism, Intelligent Design and Evolution</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/creationism-intelligent-design-and-evolution/3361</link>
    <description>So, the atheist thread is getting fouled up with talk about creationism, intelligent design and evolution.  Since atheism and evolution are not the same topic, I am creating this topic to discuss those matters and leave the atheism thread to atheism-related topics.

And, go!  ^_^

(Note to the mods: if you think this thread should be deleted or locked, please feel free to do so; I just wanted to clear the atheism thread of evolution-related discussions.  Thanks!)</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 24 Mar 2010 17:30:59 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Off Topic</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/creationism-intelligent-design-and-evolution/3361.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Creationism, Intelligent Design and Evolution</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Deutscher_Scharfschu]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=KnJX68ELbAY" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=KnJX68ELbAY</a></p>
<p><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=4A-dMqEbSk8&amp;feature=related" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Turns out we did come from monkeys</a></p>
<p>EDIT: some noob revived a thread from september, anyways, this sums up my views.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Deutscher Scharfschütze">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Deutscher Scharfschütze:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>i think the biggest problem creationists have is that they don’t understand what a scientific theory is, or rather the difference between fact, theory and law.</p>
<p>The fact of evolution is that species tend to change through time. Yes, this includes the accent of man.</p>
<p>Now the theory of evolution tries to explain <span class="bbcode-i">why</span> this happens. Of the species, the ones with beneficial mutations that help them survive, survive. meanwhile, the less equipped to survive don’t. the theory of evolution is a combination of genetics and Darwin’s theories.</p>
<p>You see, Evolution will remain a theory, because in science, you can never prove, or disprove something like that. Evolution is the backbone of modern biology, and quite frankly, it makes sense. I simply see no science in creationism, literally zero evidence or data suggest it.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/creationism-intelligent-design-and-evolution/3361/167">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/creationism-intelligent-design-and-evolution/3361/167</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 24 Mar 2010 17:30:59 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3361-167</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/creationism-intelligent-design-and-evolution/3361.rss">Creationism, Intelligent Design and Evolution</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Creationism, Intelligent Design and Evolution</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[bur]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Thank you for responding to the OP, in stead of the rest of the thread.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/creationism-intelligent-design-and-evolution/3361/166">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/creationism-intelligent-design-and-evolution/3361/166</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 24 Mar 2010 17:18:53 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3361-166</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/creationism-intelligent-design-and-evolution/3361.rss">Creationism, Intelligent Design and Evolution</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Creationism, Intelligent Design and Evolution</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Ham_Solo]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Evolution is fact.<br>
“Evolution theories” explain the “how”, not the “what”.</p>
<p>Intelligent design is nonsense.<br>
<span alt="" class="broken-image" title="This image is broken"><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-unlink svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#unlink"></use></svg></span><br>
See the second pair of limbs there?<br>
Very intelligent indeed.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/creationism-intelligent-design-and-evolution/3361/165">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/creationism-intelligent-design-and-evolution/3361/165</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 24 Mar 2010 17:16:04 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3361-165</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/creationism-intelligent-design-and-evolution/3361.rss">Creationism, Intelligent Design and Evolution</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Creationism, Intelligent Design and Evolution</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Note-anator]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>LOL !!!</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/creationism-intelligent-design-and-evolution/3361/164">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/creationism-intelligent-design-and-evolution/3361/164</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 21 Mar 2010 02:15:24 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3361-164</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/creationism-intelligent-design-and-evolution/3361.rss">Creationism, Intelligent Design and Evolution</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Creationism, Intelligent Design and Evolution</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[baconeggs]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I thought that Darwinism was the tendency to live in caves dug out of the desert.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/creationism-intelligent-design-and-evolution/3361/163">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/creationism-intelligent-design-and-evolution/3361/163</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 20 Mar 2010 23:37:16 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3361-163</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/creationism-intelligent-design-and-evolution/3361.rss">Creationism, Intelligent Design and Evolution</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Creationism, Intelligent Design and Evolution</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[danielsangeo]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Deutscher Scharfschütze">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Deutscher Scharfschütze:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Does anybody else get pissed when creationists refer to Evolution as ‘Darwinism’?<br>
They fail to realize that Evolution is much broader than Darwin’s theories as it encompasses modern genetics and is the backbone to modern biology.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I’m waiting for someone to call gravity “Newtonism” or “Copernicism”.   <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=9" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/creationism-intelligent-design-and-evolution/3361/162">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/creationism-intelligent-design-and-evolution/3361/162</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 20 Mar 2010 17:13:36 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3361-162</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/creationism-intelligent-design-and-evolution/3361.rss">Creationism, Intelligent Design and Evolution</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Creationism, Intelligent Design and Evolution</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Deutscher_Scharfschu]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Does anybody else get pissed when creationists refer to Evolution as ‘Darwinism’?<br>
They fail to realize that Evolution is much broader than Darwin’s theories as it encompasses modern genetics and is the backbone to modern biology.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/creationism-intelligent-design-and-evolution/3361/161">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/creationism-intelligent-design-and-evolution/3361/161</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 20 Mar 2010 14:42:49 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3361-161</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/creationism-intelligent-design-and-evolution/3361.rss">Creationism, Intelligent Design and Evolution</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Creationism, Intelligent Design and Evolution</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Note-anator]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>This is the opening abstract from this site, concerning Mimivirus, and what it is. I will dig further for the mentioned article. The end of the abstract mentions the possible role of mimivirus in eukaryotes - it is an interesting idea, that this DNA strand is being looked at as a bridge for evolved cells…</p>
<p><a href="https://www.virologyj.com/content/2/1/62" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://www.virologyj.com/content/2/1/62</a></p>
<p>“Abstract<br>
The discovery and genome analysis of Acanthamoeba polyphaga Mimivirus, the largest known DNA virus, challenged much of the accepted dogma regarding viruses. Its particle size (&gt;400 nm), genome length (1.2 million bp) and huge gene repertoire (911 protein coding genes) all contribute to blur the established boundaries between viruses and the smallest parasitic cellular organisms. Phylogenetic analyses also suggested that the Mimivirus lineage could have emerged prior to the individualization of cellular organisms from the three established domains, triggering a debate that can only be resolved by generating and analyzing more data. The next step is then to seek some evidence that Mimivirus is not the only representative of its kind and determine where to look for new Mimiviridae. An exhaustive similarity search of all Mimivirus predicted proteins against all publicly available sequences identified many of their closest homologues among the Sargasso Sea environmental sequences. Subsequent phylogenetic analyses suggested that unknown large viruses evolutionarily closer to Mimivirus than to any presently characterized species exist in abundance in the Sargasso Sea. Their isolation and genome sequencing could prove invaluable in understanding the origin and diversity of large DNA viruses, and shed some light on the role they eventually played in the emergence of eukaryotes.”</p>
<p>PS. Baccon, ok, I see your take very clearly, and that is a wonderful explaination. I asked simply because there is confusion sometimes regarding what one person sees as a “mutation”, compared to someone else. It is mind bending the extremes you run into in both camps - I find sometimes asking for very concise explaination a very good way to see the other person’s frame. Thanks for that. A person who is up on the terms, will say something, and the other person is not up on the terms, and makes assumptions. A person who is NOT up on their science will hear the word mution, and think of a sudden mysterious fish growing legs and being on the land… failing ot realise the emense amount of time needed for some "Mutation(s)/change " to happen.</p>
<p>_____________________________________-</p>
<p>From Science News, it is a quick overveiw of Mimivirus without going in too deep.</p>
<p><a href="https://www.sciencenews.org/view/generic/id/43277/title/Mimivirus_up_close" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://www.sciencenews.org/view/generic/id/43277/title/Mimivirus_up_close</a></p>
<hr>
<p>This is the article from Scientific America, December 2004, but does not seem to be the article that was discussing the evolution/devolution concept.</p>
<p><a href="https://www.scientificamerican.com/article.cfm?id=are-viruses-alive-2004" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://www.scientificamerican.com/article.cfm?id=are-viruses-alive-2004</a></p>
<p>I will think some more on it, and see if I can remember where the discusion came from. (Sorry - see what you have to look forward to when you get old?)</p>
<p>This article does talk about shared genes in both Bacteria and Humans - Which is interesting enough - the article is 4 pages long, and worth a careful read through. Mimivirus (Certain strains of it) can contain as many as 911 genes, with is really quite amazing really.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/creationism-intelligent-design-and-evolution/3361/160">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/creationism-intelligent-design-and-evolution/3361/160</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 19 Mar 2010 00:46:46 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3361-160</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/creationism-intelligent-design-and-evolution/3361.rss">Creationism, Intelligent Design and Evolution</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Creationism, Intelligent Design and Evolution</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Soup]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I hate most things that anti-evolutionists say (on the topic of evolution), since they’re generally nonsensical, uniformed or arrogant (the things they say, not necessarily the people).</p>
<p>Hm, without the parenthesis, that’s a very angreh post.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/creationism-intelligent-design-and-evolution/3361/159">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/creationism-intelligent-design-and-evolution/3361/159</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 18 Mar 2010 23:08:10 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3361-159</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/creationism-intelligent-design-and-evolution/3361.rss">Creationism, Intelligent Design and Evolution</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Creationism, Intelligent Design and Evolution</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[baconeggs]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I always hate it when some anti-evolution nut argues that certain adaptations don’t help a creature’s survival, completely ignoring the fact that it isn’t detrimental either so it has an even chance of being passed on.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/creationism-intelligent-design-and-evolution/3361/158">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/creationism-intelligent-design-and-evolution/3361/158</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 18 Mar 2010 22:08:35 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3361-158</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/creationism-intelligent-design-and-evolution/3361.rss">Creationism, Intelligent Design and Evolution</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Creationism, Intelligent Design and Evolution</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Soup]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>A perfect analogy, bacon.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/creationism-intelligent-design-and-evolution/3361/157">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/creationism-intelligent-design-and-evolution/3361/157</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 18 Mar 2010 12:52:13 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3361-157</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/creationism-intelligent-design-and-evolution/3361.rss">Creationism, Intelligent Design and Evolution</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Creationism, Intelligent Design and Evolution</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[baconeggs]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Note-anator">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/n/c2a13f/40.png" class="avatar"> Note-anator:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>So if I understand you correctly, you are saying that “evolution” has a duality in mechanism… evolution can happen without a mutation, as long as whatever the change is, is a survival advantage? But if it not a survival advantage, but merely a change, it is not evolution, unless it is a mutation that persists - does that mutation also have to be a survival advantage to count?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Arrgh! Evolution is not a linear process. It is not a force directing a species towards some perfect form. Evolution is simply how creatures change. You are right, not every evolution or mutation results in a survival advantage. However if it is the chances of it being passed on are greatly increased.</p>
<p>As an example let’s use a theoretical species of bird, that have no interesting characteristics and are completely grey. Let’s say one day a bird develops a mutation which causes a streak of red plumage to grow along its wing. This is a change, a mutation, evolution. However it serves no actual purpose, and doesn’t help the bird survive any better than its brethren. Despite this, it still gets passed along the family line and eventually we end up with two kinds of bird, one that has a red streak and one that is fully grey.</p>
<p>These aren’t seperate species, they can still breed together. I’m not sure of the terminology but they are more akin to seperate breeds, just as dogs are.</p>
<p>But what happens if this red plumage was actually beneficial? Let’s say that male birds with this red streak are seen as more desirable partners by females. Suddenly this bird has an advantage over its relatives, and gets far more oppurtunites to breed. As the bird’s young will also have the red streak this effect is multiplied, and soon birds with full grey plumage will hardly get any chance to mate and pass on their characteristics. The result is that the original greys are bred out and the only birds that are left are the ones with red plumage.</p>
<p>All of this is evolution. The species has changed, not neccessarily for the better, but it has altered. Evolution is not about species surviving better due to mutations, but more about which mutations persist due to the environment.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/creationism-intelligent-design-and-evolution/3361/156">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/creationism-intelligent-design-and-evolution/3361/156</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 18 Mar 2010 05:56:07 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3361-156</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/creationism-intelligent-design-and-evolution/3361.rss">Creationism, Intelligent Design and Evolution</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Creationism, Intelligent Design and Evolution</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[mattemuse]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Note-anator">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/n/c2a13f/40.png" class="avatar"> Note-anator:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Actually, some are thinking that we may have come from Mimi-virus. (or some such simular)</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>can you provide some kind of citation for this, it sounds like an interesting read.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/creationism-intelligent-design-and-evolution/3361/155">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/creationism-intelligent-design-and-evolution/3361/155</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 18 Mar 2010 05:20:22 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3361-155</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/creationism-intelligent-design-and-evolution/3361.rss">Creationism, Intelligent Design and Evolution</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Creationism, Intelligent Design and Evolution</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Note-anator]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Burbinator">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Burbinator:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Our classification of different species is of no relevance in evolution.</p>
<p>Any mutation that persists is a step in evolution. If becoming larger is not a result of mutations, then it is not evolution, unless the greater chance of survival of the species overall causes certain genetic changes.</p>
<p>BTW, saying “evo” instead of just evolution kind of annoys me, just putting that out there.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Ummmm… No relevance? To what is happening in nature, no… in terms of our being able to grasp what is going on, yes.</p>
<p>As far as a mutation, define what a mutation actually is. What mutation that is something transerfable to offspring, and is replicatable, qualifies exactly?</p>
<p>Why this becomes important, is because in a chromosome match up, would one consider the blending of genetic information a mutation of the original? How far do we take this? As far as common decent, the evidence is there. In terms of defining “Mutation” there seems to be confusion.</p>
<p>So if I understand you correctly, you are saying that “evolution” has a duality in mechanism… evolution can happen without a mutation, as long as whatever the change is, is a survival advantage? But if it not a survival advantage, but merely a change, it is not evolution, unless it is a mutation that persists - does that mutation also have to be a survival advantage to count?</p>
<p>There is also devolution, and convergent evolution as well. Mimi-virus would be an example of devoltion to some degree, because surviving in a lessor state, has actually seemed to have helped the virus survive. (If I recall the artical correctly - I think it was Scientific America - Actually, some are thinking that we may have come from Mimi-virus. (or some such simular) The strain slpit, and one went forward as it were, and one digressed.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/creationism-intelligent-design-and-evolution/3361/154">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/creationism-intelligent-design-and-evolution/3361/154</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 18 Mar 2010 04:47:21 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3361-154</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/creationism-intelligent-design-and-evolution/3361.rss">Creationism, Intelligent Design and Evolution</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Creationism, Intelligent Design and Evolution</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Soup]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="baconeggs">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/b/43a26b/40.png" class="avatar"> baconeggs:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>It’s not really an adaptation as a random mutation that has benefitted the bird.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>While adaptation has the connotations of a conscious process, it’s still perfectly find to use that term for evolution.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/creationism-intelligent-design-and-evolution/3361/153">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/creationism-intelligent-design-and-evolution/3361/153</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 18 Mar 2010 04:07:02 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3361-153</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/creationism-intelligent-design-and-evolution/3361.rss">Creationism, Intelligent Design and Evolution</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Creationism, Intelligent Design and Evolution</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[danielsangeo]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="mattemuse">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/m/dc4da7/40.png" class="avatar"> mattemuse:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Humans and apes are two different evolutionary branches, but we do share a common ancestor who was neither human nor ape.</p>
<p>:ninja:</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Technically speaking, humans ARE apes.  Humans are a member of the Great Apes along with chimpanzees and gorillas.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/creationism-intelligent-design-and-evolution/3361/152">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/creationism-intelligent-design-and-evolution/3361/152</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 18 Mar 2010 01:56:43 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3361-152</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/creationism-intelligent-design-and-evolution/3361.rss">Creationism, Intelligent Design and Evolution</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Creationism, Intelligent Design and Evolution</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[_rot_fodder]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="danielsangeo">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/user_avatar/leakfree.org/danielsangeo/40/4347_2.png" class="avatar"> danielsangeo:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Sahelanthropus.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I think I used to go to school with one of those.</p>
<p>fine fine! I’m getting out! I’m going![/SIZE]</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/creationism-intelligent-design-and-evolution/3361/151">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/creationism-intelligent-design-and-evolution/3361/151</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 18 Mar 2010 01:54:14 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3361-151</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/creationism-intelligent-design-and-evolution/3361.rss">Creationism, Intelligent Design and Evolution</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Creationism, Intelligent Design and Evolution</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[mattemuse]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="loony636">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/l/6bbea6/40.png" class="avatar"> loony636:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Eh? Then what did we evolve from?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Humans and apes are two different evolutionary branches, but we do share a common ancestor who was neither human nor ape.</p>
<p>:ninja:</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/creationism-intelligent-design-and-evolution/3361/150">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/creationism-intelligent-design-and-evolution/3361/150</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 18 Mar 2010 01:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3361-150</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/creationism-intelligent-design-and-evolution/3361.rss">Creationism, Intelligent Design and Evolution</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Creationism, Intelligent Design and Evolution</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[danielsangeo]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="loony636">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/l/6bbea6/40.png" class="avatar"> loony636:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Eh? Then what did we evolve from?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>According to evidence, the Australopithecus.  Go back further and you can find what is believed to be the common ancestor of the chimpanzee and the human:  Sahelanthropus.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/creationism-intelligent-design-and-evolution/3361/149">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/creationism-intelligent-design-and-evolution/3361/149</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 18 Mar 2010 01:44:07 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3361-149</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/creationism-intelligent-design-and-evolution/3361.rss">Creationism, Intelligent Design and Evolution</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Creationism, Intelligent Design and Evolution</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[bur]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>He believes we were created as we are by god. He believes we didn’t evolve at all.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Note-anator">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/n/c2a13f/40.png" class="avatar"> Note-anator:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Baccon&amp;eggs;</p>
<p>Have been thinking through this conversation and am realizing that I am not quite on keel here, concerning definitions. A creature getting larger, is a change from the current design, ( I cringe with the term) but it does not make it a different species. However, it is still a change.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Our classification of different species is of no relevance in evolution.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Note-anator">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/n/c2a13f/40.png" class="avatar"> Note-anator:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>So now we are looking at two things - definition of a benificial “random” mutation, and that of what we are willing to accept as being “Evo”. On the one hand, being bigger does have an impact on potential survivability - on the other, it really does not qualify as a species change… so again, we are needing to look at definition.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Any mutation that persists is a step in evolution. If becoming larger is not a result of mutations, then it is not evolution, unless the greater chance of survival of the species overall causes certain genetic changes.</p>
<p>BTW, saying “evo” instead of just evolution kind of annoys me, just putting that out there.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/creationism-intelligent-design-and-evolution/3361/148">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/creationism-intelligent-design-and-evolution/3361/148</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 18 Mar 2010 01:28:50 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3361-148</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/creationism-intelligent-design-and-evolution/3361.rss">Creationism, Intelligent Design and Evolution</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Creationism, Intelligent Design and Evolution</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[loony636]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Shadi">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/s/858c86/40.png" class="avatar"> Shadi:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I do believe in the Evolution, as well as most Educated Muslims, but I don’t believe that we evolved from apes</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Eh? Then what did we evolve from?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/creationism-intelligent-design-and-evolution/3361/147">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/creationism-intelligent-design-and-evolution/3361/147</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 18 Mar 2010 01:17:02 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3361-147</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/creationism-intelligent-design-and-evolution/3361.rss">Creationism, Intelligent Design and Evolution</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Creationism, Intelligent Design and Evolution</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Note-anator]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Baccon&amp;eggs;</p>
<p>Have been thinking through this conversation and am realizing that I am not quite on keel here, concerning definitions. A creature getting larger, is a change from the current design, ( I cringe with the term) but it does not make it a different species. However, it is still a change.</p>
<p>So now we are looking at two things - definition of a benificial “random” mutation, and that of what we are willing to accept as being “Evo”. On the one hand, being bigger does have an impact on potential survivability - on the other, it really does not qualify as a species change… so again, we are needing to look at definition.</p>
<p>Just some thoughts.</p>
<p>enjoying this conversation folks… Good input.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/creationism-intelligent-design-and-evolution/3361/146">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/creationism-intelligent-design-and-evolution/3361/146</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 18 Mar 2010 00:53:31 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3361-146</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/creationism-intelligent-design-and-evolution/3361.rss">Creationism, Intelligent Design and Evolution</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Creationism, Intelligent Design and Evolution</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[_rot_fodder]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="danielsangeo">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/user_avatar/leakfree.org/danielsangeo/40/4347_2.png" class="avatar"> danielsangeo:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>[COLOR=‘Lime’]unless [COLOR=‘Red’]your [COLOR=‘Lime’]administrative [COLOR=‘Red’]duties [COLOR=‘Lime’]call [COLOR=‘Red’]for [COLOR=‘Lime’]it (wink wink, nudge nudge, knowhatimean knowhatimean).</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>QFFT!</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/creationism-intelligent-design-and-evolution/3361/145">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/creationism-intelligent-design-and-evolution/3361/145</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 18 Mar 2010 00:52:47 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3361-145</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/creationism-intelligent-design-and-evolution/3361.rss">Creationism, Intelligent Design and Evolution</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Creationism, Intelligent Design and Evolution</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[danielsangeo]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="CatzEyes93">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/user_avatar/leakfree.org/catzeyes93/40/4402_2.png" class="avatar"> CatzEyes93:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I will stop attempting humor in the debate section.  It really is my own fault I guess eh?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>No, please keep the humor up.  The vast majority of us got it.  I’m paying Mr. Ran absolutely no attention.  I believe you should do the same unless your administrative duties call for it (wink wink, nudge nudge, knowhatimean knowhatimean).</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/creationism-intelligent-design-and-evolution/3361/144">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/creationism-intelligent-design-and-evolution/3361/144</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 18 Mar 2010 00:50:45 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3361-144</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/creationism-intelligent-design-and-evolution/3361.rss">Creationism, Intelligent Design and Evolution</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Creationism, Intelligent Design and Evolution</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[CatzEyes93]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I will stop attempting humor in the debate section.  It really is my own fault I guess eh?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/creationism-intelligent-design-and-evolution/3361/143">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/creationism-intelligent-design-and-evolution/3361/143</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 18 Mar 2010 00:47:51 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3361-143</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/creationism-intelligent-design-and-evolution/3361.rss">Creationism, Intelligent Design and Evolution</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
