<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Guess... You know you want to!</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/guess-you-know-you-want-to/4288</link>
    <description>Posting a sad Russian man is not a valid guess. Sorry

We&#39;re almost halfway through the year 2010. Now this has me wondering (and I&#39;m sure the rest of you as well) how close Black Mesa is to being released to the public.

So I thought, seeing as we only have half of a year remaining, maybe we could play a little game?

I now present to the BMS community The Unofficial Bitch Don&#39;t Know Bout My Release Date of Black Mesa: Teh Game.

[img]https://www.downwithea.com/dev/bms/BMSlol.jpg[/img]

Lol, 5 minute horribad-chop infused with old meme. Mmmm, tasty.

Rules:

1. If you are member of the BMS Team and/or have knowledge of a release date. You are void from the contest. (Not that you&#39;d post it anyways)
2. You are not allowed to edit your entries, no matter the time stamp. An edited entry will result in a VOIDED ENTRY. Post wisely!
3. You are not allowed to delete a previous entry to post a new one. All your entries will be VOIDED.
4. No more than ONE entry PER PERSON, PER HOUSEHOLD. Mutliple accounts will have all their entries VOIDED. (And I&#39;m sure banned from the forums as well)
5. Entries must be formatted Month/Day/Year and include a post time in 24-hour format (@ GMT Time). The post time of the mod is considered as the tie breaker if people pick the same day. Example: 03/21/2011 @ 145 GMT
6. Contest will close for entries on June 30th, 2010 @ 00:01 GMT!
7. Raminator brings up a good question. The winner is the person closest to the release date, so no Price is Right rules here.
8. If there is a tie with date and time, then the person who guessed first is the winner.


Prizes:

1. No prize, sorry. About 7.  That is all.

Good luck!</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 28 May 2010 16:44:09 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>The Cafeteria</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/guess-you-know-you-want-to/4288.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Guess... You know you want to!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[M8R-3e4p0o]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Posting a sad Russian man is not a valid guess. Sorry</p>
<p>We’re almost halfway through the year 2010. Now this has me wondering (and I’m sure the rest of you as well) how close Black Mesa is to being released to the public.</p>
<p>So I thought, seeing as we only have half of a year remaining, maybe we could play a little game?</p>
<p>I now present to the BMS community The Unofficial Bitch Don’t Know Bout My Release Date of Black Mesa: Teh Game.</p>
<p><span alt="" class="broken-image" title="This image is broken"><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-unlink svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#unlink"></use></svg></span></p>
<p>Lol, 5 minute horribad-chop infused with old meme. Mmmm, tasty.</p>
<p>Rules:</p>
<ol>
<li>If you are member of the BMS Team and/or have knowledge of a release date. You are void from the contest. (Not that you’d post it anyways)</li>
<li>You are not allowed to edit your entries, no matter the time stamp. An edited entry will result in a VOIDED ENTRY. Post wisely!</li>
<li>You are not allowed to delete a previous entry to post a new one. All your entries will be VOIDED.</li>
<li>No more than ONE entry PER PERSON, PER HOUSEHOLD. Mutliple accounts will have all their entries VOIDED. (And I’m sure banned from the forums as well)</li>
<li>Entries must be formatted Month/Day/Year and include a post time in 24-hour format (@ GMT Time). The post time of the mod is considered as the tie breaker if people pick the same day. Example: 03/21/2011 @ 145 GMT</li>
<li>Contest will close for entries on June 30th, 2010 @ 00:01 GMT!</li>
<li>Raminator brings up a good question. The winner is the person closest to the release date, so no Price is Right rules here.</li>
<li>If there is a tie with date and time, then the person who guessed first is the winner.</li>
</ol>
<p>Prizes:</p>
<ol>
<li>No prize, sorry. About 7.  That is all.</li>
</ol>
<p>Good luck!</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/guess-you-know-you-want-to/4288/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/guess-you-know-you-want-to/4288/1</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 May 2010 16:44:09 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-4288-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/guess-you-know-you-want-to/4288.rss">Guess... You know you want to!</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
