<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>The weapon switching</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/the-weapon-switching/9928</link>
    <description>I have found myself killed because of the weird weapon switch system this game has.

Let me give an example:
The pistol is on the first slot of the second tier
The 357 is on the second slot of the second tier

In all games, HL1, HL2, it&#39;s episodes and the expansions, I had to press 2 twice to get to the 357, no matter what.
However, in this game when I have the pistol equiped, when I press 2 twice, it ends up on the pistol because it skips past the pistol on my first press for whatever reason.

Thing that pushed it over the edge for me that I decided to post about it happened at the cliffs. I had my shotgun equipped only to see a turret further ahead, out of range of my shotgun. I decided to lob an smg grenade at it so I pressed 3 ONCE. However, that did not give me the smg, it gave me the crossbow instead. So I zoomed in instead of firing the grenade. Result: The turret took nearly all my health. I recovered quickly enough and managed to kill the turret, but my health was now at 10 instead of 80, which it would be if the weaponswitch system worked like one would expect it would.
I tried to play onward, but felt I got an unfair disadvantage due to the game having a weird weapon system that doesn&#39;t work similar to other source games, which makes no sense. I jumped down the cliff, followed by a simple quit without saving.

Thank you</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2012 23:46:20 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>The Cafeteria</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/the-weapon-switching/9928.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>The weapon switching</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[k3nny1550]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Didn’t we have a thread on this already? I’m pretty sure that the weapon switch going to the next in the queue instead of starting at the top every time we hit a number slot was mentioned. (I’d like to have 2 pressed twice be my magnum, not 2 pressed twice suddenly pulling out the 9mil instead because of a quirk in the menu.)</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/the-weapon-switching/9928/39">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/the-weapon-switching/9928/39</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2012 23:46:20 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9928-39</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/the-weapon-switching/9928.rss">The weapon switching</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The weapon switching</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[ClockworkBastard]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>All right people<br>
Lets discuss the topic itself!<br>
I think original <span class="bbcode-b">Half-life</span>’s weapon switching is better and that’s why:<br>
We played Half-life games for <span class="bbcode-b">14</span> years, we just get used to it.<br>
HL was my first ever love (I didn’t played Quake I-II before) I started my PC-gaming with Half-life. And, there were Quake III Arena demo, and I compared HL’s and Q’s weapon switching. I can understand the idea - when you take out an Big F%%king Gun of the pocket - it wont come easy, as reaching the <span class="bbcode-b">[9]</span> key on the keyboard. But I definitely liked HL style. Slowly clicking the <span class="bbcode-b">[5]</span> to choose how to blow up a foe.<br>
Yes, I still understand the <span class="bbcode-b">Black Mesa</span>’s switching, like different weapons… emm, tied up with a rope and Gordon hanging around with 4 ropes on him and a crowbar on the belt o_O<br>
No, I don’t really understand it, but it’s somehow useful…<br>
PS Still, we have <span class="bbcode-b">[q]</span> to fast switch on weapons we need one by one</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/the-weapon-switching/9928/38">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/the-weapon-switching/9928/38</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2012 11:01:56 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9928-38</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/the-weapon-switching/9928.rss">The weapon switching</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The weapon switching</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[targ]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Yeah I know he’s not using fast weapon switch, that’s what I said:</p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>He’s not using “fast weapon switch”, so you can tell from the sound effects and the menu itself that he’s using the keyboard and not scrolling.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I don’t know why you think it’s impossible. Press a button and click immediately after, and the menu is barely visible.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/the-weapon-switching/9928/37">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/the-weapon-switching/9928/37</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2012 03:12:16 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9928-37</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/the-weapon-switching/9928.rss">The weapon switching</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The weapon switching</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Dias]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="targ">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/t/c57346/40.png" class="avatar"> targ:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Why on Earth would he go through the trouble of console bindings as opposed to turning on fast weapon switch – just to fool you into thinking he’s pressing buttons when he’s not?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I never said that he was doing it to fool anybody. People often do create pretty ridiculous keybindings for reasons beyond me. As for fast weapon switch, he clearly was not using it, as you could see the weapon belt in the video.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/the-weapon-switching/9928/36">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/the-weapon-switching/9928/36</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2012 01:45:22 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9928-36</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/the-weapon-switching/9928.rss">The weapon switching</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The weapon switching</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[ac3d]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I find the numbers more reliable when under pressure</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/the-weapon-switching/9928/35">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/the-weapon-switching/9928/35</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2012 05:14:33 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9928-35</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/the-weapon-switching/9928.rss">The weapon switching</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The weapon switching</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[BendyBread]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="danielsangeo">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/user_avatar/leakfree.org/danielsangeo/40/4347_2.png" class="avatar"> danielsangeo:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Here’s how it could theoretically be faster:</p>
<p>If you know it takes four mouse-wheel clicks to get from one weapon to the other, you can simply and quickly do the four mouse-wheel clicks.  If you have to get to that same weapon by using one of the number keys along the top of the keyboard, it’s possible that you have to STILL scroll through the multiple weapons assigned to that number.</p>
<p>So, let’s take Half-Life as a for example.</p>
<p>You are currently on the 1st weapon of the 4 key, the rocket launcher, then you want to get to the crossbow, which is the 3rd weapon on the 3 key.  To get to the crossbow, you have to hit 3 three times.  With the mousewheel weapon switch, it’s a single mousewheel click in the up direction.</p>
<p>Also, depending on how your keybindings are, it might still take the same amount of time or longer to go from your fingers on WASD to the 5 key twice as it does to do 6-10 mousewheel clicks.</p>
<p>Just because YOU can’t do it doesn’t mean others cannot.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Yeah that makes sense. So as long as I know the amount of my…uh, “mousewheel clicks”, then I should theoretically be able to do it probably faster than using the keyboard and some practice? (that’s assuming I dont go from, say, the glock to the gluon gun).</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/the-weapon-switching/9928/34">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/the-weapon-switching/9928/34</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2012 04:50:53 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9928-34</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/the-weapon-switching/9928.rss">The weapon switching</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The weapon switching</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Zen609]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="targ">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/t/c57346/40.png" class="avatar"> targ:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Reference doesn’t imply dependence.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b"><span class="bbcode-i">No, that is <span class="bbcode-u">not</span> the supporting argument!</span></span></p>
<p>reference doesn’t imply dependence: just because I mention both points in the same post doesn’t mean I’m saying one is supported by the other.</p>
<p>Everything you’re saying stems from this false presumption that proposition A is predicated on proposition B.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Stop. I only made that comment to  point out an obviously bad argumentation, in the same way someone would point out a mathematical error. I have no interest in your argument itself or this issue in general. I had no intention of making any further comment.</p>
<p>Look, man, L&amp;R is real stuff that people learn in school, use in their job, teach, and research. Like other subjects, some people have some knowledge, some people don’t.</p>
<p>Here’s the structure of your argument:</p>
<p>“dias can not switch weapons with a mousewheel as quickly as the guy in the vid.”</p>
<p>then you support that assertion with this:</p>
<p>because “it’s not even theoretically possible to achieve the same speed using any control scheme that requires you to pass more intermediary selections before getting to the desired one.”</p>
<p>and you support that with:</p>
<p>“Can you find a video demonstrating otherwise?”</p>
<p>That’s the structure. It’s not difficult, it’s not exotic, it’s not couched in some complex rhetorical structure in the middle of someone’s scholarly paper. It’s pretty plain and simple. So, please stop with the dilettantism - the “false presumption” and “proposition A predicated on proposition B”, etc. It’s meaningless and incorrect.  I only made that original comment to point out an error that, to me, is no more significant than pointing out a mathematical error, I wasn’t trying to bust yer balls or something. Just take the correction (or don’t) gracefully, and move on.</p>
<p>In any event, a strand of the thread has become more a discussion of argumentation, rather than weapon-switching, and we should probably end the discussion about argumentation and get closer to the topic.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/the-weapon-switching/9928/33">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/the-weapon-switching/9928/33</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2012 02:26:18 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9928-33</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/the-weapon-switching/9928.rss">The weapon switching</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The weapon switching</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[targ]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Zen609">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/z/71e660/40.png" class="avatar"> Zen609:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>The question itself references the proposition</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Reference doesn’t imply dependence.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Zen609">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/z/71e660/40.png" class="avatar"> Zen609:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>But now you have to support it, but your supporting argument is “Can you find a video demonstrating otherwise?”</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p><span class="bbcode-b"><span class="bbcode-i">No, that is <span class="bbcode-u">not</span> the supporting argument!</span></span> Read the first sentence. Ignore the second one. I reworded it to make it as clear as I could the fact that it stands on its own.</p>
<p>Again, reference doesn’t imply dependence: just because I mention both points in the same post doesn’t mean I’m saying one is supported by the other.</p>
<p>Everything you’re saying stems from this false presumption that proposition A is predicated on proposition B. I never said that it was. I believe it’s theoretically impossible, <span class="bbcode-i"><span class="bbcode-u">as well as</span></span> continuing to doubt that Dias is specifically capable of outperforming this guy.</p>
<p>Let me break it down for you:</p>
<ul>
<li>
<p>I DON’T believe the lack of comparative video is proof that it can’t be done faster.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>I DON’T believe a comparative video would prove one way or the other whether it is theoretically possible at the upper limits.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>I DO believe that more inputs per command results in a longer time to complete a command (<span class="bbcode-i">this</span> is my basis for believing it to be theoretically impossible).</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>I DO believe that a comparative video would give credence to Dias’s claim that he can do it faster.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Dias">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/d/4491bb/40.png" class="avatar"> Dias:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>That’s has to be a video error which makes it appear as if he’s doing it a lot faster than he actually is, because it’s not possible to do it that quickly in-game.</p>
<p>Like I asked before; how do you know the guy in this “random playthrough” uses the keyboard to switch? How do you know he didn’t have a key bound to:</p>
<pre><code class="lang-auto">bind 4 "slot4; slot4; wait; +attack1; wait; -attack1"</code></pre>
<p>to swap to the crossbow or something?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Really, you’re going to claim “video error” instead of admitting the possibility that it’s real? As I said, you can also tell from the sound effects the method he’s using. I have first-hand experience that this is possible; it looks just the same when I’m playing myself (with the keyboard, of course). Why on Earth would he go through the trouble of console bindings as opposed to turning on fast weapon switch – just to fool you into thinking he’s pressing buttons when he’s not? Seems like you’re contriving far-fetched possibilities just to deny the obvious.<br>
+</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="danielsangeo">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/user_avatar/leakfree.org/danielsangeo/40/4347_2.png" class="avatar"> danielsangeo:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>You are currently on the 1st weapon of the 4 key, the rocket launcher, then you want to get to the crossbow, which is the 3rd weapon on the 3 key. To get to the crossbow, you have to hit 3 three times. With the mousewheel weapon switch, it’s a single mousewheel click in the up direction.</p>
<p>Also, depending on how your keybindings are, it might still take the same amount of time or longer to go from your fingers on WASD to the 5 key twice as it does to do 6-10 mousewheel clicks.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Both good points.</p>
<ol>
<li>
<p>There are more cases overall where keyboard-switching would be faster. The only time it wouldn’t would be in cases <span class="bbcode-i">exactly</span> like the one you describe where you’re switching to one of the weapons at the end of the list just to the left of the one you’re currently in.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Yeah it will vary from person to person – I have long fingers and don’t have any issue until I have to reach over to 6 (which I don’t in this game) – but overall muscle memory works better when it’s not context-dependent, which it is with the mousewheel.</p>
</li>
</ol>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/the-weapon-switching/9928/32">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/the-weapon-switching/9928/32</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 02 Dec 2012 21:54:53 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9928-32</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/the-weapon-switching/9928.rss">The weapon switching</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The weapon switching</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[danielsangeo]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Here’s how it could theoretically be faster:</p>
<p>If you know it takes four mouse-wheel clicks to get from one weapon to the other, you can simply and quickly do the four mouse-wheel clicks.  If you have to get to that same weapon by using one of the number keys along the top of the keyboard, it’s possible that you have to STILL scroll through the multiple weapons assigned to that number.</p>
<p>So, let’s take Half-Life as a for example.</p>
<p>You are currently on the 1st weapon of the 4 key, the rocket launcher, then you want to get to the crossbow, which is the 3rd weapon on the 3 key.  To get to the crossbow, you have to hit 3 three times.  With the mousewheel weapon switch, it’s a single mousewheel click in the up direction.</p>
<p>Also, depending on how your keybindings are, it might still take the same amount of time or longer to go from your fingers on WASD to the 5 key twice as it does to do 6-10 mousewheel clicks.</p>
<p>Just because YOU can’t do it doesn’t mean others cannot.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/the-weapon-switching/9928/31">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/the-weapon-switching/9928/31</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 02 Dec 2012 21:24:33 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9928-31</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/the-weapon-switching/9928.rss">The weapon switching</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The weapon switching</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Zen609]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="bur">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/b/87869e/40.png" class="avatar"> bur:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Zen, I think he was simply requesting a video out of interest, not demanding one as proof.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>No, that’s what he was doing. I really only commented because of the argumentation, not because I have an interest in the issue really. It seems trivial to me. Targ made a new proposition that shifted the discussion. So, the issue is not framed as “Can someone switch weapons with a mousewhee as quickly as the player has switched weapons on the vidl?”, it gets shifted to “One method is faster than another.”</p>
<p>Well, that’s likely true, that the ceiling of one method is greater than another method, the ceiling being the top speed. And that’s not really the original frame here, which was “I don’t believe that Dias can switch weapons that quickly with a mousewheel.”</p>
<p>So, targ makes a shift to a new proposition - that it’s not even theoretically possible to achieve the same speed using any control scheme that requires you to pass more intermediary selections before getting to the desired one -  and then asks dias to post a vid to demonstrate otherwise. That’s argumentum ad ignorantiam. And if dias can’t provide a vid to disprove the statement, then the statement must be true, and therefore, dias can’t switch weapons with a mousewheel as quickly as the player in the vid.</p>
<p>The issue isn’t that, but rather “can a player using a mousewheel switch weapons as quickly as the player in this vid”, not “is one method inherently and potentially faster than another for a discrete player”. Of course one method may be potentially faster than another when all other factors are equal. But targ has made this proposition to support a larger argument that: since one method must be faster than another when all other factors are equal, and, since that method is not the one used by dias, then dias can not switch weapons as fast as the player in this vid.</p>
<p>That’s not a good argument in itself, but then he employs argumentum ad ignorantiam by asking dias to find a vid to demonstrate that his method proposition is false… If he wants to say that a specific method is faster than another, then the burden of proof falls on targ, not dias.</p>
<p>But, again, an establishment that one method is ideally faster than another, is irrelevant to whether or not dias can switch weapons as quickly as the player in the video. At the very most, one could only say that dias could switch weapons faster if he practiced using the method favored by targ, but it doesn’t prove that dias, or anyone else, can not switch weapons as quickly with a mousewheel as in this vid.</p>
<p>It’s just not a good argument.</p>
<p>He should have really just asked dias to give a demonstration, rather than try to make a rhetorical argument, which mucks things up.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="bur">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/b/87869e/40.png" class="avatar"> bur:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>If you’ve memorized how far to scroll, scrolling will be faster. If you’ve memorized how many times to push a button, using the buttons will be faster.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I agree.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/the-weapon-switching/9928/30">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/the-weapon-switching/9928/30</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 02 Dec 2012 21:09:51 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9928-30</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/the-weapon-switching/9928.rss">The weapon switching</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The weapon switching</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[bur]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Zen, I think he was simply requesting a video out of interest, not demanding one as proof.</p>
<p>In any case, I’m pretty sure all of this depends entirely on what you’re used to and what you’ve learned to do best.</p>
<p>In my case, using the number buttons is way faster because it requires only a few keypushes. Scrolling requires scrolling all the way until you reach the desired weapon.</p>
<p>If you’ve memorized how far to scroll, scrolling will be faster. If you’ve memorized how many times to push a button, using the buttons will be faster.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/the-weapon-switching/9928/29">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/the-weapon-switching/9928/29</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 02 Dec 2012 20:07:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9928-29</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/the-weapon-switching/9928.rss">The weapon switching</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The weapon switching</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Dias]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="targ">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/t/c57346/40.png" class="avatar"> targ:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>He sometimes does it so fast that the menu is only visible for a single frame or not at all.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>That’s has to be a video error which makes it appear as if he’s doing it a lot faster than he actually is, because it’s not possible to do it that quickly in-game.</p>
<p>Like I asked before; how do you know the guy in this “random playthrough” uses the keyboard to switch? How do you know he didn’t have a key bound to:</p>
<pre><code class="lang-auto">bind 4 "slot4; slot4; wait; +attack1; wait; -attack1"</code></pre>
<p>to swap to the crossbow or something?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/the-weapon-switching/9928/28">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/the-weapon-switching/9928/28</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 02 Dec 2012 19:36:11 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9928-28</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/the-weapon-switching/9928.rss">The weapon switching</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The weapon switching</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Zen609]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>OK, look, I didn’t intend for my comment to take the thread to a discussion about argumentation or something like this, So, I’m going to make this one last comment in reply to yours, then I ask that you return to the discussion proper, and my apologies to the thread for the brief diversion:</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="targ">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/t/c57346/40.png" class="avatar"> targ:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>The question at the end is separate from the argument I made.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>No, it’s clearly not. You’re making this proposition, and then asking him to post a video to disprove the proposition. The question itself references the proposition: “Can you find a video demonstrating otherwise?”</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="targ">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/t/c57346/40.png" class="avatar"> targ:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>You incorrectly assumed that everything I said was predicated on the lack of a video.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>No, that’s not what I was getting at all. I was looking at the argumentative structure. I’m not arguing with you about the issue itself, nor against the other guy.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="targ">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/t/c57346/40.png" class="avatar"> targ:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Better? :freeman:</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>No, that’s not really better. It’s the same thing except the supporting argument is simply in a new paragraph. When you say, “I submit”, you’re making a proposition “that it’s not even theoretically possible for such a control scheme to achieve the same speed”. That’s fine for you to make a proposition. But now you have to support it, but your supporting argument is “Can you find a video demonstrating otherwise?” He doesn’t have to do that. You made a proposition, now you have to support that. He doesn’t have to prove that your proposition is incorrect, <span class="bbcode-i">you </span> have to prove that it is correct.</p>
<p>You should rather not have made any proposition yourself and simply requested that he prove his claim, rather than make a claim yourself. Now that you’ve made a proposition, <span class="bbcode-i">you</span> have to show some math, or make comparison videos of both methods, etc. He doesn’t have to do anything, because you’ve swooped in and made a proposition. Now it’s your argument to prove, not his to disprove.</p>
<p>But more importantly, your proposition is something else entirely, a different argument. You’re not saying that it’s not possible for someone using a mousewheel to switch weapons as quickly as the player in this vid - it certainly is - you’re saying that one config is mathematically faster than other - but that would only be given that if the two players were of an equal skill level. In other words, it reframes the issue in terms of a comparison between the performance ceilings of each config. But that doesn’t speak to player skill or to dias’ claim, which I do not doubt.</p>
<p>As for the specifics of the argument itself, I don’t want to be involved in the discussion myself. But I’ll tell you this: this is more an issue of skill level. I would also be interested in seeing dias submitting a vid showing his switching. In the way you’ve framed the argument, he doesn’t have to now, but I have no doubt that he can switch weapons at least as fast as in the previously posted vid using the mousewheel.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/the-weapon-switching/9928/27">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/the-weapon-switching/9928/27</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 02 Dec 2012 19:33:45 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9928-27</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/the-weapon-switching/9928.rss">The weapon switching</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The weapon switching</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[targ]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Zen609">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/z/71e660/40.png" class="avatar"> Zen609:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>That’s what you have to do.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Of course. What I was just explaining to you is that I already <span class="bbcode-i">did</span> do that. The question at the end is separate from the argument I made. You incorrectly assumed that everything I said was predicated on the lack of a video. To make my meaning perfectly clear, here is the same thing slightly reworded:</p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>[color=‘red’]Because it requires you to pass more intermediary selections before getting to the desired one, [color=‘red’]I submit that it’s not even theoretically possible [color=‘red’]for such a control scheme to achieve the same speed.</p>
<p>[color=‘red’](new paragraph)<br>
Can you find a video demonstrating otherwise?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Better? :freeman:</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/the-weapon-switching/9928/26">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/the-weapon-switching/9928/26</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 02 Dec 2012 18:24:27 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9928-26</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/the-weapon-switching/9928.rss">The weapon switching</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The weapon switching</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Zen609]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="targ">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/t/c57346/40.png" class="avatar"> targ:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I could have made that point just fine <span class="bbcode-i">without</span> asking for a video.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>That’s what you have to do. If you want to make the proposition, then that’s what you have to do.</p>
<p>Again, I’m not interested in involving myself in the discussion/debate, I’m just pointing out that you can’t prove anything or make a proper argument by making a proposition and then supporting it by shifting the burden of disproof to the other guy. If it’s your proposition, then it’s your burden of proof. That’s all I’m saying - I’m completely uninterested in the issue itself, and I’m only pointing out that you won’t be able to get anywhere with your discussion by utilizing bad argumentation like that.</p>
<p>Good luck.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/the-weapon-switching/9928/25">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/the-weapon-switching/9928/25</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 02 Dec 2012 17:34:32 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9928-25</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/the-weapon-switching/9928.rss">The weapon switching</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The weapon switching</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[targ]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Zen, I think you haven’t looked at the first sentence on its own closely enough and assume that the second sentence is what my belief is based on. My proposition stands alone: I believe it’s theoretically impossible because of simple math - passing <span class="bbcode-i">more</span> selections before reaching the desired one logically takes <span class="bbcode-i">more</span> time. I could have made that point just fine <span class="bbcode-i">without</span> asking for a video.</p>
<p>Asking for a video is still reasonable since I have already provided one of my own as well as presenting my reasoning. Dias has provided neither reasoning nor video evidence. I only have his word to go on so far.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/the-weapon-switching/9928/24">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/the-weapon-switching/9928/24</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 02 Dec 2012 17:12:20 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9928-24</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/the-weapon-switching/9928.rss">The weapon switching</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The weapon switching</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Zen609]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="targ">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/t/c57346/40.png" class="avatar"> targ:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I submit that it’s not even theoretically possible to achieve the same speed using any control scheme that requires you to pass more intermediary selections before getting to the desired one. Can you find a video demonstrating otherwise?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I don’t have a position in this issue/argument, but I’d like to point out just for the sake of reason that this is argumentum ad ignorantiam. You made a proposition and then attempted to support it by demanding proof of the negative… That is counter to reason.</p>
<p>If you want him to prove <span class="bbcode-i">his</span> claims, you can ask for some proof or evidence, but you can’t make a proposition and then attempt to support it with a demand for proof to the contrary.</p>
<p>Your proposition may well be correct, but your argumentation isn’t.</p>
<p>OK - carry on.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/the-weapon-switching/9928/23">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/the-weapon-switching/9928/23</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 02 Dec 2012 16:30:07 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9928-23</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/the-weapon-switching/9928.rss">The weapon switching</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The weapon switching</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[targ]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Dias">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/d/4491bb/40.png" class="avatar"> Dias:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Yes &amp; I can do it while running diagonally in any direction.<br>
Just out of curiosity, how do you know the guy in this “random playthrough” uses the keyboard to switch?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Sorry, but I simply don’t believe you. Did you watch the video? He can switch between any two weapons, no matter how many “clicks” are between them, instantly. He’s not using “fast weapon switch”, so you can tell from the sound effects and the menu itself that he’s using the keyboard and not scrolling. He sometimes does it so fast that the menu is only visible for a single frame or not at all.</p>
<p>I submit that it’s not even theoretically possible to achieve the same speed using any control scheme that requires you to pass more intermediary selections before getting to the desired one. Can you find a video demonstrating otherwise?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/the-weapon-switching/9928/22">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/the-weapon-switching/9928/22</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 02 Dec 2012 14:09:54 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9928-22</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/the-weapon-switching/9928.rss">The weapon switching</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The weapon switching</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[ClockworkBastard]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Dias">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/d/4491bb/40.png" class="avatar"> Dias:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Lots of practice, … the number of clicks away from each weapon…</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Oh my gosh… Once and <span class="bbcode-i">once again</span>.<br>
<span class="bbcode-b">Dias</span>, if you have different list of weapons every 4 minutes as for deathmatch — you <span class="bbcode-b">have to</span> watch a HUD in the corner of a screen not to miss.<br>
Ok with un-real weapon fast_switch it’s maybe a less problem for deathmatch, but when I play singleplayer I try to stay realistic.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/the-weapon-switching/9928/21">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/the-weapon-switching/9928/21</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 02 Dec 2012 10:58:58 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9928-21</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/the-weapon-switching/9928.rss">The weapon switching</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The weapon switching</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Dias]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="BendyBread">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/user_avatar/leakfree.org/bendybread/40/4457_2.png" class="avatar"> BendyBread:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>How do you do it so quickly? In all seriousness.</p>
<p>Personally I don’t know the difference(I played HL once before BM and that’s it), so to me using the numbers is fine, but how do you use the mouse wheel quickly?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Lots of practice, but you really should <span class="bbcode-i">never need</span> to switch that fast. If you know the order of the weapons you can get to each pretty quickly by knowing the number of clicks away from each weapon. If cycling between weapons quickly is really <span class="bbcode-i">that </span>important to you, then I’d suggest turning on ‘fast weapon switch’. It also helps that the guy is playing HL2, which only ever has 2 weapons per category, where as HL1 has up to 4, or OP4 which has 7 different categories. I would not be comfortable stretching my finger out to there, especially while trying to crouch.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/the-weapon-switching/9928/20">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/the-weapon-switching/9928/20</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 02 Dec 2012 06:32:52 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9928-20</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/the-weapon-switching/9928.rss">The weapon switching</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The weapon switching</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[ClockworkBastard]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Oh dudes, if somebody didn’t catch my last message…<br>
<span class="bbcode-b">Black Mesa</span> promised us a multiplayer. Deathmatch with running around and shooting two frags while in mid-air in 180° rotation… And somebody thinks that scrolling a wheel and staring at the corner of the screen selecting - if you catch those python or grenades is is already out</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/the-weapon-switching/9928/19">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/the-weapon-switching/9928/19</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 01 Dec 2012 09:53:23 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9928-19</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/the-weapon-switching/9928.rss">The weapon switching</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The weapon switching</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[BendyBread]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Dias">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/d/4491bb/40.png" class="avatar"> Dias:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Yes &amp; I can do it while running diagonally in any direction.<br>
Just out of curiosity, how do you know the guy in this “random playthrough” uses the keyboard to switch?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>How do you do it so quickly? In all seriousness.</p>
<p>Personally I don’t know the difference(I played HL once before BM and that’s it), so to me using the numbers is fine, but how do you use the mouse wheel quickly?<br>
I always panic, or I derp and end up with the wrong weapon. D;<br>
That, or I need to be standing still because I’m terrible at shooters.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/the-weapon-switching/9928/18">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/the-weapon-switching/9928/18</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 01 Dec 2012 08:03:48 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9928-18</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/the-weapon-switching/9928.rss">The weapon switching</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The weapon switching</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Dias]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="targ">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/t/c57346/40.png" class="avatar"> targ:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>You’re telling me you can mouse-switch between any two weapons as fast as he does?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Yes &amp; I can do it while running diagonally in any direction.<br>
Just out of curiosity, how do you know the guy in this “random playthrough” uses the keyboard to switch?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/the-weapon-switching/9928/17">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/the-weapon-switching/9928/17</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 01 Dec 2012 06:14:42 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9928-17</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/the-weapon-switching/9928.rss">The weapon switching</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The weapon switching</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[ClockworkBastard]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Dias">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/d/4491bb/40.png" class="avatar"> Dias:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I like to switch weapons while I <span class="bbcode-i">move</span>. Not exactly easy with number keys, is it?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I never had problems with reaching 1-5 buttons (yep, the ones above [w] key)<br>
Seriously, if someone didn’t get my previous post — Black Mesa promised the multiplayer.<br>
<a href="https://wiki.blackmesasource.com/Deathmatch" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Deathmatch</a>. You spawn, grab any weapons you stumble on the way dodging rockets, jump of another and while in air — frag one with shotgun and another one with python far away… You seriously consider mouse whilling and watching the left corner of the screen would be okay?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/the-weapon-switching/9928/16">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/the-weapon-switching/9928/16</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2012 19:07:13 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9928-16</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/the-weapon-switching/9928.rss">The weapon switching</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The weapon switching</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[targ]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Dias">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/d/4491bb/40.png" class="avatar"> Dias:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I like to switch weapons while I <span class="bbcode-i">move</span>. Not exactly easy with number keys, is it?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>It’s really not a problem. Muscle memory takes over once you know where everything is. And don’t forget about Q.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Dias">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/d/4491bb/40.png" class="avatar"> Dias:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Once you learn the order all the weapons are in, you can switch between any 2 weapons with the wheel in the same time it takes to press 5 once.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>What? :brow: Do you have 5 thumbs on your left hand? Here’s a random playthrough I found by a competent keyboard-switcher:<br>
<a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=rpg2oJWfsLQ" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=rpg2oJWfsLQ</a><br>
You’re telling me you can mouse-switch between any two weapons as fast as he does?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/the-weapon-switching/9928/15">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/the-weapon-switching/9928/15</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2012 13:09:23 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9928-15</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/the-weapon-switching/9928.rss">The weapon switching</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
