<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Laptop Power Supply Broken</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/laptop-power-supply-broken/13175</link>
    <description>So I lost my laptop charger and found it a week later. I left it in a classroom I think still plugged in, but when I found it it was unplugged. When I found it, I plugged it into an outlet and the green LED on the brick didn&#39;t turn on. I plugged it into my laptop and neither the laptop&#39;s nor the brick&#39;s LED turned on. I tested a bunch of different outlets with and without the laptop or the laptop&#39;s battery. I replaced the cable between the outlet and the brick. After testing, i&#39;ve discovered that I can get the brick&#39;s LED to come on by plugging the cable between the brick and outlet into the outlet first and into the brick second. But the second I plug the charger into the laptop the brick&#39;s LED goes out and I have to start the process over.

Not getting much off google right now, does anyone have an idea that doesn&#39;t involve buying a new charger? Could not using the charger for a week explain these symptoms? Hopefully in a repairable way?

EDIT: Can&#39;t get the brick&#39;s LED on under any conditions now.
EDIT2: LED came back on using earlier process, seems like there&#39;s a cooldown time or something from when I plug it into the laptop and it breaks to when it will work again.
EDIT3: pretty sure the laptop&#39;s charger port or mobo is shorting the power supply. Turns out the outlet plugging trick was a coincidence, plugging in normally turns on the brick&#39;s LED too.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2014 02:29:11 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Help and Support</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/laptop-power-supply-broken/13175.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Laptop Power Supply Broken</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[sersoft]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I got 3 free laptops like this already, one was a thinkpad t60 one was a dell d620 and the last one was a toshiba p100</p>
<p>what I did is open the laptop and replace both the plug in the laptop and the plug on the end of the charger with one from a PSP slim 2000 series, they have pretty durable plugs compared to most laptops.</p>
<p>if you’re going to attempt this you will need a voltmeter, soldering gun and lots of hot glue.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/laptop-power-supply-broken/13175/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/laptop-power-supply-broken/13175/5</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2014 02:29:11 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13175-5</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/laptop-power-supply-broken/13175.rss">Laptop Power Supply Broken</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Laptop Power Supply Broken</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[garrthbarrttinn]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="0_22one">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 0_22one:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Unless you want to send it off to get repaired, I think you’ll just need to buy a new charger. I’ve had this happen, and I inevitably needed to replace mine.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>The laptop’s charger port has failed on my 3 times previously, so I suspect it’s failed on me again and is short circuiting and triggering a failsafe in the PSU. I’ll probably send it in, I’ll see if I can get a different charger to test it with first.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/laptop-power-supply-broken/13175/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/laptop-power-supply-broken/13175/4</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2014 23:39:09 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13175-4</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/laptop-power-supply-broken/13175.rss">Laptop Power Supply Broken</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Laptop Power Supply Broken</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[GilCMassey]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Unless you want to send it off to get repaired, I think you’ll just need to buy a new charger. I’ve had this happen, and I inevitably needed to replace mine.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/laptop-power-supply-broken/13175/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/laptop-power-supply-broken/13175/3</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2014 22:37:08 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13175-3</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/laptop-power-supply-broken/13175.rss">Laptop Power Supply Broken</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Laptop Power Supply Broken</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Pyroclase]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>It doesn’t sound like it’s your problem, but I have gone through an insane number of laptop charging cords. Have you tried it with a different charger from somewhere?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/laptop-power-supply-broken/13175/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/laptop-power-supply-broken/13175/2</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2014 21:45:21 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13175-2</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/laptop-power-supply-broken/13175.rss">Laptop Power Supply Broken</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Laptop Power Supply Broken</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[garrthbarrttinn]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>So I lost my laptop charger and found it a week later. I left it in a classroom I think still plugged in, but when I found it it was unplugged. When I found it, I plugged it into an outlet and the green LED on the brick didn’t turn on. I plugged it into my laptop and neither the laptop’s nor the brick’s LED turned on. I tested a bunch of different outlets with and without the laptop or the laptop’s battery. I replaced the cable between the outlet and the brick. After testing, i’ve discovered that I can get the brick’s LED to come on by plugging the cable between the brick and outlet into the outlet first and into the brick second. But the second I plug the charger into the laptop the brick’s LED goes out and I have to start the process over.</p>
<p>Not getting much off google right now, does anyone have an idea that doesn’t involve buying a new charger? Could not using the charger for a week explain these symptoms? Hopefully in a repairable way?</p>
<p>EDIT: Can’t get the brick’s LED on under any conditions now.<br>
EDIT2: LED came back on using earlier process, seems like there’s a cooldown time or something from when I plug it into the laptop and it breaks to when it will work again.<br>
EDIT3: pretty sure the laptop’s charger port or mobo is shorting the power supply. Turns out the outlet plugging trick was a coincidence, plugging in normally turns on the brick’s LED too.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/laptop-power-supply-broken/13175/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/laptop-power-supply-broken/13175/1</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2014 19:00:09 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13175-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/laptop-power-supply-broken/13175.rss">Laptop Power Supply Broken</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
