<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>[SOLVED] &quot;CUtlRBTree Overflow&quot; engine error on startup</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/solved-cutlrbtree-overflow-engine-error-on-startup/15203</link>
    <description>Starting today, every time I try to launch Black Mesa the program crashes and shows the following dialogue box:

[img]https://i.imgur.com/sP5mXxJ.png[/img]

The game displays the Crowbar Collective splash screen for a brief moment (shorter than usual) and then crashes.
I&#39;ve tried to look for a solution but couldn&#39;t find anything. I&#39;ve tried verifying my installation, reinstalling the game and deleting the one custom map I had. I am not subscribed to any workshop items.
The game has been working perfectly fine for me since the day I bought it (23rd of June), minus a few random crashes here and there that aren&#39;t really noteworthy, but today it suddenly doesn&#39;t work anymore.
The only thing that&#39;s different now from when Black Mesa did work properly was that I installed Arma III, though I don&#39;t understand how this could cause Black Mesa to stop functioning.
I have tried uninstalling Arma III but Black Mesa still keeps crashing. I have also tried to launch Arma III and close it again. This also had no effect.
Every other Source game I&#39;ve tried worked perfectly fine. The ones I&#39;ve tried were Half-Life 2, Team Fortress 2, Counter-Strike: Global Offensive and Portal 2.
Others online claim that this may be caused by a lack of available memory. Using memory monitoring in task manager I was able to confirm that this is not the case.
I also doubt it could be caused by a memory leak, as to my knowledge no update was pushed on the 29th of June that could have caused a memory leak.
I have not opted into any beta branch and have not modified the game in any way except for adding a custom multiplayer map.
This problem also persists when launching a dedicated server.

I have provided a crash dump and my system specifications below.

[url=&#39;https://drive.google.com/file/d/0ByL_cAxkkfkxRHg5N2RaMF9aTlk/view?usp=sharing&#39;]Crash dump[/url]

[spoiler=Specs]
GPU: GTX 1060 6Gb
CPU: Intel Core i5 7500
RAM: 16Gb DDR4 @ 2400mhz
OS: Windows 10 Pro
1920x1080 @ 60hz
1Tb HDD (on which Black Mesa in installed)
120Gb SSD (on which Steam is installed)

As I stated before, Black Mesa used to run just fine so I doubt there&#39;s a problem with my setup.
[/spoiler]



**[b]*EDIT***[/b]
I uninstalled the Black Mesa again, this time manually deleting the files that were still left after uninstalling. After installing the game again everything seems to be working fine.
I still find it strange why it started making a fuss right after I played Arma III though.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2017 15:53:46 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>In-game Issues</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/solved-cutlrbtree-overflow-engine-error-on-startup/15203.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>[SOLVED] &quot;CUtlRBTree Overflow&quot; engine error on startup</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[0x13F]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Starting today, every time I try to launch Black Mesa the program crashes and shows the following dialogue box:</p>
<p><img src="https://i.imgur.com/sP5mXxJ.png" alt="" width="159" height="141"></p>
<p>The game displays the Crowbar Collective splash screen for a brief moment (shorter than usual) and then crashes.<br>
I’ve tried to look for a solution but couldn’t find anything. I’ve tried verifying my installation, reinstalling the game and deleting the one custom map I had. I am not subscribed to any workshop items.<br>
The game has been working perfectly fine for me since the day I bought it (23rd of June), minus a few random crashes here and there that aren’t really noteworthy, but today it suddenly doesn’t work anymore.<br>
The only thing that’s different now from when Black Mesa did work properly was that I installed Arma III, though I don’t understand how this could cause Black Mesa to stop functioning.<br>
I have tried uninstalling Arma III but Black Mesa still keeps crashing. I have also tried to launch Arma III and close it again. This also had no effect.<br>
Every other Source game I’ve tried worked perfectly fine. The ones I’ve tried were Half-Life 2, Team Fortress 2, Counter-Strike: Global Offensive and Portal 2.<br>
Others online claim that this may be caused by a lack of available memory. Using memory monitoring in task manager I was able to confirm that this is not the case.<br>
I also doubt it could be caused by a memory leak, as to my knowledge no update was pushed on the 29th of June that could have caused a memory leak.<br>
I have not opted into any beta branch and have not modified the game in any way except for adding a custom multiplayer map.<br>
This problem also persists when launching a dedicated server.</p>
<p>I have provided a crash dump and my system specifications below.</p>
<p><a href="https://drive.google.com/file/d/0ByL_cAxkkfkxRHg5N2RaMF9aTlk/view?usp=sharing" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Crash dump</a></p>
<div class="spoiler">
<p>GPU: GTX 1060 6Gb<br>
CPU: Intel Core i5 7500<br>
RAM: 16Gb DDR4 @ 2400mhz<br>
OS: Windows 10 Pro<br>
1920x1080 @ 60hz<br>
1Tb HDD (on which Black Mesa in installed)<br>
120Gb SSD (on which Steam is installed)</p>
<p>As I stated before, Black Mesa used to run just fine so I doubt there’s a problem with my setup.</p>
</div>
<p><strong>[b]<em>EDIT</em></strong>[/b]<br>
I uninstalled the Black Mesa again, this time manually deleting the files that were still left after uninstalling. After installing the game again everything seems to be working fine.<br>
I still find it strange why it started making a fuss right after I played Arma III though.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/solved-cutlrbtree-overflow-engine-error-on-startup/15203/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/solved-cutlrbtree-overflow-engine-error-on-startup/15203/1</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2017 15:53:46 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-15203-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/solved-cutlrbtree-overflow-engine-error-on-startup/15203.rss">[SOLVED] &quot;CUtlRBTree Overflow&quot; engine error on startup</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
