<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Network Printing between Windows and OSX?</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/network-printing-between-windows-and-osx/2645</link>
    <description>Probably a long shot asking this here, since most of you have no experience with OS X, but you never know!


We have 2 computers over here, one uses Windows Vista, the other is an iMac with OS X Snow Leopard. They&#39;re both connected to a hub, said hub is connected to the modem. The Windows machine has 2 printers connected to it, an HP DeskJet and an Epson Stylus.

Now, I would like to access one of those 2 printers from within OS X, so I can actually print without moving files between both computers through an USB stick or whatever. I&#39;ve put both printers in Windows Vista on &quot;Shared&quot;, but I can&#39;t seem to find them anywhere in OS X. So I guess I&#39;m doing something massively wrong.


Below is a chart of how this &quot;network&quot; looks like.

[img]https://img34.imageshack.us/img34/7954/networkprint.jpg[/img]


So, is it possible like this to get access to the printers on the Vista machine from within OS X? If so, how do I properly set it up?


PS: obviously, this entire thing has never been setup as a proper network. Though, sometimes I can see the Windows machine pop up in my OS X &quot;Shared&quot; list, but that&#39;s quite rare, so I guess the &quot;network&quot; kinda works.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 11 Feb 2011 18:21:55 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Help and Support</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/network-printing-between-windows-and-osx/2645.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Network Printing between Windows and OSX?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Mister_Brick]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Get a switch instead of a hub.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/network-printing-between-windows-and-osx/2645/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/network-printing-between-windows-and-osx/2645/3</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 Feb 2011 18:21:55 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2645-3</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/network-printing-between-windows-and-osx/2645.rss">Network Printing between Windows and OSX?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Network Printing between Windows and OSX?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[sersoft]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Apple says you need to purchase another mac and share the printer via bonjour, but I’m gonna go on a limb here and try to convince you to install Windows on the imac instead.</p>
<p>I can understand why you of all people would get a non-handheld Apple device, but asking for us to help with your iMac, especially something network related, that I cannot fathom.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/network-printing-between-windows-and-osx/2645/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/network-printing-between-windows-and-osx/2645/2</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 Feb 2011 17:58:50 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2645-2</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/network-printing-between-windows-and-osx/2645.rss">Network Printing between Windows and OSX?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Network Printing between Windows and OSX?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Bolteh]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Probably a long shot asking this here, since most of you have no experience with OS X, but you never know!</p>
<p>We have 2 computers over here, one uses Windows Vista, the other is an iMac with OS X Snow Leopard. They’re both connected to a hub, said hub is connected to the modem. The Windows machine has 2 printers connected to it, an HP DeskJet and an Epson Stylus.</p>
<p>Now, I would like to access one of those 2 printers from within OS X, so I can actually print without moving files between both computers through an USB stick or whatever. I’ve put both printers in Windows Vista on “Shared”, but I can’t seem to find them anywhere in OS X. So I guess I’m doing something massively wrong.</p>
<p>Below is a chart of how this “network” looks like.</p>
<p><span alt="" class="broken-image" title="This image is broken"><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-unlink svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#unlink"></use></svg></span></p>
<p>So, is it possible like this to get access to the printers on the Vista machine from within OS X? If so, how do I properly set it up?</p>
<p>PS: obviously, this entire thing has never been setup as a proper network. Though, sometimes I can see the Windows machine pop up in my OS X “Shared” list, but that’s quite rare, so I guess the “network” kinda works.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/network-printing-between-windows-and-osx/2645/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/network-printing-between-windows-and-osx/2645/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 16 Jan 2010 13:52:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2645-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/network-printing-between-windows-and-osx/2645.rss">Network Printing between Windows and OSX?</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
