<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Minor Bugs</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/minor-bugs/14096</link>
    <description>[b][u]Bug 1[/u][/b]: The command console is flooded with the phrase &quot;Cannot update control point 1 for effect &#39;flashlight_firstperson&#39;.&quot;

Typing the following into the console removes the flooding. ([url=&#39;https://forums.blackmesasource.com/index.php/Thread/27919-Cannot-update-control-point-1-for-effect-flashlight-firstperson-Console-Flood/?postID=607154#post607154&#39;]Thanks to UnintelGen[/url])

Alternatively, adding [url=https://localhost/mybb/attachment.php?aid=2934]StopConsoleFlood.zip[/url]this .cfg file[/attach] to the SteamApps\Common\Black Mesa\bms\cfg folder, and then typing &quot;exec StopConsoleFlood.cfg&quot; into the &quot;autoexec.cfg&quot; file and saving it will also remove the flooding.

[b][u]Bug 2[/u][/b]: In the &quot;Black Mesa&quot; menu, I&#39;ve checked &quot;always run&quot;, but I still go at normal speeds and have to hold shift to sprint. Also, it seems that the Houndeye tinnitus isn&#39;t on either, despite being checked.

[b][u]Bug 3 (maybe)[/u][/b]: It seems I can pick up dead headcrabs and human body parts? I&#39;m not sure if that&#39;s a bug or not (as it hasn&#39;t been in any other HL games), but it should be kept!
Edit: Ok, it seems I can only pick up SOME dead headcrabs. All of these headcrabs I&#39;ve (so far) encountered were not just dead props, they were headcrabs that I&#39;ve killed myself. Yet some ARE able to be picked up, and some aren&#39;t.

[b][u](Very Very Very Minor) Bug 4[/u][/b]: When hitting this (unbreakable) vent in this spot, there is no noise, and the crowbar moves slower, as if hitting air. Obviously this isn&#39;t important at all, as the vent is unopenable, and doesn&#39;t break/hinder gameplay, but I thought I may as well mention it.
[img]https://forums.blackmesasource.com/index.php/Attachment/3870/?thumbnail=1[/img] [img]https://forums.blackmesasource.com/index.php/Attachment/3871/?thumbnail=1[/img]

[b][u]Bug 5[/u][/b][u]:[/u] I had a security guard and scientist (female if it matters) following me, and when I killed the security guard, the scientist praised me, (saying things such as &quot;Good show!&quot;, or &quot;Good show, Freeman, good show!&quot;). I tested this a few times and the results were the same.
The opposite worked normally. Shooting the scientist caused the security guard to turn hostile.

[b][u](Typo) Bug 6[/u][/b]: Not sure if this is a typo or not. It may be signin, sign in, sign-in, or signing:
[img]https://forums.blackmesasource.com/index.php/Attachment/3873/?thumbnail=1[/img]

[b][u]Bug 7[/u][/b]: Just a physics bug. After breaking the crate that&#39;s blocking the generator from working, an oil can (a prop found when opening some crates) started flying around the room. [url=&#39;https://imgur.com/a/UKbkq&#39;]Click here for pictures and my position/map details.[/url]

[u][b]Bug 8[/b] [b](Maybe)[/b][/u]: The rails in &quot;On a Rail&quot; aren&#39;t electrocuting me as they did in the original. Without the electrified rails, there isn&#39;t much point in using the cart, is there?

[b][u]Bug 9[/u][/b]: This marine wouldn&#39;t notice me until I got quite close to him.

[img]https://forums.blackmesasource.com/index.php/Attachment/3892/?thumbnail=1[/img] [img]https://forums.blackmesasource.com/index.php/Attachment/3893/?thumbnail=1[/img]

[b]Bug 10[/b]: This crate in &quot;Residue Processing&quot; seems to be set to NoCollide. Gordon can walk through it and weapons act if if they&#39;re hitting air. I can&#39;t seem to upload the pictures and map/position here, but [url=&#39;https://imgur.com/a/aZwc8&#39;]here they are on imgur[/url].
[b]EDIT: This also happens with the rest of the wooden props in the water, but they can be picked up.[/b]

[b]Bug 11[/b]: When choosing points for the missiles to hit on the military screen, sometimes the red dot sticks to the top left of the screen, but it also switches (back and forth) to where you actually plant it. It only seems to be a visual effect, as the missile goes where you aim.

[b]Bug 12[/b]: Dr Steinman (is that a Bioshock reference?) is referred to as a &quot;she&quot; just before the end of the Lambda Core, but when you meet the scientist, he&#39;s actually male.

[b]Bug 13[/b]: [url=&#39;https://imgur.com/a/esFeq&#39;]These ties are ridiculous. On a few scientists, their ties rapidly go from left to right (and they repeat that forever).[/url]</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 19 May 2015 22:39:51 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>In-game Issues</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/minor-bugs/14096.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Minor Bugs</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[SpyroCoolLP]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><span class="bbcode-b"><span class="bbcode-u">Bug 1</span></span>: The command console is flooded with the phrase “Cannot update control point 1 for effect ‘flashlight_firstperson’.”</p>
<p>Typing the following into the console removes the flooding. (<a href="https://forums.blackmesasource.com/index.php/Thread/27919-Cannot-update-control-point-1-for-effect-flashlight-firstperson-Console-Flood/?postID=607154#post607154" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Thanks to UnintelGen</a>)</p>
<p>Alternatively, adding <a href="https://localhost/mybb/attachment.php?aid=2934" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">StopConsoleFlood.zip</a>this .cfg file[/attach] to the SteamApps\Common\Black Mesa\bms\cfg folder, and then typing “exec StopConsoleFlood.cfg” into the “autoexec.cfg” file and saving it will also remove the flooding.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b"><span class="bbcode-u">Bug 2</span></span>: In the “Black Mesa” menu, I’ve checked “always run”, but I still go at normal speeds and have to hold shift to sprint. Also, it seems that the Houndeye tinnitus isn’t on either, despite being checked.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b"><span class="bbcode-u">Bug 3 (maybe)</span></span>: It seems I can pick up dead headcrabs and human body parts? I’m not sure if that’s a bug or not (as it hasn’t been in any other HL games), but it should be kept!<br>
Edit: Ok, it seems I can only pick up SOME dead headcrabs. All of these headcrabs I’ve (so far) encountered were not just dead props, they were headcrabs that I’ve killed myself. Yet some ARE able to be picked up, and some aren’t.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b"><span class="bbcode-u">(Very Very Very Minor) Bug 4</span></span>: When hitting this (unbreakable) vent in this spot, there is no noise, and the crowbar moves slower, as if hitting air. Obviously this isn’t important at all, as the vent is unopenable, and doesn’t break/hinder gameplay, but I thought I may as well mention it.<br>
<img src="https://forums.blackmesasource.com/index.php/Attachment/3870/?thumbnail=1" alt="" width="" height=""> <img src="https://forums.blackmesasource.com/index.php/Attachment/3871/?thumbnail=1" alt="" width="" height=""></p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b"><span class="bbcode-u">Bug 5</span></span><span class="bbcode-u">:</span> I had a security guard and scientist (female if it matters) following me, and when I killed the security guard, the scientist praised me, (saying things such as “Good show!”, or “Good show, Freeman, good show!”). I tested this a few times and the results were the same.<br>
The opposite worked normally. Shooting the scientist caused the security guard to turn hostile.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b"><a>u</a> Bug 6[/u]</span>: Not sure if this is a typo or not. It may be signin, sign in, sign-in, or signing:<br>
<img src="https://forums.blackmesasource.com/index.php/Attachment/3873/?thumbnail=1" alt="" width="" height=""></p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b"><span class="bbcode-u">Bug 7</span></span>: Just a physics bug. After breaking the crate that’s blocking the generator from working, an oil can (a prop found when opening some crates) started flying around the room. <a href="https://imgur.com/a/UKbkq" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Click here for pictures and my position/map details.</a></p>
<p><span class="bbcode-u"><span class="bbcode-b">Bug 8</span> <a>b</a>[/b]</span>: The rails in “On a Rail” aren’t electrocuting me as they did in the original. Without the electrified rails, there isn’t much point in using the cart, is there?</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b"><span class="bbcode-u">Bug 9</span></span>: This marine wouldn’t notice me until I got quite close to him.</p>
<p><img src="https://forums.blackmesasource.com/index.php/Attachment/3892/?thumbnail=1" alt="" width="" height=""> <img src="https://forums.blackmesasource.com/index.php/Attachment/3893/?thumbnail=1" alt="" width="" height=""></p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Bug 10</span>: This crate in “Residue Processing” seems to be set to NoCollide. Gordon can walk through it and weapons act if if they’re hitting air. I can’t seem to upload the pictures and map/position here, but <a href="https://imgur.com/a/aZwc8" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">here they are on imgur</a>.<br>
<span class="bbcode-b">EDIT: This also happens with the rest of the wooden props in the water, but they can be picked up.</span></p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Bug 11</span>: When choosing points for the missiles to hit on the military screen, sometimes the red dot sticks to the top left of the screen, but it also switches (back and forth) to where you actually plant it. It only seems to be a visual effect, as the missile goes where you aim.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Bug 12</span>: Dr Steinman (is that a Bioshock reference?) is referred to as a “she” just before the end of the Lambda Core, but when you meet the scientist, he’s actually male.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Bug 13</span>: <a href="https://imgur.com/a/esFeq" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">These ties are ridiculous. On a few scientists, their ties rapidly go from left to right (and they repeat that forever).</a></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/minor-bugs/14096/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/minor-bugs/14096/1</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 19 May 2015 22:39:51 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14096-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/minor-bugs/14096.rss">Minor Bugs</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
