<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Saved games WON&#39;T LOAD</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/saved-games-wont-load/10177</link>
    <description>So I&#39;ve been playing for a couple hours, saving along the way.. some auto-saves here and there, some ESC Save Game saves too.. I finally died and my screen went black for about 10 seconds so I began to think k maybe it&#39;s still just loading.. but then I hit ESC and it took me back to the main menu and when I went to try and load my game, it would just pop me right back into the main menu straight away as though nothing had happened. 

This is happening now to all my saves that I played with today. Help please? :/ Kinda annoyed I lost all that progress..


EDIT: I THINK I know the problem lol.. I had about 5mb of space left on my drive I think that was the problem  :slight_smile:</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 16 Sep 2012 07:37:28 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>In-game Issues (Mod)</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/saved-games-wont-load/10177.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Saved games WON&#39;T LOAD</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Biz]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>So I’ve been playing for a couple hours, saving along the way… some auto-saves here and there, some ESC Save Game saves too… I finally died and my screen went black for about 10 seconds so I began to think k maybe it’s still just loading… but then I hit ESC and it took me back to the main menu and when I went to try and load my game, it would just pop me right back into the main menu straight away as though nothing had happened.</p>
<p>This is happening now to all my saves that I played with today. Help please? <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/confused.png?v=9" title=":confused:" class="emoji" alt=":confused:"> Kinda annoyed I lost all that progress…</p>
<p>EDIT: I THINK I know the problem lol… I had about 5mb of space left on my drive I think that was the problem  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=9" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/saved-games-wont-load/10177/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/saved-games-wont-load/10177/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 16 Sep 2012 07:37:28 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-10177-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/saved-games-wont-load/10177.rss">Saved games WON&#39;T LOAD</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
