<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>FAQ - General Forum Etiquett - PLEASE READ</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/faq-general-forum-etiquett-please-read/69</link>
    <description>[b][COLOR=&#39;DarkOrange&#39;]THE FORUM NEWBIE SURVIVAL GUIDE![/SIZE][/b]
[align=left][b]NOTE: These are not official rules, but abiding by them just may prevent you from being flamed to a crisp by community members.
[/SIZE][/b][/align]
[COLOR=&#39;DarkOrange&#39;][b]*Rule 1:[/b][/SIZE]
[b]CORRECT LANGUAGE MECHANICS, GRAMMAR, AND SPELLING are all appreciated. [/b]
Things to watch for:
* Run on Sentences (Periods, commas, semi-colons, and colons were invented for a reason)
* Using single letters to replace complete words (u=you and the like)
* Removal of vowels (pls instead of please)
* They&#39;re, their, there mix-ups (make sure you have the right one)
* Extra apostrophes (It&#39;s=It is, Its=Possession)

Remember, this isn&#39;t a chatroom, this is a forum. You have, quite literally, all the time in the world to write your post. Make your English teacher proud!

[b][COLOR=&#39;DarkOrange&#39;]* Rule 2:[/SIZE][/b]
[b]MAKE SURE YOUR POST HAS SOME SENSE TO IT![/b]

If I had a pound of gold for every time I&#39;ve had to wade through a post that seems like they put a bunch of ideas into a shotgun, pulled the trigger, then picked up the random pieces of ideas then posted that, I&#39;d make Bill Gates look poor.

Remember: A good idea not written well, looks like a bad idea.

[COLOR=&#39;DarkOrange&#39;][b]* Rule 3:[/SIZE][/b]
[b]KEEP RELEVANT DISCUSSION TO THE RELEVANT FORUM![/b]

Want to:
* Comment on the news? ==&gt; [url=&#39;https://www.blackmesasource.com/forums/forumdisplay.php?f=2&#39;][COLOR=&#39;DarkOrange&#39;][b]NEWS[/b][/url]
* Discuss the modification? ==&gt; [url=&#39;https://www.blackmesasource.com/forums/forumdisplay.php?f=3&#39;][COLOR=&#39;DarkOrange&#39;][b]THE CAFETERIA[/b][/url]
* Share an idea? ==&gt; [url=&#39;https://www.blackmesasource.com/forums/forumdisplay.php?f=4&#39;][COLOR=&#39;DarkOrange&#39;][b]SUGGESTION BOX[/b][/url]
* Help the Developers along with the rest of the community? ==&gt; [url=&#39;https://www.blackmesasource.com/forums/forumdisplay.php?f=5&#39;][COLOR=&#39;DarkOrange&#39;][b]COMMUNITY PROJECTS[/b][/url]
* Give Site feedback? ==&gt; [url=&#39;https://www.blackmesasource.com/forums/forumdisplay.php?f=6&#39;][COLOR=&#39;DarkOrange&#39;][b]WEBSITE SUPPORT[/b][/url]
* Talk about anything? ==&gt; [url=&#39;https://www.blackmesasource.com/forums/forumdisplay.php?f=8&#39;][COLOR=&#39;DarkOrange&#39;][b]OFF TOPIC[/b][/url]
* Talk about technology and gaming? ==&gt; [b][url=&#39;https://www.blackmesasource.com/forums/forumdisplay.php?f=9&#39;][COLOR=&#39;DarkOrange&#39;]TECHNOLOGY AND GAMING[/b][/url]
* Ask for help? ==&gt; [url=&#39;https://www.blackmesasource.com/forums/forumdisplay.php?f=10&#39;][b][COLOR=&#39;DarkOrange&#39;]HELP AND SUPPORT[/url][/b]
* Talk about half-life saga? ==&gt; [url=&#39;https://www.blackmesasource.com/forums/forumdisplay.php?f=19&#39;][b][COLOR=&#39;DarkOrange&#39;]HALF-LIFE SERIES[/b][/url]
* Show your artwork ==&gt; [url=&#39;https://www.blackmesasource.com/forums/forumdisplay.php?f=11&#39;][b][COLOR=&#39;DarkOrange&#39;]SHOW OFF[/b][/url]

There are enough different sub-forums for everyone, make sure your post is in the right place!

[b][COLOR=&#39;DarkOrange&#39;]* Rule 4:[/SIZE][/b]
[b]TREAT OTHERS THE WAY YOU WOULD LIKE TO BE TREATED![/b]

There is little to be gained by simply calling somebody a moron. Remember, if it is an idea for the mod, give constructive criticism and your view on the idea, and if it is something in the off-topic section, remember that everybody has different morals, religions, philosophies on life, and the list goes on.

Just remember that the more respect you give out, odds are the more respect will be given to you in return.
[b][COLOR=&#39;DarkOrange&#39;]
* Rule 5:[/SIZE][/b]
[b]DON&#39;T CLAIM THE MORAL OR INTELLECTUAL HIGH GROUND ANYWHERE!
[/b]

Attempting to claim the moral or intellectual high ground only serves to derail threads and turn them into flamming matches. As long as you only criticize or defend suggested ideas and nothing more, this can be avoided.

[b][COLOR=&#39;DarkOrange&#39;]* Rule 6:[/SIZE][/b]

Always read PMs, especially from Moderators/Admins/Devs (Or we will pwn you ), [b][COLOR=&#39;DarkOrange&#39;]PM&#39;s ARE A SERVICE AND A PRIVILEGE. DO NOT ABUSE![/b]

Private Messages are very helpful in defusing potential situations, and can benefit in creating closer ties between members. They are also helpful in establishing direct links (without the need for publicity) between the Moderators/Administrators/Developers if disciplinary action or threat of said action is to be taken against a particular forum member. However, it is also a privilege. This, therefore, does not give any member (administrative or basic) to flame/bully/spam in any other members&#39; PM Inbox.

[b][COLOR=&#39;DarkOrange&#39;]* Rule 7:[/SIZE][/b]
[b]BEFORE POSTING AN IDEA, ASK YOURSELF THESE THREE QUESTIONS:[/b]

* 1) Will it help make the game better? And enough to justify the work involved?
* 2) Will it change or alter game play in a good way, a bad way, or not at all?
* 3) Will it contradict a &quot;rule&quot; of the HL universe or a major story element, will it add to and flesh out the story within the rules of the HL universe, or will it not change the story at all.

A &quot;no&quot; answer to question 1 automatically rejects the idea. A &quot;bad way&quot; answer to question 2 gets it rejected. A &quot;not at all&quot; answer to question 2 puts the idea in doubt. And obviously a &quot;contradicts major story element&quot; answer to question 3 nukes the idea as well.

Question #3 is to be handled carefully. A &quot;major story element&quot; is any story element that was in any of the other HL games, suggested by a Valve dev interview, or anticipated to happen in future Valve games.

[b][COLOR=&#39;DarkOrange&#39;]* Rule 8:[/SIZE][/b]
[b]READ POSTS PROPERLY BEFORE YOU REPLY![/b]

You may misinterpret something on initial reading. Nine times out of ten this is minor. However you could make a major mistake by taking something the wrong way, when really what is meant is drastically or entirely different. This rule is connected to Rules 1 and 2, as without using the English Language correctly and without having a post which is easy to understand, misinterpretations are only too easy to make.

[b][COLOR=&#39;DarkOrange&#39;]* Rule 9:[/SIZE][/b]
[b]MAKE SURE YOUR TOPIC HAS A DESCRIPTIVE TITLE![/b]

When we go into a topic entitled, &quot;Hi everyone!&quot; We expect a greeting. When we go into a topic named, &quot;On headcrabs, and their primary attack,&quot; we expect something about when headcrabs attack. Don&#39;t name a topic &quot;Whazzupppp!!!!11!oneone!&quot;, then put forth an elaborate suggestion about a topic already discussed to death and expect to walk away lacking scorch marks.

[b][COLOR=&#39;DarkOrange&#39;]* Rule 10:[/SIZE][/b]
[b]UNDERSTAND THAT ASPECTS OF THE MOD MAY BE CHANGED REGARDLESS OF WHAT THE DEVELOPERS HAVE SAID![/b]

This rule comes straight from most developers. There is a reason why we don&#39;t get definite answers to many if not all of our questions about what will be in the mod. Everything within the mod is subject to change until it is released, and then even after that things might be changed via patches! Remember this next time you are about to demand a positive yes or no answer from a developer on a subject.

[b][COLOR=&#39;DarkOrange&#39;]* Rule 11:[/SIZE][/b]
[b]ODDS ARE IF YOU&#39;RE SAYING THINGS LIKE: &quot;PLEASE DON&#39;T FLAME ME,&quot; AND &quot;THIS MAY ALREADY HAVE BEEN DISCUSSED,&quot; YOU SHOULD NOT HIT THE POST BUTTON![/b]

If you&#39;re in question of whether or not you&#39;ll be flamed for posting something, odds are you&#39;re better off not posting said article. Remember, if you must say &quot;this may already have been discussed&quot;, do a search first. The answers are very likely within the threads that pop up.

[b][COLOR=&#39;DarkOrange&#39;]* Rule 12:[/SIZE][/b]
[b]PLEASE USE THE &quot;GOT A QUESTION?&quot; THREAD FOR MINOR QUESTIONS[/b]

[b][COLOR=&#39;DarkOrange&#39;]* Rule 13:[/SIZE][/b]
[b][COLOR=&#39;DarkOrange&#39;]DO NOT TALK ABOUT THE LEAK (NEVER EVER EVER)[/b]

[b][COLOR=&#39;DarkOrange&#39;]* Rule 14:[/SIZE][/b]
[b]For more general information about the actual mod work, please see the [i]WIKI[/i] FAQ&#39;s for details[/b]
[url=&#39;https://wiki.blackmesasource.com/index.php/General_FAQ&#39;]General FAQ[/url] || [url=&#39;https://wiki.blackmesasource.com/index.php/Single-player_FAQ&#39;]Single-Player FAQ[/url] || [url=&#39;https://wiki.blackmesasource.com/index.php/Deathmatch_FAQ&#39;]Deathmatch FAQ[/url]

[b][COLOR=&#39;DarkOrange&#39;]APPLYING TO BLACK MESA[/SIZE][/b]
Rules of conduct:

If you are considering applying to Black Mesa, then please take a moment to read this thread. First, and foremost, applications WILL NOT be considered without sample work or a portfolio for us to review. This means if you submit an application saying &quot;i want to make maps&quot; but do not attach screenshots, example work or a link to your portfolio, then your application will be discarded. The same goes for applicants in other areas as well. Also, please note that we recieve a high volume of applications every day, and as such, are busy processing and reviewing each one. We reply to applications when we need further clarification on some aspect of your application, when it has been reviewed and a decision has been reached, or when there is an exceptional delay in the processing of applications (over a week). If your application is not replied to instantly, do not send a bunch of additional copies to the jobs address; it just floods our inboxes and makes you look unprofessional. If there is an extreme delay or you have any questions, then contact a moderator through the forums and the status of your application will be looked into.

DO NOT post application threads on the forum. Please send all applications to jobs at blackmesasource dot com for them to be reviewed in a timely manner. Sending applications to individual developers or other mailboxes increases the chances of your application being deleted or delayed. (I shouldn&#39;t have even had to say that here, because its printed on the jobs page which you should be reading before applying.

Due to a problem in Comcast&#39;s method of spam blocking, your email may be blocked when forwarding to one recipient of the jobs at blackmesasource dot com email. Please note that unless the automailer reports problems with YOU personally sending the email, we have recieved it. There is no need to send multiple copies.

Due to the high volume of applications we recieve, it is difficult to remember everyone&#39;s name and email address. If you have additional work to append to your application, you would do well to reply to your original email which makes it easier for us to append to your application document and easier to keep track of. It also helps us to remember who&#39;s original application is being modified. However, it&#39;s much easier if you select your work and submit your application in one go and do not append it further - This makes it a difficult and time-consuming process for us.

If you have any further questions, or ever have questions about the status of your application, please contact a developer through these forums.

Thank you to Mad Scientist and Ares for your founding of this announcement in thread form.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 20 May 2009 16:40:28 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>The Cafeteria</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/faq-general-forum-etiquett-please-read/69.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>FAQ - General Forum Etiquett - PLEASE READ</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[raw_bean]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I’d prefer it if you just report posts rather than mini-mod Spidey, but I can’t disagree with you there.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/faq-general-forum-etiquett-please-read/69/36">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/faq-general-forum-etiquett-please-read/69/36</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 20 May 2009 16:40:28 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-69-36</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/faq-general-forum-etiquett-please-read/69.rss">FAQ - General Forum Etiquett - PLEASE READ</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>FAQ - General Forum Etiquett - PLEASE READ</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Spidey300]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <ol>
<li>
<p>Please don’t revive a thread which is just meant for info without contributing anything to the Thread Topic.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Use the “Edit” to edit your previous post and not double post.</p>
</li>
</ol>
<p>I think this thread would be better off locked, and only opened when Keresh, devs or someone else have something to add to the FAQ.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/faq-general-forum-etiquett-please-read/69/35">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/faq-general-forum-etiquett-please-read/69/35</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 20 May 2009 16:10:06 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-69-35</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/faq-general-forum-etiquett-please-read/69.rss">FAQ - General Forum Etiquett - PLEASE READ</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>FAQ - General Forum Etiquett - PLEASE READ</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[chipstix4]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Nice job Karesh although some idiots will completely ignore this warning and go ahead posting about “Adrian shepherd should be in it durrgghh i touch myself”</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Patonki">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/p/e79b87/40.png" class="avatar"> Patonki:</div>
<blockquote>
<p><a href="https://img24.imageshack.us/img24/8044/iamdissapoint2.jpg" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://img24.imageshack.us/img24/8044/iamdissapoint2.jpg</a></p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>keresh is a boomer??? D <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/smiley.png?v=9" title=":smiley:" class="emoji" alt=":smiley:"> :</p>
<p>[COLOR=‘Red’]raw_bean: Use the edit button to add to your previous post in future, rather than double posting.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/faq-general-forum-etiquett-please-read/69/34">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/faq-general-forum-etiquett-please-read/69/34</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 20 May 2009 13:18:38 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-69-34</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/faq-general-forum-etiquett-please-read/69.rss">FAQ - General Forum Etiquett - PLEASE READ</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>FAQ - General Forum Etiquett - PLEASE READ</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Siggs]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Hahahaha, that rocks Patonki  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=9" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"><br>
.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/faq-general-forum-etiquett-please-read/69/33">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/faq-general-forum-etiquett-please-read/69/33</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 11 May 2009 23:05:59 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-69-33</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/faq-general-forum-etiquett-please-read/69.rss">FAQ - General Forum Etiquett - PLEASE READ</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>FAQ - General Forum Etiquett - PLEASE READ</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Ramirezoid]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Do you actually look like mid-90’s Hulk or is that just speculation?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/faq-general-forum-etiquett-please-read/69/32">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/faq-general-forum-etiquett-please-read/69/32</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 11 May 2009 23:02:06 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-69-32</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/faq-general-forum-etiquett-please-read/69.rss">FAQ - General Forum Etiquett - PLEASE READ</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>FAQ - General Forum Etiquett - PLEASE READ</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Keresh]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Raminator">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/r/6bbea6/40.png" class="avatar"> Raminator:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>keresh i am disappoint</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>:fffuuu:</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Patonki">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/p/e79b87/40.png" class="avatar"> Patonki:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I AM A FAG</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Well duh  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=9" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/faq-general-forum-etiquett-please-read/69/31">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/faq-general-forum-etiquett-please-read/69/31</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 07 May 2009 17:32:02 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-69-31</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/faq-general-forum-etiquett-please-read/69.rss">FAQ - General Forum Etiquett - PLEASE READ</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>FAQ - General Forum Etiquett - PLEASE READ</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Patonki]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>~5 minutes.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/faq-general-forum-etiquett-please-read/69/30">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/faq-general-forum-etiquett-please-read/69/30</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 07 May 2009 14:05:33 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-69-30</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/faq-general-forum-etiquett-please-read/69.rss">FAQ - General Forum Etiquett - PLEASE READ</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>FAQ - General Forum Etiquett - PLEASE READ</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[WonManArmy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>hahaha how long did it take you to make that ?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/faq-general-forum-etiquett-please-read/69/29">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/faq-general-forum-etiquett-please-read/69/29</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 07 May 2009 12:45:25 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-69-29</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/faq-general-forum-etiquett-please-read/69.rss">FAQ - General Forum Etiquett - PLEASE READ</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>FAQ - General Forum Etiquett - PLEASE READ</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Patonki]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><span alt="" class="broken-image" title="This image is broken"><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-unlink svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#unlink"></use></svg></span></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/faq-general-forum-etiquett-please-read/69/28">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/faq-general-forum-etiquett-please-read/69/28</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 07 May 2009 12:02:58 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-69-28</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/faq-general-forum-etiquett-please-read/69.rss">FAQ - General Forum Etiquett - PLEASE READ</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>FAQ - General Forum Etiquett - PLEASE READ</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Lamsey]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Ram’s a pretty cool guy, eh am dissapoint and doesn’t afraid of anything</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/faq-general-forum-etiquett-please-read/69/27">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/faq-general-forum-etiquett-please-read/69/27</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 07 May 2009 11:31:15 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-69-27</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/faq-general-forum-etiquett-please-read/69.rss">FAQ - General Forum Etiquett - PLEASE READ</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>FAQ - General Forum Etiquett - PLEASE READ</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Grey_Acumen]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I AM<br>
ERROR.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/faq-general-forum-etiquett-please-read/69/26">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/faq-general-forum-etiquett-please-read/69/26</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 07 May 2009 11:19:18 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-69-26</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/faq-general-forum-etiquett-please-read/69.rss">FAQ - General Forum Etiquett - PLEASE READ</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>FAQ - General Forum Etiquett - PLEASE READ</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Deimos]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Raminator">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/r/6bbea6/40.png" class="avatar"> Raminator:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>keresh i am disappoint</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>hi disappoint.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/faq-general-forum-etiquett-please-read/69/25">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/faq-general-forum-etiquett-please-read/69/25</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 07 May 2009 08:48:11 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-69-25</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/faq-general-forum-etiquett-please-read/69.rss">FAQ - General Forum Etiquett - PLEASE READ</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>FAQ - General Forum Etiquett - PLEASE READ</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Keresh]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>You know, Alcator, that post was originally made by Klaymore, so I wasn’t able to fix ANYTHING till I’ve reposted it after the crash. Be patient.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/faq-general-forum-etiquett-please-read/69/24">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/faq-general-forum-etiquett-please-read/69/24</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 06 May 2009 16:30:12 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-69-24</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/faq-general-forum-etiquett-please-read/69.rss">FAQ - General Forum Etiquett - PLEASE READ</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>FAQ - General Forum Etiquett - PLEASE READ</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Alcator]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>you know, Keresh, I would think that after 5 months, you would already be able to fix the Release date paragraph to mention “The MOD is promised to be released in the year 2009, which means the latest possible date is 31st December 2009.”</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/faq-general-forum-etiquett-please-read/69/23">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/faq-general-forum-etiquett-please-read/69/23</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 06 May 2009 16:25:54 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-69-23</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/faq-general-forum-etiquett-please-read/69.rss">FAQ - General Forum Etiquett - PLEASE READ</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>FAQ - General Forum Etiquett - PLEASE READ</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[St4va]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I never got the point of the helmet… what is that that you want from it ?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/faq-general-forum-etiquett-please-read/69/22">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/faq-general-forum-etiquett-please-read/69/22</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 06 May 2009 07:46:19 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-69-22</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/faq-general-forum-etiquett-please-read/69.rss">FAQ - General Forum Etiquett - PLEASE READ</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>FAQ - General Forum Etiquett - PLEASE READ</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Grey_Acumen]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I was planning to do it even before the forum crashed, but there were so many threads to read through before. I figured with the new forums, things could just be added as it went. I’m willing to offer my help too, and already sent RB a message about it.</p>
<p>Personally, I’d like to see some sorting by category to help people find what they’re looking for, like:</p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>Engine Issues: Will dx 7, 8, 9 work? will that purple checkerboard pattern pop up at those lower dx levels like what happens in synergy? is autosaving enabled by default? will chapter selecting be available from the start/at all? will developer commentary be added? achievements? Mirrors? Autoaim on/off variable separate from difficulty?</p>
<p>Maps: Will XYZ be included? Training Room?</p>
<p>Gordon:<br>
Subcategory Weapons - see <a href="https://forums.blackmesasource.com/showthread.php?t=78" data-bbcode="true" rel="noopener nofollow ugc">this thread</a> Can we use Portalgun/Gravitygun/M4Skin/OP4 weapons?<br>
Subcategory HEV suit: Helmet? Movement? Sprint? Zoom? Flashlight duration? HEV speech?</p>
<p>NPCs:<br>
Subcategory Scientists - Female, asian, how do they act, etc?<br>
Subcategory Guards - ditto.</p>
<p>Enemies:<br>
subcategory etc etc etc</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I’d also like to see a similar thread in the Suggestions section called “constantly rejected suggestions” which would obviously have some subjects that overlap with the FAQ, but would be oriented on suggestions that have already been made and confirmed to never come to fruition.</p>
<p>It would also be nice to have each of the categories as their own post in their respective threads so that anyone could easily grab a link from a specific point in the FAQ or CRS for newbie users who hadn’t even bothered reading it.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/faq-general-forum-etiquett-please-read/69/21">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/faq-general-forum-etiquett-please-read/69/21</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 05 May 2009 00:23:19 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-69-21</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/faq-general-forum-etiquett-please-read/69.rss">FAQ - General Forum Etiquett - PLEASE READ</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>FAQ - General Forum Etiquett - PLEASE READ</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Keresh]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Hmmm. Thanks Lamsey, I’ll fix that right away.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/faq-general-forum-etiquett-please-read/69/20">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/faq-general-forum-etiquett-please-read/69/20</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 04 May 2009 22:17:20 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-69-20</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/faq-general-forum-etiquett-please-read/69.rss">FAQ - General Forum Etiquett - PLEASE READ</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>FAQ - General Forum Etiquett - PLEASE READ</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Lamsey]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Suggestion:</p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>ADDITIONAL APPEARANCES OF ELI : Eli will be the scientist who sends you up to get help shortly after the resonance cascade.</p>
<p>APPEARANCES OF CHARACTERS WHO ARE ONLY MADE KNOWN TO THE PLAYER IN HL2 AND THE EPISODES: Dr Breen, Alyx, Dog, and other characters who made no appearance in HL1 will not appear in BM. Subtle references may be made but that is irrelevant at this point and will probably not be focused on until you play the actual game and find them yourself!</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Should become</p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>ADDITIONAL APPEARANCES OF ELI<span class="bbcode-b"> AND KLEINER</span>: Eli will be the scientist who sends you up to get help shortly after the resonance cascade.<span class="bbcode-b"> Kleiner will be the injured scientist who Eli is “afraid to move”.</span></p>
<p>APPEARANCES OF CHARACTERS WHO ARE ONLY MADE KNOWN TO THE PLAYER IN HL2 AND THE EPISODES: Dr Breen, Alyx, Dog, <span class="bbcode-b">Magnusson</span> and other characters who made no appearance in HL1 will not appear in BM. Subtle references may be made but that is irrelevant at this point and will probably not be focused on until you play the actual game and find them yourself!</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/faq-general-forum-etiquett-please-read/69/19">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/faq-general-forum-etiquett-please-read/69/19</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 04 May 2009 21:52:56 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-69-19</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/faq-general-forum-etiquett-please-read/69.rss">FAQ - General Forum Etiquett - PLEASE READ</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>FAQ - General Forum Etiquett - PLEASE READ</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[St4va]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Wtf Spam ?</p>
<p>Thanks for the info anyway =]</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/faq-general-forum-etiquett-please-read/69/18">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/faq-general-forum-etiquett-please-read/69/18</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 04 May 2009 11:30:37 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-69-18</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/faq-general-forum-etiquett-please-read/69.rss">FAQ - General Forum Etiquett - PLEASE READ</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>FAQ - General Forum Etiquett - PLEASE READ</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Keresh]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="raw_bean">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/r/439d5e/40.png" class="avatar"> raw_bean:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Good one Keresh, I’m intending to do some editing and updating on this, but it’s good to have the old post there to work from.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Actually I’m intending to do some editing myself but I’m glad that someone will help me  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=9" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/faq-general-forum-etiquett-please-read/69/17">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/faq-general-forum-etiquett-please-read/69/17</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 03 May 2009 19:31:07 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-69-17</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/faq-general-forum-etiquett-please-read/69.rss">FAQ - General Forum Etiquett - PLEASE READ</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>FAQ - General Forum Etiquett - PLEASE READ</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[_amp_955_dam]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Why don’t you include the download locations to the teaser and main trailer?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/faq-general-forum-etiquett-please-read/69/16">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/faq-general-forum-etiquett-please-read/69/16</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 03 May 2009 17:19:11 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-69-16</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/faq-general-forum-etiquett-please-read/69.rss">FAQ - General Forum Etiquett - PLEASE READ</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>FAQ - General Forum Etiquett - PLEASE READ</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[raw_bean]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Good one Keresh, I’m intending to do some editing and updating on this, but it’s good to have the old post there to work from.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/faq-general-forum-etiquett-please-read/69/15">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/faq-general-forum-etiquett-please-read/69/15</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 03 May 2009 17:16:35 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-69-15</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/faq-general-forum-etiquett-please-read/69.rss">FAQ - General Forum Etiquett - PLEASE READ</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>FAQ - General Forum Etiquett - PLEASE READ</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Spidey300]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>You mean you lol’d “again”, right, right, right!</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/faq-general-forum-etiquett-please-read/69/14">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/faq-general-forum-etiquett-please-read/69/14</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 03 May 2009 17:07:37 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-69-14</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/faq-general-forum-etiquett-please-read/69.rss">FAQ - General Forum Etiquett - PLEASE READ</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>FAQ - General Forum Etiquett - PLEASE READ</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[_amp_955_dam]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Thanks for posting this all up again Keresh.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Keresh">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/k/85f322/40.png" class="avatar"> Keresh:</div>
<blockquote>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">[COLOR=‘Red’]Barney the dinosaur will also not appear</span>.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I lol’d  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/smiley.png?v=9" title=":smiley:" class="emoji" alt=":smiley:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/faq-general-forum-etiquett-please-read/69/13">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/faq-general-forum-etiquett-please-read/69/13</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 03 May 2009 16:28:18 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-69-13</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/faq-general-forum-etiquett-please-read/69.rss">FAQ - General Forum Etiquett - PLEASE READ</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>FAQ - General Forum Etiquett - PLEASE READ</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Lamsey]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>&lt;_&lt;</p>
<blockquote>
<p>_&gt;</p>
</blockquote>
<p><span alt="" class="broken-image" title="This image is broken"><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-unlink svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#unlink"></use></svg></span></p>
<p><img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=9" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji only-emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/faq-general-forum-etiquett-please-read/69/12">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/faq-general-forum-etiquett-please-read/69/12</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 03 May 2009 11:37:51 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-69-12</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/faq-general-forum-etiquett-please-read/69.rss">FAQ - General Forum Etiquett - PLEASE READ</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
