<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Peak Oil?</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/peak-oil/4229</link>
    <description>[url=&#39;https://a.blip.tv/scripts/flash/showplayer.swf?file=http%3A%2F%2Fblip.tv%2Frss%2Fflash%2F3668712%3Freferrer%3Dhttp%25253A%25252F%25252Fblog.joerogan.net%25252F%26source%3D3&amp;showplayerpath=http%3A%2F%2Fblip.tv%2Fscripts%2Fflash%2Fshowplayer.swf&amp;feedurl=http%3A%2F%2Fcairns.blip.tv%2Frss%2Fflash&amp;brandname=blip.tv&amp;brandlink=http%3A%2F%2Fblip.tv%2F%3Futm_source%3Dbrandlink&amp;enablejs=true&#39;]watch this[/url]

tl;dr: human population increased drastically when we started burning fossil fuel, therefore the current population is unsustainable without the current level of oil supply. We&#39;ve reached the point where no new oil supplies are being found, therefore we are now at the point where the population level will &quot;correct&quot; itself.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 30 May 2010 18:36:25 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Off Topic</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/peak-oil/4229.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Peak Oil?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[mattemuse]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I guess we just fundamentally disagree about the influence (or lack thereof) that public opinion has on US foreign policy. You certainly won’t get any argument from me when you say that foreign policy is a strong driver of public opinion (“once the US was engaged in war,  people threw their support behind Bush”), but there’s an abundance of evidence which implies the inverse is not the case.</p>
<p>Revisiting my point about Iraq withdrawal:</p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>American commanders, worried about increased violence in the wake of Iraq’s inconclusive elections, are now reconsidering the pace of a major troop pullout this summer</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p><a href="https://news.yahoo.com/s/ap/20100511/ap_on_re_mi_ea/ml_iraq_troop_withdrawal" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">AP</a></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/peak-oil/4229/63">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/peak-oil/4229/63</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 30 May 2010 18:36:25 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-4229-63</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/peak-oil/4229.rss">Peak Oil?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Peak Oil?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[loony636]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="mattemuse">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/m/dc4da7/40.png" class="avatar"> mattemuse:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I may not have your fancy college education</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Yeah, sorry about that. I didn’t mean to come across as bigoted, I just misinterpreted your post as somewhat more ad hominem that what it actually was. My bad.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="mattemuse">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/m/dc4da7/40.png" class="avatar"> mattemuse:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>but the public’s total non-reaction to Obama … planning to “leave” Iraq with only 50,000 combat troops and 70,000 Blackwater mercs staying behind, implies the US populace hasn’t learned the lesson you seem to think they have learned.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I would say that with Iraq there are a number of issues needed for dissection. Firstly the problems with analysing motivations before the war; I agree that the issue was far less pre-determined than the decision to go to war in Afghanistan, but there was plainly a majority of support for the war. The means by which that war should be fought was, to me, a different question; there was overwhelming support for a war in Iraq, just a differing of opinion on <span class="bbcode-i">which war</span> should ultimately be fought.</p>
<p>I just found <a href="https://www.pollingreport.com/iraq.htm" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">this</a> too. Some of the statistics are very telling. There’s pages and pages of raw data on the war in Iraq. Here, I think, is the most telling poll:</p>
<p><span alt="" class="broken-image" title="This image is broken"><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-unlink svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#unlink"></use></svg></span></p>
<p>Once the US was engaged in the war, people threw their support behind Bush. There’s a lot of different and conflicting polling data, but the fact that they re-elected him a year later (and yes, that’s putting aside the incompetency of his opposition) shows that they at least didn’t entirely hate him and/or disapprove of what he had done.</p>
<p>However, as the war dragged on and people realised the monumental mistake that the invasion was, people started to move away from supporting bush. There are a lot of polls in the aforementioned article that state that a majority (somewhere in the order of &gt;60%) believe that going into Iraq <span class="bbcode-i">was</span> a mistake. And that’s not even taking into account the percentage that believe that it could’ve been done better.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="mattemuse">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/m/dc4da7/40.png" class="avatar"> mattemuse:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Also note the non-reaction to Obama walking back his deadline for the Iraq deadline, most people don’t even know he did it.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>I don’t understand. Obama didn’t go back on anything; the US is still on course for the withdrawal plan, and General Ray Odierno said that the US forces would be completely withdrawn by the end of 2011. Furthermore, its not that strange for the US troops to remain behind; its much better that they stay and ensure a stable government which can properly enforce law and order than having another post-Cold War Afghanistan on their hands. Plus, its not really related to the issue at hand; most, if not all, people want a withdrawal from Iraq, especially given that the US has actually achieved all of its aims there, no matter how you try to interpret their original reasons for going in there (i.e. stable, US-friendly government installed with no more WMDs).</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="mattemuse">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/m/dc4da7/40.png" class="avatar"> mattemuse:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>escalating the Afghanistan war with 50,000 more combat troops and expanded military operations Pakistan, and</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
</blockquote>
</aside>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Well, you see, Afghanistan is <span class="bbcode-i">very</span> different. Focus on that war petered off with the troop surge in Iraq, and its only very recently that the US forces in Afghanistan have actually been moving towards a sustainable long-term solution for the country. Reconstructing a country that hasn’t had a stable government in 30 years is no mean feat, and the fact that they didn’t pay much attention to proper strategies (other than the destruction of AQ) until late in the Bush presidency and now in the Obama presidency proper means that a longer commitment is necessary there for the US to actually do what they originally wanted to achieve; stop the breeding ground of Islamic extremism.</p>
<p>Afghanistan is also fundamentally different because the war was fought on self-defence grounds. I don’t think there’s any contention that people wouldn’t support a war that was fought in self-defence, but there’s no way that that’s applicable to the current case. Saying that people will support a war to acquire oil deposits in the Middle East is fundamentally different to saying that people will support a war to destroy people who threaten their existence. I think they’ll be more apprehensive about engaging in wars where the threat <span class="bbcode-i">isn’t</span> clear (i.e. Iraq), but I doubt they’ll be more cautious about engaging in wars that threaten the country; that goes to the root of one’s sense of community, and nothing is going to change that. But if the Government tries to sell a war on the basis of oil, I seriously doubt that, given the above discussion, the people will support it. And that means no war.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/peak-oil/4229/62">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/peak-oil/4229/62</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 30 May 2010 16:47:27 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-4229-62</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/peak-oil/4229.rss">Peak Oil?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Peak Oil?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[bur]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>The Vietnam war is also a good indication of how easy it is to forget the past.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/peak-oil/4229/61">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/peak-oil/4229/61</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 30 May 2010 16:33:20 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-4229-61</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/peak-oil/4229.rss">Peak Oil?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Peak Oil?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[mattemuse]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Ok, looking at wikipedia, it’s obvious you’re cherry-picking the highest poll number to support your argument. You’re citing numbers from May and February, <span class="bbcode-b">but none from March, the actual date we invaded</span>:</p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>Days before the March 20 invasion, a USA TODAY/CNN/Gallup Poll found support for the war was related to UN approval. Nearly six in 10 said they were ready for such an invasion “in the next week or two.” But that support dropped off if the U.N. backing was not first obtained. If the U.N. Security Council were to reject a resolution paving the way for military action, 54% of Americans favored a U.S. invasion. And if the Bush administration didn’t not seek a final Security Council vote, support for a war dropped to 47%.[8]</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="loony636">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/l/6bbea6/40.png" class="avatar"> loony636:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Obama announced that he’s leaving. Why? Because popular support has disappeared […] the US populace has already seen how destructive one military campaign in the Middle East has been.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I may not have your fancy college education, but the public’s total non-reaction to Obama escalating the Afghanistan war with 50,000 more combat troops and expanded military operations Pakistan, and planning to “leave” Iraq with <span class="bbcode-b">only</span> 50,000 combat troops and 70,000 Blackwater mercs staying behind, implies the US populace hasn’t learned the lesson you seem to think they have learned. Also note the non-reaction to Obama walking back his deadline for the Iraq deadline, most people don’t even know he did it.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/peak-oil/4229/60">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/peak-oil/4229/60</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 30 May 2010 15:54:44 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-4229-60</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/peak-oil/4229.rss">Peak Oil?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Peak Oil?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[loony636]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="mattemuse">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/m/dc4da7/40.png" class="avatar"> mattemuse:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>It’s just crazy reading this stuff, do people really think like that? The US populace was aggresively propagandized before the Iraq war, and it still barely had 50% support. Now it’s more like 30% and it’s still going on with no signs of stopping!</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I believe you’re confusing Bush’s election with popular support for the Iraq war. If you look at <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Popular_opinion_in_the_US_on_the_invasion_of_Iraq" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">this</a> Wikipedia page, you can see this:</p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>Only 27% opposed military action, the smallest percentage since the polls began in April 2002. The percentage of Americans supporting an invasion without UN support jumped eight points to 37%.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>And this:</p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>A Gallup poll made on behalf of CNN and the newspaper USA Today concluded that 79% of Americans thought the Iraq War was justified, with or without conclusive evidence of illegal weapons. 19% thought weapons were needed to justify the war.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>That may have changed quickly, but at the time Bush went to war he did so <span class="bbcode-i">with</span> popular support.</p>
<p>Moreover: <a href="https://www.washingtonpost.com/wp-dyn/content/article/2009/02/27/AR2009022700566.html" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Obama announced that he’s leaving</a>. Why? Because popular support has disappeared. That and because he’s nice.</p>
<p>Yeah. Just crazy. I’m doing a Politics major at University, with one unit on the Middle East, so I’m <span class="bbcode-i">fairly</span> confident that what I’m spouting isn’t completely ludicrous.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="mattemuse">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/m/dc4da7/40.png" class="avatar"> mattemuse:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Imagine how easy it would be to convince the US populace to fight a war for possession of the substance that our entire way of life (economic, consumer society, military) is totally dependent on! In fact I’m surprised it hasn’t started already (hm).</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Two reasons: Firstly, the US populace has already seen how destructive one military campaign in the Middle East has been. They’ve seen the images of TV, they’ve seen the destruction it has wreaked on their economy, and they have seen the death tolls that have resulted. They will not be eager to fight another.</p>
<p>Secondly, the public trend has been <span class="bbcode-i">away</span> from oil dependency, especially since the whole global warming revelation (and the spill in the Gulf of Mexico didn’t help), and I can’t see them fighting a war to preserve the diminishing supplies of a resource that, by the time this becomes an issue, we will, most likely, no longer require.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/peak-oil/4229/59">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/peak-oil/4229/59</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 30 May 2010 13:53:49 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-4229-59</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/peak-oil/4229.rss">Peak Oil?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Peak Oil?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[DansonDelta40]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I can imagine the propaganda ad already:</p>
<p>“Our American Way of Life. Isn’t it grand? Shopping in the Mall, HDTV, Playstation 4, Hummer Truck in the 'yard… seems perfect. But - what if it’s not? Friends, your future could be in serious danger, because all of these things you have and can do are dependent on the burning of fossil fuels. Our national ressources are already running out. What will you do when your Mall is no longer supplied, when no new computers, video games and TVs can be produced, when your car won’t drive anymore?<br>
Thankfully, though, there is a solution. American Intelligence has discovered a large oil supply readily available for exploitation. The only thing standing in our way to continue our great American Way of life as it used to be, is a couple of ragheads guarding it because of some religious mambo-jambo. We’d just have to bomb the shit out of them and our future would be secured. What do you say?”</p>
<p>American Public: “DO EEET FAGGOT!”</p>
<p>I’d bet on it.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/peak-oil/4229/58">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/peak-oil/4229/58</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 30 May 2010 09:49:51 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-4229-58</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/peak-oil/4229.rss">Peak Oil?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Peak Oil?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[mattemuse]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>It’s just crazy reading this stuff, do people really think like that? The US populace was aggresively propagandized before the Iraq war, and it still barely had 50% support. Now it’s more like 30% and it’s still going on with no signs of stopping! How does this example support your point about popular support? And furthermore, when a propaganda campaign can create 50% support for a pointless and counterproductive war, imagine how easy it would be to convince the US populace to fight a war for possession of the substance that our entire way of life (economic, consumer society, military) is totally dependent on! In fact I’m surprised it hasn’t started already (hm).</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/peak-oil/4229/57">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/peak-oil/4229/57</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 29 May 2010 19:17:14 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-4229-57</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/peak-oil/4229.rss">Peak Oil?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Peak Oil?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[loony636]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>The only reason he was able to justify the invasion was because the US populace wanted him to. That was the issue Clinton ran into in Somalia; when nobody at home wants you to invade, they wont stand by while US troops die, which is why he was ultimately forced to pull out.</p>
<p>The reason why it’ll be different is, perhaps, twofold (and that’s assuming you get another Bush). Firstly, the people in the US have already been shown the massive toll of trying to sustain a war in a Middle Eastern country. Furthermore, the issue wont be able to be disguised as ‘national security’ any more. Secondly, and perhaps most notably, given the current shift away from using oil, when the time comes when oil is ‘running out’ (thanks for the clarification above), people wont be as doggedly supporting of a military invasion aimed at securing the last remnants of an outdated energy source. Ergo, no popular support and, therefore, no war.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/peak-oil/4229/56">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/peak-oil/4229/56</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 29 May 2010 12:17:11 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-4229-56</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/peak-oil/4229.rss">Peak Oil?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Peak Oil?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[DansonDelta40]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>Will Washington really dive that blindly into a massive military incursion just so one industry in America can screw it up for everyone else? I think not.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p><span alt="" class="broken-image" title="This image is broken"><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-unlink svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#unlink"></use></svg></span></p>
<p>Yeah, that would be really dumb. Good thing nobody would ever make such a stupid decision. Oh wait…</p>
<p><span alt="" class="broken-image" title="This image is broken"><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-unlink svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#unlink"></use></svg></span></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/peak-oil/4229/55">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/peak-oil/4229/55</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 29 May 2010 10:00:31 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-4229-55</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/peak-oil/4229.rss">Peak Oil?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Peak Oil?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[baconeggs]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>He’s saying that “running out” means “it won’t be cost effective to get any remaining oil”. So it’ll run out in the sense that it will stop being extracted.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/peak-oil/4229/54">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/peak-oil/4229/54</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 29 May 2010 08:26:30 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-4229-54</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/peak-oil/4229.rss">Peak Oil?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Peak Oil?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Mr.Shadow]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="loony636">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/l/6bbea6/40.png" class="avatar"> loony636:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Oil can never actually ‘run out’ …oil will still run out.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Does not compute.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/peak-oil/4229/53">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/peak-oil/4229/53</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 May 2010 16:06:33 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-4229-53</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/peak-oil/4229.rss">Peak Oil?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Peak Oil?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[loony636]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Burbinator">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Burbinator:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Notice how he said “I say <span class="bbcode-b">could</span>,” taking care to put ‘could’ in bold?</p>
<p>also what mattemuse said</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Well Palin <span class="bbcode-i">could</span> have become President, so…</p>
<p>Oh wait, that could’ve actually happened. And its not funny. My bad.</p>
<p>My point is that its not likely. At all.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="mattemuse">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/m/dc4da7/40.png" class="avatar"> mattemuse:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>national defense is 100% reliant on oil (the US military is the worlds largest consumer of oil)<br>
the US economy is 100% reliant on oil<br>
food production is 100% reliant on oil<br>
and last but not least the oil industry has a massive influence over the US government</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Firstly, a general point about Oil. Oil will never actually ‘run out’. The issue is that it will become far too expensive to extract, which will make it supremely unprofitable as supply proves totally incapable of matching up with demand. As it runs out and becomes more expensive, every industry that can will shift away from it in an effort to reduce costs. This will mean that the only industries still using the fuel will be those that can’t readily switch (e.g. planes and, probably, the military).</p>
<p>What’s required for them is longer term change. They can’t just whack a hydrogen engine in the front of their vehicles and go; they need more innovation. If this innovation isn’t present by the time oil starts to dwindle to drastically low levels (which, frankly, wont be soon), then the army can keep consuming oil until it develops the technology to completely convert.</p>
<p>If the Government wants to monopolise on the oil currently coming into America, it can <span class="bbcode-i">very</span> easily do so. How? It raises the tax on oil to over 9000% (or some similarly large number). This means nobody will buy it. That means that it can use it all for its own purposes, while it commits to long-term change in operating procedures to bring costs down.</p>
<p>As for the rest of your examples, I don’t see how the US Economy and food production is 100% reliant on oil, nor do I see why they would want to still be that reliant on oil when the price skyrockets. They will much prefer technological development over another costly armed invasion of another, most likely Arab, country to requisition oil supplies.</p>
<p>Lastly, to Big Oil. Its true that they have a massive stake in Washington. Three issues. Firstly, Obama just told them to get stuffed over the incident in the Gulf of Mexico and I’d look for big reforms both there and in relation to the relationship between Washington and the other Big industries. Secondly, they wont have that same kind of power when the loss of oil takes the wind out of their sales and they have no money. Thirdly, <span class="bbcode-i">they</span> will be as interested in developing and moving away from unrenewable sources of energy as anyone else, since the cost of not doing so would be huge. Even if America goes to war and physically takes over every single oil field, oil will still run out. Big Oil realises this and will, either by its own volition or that of its shareholders and consumers, be forced to develop.</p>
<p>On that point of invasion; who says invasion is the best way to acquire resource security anyway? What are you going to do, waltz into these countries and hold the workers at gunpoint? Occupy the countries and bring in your own workers? How on <span class="bbcode-i">earth</span> is that the economic decision to make? Not to mention the fact that its just a stop-gap solution that will effectively destroy every other aspect of America’s international relations? Will Washington really dive that blindly into a massive military incursion just so one industry in America can screw it up for everyone else? I think not.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/peak-oil/4229/52">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/peak-oil/4229/52</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 May 2010 15:39:18 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-4229-52</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/peak-oil/4229.rss">Peak Oil?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Peak Oil?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[bur]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>The factories that produce weapons use fossil fuels, so yes. I also imagine many plastics being used in most of the things soldiers use, so more fossil fuel usage there.</p>
<p>Of course, the stuff that’s already been produced isn’t going anywhere.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/peak-oil/4229/51">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/peak-oil/4229/51</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 May 2010 11:45:08 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-4229-51</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/peak-oil/4229.rss">Peak Oil?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Peak Oil?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[DansonDelta40]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I am pretty sure (or at least can imagine) that the burning of fossil fuels is somehow connected even with the manufacturing of small military grade firearms and ammunition, so even foot soldiers are reliant on it in a way. Unless you only equip them with knifes - oh wait, you gotta burn coal to forge a knife. Damn…</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/peak-oil/4229/50">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/peak-oil/4229/50</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 May 2010 10:46:43 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-4229-50</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/peak-oil/4229.rss">Peak Oil?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Peak Oil?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[baconeggs]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I’m pointing out your flaw in saying that it’s ONE HUNDRED percent dependant upon oil. I’m not saying a large contingent of the military needs it.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/peak-oil/4229/49">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/peak-oil/4229/49</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 May 2010 07:50:49 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-4229-49</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/peak-oil/4229.rss">Peak Oil?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Peak Oil?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[mattemuse]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="baconeggs">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/b/43a26b/40.png" class="avatar"> baconeggs:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Using the logic of mattemuse the US military, economy and food industry is entirely comprised of a black liquid. I’m pretty sure the army could revert back to militia if it had to.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>that’s pretty retarded. militias typically keep up to date with the latest ICBMs and stealth bombers*, do they?</p>
<p>*not powered by fossil fuel, of course</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/peak-oil/4229/48">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/peak-oil/4229/48</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 May 2010 05:57:43 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-4229-48</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/peak-oil/4229.rss">Peak Oil?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Peak Oil?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[baconeggs]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Using the logic of mattemuse the US military, economy and food industry is entirely comprised of a black liquid. I’m pretty sure the army could revert back to militia if it had to.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/peak-oil/4229/47">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/peak-oil/4229/47</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 May 2010 05:51:19 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-4229-47</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/peak-oil/4229.rss">Peak Oil?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Peak Oil?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[bur]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>without any allusions to the Cold War, loony</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/peak-oil/4229/46">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/peak-oil/4229/46</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 27 May 2010 19:55:51 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-4229-46</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/peak-oil/4229.rss">Peak Oil?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Peak Oil?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[mattemuse]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="loony636">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/l/6bbea6/40.png" class="avatar"> loony636:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Uhhh, yeah, really. Why would the government care if we ran out of oil? Explain it rationally, reasonably, and without any allusions to the Cold War.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>national defense is 100% reliant on oil (the US military is the worlds largest consumer of oil)<br>
the US economy is 100% reliant on oil<br>
food production is 100% reliant on oil<br>
and last but not least the oil industry has a massive influence over the US government</p>
<p>Now explain to me rationally and reasonably how this is somehow not blindingly obvious to everyone?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/peak-oil/4229/45">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/peak-oil/4229/45</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 27 May 2010 16:07:28 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-4229-45</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/peak-oil/4229.rss">Peak Oil?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Peak Oil?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[mattemuse]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I was with you until the avacado ban, avacados are nature’s most perfect food</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/peak-oil/4229/44">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/peak-oil/4229/44</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 27 May 2010 16:04:49 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-4229-44</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/peak-oil/4229.rss">Peak Oil?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Peak Oil?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[hercule_poirots_nuts]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>you diddnt do anything today that diddnt consume fossil fuels</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/peak-oil/4229/43">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/peak-oil/4229/43</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 27 May 2010 15:40:38 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-4229-43</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/peak-oil/4229.rss">Peak Oil?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Peak Oil?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[hercule_poirots_nuts]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="loony636">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/l/6bbea6/40.png" class="avatar"> loony636:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Uhhh, yeah, really. Why would the government care if we ran out of oil? Explain it rationally, reasonably, and without any allusions to the Cold War.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>because our whole way of life is dependant on it on every level</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/peak-oil/4229/42">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/peak-oil/4229/42</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 27 May 2010 15:36:33 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-4229-42</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/peak-oil/4229.rss">Peak Oil?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Peak Oil?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[hercule_poirots_nuts]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>if i was in charge i would outlaw cars and focus on public transport infrastructure and bringing people back in from the suburbs. also i would ban avacados cuz they are fucking gross</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/peak-oil/4229/41">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/peak-oil/4229/41</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 27 May 2010 15:35:37 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-4229-41</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/peak-oil/4229.rss">Peak Oil?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Peak Oil?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[loony636]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="mattemuse">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/m/dc4da7/40.png" class="avatar"> mattemuse:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>really?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Uhhh, yeah, really. Why would the government care if we ran out of oil? Explain it rationally, reasonably, and without any allusions to the Cold War.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/peak-oil/4229/40">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/peak-oil/4229/40</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 27 May 2010 15:34:56 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-4229-40</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/peak-oil/4229.rss">Peak Oil?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Peak Oil?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Someonerandm]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Bluemen230">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Bluemen230:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>How come no one has mentioned electric cars yet :facepalm:</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>From what I know Hydrogen fuel cells are much more efficient and I really hope they, not electric cars, are the way of the future.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/peak-oil/4229/39">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/peak-oil/4229/39</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 27 May 2010 15:12:50 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-4229-39</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/peak-oil/4229.rss">Peak Oil?</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
