<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Windows 7 (Home Premium) -- No Login Screen</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/windows-7-home-premium-no-login-screen/7751</link>
    <description>Okay, this is new.  And frustrating.

I was using my desktop (HP p6310f) and everything was going swimmingly until I received a blue screen out of nowhere.  &quot;BAD_POOL_CALLER&quot;.  Thought maybe it was a transitory thing and rebooted.

I began to look at the reasons something like this would happen online when I got another blue screen.  &quot;A device driver attempting to corrupt the system has been caught.  The faulty driver currently on the kernel stack must be replaced with a working version.&quot;

:|

So, anyway, I tried to boot into safe mode.  Windows did not show a log-in screen.  I could not pull up Task Manager via the usual steps (CTRL-ALT-DEL or CTRL-SHIFT-ESC).  I know Windows is running, at least in a limited fashion because if I push the Shift key five times, I get the sticky-keys dialog.  But that&#39;s the only thing I can do.

I&#39;ve tried to System Recovery, I&#39;ve tried to go back to multiple restore points, and nothing seems to be working.

Does anyone have any ideas?  I don&#39;t particularly want to wipe and reinstall Windows.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 31 Aug 2011 05:01:22 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Help and Support</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/windows-7-home-premium-no-login-screen/7751.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Windows 7 (Home Premium) -- No Login Screen</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[BaTz281]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Every so often it’s good to have a fresh start.  From what I’ve read, in Windows 8 Microsoft plans to include an “inplace install”, better than Windows 7, that will be like a “reset” button for the OS.  Will have to see <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=9" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/windows-7-home-premium-no-login-screen/7751/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/windows-7-home-premium-no-login-screen/7751/6</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 31 Aug 2011 05:01:22 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7751-6</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/windows-7-home-premium-no-login-screen/7751.rss">Windows 7 (Home Premium) -- No Login Screen</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Windows 7 (Home Premium) -- No Login Screen</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[danielsangeo]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>UPDATE: I bit the bullet.</p>
<p>Seeing that there was no way to get around it, I used the system recovery tools to open a command prompt (launching services.msc or gpedit.msc did not work), copied all the data from the primary drive to a secondary drive, disconnected the secondary drive, and wiped the primary drive, and reinstalled Windows.</p>
<p>Installing updates now then will reconnect the secondary drive and move the data back.</p>
<p>Thanks for attempts at assistance, folks.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/windows-7-home-premium-no-login-screen/7751/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/windows-7-home-premium-no-login-screen/7751/5</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 30 Aug 2011 00:17:55 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7751-5</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/windows-7-home-premium-no-login-screen/7751.rss">Windows 7 (Home Premium) -- No Login Screen</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Windows 7 (Home Premium) -- No Login Screen</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[sersoft]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>if safe mode worked you could simply create another user account or enable Administrator, this sounds like something messed with the drivers and windows had to stop some essential services, I would suggest a reinstall (format recommended)</p>
<p>unless you can run cmd somehow and launch services.msc or gpedit.msc</p>
<p>try shift+f10 or F11</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/windows-7-home-premium-no-login-screen/7751/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/windows-7-home-premium-no-login-screen/7751/4</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 29 Aug 2011 16:43:52 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7751-4</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/windows-7-home-premium-no-login-screen/7751.rss">Windows 7 (Home Premium) -- No Login Screen</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Windows 7 (Home Premium) -- No Login Screen</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[danielsangeo]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I have been able to make some progress with system recovery tools via mashing F8 while loading Windows.</p>
<p>The RAM is not at issue because I’ve run many RAM tests including memtest86 and they’ve passed with flying colors.</p>
<p>System Restore is being finicky.  It says that it can’t access a particular file possibly because of an anti-virus, but as I am running this via F8-&gt;System Recovery, I don’t see how that’s possible.  Prior to this, I was using “avast!”.</p>
<p>UPDATE: I am copying all my files on the primary drive over to a backup drive just in case something happens and I do need to wipe the primary drive and start over…</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/windows-7-home-premium-no-login-screen/7751/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/windows-7-home-premium-no-login-screen/7751/3</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 29 Aug 2011 12:34:28 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7751-3</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/windows-7-home-premium-no-login-screen/7751.rss">Windows 7 (Home Premium) -- No Login Screen</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Windows 7 (Home Premium) -- No Login Screen</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[BaTz281]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Based on the “bad_pool_caller”, it sounds like it could be a bad driver (as the error message states) but the second error and your issue with the logon screen is possibly a bit different.  If you have more than one stick of RAM in that machine, I’d pull them all out and try booting the machine with only one stick at a time installed.  I’d give safe mode another try as well, perhaps see if you can identify the faulty driver from the Event Viewer.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/windows-7-home-premium-no-login-screen/7751/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/windows-7-home-premium-no-login-screen/7751/2</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 29 Aug 2011 12:19:41 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7751-2</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/windows-7-home-premium-no-login-screen/7751.rss">Windows 7 (Home Premium) -- No Login Screen</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Windows 7 (Home Premium) -- No Login Screen</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[danielsangeo]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Okay, this is new.  And frustrating.</p>
<p>I was using my desktop (HP p6310f) and everything was going swimmingly until I received a blue screen out of nowhere.  “BAD_POOL_CALLER”.  Thought maybe it was a transitory thing and rebooted.</p>
<p>I began to look at the reasons something like this would happen online when I got another blue screen.  “A device driver attempting to corrupt the system has been caught.  The faulty driver currently on the kernel stack must be replaced with a working version.”</p>
<p><img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/expressionless.png?v=9" title=":expressionless:" class="emoji only-emoji" alt=":expressionless:"></p>
<p>So, anyway, I tried to boot into safe mode.  Windows did not show a log-in screen.  I could not pull up Task Manager via the usual steps (CTRL-ALT-DEL or CTRL-SHIFT-ESC).  I know Windows is running, at least in a limited fashion because if I push the Shift key five times, I get the sticky-keys dialog.  But that’s the only thing I can do.</p>
<p>I’ve tried to System Recovery, I’ve tried to go back to multiple restore points, and nothing seems to be working.</p>
<p>Does anyone have any ideas?  I don’t particularly want to wipe and reinstall Windows.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/windows-7-home-premium-no-login-screen/7751/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/windows-7-home-premium-no-login-screen/7751/1</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 29 Aug 2011 10:02:34 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7751-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/windows-7-home-premium-no-login-screen/7751.rss">Windows 7 (Home Premium) -- No Login Screen</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
