<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Where is folder with HECU Marines audio?...</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/where-is-folder-with-hecu-marines-audio/11445</link>
    <description>Hi Bros - long time no see... been extraordinarily busy for weeks -- but have managed to play BM some at night... I love just about every last thing about this game, except one: the HECU Marines and their taunts (or just about anything that comes out of their mouths) is like a fucking ice-pick in my head!... I have never, ever hated enemy speech so much.. and I have played many, many games.

I just spent about a half hour in Adobe Audition, going through every folder that seems to have any possibility of having those files... in the hopes of muting them... especially &quot;DO IT!!!&quot; and &quot;We are going to KICK YOUR ASS!!&quot;... but I will most certainly be muting every last one, if and when I find them.

And there does not seem to be a way to disable any audio through console commands... or am I wrong?

Please, someone, anyone.... where on god&#39;s green fucking earth are the wav files I am so desperate to mute? And please don&#39;t tell me they are somehow embedded in the soundcache files or something.

Sorry if anyone reading this made those... don&#39;t quit your day job.   :wink:</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 11 Oct 2012 01:17:08 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Help!</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/where-is-folder-with-hecu-marines-audio/11445.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Where is folder with HECU Marines audio?...</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Gasher]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I have no idea how I missed that folder!.. Thank you sooo much bro. Now I can enjoy this game.</p>
<p>:jizz:</p>
<p>Edit: Whew!.. that sure took a while. I think I got carpal tunnel to boot. I <span class="bbcode-b">did</span> mute these with <span class="bbcode-i">Silence</span> in Audition (thinking that this was the safest bet to not break game)… went way quicker once I mapped that to a key. Ctr A, Num 0, Ctr S, Ctr W… over and over and over. And I felt stupid, petty and actually <span class="bbcode-b">guilty</span>, while doing it. I know that someone, put a lot of hard work into these… but there lies the problem… some <span class="bbcode-b">one</span>. The HECUs should have been voiced (in my very most humble opinion) by no less than 4 guys - with very different voices. And there is just waaay too much HECU speech… and way too often. Also, having serious walkie-talkie distortion like original would have made these bearable for me. And prolly a little spooky too.</p>
<p>Edit edit: Whoa!.. like a completely different game!! HECUs are now almost like Assassins!!!.. I am enjoying BM quite a bit more… silence is golden indeed. Of course, for all I know just deleting them would have worked fine and not broken game. One could always back up BMS\sound\vo\npc\hgrunt and BMS\sound\vo\npc\hgrunt_young folders first.</p>
<p>Black Mesa, minus HECU speech, is a masterpiece. I highly recommend this to anyone for your 2nd play-through. It really does feel like another game… One that is way more serious in tone/mood… and tons more ambient, eerie and mysterious. I play with music off too. Once you kill hecu and music, you will hear (that much better) the really good shit… the ambient environment sounds… which are the real star of BM’s audio, if you ask me.</p>
<p>And I got over my guilt - real quick. So nice to be able to tailor something to your own tastes… as I am sure many of you blokes absolutely love the HECU speech and would think this whole idea is completely retarded.</p>
<p>Oh… and it takes things up about ten notches in the difficulty dept. Not knowing where those bastards are coming from, and not having their attacks telegraphed to you in advance, is fucking crazy… you will trip when you see how much more difficult things are.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/where-is-folder-with-hecu-marines-audio/11445/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/where-is-folder-with-hecu-marines-audio/11445/3</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 11 Oct 2012 01:17:08 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11445-3</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/where-is-folder-with-hecu-marines-audio/11445.rss">Where is folder with HECU Marines audio?...</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Where is folder with HECU Marines audio?...</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[ThePsycho]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>BMS\sound\vo\npc</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/where-is-folder-with-hecu-marines-audio/11445/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/where-is-folder-with-hecu-marines-audio/11445/2</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 11 Oct 2012 01:04:20 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11445-2</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/where-is-folder-with-hecu-marines-audio/11445.rss">Where is folder with HECU Marines audio?...</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Where is folder with HECU Marines audio?...</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Gasher]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Hi Bros - long time no see… been extraordinarily busy for weeks – but have managed to play BM some at night… I love just about every last thing about this game, except one: the HECU Marines and their taunts (or just about anything that comes out of their mouths) is like a fucking ice-pick in my head!.. I have never, ever hated enemy speech so much… and I have played many, many games.</p>
<p>I just spent about a half hour in Adobe Audition, going through every folder that seems to have any possibility of having those files… in the hopes of muting them… especially “DO IT!!!” and “We are going to KICK YOUR ASS!!”… but I will most certainly be muting every last one, if and when I find them.</p>
<p>And there does not seem to be a way to disable any audio through console commands… or am I wrong?</p>
<p>Please, someone, anyone… where on god’s green fucking earth are the wav files I am so desperate to mute? And please don’t tell me they are somehow embedded in the soundcache files or something.</p>
<p>Sorry if anyone reading this made those… don’t quit your day job.   <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/wink.png?v=9" title=":wink:" class="emoji" alt=":wink:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/where-is-folder-with-hecu-marines-audio/11445/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/where-is-folder-with-hecu-marines-audio/11445/1</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 11 Oct 2012 00:38:11 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11445-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/where-is-folder-with-hecu-marines-audio/11445.rss">Where is folder with HECU Marines audio?...</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
