<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Bad savepoint in blast pit. Slight audio glitches [Fixed]</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/bad-savepoint-in-blast-pit-slight-audio-glitches-fixed/9594</link>
    <description>Two things -

1. In Blast Pit, after you fire the rocket engine and go down to where the tentacles were, you go down a ladder to the next section. However, it&#39;s possible, and rather easy IMO, to miss hitting the ladder and instead you fall down into the next part. This wouldn&#39;t be such a big deal except there&#39;s a save point in the middle of the ladder, so it&#39;ll get you into an endless loop of falling and dying. The only solution is to load an earlier save. For the record, I saved after I killed the tentacle, so I&#39;m not sure where the previous save point was. Don&#39;t know how hard it would be to move it, or how much trouble it will cause players, but I thought I&#39;d point it out.

2. Sometimes when I move my view around I&#39;ll get a slight glitch where the audio and video seems to skip a frame or two. Not a huge issue either. Could be just on my end.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 14 Sep 2012 23:05:25 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>In-game Issues (Mod)</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/bad-savepoint-in-blast-pit-slight-audio-glitches-fixed/9594.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Bad savepoint in blast pit. Slight audio glitches [Fixed]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[sersoft]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I managed to avoid the loop but i also get audio skips when looking around in a new area.</p>
<p>I think its my slow 800mhz RAM.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/bad-savepoint-in-blast-pit-slight-audio-glitches-fixed/9594/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/bad-savepoint-in-blast-pit-slight-audio-glitches-fixed/9594/2</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 14 Sep 2012 23:05:25 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9594-2</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/bad-savepoint-in-blast-pit-slight-audio-glitches-fixed/9594.rss">Bad savepoint in blast pit. Slight audio glitches [Fixed]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Bad savepoint in blast pit. Slight audio glitches [Fixed]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Orpheon]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Two things -</p>
<ol>
<li>
<p>In Blast Pit, after you fire the rocket engine and go down to where the tentacles were, you go down a ladder to the next section. However, it’s possible, and rather easy IMO, to miss hitting the ladder and instead you fall down into the next part. This wouldn’t be such a big deal except there’s a save point in the middle of the ladder, so it’ll get you into an endless loop of falling and dying. The only solution is to load an earlier save. For the record, I saved after I killed the tentacle, so I’m not sure where the previous save point was. Don’t know how hard it would be to move it, or how much trouble it will cause players, but I thought I’d point it out.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Sometimes when I move my view around I’ll get a slight glitch where the audio and video seems to skip a frame or two. Not a huge issue either. Could be just on my end.</p>
</li>
</ol>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/bad-savepoint-in-blast-pit-slight-audio-glitches-fixed/9594/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/bad-savepoint-in-blast-pit-slight-audio-glitches-fixed/9594/1</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 14 Sep 2012 22:59:31 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9594-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/bad-savepoint-in-blast-pit-slight-audio-glitches-fixed/9594.rss">Bad savepoint in blast pit. Slight audio glitches [Fixed]</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
