<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>AAA title prices</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/aaa-title-prices/9070</link>
    <description>next time you have to pay $60 US for a AAA title you can think hey, thats not to bad. atleast im not Australian. :fffuuu:

[url]https://www.ausgamers.com/news/read/3228013/australian-videogame-pricing-detailed-in-government-enquiry-submission[/url]</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 26 Jul 2012 03:36:40 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Technology and Gaming</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/aaa-title-prices/9070.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>AAA title prices</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[av3nger]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Termo543">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/t/c37758/40.png" class="avatar"> Termo543:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I don’t see what the problems with violence and porn is though. we young Americans are turning out just. Fucking. Perfect.</p>
<p>(sarcasm intended)</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Yeah. If you were serious about that…you’d be a massive unintellectual.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/aaa-title-prices/9070/27">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/aaa-title-prices/9070/27</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jul 2012 03:36:40 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9070-27</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/aaa-title-prices/9070.rss">AAA title prices</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>AAA title prices</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[striker]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Now that you say so… i know at least of one  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/wink.png?v=9" title=":wink:" class="emoji" alt=":wink:"></p>
<p>OTT: some mod should move this discussion in another thread, or OP rename it…</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/aaa-title-prices/9070/26">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/aaa-title-prices/9070/26</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jul 2012 09:13:34 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9070-26</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/aaa-title-prices/9070.rss">AAA title prices</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>AAA title prices</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[tonkat]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>then those sneaky germans at valve?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/aaa-title-prices/9070/25">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/aaa-title-prices/9070/25</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jul 2012 03:58:18 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9070-25</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/aaa-title-prices/9070.rss">AAA title prices</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>AAA title prices</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[striker]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="tonkat">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/t/57b2e6/40.png" class="avatar"> tonkat:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>blocking the ip rather than the game itself is one sneaky little trick.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>That’s actually done by the steam client itself. So Valve to blame there.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/aaa-title-prices/9070/24">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/aaa-title-prices/9070/24</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jul 2012 23:42:17 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9070-24</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/aaa-title-prices/9070.rss">AAA title prices</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>AAA title prices</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[tonkat]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>yeah but you guys are always angry at something.</p>
<p>those germans on the other hand a crafty. blocking the ip rather than the game itself is one sneaky little trick.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/aaa-title-prices/9070/23">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/aaa-title-prices/9070/23</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jul 2012 23:26:51 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9070-23</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/aaa-title-prices/9070.rss">AAA title prices</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>AAA title prices</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Termo543]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I don’t see what the problems with violence and porn is though. we young Americans are turning out just. Fucking. Perfect.</p>
<p>(sarcasm intended)</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/aaa-title-prices/9070/22">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/aaa-title-prices/9070/22</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jul 2012 20:58:26 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9070-22</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/aaa-title-prices/9070.rss">AAA title prices</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>AAA title prices</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[striker]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Ok, Gasher, this has nothing to do with pricing, but yes, there are countries, where you cannot buy some games. JFYI I’ll explain to you an example how it’s handled in Germany atm.<br>
There is a youth protection law in Germany which actually serves a good goal. It is there to keep porn, violence (at least the worse, unnecessary violence), booze, etc. away from children and youths (that is persons under 18 - there are exceptions for things like beer/wine, softporn and some bloody movies for over 16-year olds). So far so good.</p>
<p>A <span class="bbcode-b">privately run</span> company (USK) with representatives of the entertainment industry rates all movies, games and other entertainment media for their “compatability” for youths. This has nothing to do with the government. It is a self-sufficient system of the industry itself - but abiding to the youth protection law.<br>
After the rating, a big coloured marker is pasted on the media to show parents and vendors at what age you are allowed to buy it (and it is illegal to sell to younger people).</p>
<p>A <span class="bbcode-b">government office</span> (BPjM) only kicks in by request of the youths department, if it is made aware of a piece of media which could be dangerous to the development of children. The BPjM employs professional testers of all ages, who give a recommendation for an age-classification of games or movies. Then the review is brought before a board of representative which decides, how the media is classified:<br>
I) it is not dangerous to youths --&gt; the USK-Rating stays in place, nothing changes<br>
II) it is dangerous to youths --&gt; it gets indexed, meaning it may not be sold to underaged people, there may be no advertising of this media, there may be no coverage in Magazines or other written/televised sources, it has to be sold “under the vendors desk” and only to adults, who have proven their age<br>
III) it violates the constitution (mostly the case with cases of discrimination, racism, contradicts human dignity, glorifies violence/felonies or the display of symbols of the third reich, which are unconstitutional) --&gt; the game/movie is<br>
a) forbidden (may not be sold, imported in order to be sold, shared, etc. - you may however buy it overseas, if you only use it yourself)<br>
b) seized (taken out of shelves, import stop and the posession ist prosecuted - I don’t know of any example, where this has happened before - one exception is the depiction of the third reich in movies, which is seen as historical correct art/games are not considered art - it would also be weird watching a wwII movie with black duck in a white circle on a red flag as a nazi symbol)</p>
<p>Needless to state, that the government does not itself censor the media. It only prosecutes those who don’t abide to the restrictions stated above.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">CONCLUSION</span>:<br>
It are the companies, who either don’t sell their product in Germany, because there is no way they see any revenue coming back to them, as they’re not allowed to advertise, or if they want to sell it, they cut/change so much contents of the game, that it has a chance of staying in the shelves.<br>
This leads to things like C&amp;C having not soldiers but robots who don’t die crying out but rather sounding like a crumbled tin of coke and “bleeding” black oil. It leads to Black Ops not being allowed to be sold with the airport scene as it glorifies an inhumane act (you can’t even play a gifted uncut version, because it asks for an IP on start up/installation and closes connection for all german IPs).<br>
It leads to steam not asking for ones age - I don’t mean the thingy, where you can put in anything you like, steam doesn’t ask you for ID - but rather leads to Valve truncating it’s game catalogue for everybody in Germany (and other countries respectively).</p>
<p>There is an initiative on the steam groups (for uncut) for a safe age-verification system in steam, so adults can buy uncut games. So far the widening of business possibilities doesn’t seem to be enough for Valve to implementing such a system - they would be the first and the business opportunity would be great if they could hold the monopoly for imported uncut games.</p>
<p>Edit: Now Valve seems to even want to restrict cross-border gifting, so that no one can play titles they’re not allowed to (and frankly the more obvious reason ist that they can’t juggle with exchange rates). This is very short sighted. As you are allowed to buy any game that ist not <span class="bbcode-u">seized</span> (and that rarely happens) when you’re 18, adult Germans are driven to either import the uncut retail version at ridiculous prices or go to a game shop and ask for the stash “under the vendors desk”. While steam is a very convenient way to buy games, not all retail versions use the steamworks system. So you’re practically driven underground because there is no way of age-verification on steam. Granted such a system is difficult to implement for all the different countries, the loss of costumers due to lack of service is something Valve cannot afford. And here I am, always thinking Germans don’t understand what costumer service means (here it means, “let the costumer care for himself”). Steam also wouldn’t have such a problem with the gifting scene, as its more comfortable to not ask somebody to gift a game to you (IMO steam gifts are always a good thing in terms of no delivery costs <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/wink.png?v=9" title=":wink:" class="emoji" alt=":wink:"> ).</p>
<p>[/SIZE]  <span class="bbcode-u"><span class="bbcode-b">tl;dr-Version</span></span>[/SIZE]: youth protection sometimes over-achieves it’s goal when even adults aren’t able to consume media which could be dangerous for children.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/aaa-title-prices/9070/21">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/aaa-title-prices/9070/21</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jul 2012 15:41:51 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9070-21</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/aaa-title-prices/9070.rss">AAA title prices</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>AAA title prices</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[unix87]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Gasher">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/g/f08c70/40.png" class="avatar"> Gasher:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Yeah, but do they <span class="bbcode-i">censor</span> you?.. not allow you to buy <span class="bbcode-b">at all</span>?.. because of violence etc?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>When a game is not available, I see something like this:<br>
<span alt="" class="broken-image" title="This image is broken"><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-unlink svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#unlink"></use></svg></span></p>
<p>For me, Skyrim is not available, but I can still have games like Oblivion, Fallout 3/New Vegas, Left 4 Dead 1/2, GTA games or Borderlands with full gore etc. When I search for Skyrim on Steam, I get zero results. I can search for it via Google, but I can’t open the page. I think it was the publishers decision not to sell the game in our country, because I haven’t heard of any censorship laws here.</p>
<p>I read somewhere people saying that they bought a game while living in one country, then moved to another country and could no longer play that game.</p>
<p>I only managed to overcome this issue with a free to play game (that was also not available in my region) by getting that game’s code on Steam and putting together a URL that would open the install window on my Steam app.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/aaa-title-prices/9070/20">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/aaa-title-prices/9070/20</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jul 2012 11:38:15 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9070-20</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/aaa-title-prices/9070.rss">AAA title prices</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>AAA title prices</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[tonkat]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="johnyo">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/j/a9a28c/40.png" class="avatar"> johnyo:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>tonkat, your spelling is atrocious.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>and i will always agree.</p>
<p>-edit i actually just read what i had typed earlier. feel like i reside from Broadmeadows now.<br>
adn this is what happens in Broady</p>
<p><img src="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/original/3X/7/d/7dd5d7d035da441a3d698e18690176fb8a24baef.jpeg" alt="" data-base62-sha1="hXbQ6mybek7jnwbmcB4NRjtSF3h" width="430" height="289"></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/aaa-title-prices/9070/19">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/aaa-title-prices/9070/19</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jul 2012 00:28:48 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9070-19</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/aaa-title-prices/9070.rss">AAA title prices</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>AAA title prices</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Brombaq]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Ramirezoid">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/r/ba9def/40.png" class="avatar"> Ramirezoid:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>But still, it’s safer to bitch about it than leave him alone or attempt to help him in a friendly manner.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I never heard that friendliness you are talking about… where can i buy such thing?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/aaa-title-prices/9070/18">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/aaa-title-prices/9070/18</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 21 Jul 2012 14:53:58 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9070-18</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/aaa-title-prices/9070.rss">AAA title prices</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>AAA title prices</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Ramirezoid]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>And yet his sentences somehow manage to be perfectly coherent. But still, it’s safer to bitch about it than leave him alone or attempt to help him in a friendly manner. I mean, what if he uses the wrong (but otherwise phonetically identical to the right) words again?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/aaa-title-prices/9070/17">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/aaa-title-prices/9070/17</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 21 Jul 2012 14:22:21 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9070-17</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/aaa-title-prices/9070.rss">AAA title prices</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>AAA title prices</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[johnyo]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>tonkat, your spelling is atrocious.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/aaa-title-prices/9070/16">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/aaa-title-prices/9070/16</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 21 Jul 2012 11:53:13 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9070-16</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/aaa-title-prices/9070.rss">AAA title prices</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>AAA title prices</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Brombaq]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Just because they have it worse there doesnt mean <span class="bbcode-u">most</span> games arent overpriced piles of shit</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/aaa-title-prices/9070/15">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/aaa-title-prices/9070/15</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 21 Jul 2012 00:24:12 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9070-15</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/aaa-title-prices/9070.rss">AAA title prices</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>AAA title prices</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[tonkat]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Gasher">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/g/f08c70/40.png" class="avatar"> Gasher:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Yeah, but do they <span class="bbcode-i">censor</span> you?.. not allow you to buy <span class="bbcode-b">at all</span>?.. because of violence etc?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>some games they have, there bringing in an r18 classificatory atm how ever, but game like l4d2 and that you could simply adjust one line of code to change it back to standard.</p>
<p>our government is stupid and dont realize we just go around them any way.<br>
but all thats ever held it back is one front bencher being a douche.</p>
<p>but he didnt make any sense, he banned l4d2 but we were aloud to play other games that had far more violence and sex scene’s.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/aaa-title-prices/9070/14">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/aaa-title-prices/9070/14</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jul 2012 23:52:11 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9070-14</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/aaa-title-prices/9070.rss">AAA title prices</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>AAA title prices</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Gasher]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Yeah, but do they <span class="bbcode-i">censor</span> you?.. not allow you to buy <span class="bbcode-b">at all</span>?.. because of violence etc?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/aaa-title-prices/9070/13">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/aaa-title-prices/9070/13</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jul 2012 23:15:16 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9070-13</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/aaa-title-prices/9070.rss">AAA title prices</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>AAA title prices</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[tonkat]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>yeah you cant actually do it, same with origin, if i log onto the us origin store try to make the purchase as soon as i got threw the pay screen it notices im not a us citizen and reverts back to au prices.</p>
<p>havent tryd gifting threw steam though pretty good idea. but alot of games it ends up cheaper threw <a href="http://ozgameshop.com" rel="nofollow noopener">ozgameshop.com</a> etc just because you pay no freight and your only paying 60 bucks for triple a title.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="OrderOfDagon">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/user_avatar/leakfree.org/orderofdagon/40/4963_2.png" class="avatar"> OrderOfDagon:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>The US makes up for it in different ways - don’t worry.</p>
<p>Anyways, isn’t Raminator in Sydney, Australia? lol</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>newcastle i think. still about 2 hours out of sydney. i think.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/aaa-title-prices/9070/12">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/aaa-title-prices/9070/12</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jul 2012 22:55:33 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9070-12</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/aaa-title-prices/9070.rss">AAA title prices</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>AAA title prices</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[OrderOfDagon]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>The US makes up for it in different ways - don’t worry.</p>
<p>Anyways, isn’t Raminator in Sydney, Australia? lol</p>
<p>Edit: Newcastle apparently</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/aaa-title-prices/9070/11">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/aaa-title-prices/9070/11</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jul 2012 22:54:36 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9070-11</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/aaa-title-prices/9070.rss">AAA title prices</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>AAA title prices</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Gasher]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Hold on a sec… are you gents saying that you are not able to jump on Steam, buy a game (that your country deems too violent for you… even when you are an adult) and pay for it with PayPal… and just dl it?.. Do your countries have some kind of firewalls for this shite?..</p>
<p>Whaaaaa? I seriously did not know that, if this is indeed the case… And I thought US was run by the biggest tight-asses on the planet.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/aaa-title-prices/9070/10">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/aaa-title-prices/9070/10</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jul 2012 21:14:11 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9070-10</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/aaa-title-prices/9070.rss">AAA title prices</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>AAA title prices</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[lunertexcosmo]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>And then all these companies start going “Waaaahhhh!!!  Why do people keep pirating!!!”</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/aaa-title-prices/9070/9">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/aaa-title-prices/9070/9</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jul 2012 12:48:06 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9070-9</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/aaa-title-prices/9070.rss">AAA title prices</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>AAA title prices</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Siggs]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Get people to gift you games from the US and EU, then paypal them the monies back. It’s perfect seeing as most steam transactions are paypal anyway.</p>
<p>I gifted a friend in Sydney L4D2 to get around the censorship, he payed me back. Cheaper gaming, better gaming.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/aaa-title-prices/9070/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/aaa-title-prices/9070/8</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jul 2012 12:44:53 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9070-8</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/aaa-title-prices/9070.rss">AAA title prices</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>AAA title prices</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Gregorovich]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Gah, double-post…</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/aaa-title-prices/9070/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/aaa-title-prices/9070/7</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jul 2012 10:02:27 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9070-7</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/aaa-title-prices/9070.rss">AAA title prices</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>AAA title prices</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Gregorovich]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>And this, gentlemen, is why pirating was invented.</p>
<p><img src="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/original/3X/7/6/76a88720401b441de47e474e048ae0abf46bb061.jpeg" alt="" data-base62-sha1="gVHpsRU9xGb8lEcJuAiFQvom0c9" width="400" height="334"></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/aaa-title-prices/9070/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/aaa-title-prices/9070/6</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jul 2012 10:01:42 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9070-6</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/aaa-title-prices/9070.rss">AAA title prices</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>AAA title prices</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[DiePoente]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>In related news, Medal of Honor and Battlefield 4, by EA, are going to cost 10$ more for everyone.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/aaa-title-prices/9070/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/aaa-title-prices/9070/5</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jul 2012 09:09:53 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9070-5</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/aaa-title-prices/9070.rss">AAA title prices</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>AAA title prices</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Fnork]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>If I read that chart right, it’s still nothing compared to Sweden. The prices for new games here range from the equivalent of ~85 to ~110$.</p>
<p>I don’t know how well that translates, though, considering the different economies as a whole, but I still find the prices ridiculously high. Whenever I buy a game I either wait a year until the prices drop to about 50$ or buy from the UK.</p>
<p>You people all got it easy.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/aaa-title-prices/9070/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/aaa-title-prices/9070/4</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jul 2012 07:45:09 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9070-4</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/aaa-title-prices/9070.rss">AAA title prices</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>AAA title prices</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[fade]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>FUCK YEAH STRAYA CUNT</p>
<p>any half savvy aussie gamer knows better than to buy retail and grey imports their games instead… believe it or not in alot of cases retailers themselves have even begun to get in on the act over here, including some of our big chains like Harvey Norman and JB Hi Fi…</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/aaa-title-prices/9070/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/aaa-title-prices/9070/3</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jul 2012 06:29:24 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9070-3</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/aaa-title-prices/9070.rss">AAA title prices</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
