<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>My only complain ...</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/my-only-complain/12714</link>
    <description>I like almost everything about this mod, it is great! My only critique is that you replaced a lot of the iconic sound effects from the original game with new ones, like the small green portals that spawn the aliens, the aliens itself, doors, gateways, trains etc. I think that decision removed a bit of the atmosphere and flair which the Original Game made so special. The sound editing per se is very well done and professional, but I think it doesn&#39;t fit in the HL Universe or let&#39;s say that I think the original sound effects fit much better.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2013 21:28:25 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>The Cafeteria</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/my-only-complain/12714.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>My only complain ...</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[danielsangeo]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=yfm_snCzGX8" data-bbcode="true">How about this?</a></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/my-only-complain/12714/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/my-only-complain/12714/2</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2013 21:28:25 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12714-2</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/my-only-complain/12714.rss">My only complain ...</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My only complain ...</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[dahaka]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I like almost everything about this mod, it is great! My only critique is that you replaced a lot of the iconic sound effects from the original game with new ones, like the small green portals that spawn the aliens, the aliens itself, doors, gateways, trains etc. I think that decision removed a bit of the atmosphere and flair which the Original Game made so special. The sound editing per se is very well done and professional, but I think it doesn’t fit in the HL Universe or let’s say that I think the original sound effects fit much better.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/my-only-complain/12714/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/my-only-complain/12714/1</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2013 21:01:54 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12714-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/my-only-complain/12714.rss">My only complain ...</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
