<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Mirror&#39;s Edge</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/mirrors-edge/3546</link>
    <description>I&#39;ll narrow it down since the title is simple. Discuss about the game if you want (rate, hate, appreciate) but I also want to know if theyre any games like Mirror&#39;s Edge out there. The sort of more run away than fighting games you should suggest. I also like the games where you climb walls and that sort of thing.Thanks  :smiley:</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 29 Mar 2010 16:51:03 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Technology and Gaming</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/mirrors-edge/3546.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Mirror&#39;s Edge</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[bigfan421]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>i dunno about overpriced…<br>
I picked up a <span class="bbcode-i">new</span> copy for less than $10 USD<br>
(then again that was a resale shop whose prices are <span class="bbcode-b">always</span> low)</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/mirrors-edge/3546/35">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/mirrors-edge/3546/35</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 29 Mar 2010 16:51:03 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3546-35</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/mirrors-edge/3546.rss">Mirror&#39;s Edge</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Mirror&#39;s Edge</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Coolm4n]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I loved this game but it was a bit (read: a lot) overpriced.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/mirrors-edge/3546/34">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/mirrors-edge/3546/34</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 29 Mar 2010 15:45:47 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3546-34</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/mirrors-edge/3546.rss">Mirror&#39;s Edge</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Mirror&#39;s Edge</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Sitten_duck]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Orpheon">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/o/6bbea6/40.png" class="avatar"> Orpheon:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>For the most part running would work for me, but there were a few situations I found I couldn’t get through without fighting, especially near the end when they start throwing five or six SWAT guys at you at once. In those cases, I just played it smart and cornered them one at a time and they went down easy. Also, sitten, I don’t recall the ninjas having guns. Were you playing on the hardest difficulty?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I don’t know, I would load it up to remind myself, but I uninstalled it because I was falling behind on studies and I was attempting to prevent myself from wasting time. I distinctly remember that on occasion they would pull out a hand gun and open fire on you, but quickly put it away in a close quarters fight. There are a few times in the game that you can’t run, and if you are unlucky enough to have them hot on your heels and make a misstep that lands you in a corner, you have two or more in your path and they make it next to impossible to get away without a fight, and at that point, its very difficult to get any headway with not one, but two of them beating away at you.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/mirrors-edge/3546/33">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/mirrors-edge/3546/33</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 29 Mar 2010 14:35:36 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3546-33</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/mirrors-edge/3546.rss">Mirror&#39;s Edge</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Mirror&#39;s Edge</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Leo99999]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>So far the game is fantastic!  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/smiley.png?v=9" title=":smiley:" class="emoji" alt=":smiley:">  the graphics are off the hook and I actually love the animated cutscenes. I have to agree with blatstuff on his Psychonauts point though. That game is amazing with a sweet artstyle, comprehensive platforming and combat system, wacky premise and awesome story! Anyone who enjoys 3D platformers should check it out</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/mirrors-edge/3546/32">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/mirrors-edge/3546/32</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 28 Mar 2010 11:56:46 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3546-32</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/mirrors-edge/3546.rss">Mirror&#39;s Edge</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Mirror&#39;s Edge</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[_amp_955_dam]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Mirror’s Edge was the first nex-gen game I played, and it is awesome, I love everything about it.</p>
<p>Looking forward to the sequels. As long as they don’t destroy the story.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/mirrors-edge/3546/31">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/mirrors-edge/3546/31</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 28 Mar 2010 11:27:57 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3546-31</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/mirrors-edge/3546.rss">Mirror&#39;s Edge</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Mirror&#39;s Edge</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[blatstuff]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I keep seeing 60 bucks mentioned.  Was this on console?  I’m amazed this game ever cost that much, it wasn’t worth half that.</p>
<p>That said, I paid 5 bucks for it on Steam (on sale).  best 5 bucks I’ve ever spent on a game, by far.  I had a LOT of fun with this game.</p>
<p>Give me any game that is unique with good play controls and I’m in.  I think people complain that the controls weren’t good with guns, and I understand the complaint.  But as someone mentioned earlier it fits this game well.  You can’t rely on guns because you have to toss them after unloading a clip and I think that’s good.  It makes you stay fluid in your movements, which is the entire point of the game.</p>
<p>For those that love Mirror’s Edge I recommend Psyconaughts.  You can find this one cheap on Steam also.  It’s a third person shooter, with some platforming elements and VERY unique environments.  The game starts out slowly but once it picks up it never stops getting better and better.  Again, give me any game that is unique and I’m in.  This game more than fits that bill.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/mirrors-edge/3546/30">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/mirrors-edge/3546/30</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 28 Mar 2010 10:12:12 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3546-30</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/mirrors-edge/3546.rss">Mirror&#39;s Edge</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Mirror&#39;s Edge</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Orpheon]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>For the most part running would work for me, but there were a few situations I found I couldn’t get through without fighting, especially near the end when they start throwing five or six SWAT guys at you at once. In those cases, I just played it smart and cornered them one at a time and they went down easy. Also, sitten, I don’t recall the ninjas having guns. Were you playing on the hardest difficulty?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/mirrors-edge/3546/29">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/mirrors-edge/3546/29</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 28 Mar 2010 08:03:31 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3546-29</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/mirrors-edge/3546.rss">Mirror&#39;s Edge</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Mirror&#39;s Edge</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Zageron]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I always wondered why people complained about the combat system.<br>
I never stuck around in those situations, I just ran. (Which was the purpose of the game.)</p>
<p>IMO there was no use for a combat system, and it is not a valid con.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/mirrors-edge/3546/28">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/mirrors-edge/3546/28</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 28 Mar 2010 07:32:15 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3546-28</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/mirrors-edge/3546.rss">Mirror&#39;s Edge</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Mirror&#39;s Edge</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NavMan]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Leo99999">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/l/97f17d/40.png" class="avatar"> Leo99999:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Hahahaha yeah! Just bought this for $4 at GAME so I’ll load it up and say what I think of it!  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/smiley.png?v=9" title=":smiley:" class="emoji" alt=":smiley:"></p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p><em>hi five</em></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/mirrors-edge/3546/27">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/mirrors-edge/3546/27</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 28 Mar 2010 06:47:48 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3546-27</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/mirrors-edge/3546.rss">Mirror&#39;s Edge</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Mirror&#39;s Edge</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Sitten_duck]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="loony636">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/l/6bbea6/40.png" class="avatar"> loony636:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I can’t imagine anything worse than playing a first person platformer. The whole point of platforming in the style of Prince of Persia is that you use the third person perspective to gain a full perception of what’s around you, where you’re going, and where to jump to avoid the spikes/enemies/spinning disk blades/etc.</p>
<p>Now, that said, some of Mirror’s Edge’s concepts looked interesting, but apparently they were horribly executed (I can’t say, since I had no incentive to spend precious dollars or megabytes on what was, fairly conclusively, an awful game).</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>As others have said, this is a serious case of “Don’t knock it till you play it”. I have been wanting this game since it first came out, but held off on it because I didn’t have the cash to get it. I finally got it this Christmas through steam for $5. I got close to the ending, but never actually finished it (other more important things took priority at the time, and I just haven’t gotten back to finishing it yet). Anyway, there are only three real complaints I have had: 1) The e-surance style cut screens were not appreciated. They have a beautiful game, they should use it. 2) The combat system needs work. It took me a little bit to get use to fighting stationary armed opponents, but it was next to impossible for me to fight their free-running ninjas. If you get too far away from them they shoot you. If you get too close to them they’ll hand you your butt. They move around alot and thus you miss alot but they never miss, and most of the hits your able to land they just counter it and drop you. I often times had to resort to somehow finding a gun and killing them that way. If that wasn’t bad enough they travel in large groups and don’t hesitate to attack you while your busy with another one. I died countless times, very quickly. A better combat system is a must. 3) They needed a better method to direct the players attention to where they need to go. On rooftops, its obvious on the inside its not, and the hint button just points you to your ultimate goal, not how to get there. So if you knew where you needed to go, but couldn’t figure out how to get there, its no use.</p>
<p>I would prefer a lengthier game, but if a game is good, like portal, then it doesn’t bother me too much that its short. (granted I payed $5 for it and not the $60 that console gamers did, so I can understand if you feel bothered by its length for that price). Having a sandbox style gameplay would be cool, but it never bothered me too much about how linear it was. I have been playing Linear games for years.</p>
<p>Anyway, despite all this, Mirror’s edge was FAR FAR FAR from being a " fairly conclusively, an awful game." It was a good game, and it was brimming with potential. I just hope that the sequel learns from this one and addresses it complaints, and allows that potential to be realized. Anyway, to echo what I said earlier, don’t knock it till you try it, it wasn’t as bad as you make it out to be. A rough cut diamond is still a diamond, just take it to the jewelers and have it brought into shape. That’s my two cents worth anyway.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/mirrors-edge/3546/26">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/mirrors-edge/3546/26</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 28 Mar 2010 06:17:11 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3546-26</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/mirrors-edge/3546.rss">Mirror&#39;s Edge</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Mirror&#39;s Edge</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Zageron]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Great Game. (Especially for $19)<br>
Short and sweet, great game play, awesome graphics, sweet story, epic ending.</p>
<p>I can’t wait for a sequel, or similar game.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/mirrors-edge/3546/25">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/mirrors-edge/3546/25</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 28 Mar 2010 06:04:46 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3546-25</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/mirrors-edge/3546.rss">Mirror&#39;s Edge</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Mirror&#39;s Edge</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Leo99999]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Hahahaha yeah! Just bought this for $4 at GAME so I’ll load it up and say what I think of it!  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/smiley.png?v=9" title=":smiley:" class="emoji" alt=":smiley:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/mirrors-edge/3546/24">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/mirrors-edge/3546/24</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 28 Mar 2010 05:25:20 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3546-24</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/mirrors-edge/3546.rss">Mirror&#39;s Edge</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Mirror&#39;s Edge</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[baconeggs]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I don’t know if was a glitch but all my guns had no sound, leading to quite boring gunfights.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/mirrors-edge/3546/23">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/mirrors-edge/3546/23</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 28 Mar 2010 05:16:57 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3546-23</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/mirrors-edge/3546.rss">Mirror&#39;s Edge</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Mirror&#39;s Edge</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Orpheon]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I too enjoyed it. I think it was mostly well done, but could have used some tweaking in some areas. As some said earlier, getting shot at while running is cool for a bit but then it gets aggravating if you miss a turn or can’t find where to go. The parkour needs to be more fluid and give you more sensation of speed. I often found I was getting into a good pace and then I’d hit a ledge and have to climb up, killing my momentum. And yes, the entire game should have been longer. The gunplay on the other hand was great (after all it’s a DICE game), and the art style was good too.</p>
<p>Overall I think of it as sort of a Portal type game - a unique concept that was successfully proven and now has an opportunity for expansion and development.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/mirrors-edge/3546/22">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/mirrors-edge/3546/22</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 28 Mar 2010 04:25:26 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3546-22</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/mirrors-edge/3546.rss">Mirror&#39;s Edge</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Mirror&#39;s Edge</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Jingles]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I thought it was an awesome game, just a little short.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/mirrors-edge/3546/21">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/mirrors-edge/3546/21</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 27 Mar 2010 10:05:38 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3546-21</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/mirrors-edge/3546.rss">Mirror&#39;s Edge</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Mirror&#39;s Edge</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[TheKeeper]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="FireTime">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/f/ba8739/40.png" class="avatar"> FireTime:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I thoroughly enjoyed the game but I wouldn’t pay $60 for it. I was able to barrow it from my friend. They either needed to make it longer or cheaper.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I thoroughly enjoyed the game and did pay $60. WTF was I thinking. I mean the game is very original but way too short and poor ending. I know it did sell poorly, but they didn’t pull the plug on it and thank god. Do we really wanna be playing different renditions of call of duty for the rest of our lives.</p>
<p>I’d like to take this time to make a shout out to God of war 3. All I have to say is, check mate 360 fan boys, check mate.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/mirrors-edge/3546/20">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/mirrors-edge/3546/20</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 27 Mar 2010 06:54:29 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3546-20</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/mirrors-edge/3546.rss">Mirror&#39;s Edge</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Mirror&#39;s Edge</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Schizophriend]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Brother Shrike">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Brother Shrike:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>the story sucked, the cutscenes sucked, the character models/animation sucked, and the voice acting sucked, but the game somehow was unbelievably fun and entertaining. People say that the gunplay sucks, too, but I thought it fit perfectly into the other gameplay. And the first person part somehow worked as well.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Basically. I wouldnt say it “sucked”, but there wasnt really anything special about those points.</p>
<p>The gameplay however was really fun. The only nitpick I would have is that I wish they had more levels where you werent being shot at as much and were able to just cross vast distances doing cool jumps and stuff. Later in the game it was either slow moving puzzles or running while being shot at. I liked the running through random buildings not being shot at early in the game. I would have liked a few more of those sprinkled in througout.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/mirrors-edge/3546/19">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/mirrors-edge/3546/19</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 27 Mar 2010 06:36:31 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3546-19</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/mirrors-edge/3546.rss">Mirror&#39;s Edge</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Mirror&#39;s Edge</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[FireTime]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Ajax">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/a/a87d85/40.png" class="avatar"> Ajax:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>…Mirror’s Edge was planned to be a trilogy…</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I herd that 1 sold so poorly they they canceled the sequels.</p>
<p>EDIT: Cancel that, Apparently they did confirm that there going to make a second BUT it was placed on the back burner to work on better selling titles.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/mirrors-edge/3546/18">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/mirrors-edge/3546/18</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 27 Mar 2010 05:29:15 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3546-18</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/mirrors-edge/3546.rss">Mirror&#39;s Edge</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Mirror&#39;s Edge</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Deathmonkey7]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I loved Mirror’s Edge.  It was great fun.  And oddly one of my favorite parts of it was the gunplay.  I’m not sure if people are just too used to combat in other games or what, but I loved beating the shit out of somebody, stealing their gun, unloading a clip into someone else then throwing down the gun before roundhouse kicking another guy.  Awesome.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/mirrors-edge/3546/17">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/mirrors-edge/3546/17</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 27 Mar 2010 05:16:30 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3546-17</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/mirrors-edge/3546.rss">Mirror&#39;s Edge</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Mirror&#39;s Edge</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Ajax]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I loved it, but I wish it was longer and gave you more of a clue as to what you were supposed to do. I died hundreds of times because I either had no idea where I was going, or I timed something wrong. It was fun, though. Voice acting was OK…animations were passable. Hated the art style, though, and hated the cutscenes. And it was WAY too damn short and linear.</p>
<p>And Mirror’s Edge was planned to be a trilogy, I believe. Hopefully part 2 will be far more open and freeform than part 1.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/mirrors-edge/3546/16">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/mirrors-edge/3546/16</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 27 Mar 2010 05:02:01 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3546-16</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/mirrors-edge/3546.rss">Mirror&#39;s Edge</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Mirror&#39;s Edge</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Brother_Shrike]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="loony636">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/l/6bbea6/40.png" class="avatar"> loony636:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>…fairly conclusively, an awful game</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>You might want to reread those reviews, champ. That and or play it before you knock it. It got average/ above average reviews, not exactly what I’d call awful. 81 on metacritic.</p>
<p>With that said, the story sucked, the cutscenes sucked, the character models/animation sucked, and the voice acting sucked, but the game somehow was unbelievably fun and entertaining. People say that the gunplay sucks, too, but I thought it fit perfectly into the other gameplay. And the first person part somehow worked as well.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/mirrors-edge/3546/15">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/mirrors-edge/3546/15</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 27 Mar 2010 04:37:18 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3546-15</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/mirrors-edge/3546.rss">Mirror&#39;s Edge</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Mirror&#39;s Edge</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Nedepp]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="SwampFox56">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/s/ce73a5/40.png" class="avatar"> SwampFox56:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>sounds cool. can you provide a link er somthing?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>im too lazy. go on <a href="http://garrysmod.org" rel="nofollow noopener">garrysmod.org</a> and search parkour. the one that says parkour gmod should be it.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/mirrors-edge/3546/14">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/mirrors-edge/3546/14</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 27 Mar 2010 04:15:29 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3546-14</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/mirrors-edge/3546.rss">Mirror&#39;s Edge</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Mirror&#39;s Edge</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[SwampFox56]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Nedepp">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/n/d9b06d/40.png" class="avatar"> Nedepp:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>That’s what I sort of though about Portal. I’m now satisfied because i found out about the Parkour gamemode on Garrys Mod and now I can run around cities and climb walls. You guys who like Mirror’s Edge should check it out if you haven’t.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>sounds cool. can you provide a link er somthing?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/mirrors-edge/3546/13">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/mirrors-edge/3546/13</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 27 Mar 2010 04:12:46 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3546-13</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/mirrors-edge/3546.rss">Mirror&#39;s Edge</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Mirror&#39;s Edge</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Nedepp]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Omega_Absolute">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/o/8e8cbc/40.png" class="avatar"> Omega_Absolute:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I loved the game as well.</p>
<p>What I liked the most was that it was a very pristine looking game that came out when every game was trying to look grungy (fallout, etc, etc). Sorta like a breath of fresh air.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>That’s what I sort of though about Portal. I’m now satisfied because i found out about the Parkour gamemode on Garrys Mod and now I can run around cities and climb walls. You guys who like Mirror’s Edge should check it out if you haven’t.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/mirrors-edge/3546/12">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/mirrors-edge/3546/12</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 27 Mar 2010 03:13:11 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3546-12</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/mirrors-edge/3546.rss">Mirror&#39;s Edge</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Mirror&#39;s Edge</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Ballsopt]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>pine fresh</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/mirrors-edge/3546/11">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/mirrors-edge/3546/11</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 27 Mar 2010 03:04:29 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3546-11</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/mirrors-edge/3546.rss">Mirror&#39;s Edge</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
