<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Glitch</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/glitch/10925</link>
    <description>Hello I&#39;ve come across a glitch in game and can&#39;t find a reason for it, hoping you can help.

As I entered &quot;surface tension&quot; through the bunker door, I had all the normal weapons including the Tau Cannon.  The loading screen popped up as normal and &quot;Surface Tension&quot; appeared on screen for the new chapter but then I took a few steps backwards, the loading screen popped up again, and when it had finished the only weapons I had were the Crowbar, pistols with minimum ammo and a satchel charge...

I assume the Tau cannon is only available for collection at one point in the game so if I continue on from here, I go without it as the autosave over wrote when I re-entered Surface tension.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 20 Sep 2012 20:07:53 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>In-game Issues (Mod)</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/glitch/10925.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Glitch</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[elivance]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>It’s a known issue, add  your topic here:<br>
<a href="https://forums.blackmesasource.com/showthread.php?t=13981" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://forums.blackmesasource.com/showthread.php?t=13981</a></p>
<p>There you’ll find a solution to retrieve your weapons.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/glitch/10925/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/glitch/10925/2</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 20 Sep 2012 20:07:53 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-10925-2</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/glitch/10925.rss">Glitch</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Glitch</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[malevolent]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Hello I’ve come across a glitch in game and can’t find a reason for it, hoping you can help.</p>
<p>As I entered “surface tension” through the bunker door, I had all the normal weapons including the Tau Cannon.  The loading screen popped up as normal and “Surface Tension” appeared on screen for the new chapter but then I took a few steps backwards, the loading screen popped up again, and when it had finished the only weapons I had were the Crowbar, pistols with minimum ammo and a satchel charge…</p>
<p>I assume the Tau cannon is only available for collection at one point in the game so if I continue on from here, I go without it as the autosave over wrote when I re-entered Surface tension.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/glitch/10925/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/glitch/10925/1</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 20 Sep 2012 19:32:47 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-10925-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/glitch/10925.rss">Glitch</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
