<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Dishonored</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/dishonored/8328</link>
    <description>Okay so I just heard about this game and am really excited about it.

[url=&#39;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Dishonored_%28video_game%29&#39;]https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Dishonored_%28video_game%29[/url]

It&#39;s basically a steampunk-ish stealth action game set in an open world and the AI is dynamic, which makes me think it&#39;s similar AI to the Stalker games. You get melee weapons, guns, and you have special powers, such as stopping time, that you can get. They&#39;re really going for player choice as well and one of the lead developers worked on Deus Ex. 

I&#39;m currently reading [url=&#39;https://www.rockpapershotgun.com/2011/08/22/dishonored-interview/&#39;]this[/url] interview with the developers and some of the stuff they&#39;re talking about is really cool, especially the part where they talk about testers doing stuff they hadn&#39;t thought of while testing the game.
[quote]
Harvey Smith: Yeah, or I took these two powers and they work in  combination that was not planned, but I tried it and it just worked. All  the time we saw testers do things we never planned. Like, the time stop  power. A guy runs into a room, there are six guys – and six guys in our  game is serious problem – so he stops time, then he puts an arrow in  the air, an arrow in the air, an arrow in the air [air-draws a  semi-circle in front of him]… Anything touching you moves at real-time,  so if you bump a lamp it falls, but as soon as it’s half a second away  from you it stops. So if you hit a guard, he animates but then stops. So  the crossbow bolts leave you for half a second and stop, and then when  time resumes all the guards die at once, they all get hit by crossbow  bolts at once. And it was magical the first time we saw somebody do  that. It’s just this general purpose approach  to making game systems. 

I can tell you [i]crazy[/i] ones, like a guy stops time and as  somebody shoots the bullet hangs in the air, then he possesses the guy,  walks him around in front of the bullet, and then ejects and then when  time resumes the bullet kills him. He suicided in this weird way.  There’s all these crazy combinations that we had no plans for, but we  trust that if we make things general purpose, the player can get  creative. It’s super-cool. That’s our main thing about the game. On one  level, you’re a supernatural assassin in a retro-future world, but on  another level there’s a lot of variability in this game and it’s  ultimately going to be [i]your[/i] playthrough.
[/quote]
Can&#39;t. Fucking. Wait.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 30 Aug 2012 12:29:46 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Technology and Gaming</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/dishonored/8328.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Dishonored</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Ry_amp_955_n]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=xHKn58eqlx4" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">BAMPITY BAMP cool video of new sweet art and the city of Dunwall</a><br>
“creating steampunk beauty”</p>
<p>EDIT: another video that came out just hours ago: <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=PpfmLa_zbdw" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=PpfmLa_zbdw</a></p>
<p>EDIT2: another source for 4 good videos called <a href="https://www.youtube.com/user/khizbu/feed" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">“Enter the void” 1-4</a> of the open city and each powers being used interestingly. the wind gust power video is awesome.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/dishonored/8328/95">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/dishonored/8328/95</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 30 Aug 2012 12:29:46 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8328-95</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/dishonored/8328.rss">Dishonored</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Dishonored</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[xalener]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Ryλn">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Ryλn:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Archers using double-sided compound bows on hydraulic stilts.<br>
Also, steam boats with rudders in the FRONT, lol. I bet Antonov has something to do with these odd-looking technologies. I like it.</p>
<p>Edit: They are called “Tall Boys”, according to the official Dishonored Wiki.</p>
<p>"Tall Boys are an elite guard unit. They use a suit that is an amalgamation of spindle-legged armature, which keeps them out of reach of the rats that swarm Dunwall, and heavy armor plating, which protects them during confrontations. Although their attack power is significant, they turn slowly; a circle-strafe is an effective way to create an opening within which to take a few shots.<br>
Each tall boy uses a longbow, and has a light attached to its suit, which it can use to peer into shadows. They also wield flamethrowers.</p>
<p>Tall boys will react to alerts aired via loudspeaker if they are near enough to hear them. They can pass through walls of light unharmed." -Wiki<br>
<img src="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/optimized/3X/7/d/7da453109c865e6a7150968d18c54943197c0e55_2_357x500.jpeg" alt="" data-base62-sha1="hVtKkRNZSnDeNIskneppthZLPeJ" width="357" height="500" srcset="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/optimized/3X/7/d/7da453109c865e6a7150968d18c54943197c0e55_2_357x500.jpeg, https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/optimized/3X/7/d/7da453109c865e6a7150968d18c54943197c0e55_2_535x750.jpeg 1.5x, https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/optimized/3X/7/d/7da453109c865e6a7150968d18c54943197c0e55_2_714x1000.jpeg 2x" data-small-upload="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/optimized/3X/7/d/7da453109c865e6a7150968d18c54943197c0e55_2_10x10.png"></p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>So fucking good.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/dishonored/8328/94">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/dishonored/8328/94</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 11 Aug 2012 23:39:52 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8328-94</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/dishonored/8328.rss">Dishonored</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Dishonored</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Ry_amp_955_n]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Archers using double-sided compound bows on hydraulic stilts.<br>
Also, steam boats with rudders in the FRONT, lol. I bet Antonov has something to do with these odd-looking technologies. I like it.</p>
<p>Edit: They are called “Tall Boys”, according to the official Dishonored Wiki.</p>
<p>"Tall Boys are an elite guard unit. They use a suit that is an amalgamation of spindle-legged armature, which keeps them out of reach of the rats that swarm Dunwall, and heavy armor plating, which protects them during confrontations. Although their attack power is significant, they turn slowly; a circle-strafe is an effective way to create an opening within which to take a few shots.<br>
Each tall boy uses a longbow, and has a light attached to its suit, which it can use to peer into shadows. They also wield flamethrowers.</p>
<p>Tall boys will react to alerts aired via loudspeaker if they are near enough to hear them. They can pass through walls of light unharmed." -Wiki<br>
<div class="lightbox-wrapper"><a class="lightbox" href="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/original/3X/7/d/7da453109c865e6a7150968d18c54943197c0e55.jpeg" data-download-href="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/7da453109c865e6a7150968d18c54943197c0e55" title=""><img src="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/optimized/3X/7/d/7da453109c865e6a7150968d18c54943197c0e55_2_357x500.jpeg" alt="" data-base62-sha1="hVtKkRNZSnDeNIskneppthZLPeJ" width="357" height="500" srcset="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/optimized/3X/7/d/7da453109c865e6a7150968d18c54943197c0e55_2_357x500.jpeg, https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/optimized/3X/7/d/7da453109c865e6a7150968d18c54943197c0e55_2_535x750.jpeg 1.5x, https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/optimized/3X/7/d/7da453109c865e6a7150968d18c54943197c0e55_2_714x1000.jpeg 2x" data-small-upload="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/optimized/3X/7/d/7da453109c865e6a7150968d18c54943197c0e55_2_10x10.png"><div class="meta"><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-far-image svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#far-image"></use></svg><span class="filename"></span><span class="informations">1600×2235 201 KB</span><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-discourse-expand svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#discourse-expand"></use></svg></div></a></div></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/dishonored/8328/93">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/dishonored/8328/93</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 06 Aug 2012 19:28:08 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8328-93</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/dishonored/8328.rss">Dishonored</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Dishonored</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[OrderOfDagon]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Ryλn">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Ryλn:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I can see where Dagon is coming from when he talks about the game coming on too strong and… yatyatayata… This game looks really neat and it’s going to be legitimately fun playing it.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>You’re probably right. I have just seen so many guards and so many similar looking city streets in the videos that I think I may be getting tunnel vision when I try to think about how I feel about the game. I’m sure there will be other places and other people to kill. I mean, I totally forget about those bi-pod walkers things – those should be fun to set traps for.</p>
<p>Edit: Wow, after watching the gameplay trailer I feel that I was way off in my instincts. The different environments and enemies seems to be way more bountiful than I anticipated.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/dishonored/8328/92">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/dishonored/8328/92</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 06 Aug 2012 18:24:25 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8328-92</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/dishonored/8328.rss">Dishonored</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Dishonored</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Ry_amp_955_n]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Just watch this cinematic gameplay trailer with awesome spine-chilling, but fitting music: <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=-XbQgdSlsd0" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=-XbQgdSlsd0</a></p>
<p>the slow-mo killing bit with the music is just great.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/dishonored/8328/91">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/dishonored/8328/91</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 06 Aug 2012 17:28:05 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8328-91</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/dishonored/8328.rss">Dishonored</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Dishonored</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Bloodshot]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="OrderOfDagon">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/user_avatar/leakfree.org/orderofdagon/40/4963_2.png" class="avatar"> OrderOfDagon:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I’m basically going to be playing Bioshock in a gray and boring steam-punk version of Innsmouth instead of in an underwater utopia.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>You just basically described how almost anyone who’s played System Shock 2 feels about Bioshock as well.</p>
<p>You can go back and play it and then you realize you <span class="bbcode-i">are</span> playing system shock 2 in an underwater utopia, instead of a dank and infested starship, and minus all the deeper character choices you have to make.</p>
<p>Though I have no idea why you think this setting is boring, and at least the game is copying off of uncommon games instead of just typical ones.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/dishonored/8328/90">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/dishonored/8328/90</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 06 Aug 2012 16:21:25 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8328-90</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/dishonored/8328.rss">Dishonored</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Dishonored</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Ry_amp_955_n]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I can see where Dagon is coming from when he talks about the game coming on too strong and combining too many game elements into one, but Dishonored will pull it off.</p>
<p>The gameplay, environment, and storyline are the important parts. And we’ve seen that the gameplay is brutal good as you can open up a guard’s throat or stick your sword into his face while watching his eyes unfocus as he dies, push him off of a railed 100ft balcony, or strangle him to death then placing his unconscious still breathing body in a garbage dumpster. The environment looks colorful and mysterious and flavorful in many ways so I disagree with you there. And the storyline seems good enough so far: Framed as a killer of the empress, corrupted government in fancy steampunk universe, a supernatural force gives you powers… And we all know there’s gonna be some plot twists that’ll make your jaw drop. Bioshock was chock full of them and so will Dishonored.</p>
<p>tl;dr: This game looks really neat and it’s going to be legitimately fun playing it.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/dishonored/8328/89">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/dishonored/8328/89</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 06 Aug 2012 15:14:48 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8328-89</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/dishonored/8328.rss">Dishonored</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Dishonored</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[mankyman6]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="OrderOfDagon">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/user_avatar/leakfree.org/orderofdagon/40/4963_2.png" class="avatar"> OrderOfDagon:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>This game is so gosh darn awesome!  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/smiley.png?v=9" title=":smiley:" class="emoji" alt=":smiley:"></p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>You’re damn right it is!  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=9" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/dishonored/8328/88">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/dishonored/8328/88</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 06 Aug 2012 11:09:38 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8328-88</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/dishonored/8328.rss">Dishonored</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Dishonored</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[OrderOfDagon]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I feel like a dick for saying this, especially because everyone but me seems to feel otherwise, but I can’t see a single thing that interests me in the game. It looks like a bunch uninteresting fetch quests that can be solved utilizing one of a dozen unoriginal powers or stealth tactics to progress the game to some key-story point. So if the story isn’t excellent, I’m basically going to be playing Bioshock in a gray and boring steam-punk version of Innsmouth instead of in an underwater utopia.</p>
<p>I don’t know, I’m not trying to be critical, I’m just trying to explain how I feel for the game. The environment and everything looks so mundane to me. It looks (not graphically, but stylistically) bland and uncolorful even in the most basic of ways, and I feel like my eyes would get so damn bored with environment really fast.</p>
<p>…I’m not even trying to shoot down the game, I just don’t see why everyone feels so good about it – I mean, I get it; Assassin’s Creed, Bioshock, Thief all rapped up into one. But I mean, it took a bunch different things from other games that worked well with unique environments and put them all into one random environment that looks more like a setting for a horror game. I have to relate to trunk_slamwhatever’s feelings (not his stupid associations or opinions, but his reaction to the game itself) about the game taking a bunch of other ideas and making them seem less effective. And what with all the over-the-top, show-offy, trying-to-impress-you type abilities like possession and the time stopping thing, I do agree that the game feels like it’s trying too hard to combine a bunch of unoriginal elements into one boring looking game.</p>
<p>A good story can solve all of this – but my intuition tells me this game will have no such thing (I’m deriving that from the way the game looks, so I’m not betting on my foresight, I’m just saying it exists). I just don’t think the game will give me a drive or a reason to care. A bunch of different ways to kill bland-looking NPCs just isn’t selling me on this game…</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/dishonored/8328/87">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/dishonored/8328/87</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 06 Aug 2012 07:50:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8328-87</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/dishonored/8328.rss">Dishonored</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Dishonored</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[xalener]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I’m DISABLED<br>
…</p>
<p>I’M DISHONORED.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/dishonored/8328/86">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/dishonored/8328/86</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 06 Aug 2012 01:00:23 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8328-86</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/dishonored/8328.rss">Dishonored</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Dishonored</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[BahamutBBob]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Hello IT.</p>
<p>Have you tried turning it off and on again?</p>
<p>Is it plugged in?</p>
<p>No problem, mate.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/dishonored/8328/85">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/dishonored/8328/85</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 05 Aug 2012 21:56:30 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8328-85</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/dishonored/8328.rss">Dishonored</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Dishonored</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[xalener]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=UxVivkXUfdU&amp;feature=fvwrel" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">The IT crowd.</a>It’s fucking amazing. It’s like The Mighty Boosh mixed with The Office. It actually has quite a bit of the Boosh cast actually.</p>
<p>This also reinforces the “no such thing as 100% originality anymore” argument actually. This show is fucking amazing, has a huge following, and is pretty much a straight mixture of two different pre-existing shows, with the exception of the live studio audience format. That doesn’t take away from any of it’s fidelity though, of course.</p>
<p>Also, <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?feature=fvwp&amp;NR=1&amp;v=1x-ATlpqo1M" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">dat bones</a>.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/dishonored/8328/84">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/dishonored/8328/84</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 05 Aug 2012 06:46:40 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8328-84</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/dishonored/8328.rss">Dishonored</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Dishonored</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Kairouseki]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>What show is it? I tried reverse image searching it but came up with nothing.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/dishonored/8328/83">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/dishonored/8328/83</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 05 Aug 2012 03:35:41 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8328-83</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/dishonored/8328.rss">Dishonored</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Dishonored</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[BahamutBBob]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="xalener">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/x/cc9497/40.png" class="avatar"> xalener:</div>
<blockquote>
<p><img src="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/original/3X/6/0/60b77a763630d12f47c4ed5ef098e1989c160fe7.gif" alt="" data-base62-sha1="dNAW8I3fypX32O48QLW6iNKnatN" width="427" height="240"></p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Love that show.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/dishonored/8328/82">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/dishonored/8328/82</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 05 Aug 2012 02:43:58 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8328-82</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/dishonored/8328.rss">Dishonored</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Dishonored</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Aiden_Pearce]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Kairouseki">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/k/57b2e6/40.png" class="avatar"> Kairouseki:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Nothing is 100% original anymore. If it can take good aspects of other games and combine them well then that’s good. And it looks nothing like DEHR or Syndicate.</p>
<p>I posted this on another forum as well but why do they have to hire a-list actors? All it does is bump up the cost of making the game and then people complain about games costing so much to make. It’s worse than increasingly detailed graphics in that respect.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>They should’ve just hired Nolan North,it would’ve saved them a lot of money  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=9" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:">  .</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/dishonored/8328/81">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/dishonored/8328/81</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 04 Aug 2012 13:55:16 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8328-81</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/dishonored/8328.rss">Dishonored</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Dishonored</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Ry_amp_955_n]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I’m playing this game the day that it comes out. It looks super fun and the city-style/artwork in the game won me from the start. I’m expecting good things from this game. October 8, gentlemen.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/dishonored/8328/80">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/dishonored/8328/80</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 04 Aug 2012 13:07:04 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8328-80</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/dishonored/8328.rss">Dishonored</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Dishonored</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[xalener]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Kairouseki">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/k/57b2e6/40.png" class="avatar"> Kairouseki:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Nothing is 100% original anymore. If it can take good aspects of other games and combine them well then that’s good. And it looks nothing like DEHR or Syndicate.</p>
<p>I posted this on another forum as well but why do they have to hire a-list actors? All it does is bump up the cost of making the game and then people complain about games costing so much to make. It’s worse than increasingly detailed graphics in that respect.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Doesn’t matter had Sarandon</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/dishonored/8328/79">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/dishonored/8328/79</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 04 Aug 2012 00:48:41 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8328-79</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/dishonored/8328.rss">Dishonored</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Dishonored</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Eric_Fong]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Two post above me are funny because it’s truth :lol:</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/dishonored/8328/78">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/dishonored/8328/78</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 04 Aug 2012 00:02:57 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8328-78</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/dishonored/8328.rss">Dishonored</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Dishonored</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Bloodshot]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="trunk_slamchest">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/t/278dde/40.png" class="avatar"> trunk_slamchest:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>it feels like dishonored is just trying way too hard.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Replace “Dishonored” with “trunk_slamchest” and you’d be right on the money.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/dishonored/8328/77">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/dishonored/8328/77</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 Aug 2012 23:50:46 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8328-77</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/dishonored/8328.rss">Dishonored</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Dishonored</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[xalener]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="trunk_slamchest">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/t/278dde/40.png" class="avatar"> trunk_slamchest:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Syndicate 2.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p><img src="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/original/3X/6/0/60b77a763630d12f47c4ed5ef098e1989c160fe7.gif" alt="" data-base62-sha1="dNAW8I3fypX32O48QLW6iNKnatN" width="427" height="240"></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/dishonored/8328/76">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/dishonored/8328/76</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 Aug 2012 23:42:54 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8328-76</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/dishonored/8328.rss">Dishonored</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Dishonored</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Kairouseki]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Nothing is 100% original anymore. If it can take good aspects of other games and combine them well then that’s good. And it looks nothing like DEHR or Syndicate.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Aiden Pearce">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Aiden Pearce:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>The voice acting cast they managed to get is really respectful(to say the least),Susan Sarandon(Thelma &amp; Louise,The Client)Chloe Moretz(Kick Ass,Let Me In)Michael Madsen(Reservoir Dogs)and many others <a href="https://www.joystiq.com/2012/08/03/dishonoreds-voice-cast-full-of-honored-hollywood-talent/" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://www.joystiq.com/2012/08/03/dishonoreds-voice-cast-full-of-honored-hollywood-talent/</a> .</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I posted this on another forum as well but why do they have to hire a-list actors? All it does is bump up the cost of making the game and then people complain about games costing so much to make. It’s worse than increasingly detailed graphics in that respect.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/dishonored/8328/75">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/dishonored/8328/75</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 Aug 2012 17:11:43 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8328-75</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/dishonored/8328.rss">Dishonored</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Dishonored</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[trunk_slamchest]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="xalener">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/x/cc9497/40.png" class="avatar"> xalener:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Viktor Antonov ain’t just some guy.</p>
<p>He’s the badass mother fucker who set the bar of design so high in Half Life 2 that when the actual execution was only 50% as cool as his work, it was still good.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>holy shit you need to stop ball hugging anatonov.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Bloodshot">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/b/839c29/40.png" class="avatar"> Bloodshot:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I feel like I’m watching Thief when he sneaks and moves through the environment, Dark Messiah when he kills, and HL2 when he looks around.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>so pretty much…nothing original and everything we have seen before?</p>
<p>“you lose all individuality when youre just using other peoples ideas.” - trunk slamchest</p>
<p>dishonored wont live up to the expectations because it just looks like DE:HR 2 or Syndicate 2.</p>
<p>it feels like dishonored is just trying way too hard.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/dishonored/8328/74">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/dishonored/8328/74</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 Aug 2012 16:06:13 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8328-74</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/dishonored/8328.rss">Dishonored</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Dishonored</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Aiden_Pearce]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>The voice acting cast they managed to get is really respectful(to say the least),Susan Sarandon(Thelma &amp; Louise,The Client)Chloe Moretz(Kick-Ass,Let Me In)Michael Madsen(Reservoir Dogs)and many others <a href="https://www.joystiq.com/2012/08/03/dishonoreds-voice-cast-full-of-honored-hollywood-talent/" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://www.joystiq.com/2012/08/03/dishonoreds-voice-cast-full-of-honored-hollywood-talent/</a> .</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/dishonored/8328/73">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/dishonored/8328/73</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 Aug 2012 14:44:59 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8328-73</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/dishonored/8328.rss">Dishonored</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Dishonored</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Ibanez]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>that audience was kinda fucked up. I thought it was weird for a while when they were cheering for practically everything he did, especially killing guards, but when they actually boo’d him for not murdering that half naked girl, I was actually disgusted.</p>
<p>P.S. Game looks incredible, but that’s old hat by now.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/dishonored/8328/72">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/dishonored/8328/72</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jul 2012 21:22:46 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8328-72</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/dishonored/8328.rss">Dishonored</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Dishonored</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[gibbelin]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Best gameplay footage I’ve seen yet. Glad to see they’re keeping with the “really stupid guards” tradition. I’m sure the game will get knocked for it, but it would feel wrong if it were any other way.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/dishonored/8328/71">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/dishonored/8328/71</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jul 2012 19:14:45 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8328-71</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/dishonored/8328.rss">Dishonored</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
