<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Black mesa We-ve got hostile pre disaster</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/black-mesa-we-ve-got-hostile-pre-disaster/63323</link>
    <description>Hellow, i&#39;m new to this forum, and i&#39;d like to report a problem: I have Black Mesa 1.0 and I&#39;ve installed the We-ve got hostiles pre-disaster map  (version 0.2) but every time I lanch the map, the game closes directly, I&#39;ve tried a complete check of the local files, but it doesn&#39;t work, I find that regretable, because I really wanted to visit this place before disaster. Well, I hope someone will read me and help me solve the problem (This is a message from an English-French translator, so sorry for the many mistakes if any)</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 21 Jun 2020 12:35:01 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>In-game Issues</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/black-mesa-we-ve-got-hostile-pre-disaster/63323.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Black mesa We-ve got hostile pre disaster</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[sam.devray]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Hellow, i’m new to this forum, and i’d like to report a problem: I have Black Mesa 1.0 and I’ve installed the We-ve got hostiles pre-disaster map  (version 0.2) but every time I lanch the map, the game closes directly, I’ve tried a complete check of the local files, but it doesn’t work, I find that regretable, because I really wanted to visit this place before disaster. Well, I hope someone will read me and help me solve the problem (This is a message from an English-French translator, so sorry for the many mistakes if any)</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/black-mesa-we-ve-got-hostile-pre-disaster/63323/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/black-mesa-we-ve-got-hostile-pre-disaster/63323/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jun 2020 12:35:01 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-63323-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/black-mesa-we-ve-got-hostile-pre-disaster/63323.rss">Black mesa We-ve got hostile pre disaster</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
