<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Fallout: New Vegas</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/fallout-new-vegas/2929</link>
    <description>The trailer for &quot;Fallout: New Vegas&quot; has been released a few days ago.
[url]https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=epFupigyIN8[/url]
Yes, I did in fact came.

Oh, and here&#39;s some shit from some magazine:
[url=https://img268.imageshack.us/i/7n4fdz.jpg/][img]https://img268.imageshack.us/img268/9591/7n4fdz.jpg[/img][/url]
[url=https://img694.imageshack.us/i/bx50uc.jpg/][img]https://img694.imageshack.us/img694/5984/bx50uc.jpg[/img][/url]
[url=https://img694.imageshack.us/i/wknbhz.jpg/][img]https://img694.imageshack.us/img694/8019/wknbhz.jpg[/img][/url]
[url=https://img130.imageshack.us/i/pnb5dh.jpg/][img]https://img130.imageshack.us/img130/4869/pnb5dh.jpg[/img][/url]
[url=https://img130.imageshack.us/i/xco6g2.jpg/][img]https://img130.imageshack.us/img130/6631/xco6g2.jpg[/img][/url]
[url=https://img59.imageshack.us/i/7k5cpv.jpg/][img]https://img59.imageshack.us/img59/9997/7k5cpv.jpg[/img][/url]
[url=https://img59.imageshack.us/i/fzkqs2.jpg/][img]https://img59.imageshack.us/img59/2300/fzkqs2.jpg[/img][/url]

Details from this article:

# There is an optional hardcore mode, the character needs to drink water, ammo has weight, healing isn&#39;t instant etc.

# Normal mode is more similar to Fallout 3 gameplay.

# The storyline is focused on the New California Republic vs. Caesar&#39;s Legion (slavers from the east) vs. New Vegas residents.

# You are not a vault dweller but are given a Pip-Boy by someone who is one.

# There is a screenshot of a vault suit as well.

# There is an assault rifle looking like the M4, as well as a new big gun with a backpack, held like a minigun.

# There are special moves for melee weapons in VATS - specifically a move for a golf club called &quot;Fore&quot; which seems to be a groin shot.

# The Hoover Dam is in the game and is supplying electricity to the city.

# There is a quest to rescue a ghoul from some super mutants. The ghoul can then become your companion

# The Geckos are back.

# There are both dumb and intelligent super mutants, including the elite Nightkin. On at least one occasion you can convince them to fight amongst themselves.

# Some super mutants look similar to the ones in Fallout 3, while others are new. There is e.g. a female super mutant with a 1950s hairstyle who apparently is one of their leaders.

# Screenshots include a guy with a beard and straw hat, a ghoul and an NCR Ranger.

# The only picture of New Vegas itself is concept art and not a screenshot.

# Some location screenshots include a huge model dinosaur advertising a hotel, some satellite dishes, an array of solar panels

# A character generation shot showing a &quot;vigour machine&quot; instead of the skill book

# NCR base is the McCarran Airport, Caesar&#39;s Legion is based in the Vegas Strip, while super mutants are based in a place called Black Mountain.

# There is also a town called Fremont and another called Primm. A topless reuve is mentioned as being in the latter. Area 51 also appears.

# NCR Ranger armor is similar to a brown combat armor with sleeves, there are concept arts of a Ranger.

# Skils have a bigger effect on conversation choices. E.g. someone with a high Explosives skill may be able to have a coversation about explosives where appropriate.

# There is a Reputation system in addition to Karma.

# First-person action RPG with the same engine as Fallout 3.

# Set in the Mojave wastelands. Vegas didn&#39;t get many nukes. More intact buildings, as well as desert vegetation. Vegas itself is mostly intact.

# Both karma and reputation are tracked. If I&#39;m reading it right there&#39;s separate reputations for each of the settlements, as in 1 and 2.

# All dialogue options are shown to all players, regardless of whether you have the stats to succeed or not, though there&#39;s no punishment for failure.

# Bartering is not just lower prices but negotiating for better rewards.

# Weapons also now have knock-back upon death, with shotguns sending people flying.

# Followers can be managed through a context-sensitive menu, with orders like &quot;follow&quot;, &quot;stay&quot; or &quot;attack&quot;.

# You&#39;re a courier, wounded and left for dead in a shallow grave. A friendly robot, Victor, digs you out, and his doctor owner Mitchell patches you up. You take a &quot;vigour test&quot;, which is some sort of electric parlour game. This decides who you are and sets up SPECIAL. You can also take some Rorschach tests, but the mag says this is for fun. The Doc then gives you a Pipboy as he was once a Vault dweller.

# &quot;Hoover Dam&quot;, and &quot;Helios&quot; (a solar plant, confirmed by the mag to have been built by Poseidon) are fought into and then you can direct the power to wherever you choose. In the case of Helios you can also keep the plant for your self, use the energy to call down a powerful laser, or even try to distribute to all equally, however there is a risk of overloading the reactors.

# There is a &quot;reputation system&quot;, in which all three factions (NCR, Ceasar&#39;s Legion and the locals) will either see you as good or bad toward them individually.

# There is a screenshot of three Capital Wasteland mutants running toward the player, who is wielding what *looks* to be a heavy incinerator, but has a TV screen and no flamer fuel tanks. He&#39;s also wearing NCR combat armour, which is in gold/mustard colours.

# There are two separate screens of supermutants that look to be more local, grey skin, and the two are wearing very different clothes. One is Tabitha, who is hearing a blonde wig and love heart glasses. The mag implies she&#39;s &quot;not all there&quot;.

# On that quest, you rescue Raul, a ghoul who Tabitha kept alive to fix her favourite robot. He appears to be a follower, as the mag says you can give him items, and also commands, such as &quot;stay, follow or attack&quot;, and also tell him to switch to melee, in which case he&#39;ll mutter &quot;sure, I&#39;ll put away my rather effective gun, and switch to this piece of um, metal tubing here&quot;.

# From what I read, the &quot;all dialog&quot; thing seems to imply there will be failures for skill checks as well as speech checks, though, as the mag states, there is no penalty for failing a skill check. In fact, the mag gives an example: A woman who the player tried a Sneak skill attempt on in conversation failed when convincing her an ambush would help the town be rid of a gang of raiders. She simply says &quot;Good luck with your, uh, ambush&quot;

# Vault 21 is in the game

So yeah, it looks awesome. Discuss.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 17 Jun 2010 23:05:52 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Technology and Gaming</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/fallout-new-vegas/2929.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Fallout: New Vegas</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[_amp_955_dam]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Simple humour. I like it.</p>
<p>That’s what the Fallout 3 beta actually looked like.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/fallout-new-vegas/2929/116">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/fallout-new-vegas/2929/116</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jun 2010 23:05:52 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2929-116</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/fallout-new-vegas/2929.rss">Fallout: New Vegas</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Fallout: New Vegas</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Savant]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><span alt="" class="broken-image" title="This image is broken"><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-unlink svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#unlink"></use></svg></span><br>
^needs more humour like this</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/fallout-new-vegas/2929/115">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/fallout-new-vegas/2929/115</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jun 2010 22:10:13 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2929-115</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/fallout-new-vegas/2929.rss">Fallout: New Vegas</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Fallout: New Vegas</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[DansonDelta40]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="baconeggs">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/b/43a26b/40.png" class="avatar"> baconeggs:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I’ll also be interesting to find out more about Fallout’s America outside of the capital. (I never got into the orginal games so my knowledge of the lore is a bit limited)</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p><a href="https://fallout.wikia.com/wiki/Fallout_Wiki" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">FYI: The Fallout wiki</a></p>
<p>You might wanna check it out, then. It’s worth a read.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Savant">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/s/9fc348/40.png" class="avatar"> Savant:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>It looks, but damn, the strip needs more detail</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>It’s all work in progress, everything shown in the video. Sawyer also talks about the ironsights not being the final version of what it will look like. There’s still a lot of fine tuning to be done, and details will be added doubtlessly.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/fallout-new-vegas/2929/114">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/fallout-new-vegas/2929/114</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jun 2010 21:59:15 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2929-114</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/fallout-new-vegas/2929.rss">Fallout: New Vegas</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Fallout: New Vegas</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Surplus]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="vivanto">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/v/ecd19e/40.png" class="avatar"> vivanto:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Anyone know if it’ll be moddable just like Fo3?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>yes</p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>Or better yet, if they improved anything on their scripting language?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>idk</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/fallout-new-vegas/2929/113">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/fallout-new-vegas/2929/113</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jun 2010 17:40:46 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2929-113</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/fallout-new-vegas/2929.rss">Fallout: New Vegas</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Fallout: New Vegas</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[vivanto]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Anyone know if it’ll be moddable just like Fo3? Or better yet, if they improved anything on their scripting language?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/fallout-new-vegas/2929/112">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/fallout-new-vegas/2929/112</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jun 2010 17:32:16 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2929-112</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/fallout-new-vegas/2929.rss">Fallout: New Vegas</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Fallout: New Vegas</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[eternalness]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>GET OUT OF HERE STALKER!!!</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/fallout-new-vegas/2929/111">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/fallout-new-vegas/2929/111</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jun 2010 17:08:11 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2929-111</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/fallout-new-vegas/2929.rss">Fallout: New Vegas</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Fallout: New Vegas</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Someonerandm]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Hey, i just noticed hardcore mode sound like a normal game of STALKER.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/fallout-new-vegas/2929/110">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/fallout-new-vegas/2929/110</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jun 2010 16:27:13 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2929-110</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/fallout-new-vegas/2929.rss">Fallout: New Vegas</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Fallout: New Vegas</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypt]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I’m really looking forward to this game. One of the few games that I’m actually interested in before the release. Not to fond of not being a Vault dweler though, and I hope the speech system is improved, along with the facial expressions… Sad that a game from 2004 has better facial expressions and lip synching than most games from more recent times</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/fallout-new-vegas/2929/109">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/fallout-new-vegas/2929/109</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jun 2010 15:31:56 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2929-109</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/fallout-new-vegas/2929.rss">Fallout: New Vegas</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Fallout: New Vegas</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Savant]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>It looks, but damn, the strip needs more detail</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/fallout-new-vegas/2929/108">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/fallout-new-vegas/2929/108</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jun 2010 12:08:59 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2929-108</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/fallout-new-vegas/2929.rss">Fallout: New Vegas</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Fallout: New Vegas</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[baconeggs]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Hmmmm, Post-War Vegas kinda looks like The Bar from STALKER, with the whole raggedy metropolis springing out of a wasteland idea. Good to see that they’ve kept the style from F3 while giving it a new flavour and improvements. It’ll also be interesting to find out more about Fallout’s America outside of the capital. (I never got into the orginal games so my knowledge of the lore is a bit limited)</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/fallout-new-vegas/2929/107">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/fallout-new-vegas/2929/107</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jun 2010 11:41:14 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2929-107</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/fallout-new-vegas/2929.rss">Fallout: New Vegas</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Fallout: New Vegas</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[DansonDelta40]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><a href="https://www.fallout-game.de/content/view/283/1/" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">12 minutes of NV Gameplay with Josh Sawyer</a></p>
<p>Enjoy, folks! It’s got ironsights, craftable ammo and way better gun sounds this time. Wohoo!</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/fallout-new-vegas/2929/106">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/fallout-new-vegas/2929/106</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jun 2010 11:30:48 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2929-106</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/fallout-new-vegas/2929.rss">Fallout: New Vegas</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Fallout: New Vegas</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Aaron]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I pre-ordered Fallout New Vegas’s Collectors Edition.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/fallout-new-vegas/2929/105">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/fallout-new-vegas/2929/105</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 09 Jun 2010 15:37:38 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2929-105</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/fallout-new-vegas/2929.rss">Fallout: New Vegas</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Fallout: New Vegas</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Savant]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I really hopes this fallout returns to the ol’ good humour and comedy of Fallout 1 and 2</p>
<p>And as for the gameplay/replayability, I demand awesome</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/fallout-new-vegas/2929/104">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/fallout-new-vegas/2929/104</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 09 Jun 2010 15:30:28 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2929-104</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/fallout-new-vegas/2929.rss">Fallout: New Vegas</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Fallout: New Vegas</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Medevilae]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Maxey">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/user_avatar/leakfree.org/maxey/40/4358_2.png" class="avatar"> Maxey:</div>
<blockquote>
<p><a href="https://www.vg247.com/2010/06/09/fallout-new-vegas-to-include-steamworks-drm/" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://www.vg247.com/2010/06/09/fallout-new-vegas-to-include-steamworks-drm/</a></p>
<p>Fallout: New Vegas to ditch Games for Windows Live and use Steamworks instead.</p>
<p>This game is sounding more and more awesome everyday.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>OH MY GOD THANK YOU.</p>
<p>I DESPISE Microsoft trying to compete with Steam, because it usually ends up that in order to use Steam AND GFWL, developers are forced to put GFWL’s shitty in-game-xbox-esque overlay that forces you to get a GFWL account and any time there is an update you HAVE to download it WHEN it is released or you can’t use your game, and… Well the list goes on, really. Not to mention their downloadable client is a ripoff of Steam in xbox colors.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/fallout-new-vegas/2929/103">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/fallout-new-vegas/2929/103</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 09 Jun 2010 14:53:29 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2929-103</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/fallout-new-vegas/2929.rss">Fallout: New Vegas</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Fallout: New Vegas</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Maxey]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><a href="https://www.vg247.com/2010/06/09/fallout-new-vegas-to-include-steamworks-drm/" data-bbcode="true">https://www.vg247.com/2010/06/09/fallout-new-vegas-to-include-steamworks-drm/</a></p>
<p>Fallout: New Vegas to ditch Games for Windows Live and use Steamworks instead.</p>
<p>This game is sounding more and more awesome everyday.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/fallout-new-vegas/2929/102">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/fallout-new-vegas/2929/102</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 09 Jun 2010 14:17:14 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2929-102</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/fallout-new-vegas/2929.rss">Fallout: New Vegas</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Fallout: New Vegas</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Bmsmg]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Yup. Fuckin’ WIN.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/fallout-new-vegas/2929/101">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/fallout-new-vegas/2929/101</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 18 Mar 2010 09:03:40 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2929-101</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/fallout-new-vegas/2929.rss">Fallout: New Vegas</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Fallout: New Vegas</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Nerdinium]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>isn’t that basically like the incinerator from Fallout 3 but instead it just fires grenades and not balls of a partially unlit mix of napalm and other petrol based liquid ?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/fallout-new-vegas/2929/100">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/fallout-new-vegas/2929/100</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 17 Mar 2010 20:48:55 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2929-100</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/fallout-new-vegas/2929.rss">Fallout: New Vegas</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Fallout: New Vegas</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Apollomasque]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>It has a machine gun grenade launcher.<br>
Nuff said.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/fallout-new-vegas/2929/99">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/fallout-new-vegas/2929/99</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 17 Mar 2010 20:45:17 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2929-99</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/fallout-new-vegas/2929.rss">Fallout: New Vegas</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Fallout: New Vegas</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Nerdinium]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>well , if you loved Fallout 3 , then you’d love New Vegas , after all - it IS built with essentially the same engine</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/fallout-new-vegas/2929/98">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/fallout-new-vegas/2929/98</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 17 Mar 2010 19:10:19 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2929-98</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/fallout-new-vegas/2929.rss">Fallout: New Vegas</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Fallout: New Vegas</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Bmsmg]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Nerdinium">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/n/779978/40.png" class="avatar"> Nerdinium:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>i must say , the slugishness of the game was very irritable and also the fact that they didnt make animations for the player to climb over rocks or other objects and just left it jumping over them which felt really unnatural , and also that you sometimes “piled” up a few actions for the character to execute and you had to wait to bring up your pip-boy if you wanted to change something , that was really aggravating</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>^this^<br>
I love fallout 3. Yes, it has glitches, but that’s why we have mods.<br>
I’m torn over whether to buy the earlier fallouts. They look good, but it’s all point and click. Whats worse is that it’s forced third-person.</p>
<p>Unless it’s crucial (as in prototype or just cause 2) I will not buy a game with third person. It just ruins it.</p>
<p>On the other hand, new vegas looks incredible. Can’t wait to get it.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/fallout-new-vegas/2929/97">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/fallout-new-vegas/2929/97</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 17 Mar 2010 00:55:34 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2929-97</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/fallout-new-vegas/2929.rss">Fallout: New Vegas</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Fallout: New Vegas</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Nerdinium]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>i must say , the slugishness of the game was very irritable and also the fact that they didnt make animations for the player to climb over rocks or other objects and just left it jumping over them which felt really unnatural , and also that you sometimes “piled” up a few actions for the character to execute and you had to wait to bring up your pip-boy if you wanted to change something , that was really aggravating</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/fallout-new-vegas/2929/96">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/fallout-new-vegas/2929/96</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 16 Mar 2010 18:26:09 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2929-96</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/fallout-new-vegas/2929.rss">Fallout: New Vegas</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Fallout: New Vegas</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Geeba]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Must admit VATS wasnt good… real time it was AWESOME! top game I played all the DLC too…</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/fallout-new-vegas/2929/95">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/fallout-new-vegas/2929/95</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 16 Mar 2010 15:03:59 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2929-95</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/fallout-new-vegas/2929.rss">Fallout: New Vegas</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Fallout: New Vegas</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[trance]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Turn based is crap.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/fallout-new-vegas/2929/94">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/fallout-new-vegas/2929/94</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 16 Mar 2010 14:35:16 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2929-94</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/fallout-new-vegas/2929.rss">Fallout: New Vegas</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Fallout: New Vegas</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Grey_Area]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Someonerandm">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/s/d78d45/40.png" class="avatar"> Someonerandm:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I think the combat was slow, personally. VATS makes it pretty much turn-based, minus the strategy.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Hmm, let me see.<br>
Fallout 1. Turn Based Combat.<br>
Fallout 2. Turn Based Combat.<br>
Fallout Tactics. Real Time or Turn Based Combat.</p>
<p>Bethesda would have been insane not to include some form of turn based combat as a nod to all the Fallout fans from way back. But they gave you the choice. I played F3 using both the VATS and just real time combat. Was fine. The game is a first person RPG and not just a straight shooter.</p>
<p>The movement reminded me much more of games like Battlefield Vietnam where they were going for a sense of realism over fast run and gun.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/fallout-new-vegas/2929/93">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/fallout-new-vegas/2929/93</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 16 Mar 2010 08:40:36 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2929-93</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/fallout-new-vegas/2929.rss">Fallout: New Vegas</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Fallout: New Vegas</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Someonerandm]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I think the combat was slow, personally. VATS makes it pretty much turn-based, minus the strategy.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/fallout-new-vegas/2929/92">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/fallout-new-vegas/2929/92</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 16 Mar 2010 05:34:31 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2929-92</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/fallout-new-vegas/2929.rss">Fallout: New Vegas</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
