<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Map bm_c3a1b will not load</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/map-bm-c3a1b-will-not-load/11318</link>
    <description>I haven&#39;t found this one yet in the 44+ pages of bugs noted here so far nor in the off-site bug tracker...

====================

While climbing up the manhole ladder at the end of map bm_c3a1a, the next map -- bm_c3a1b -- will not load.  The screen holds at the &quot;Loading...&quot; background and locks-up the computer (ctrl-alt-del is rendered inoperative), forcing me to cold reboot the system.

Starting fresh at the game&#39;s menu screen, it also fails to load using the developer&#39;s console (typing &quot;map bm_c3a1b&quot;) -- the system hangs the same as described above as if I were playing the game.  I can manually load the maps on either &#39;side&#39; from the console (bm_c3a1a &amp; bm_c3b1a), so it appears to be something with that particular map.

I&#39;ve reinstalled the game a second time, and even downloaded the install files a second time from a different mirror site; even though the MD5 checksum for the 7z download passed, it&#39;s still a &quot;no go.&quot;

There is no mdump file generated for this problem.  Here is the information about the map size, but unlike others who have had similar load problems, the map seems to be about the same size as the others:

bm_c3a1b.bsp = 40.3 MB (42,261,692 bytes)

Here are my computer specs:
(Please note that I am fully prepared for the laughter, scorn and derision that will certainly result.)

====================

CPU: Intel Pentium 4 / 2.4 GHz (from early 2002)
RAM: 2 GB SDRAM DDR 333 PC2700 DIMM (two 1 GB chipsets)
OS: Windows XP Home Edition v2002 SP3
GPU: 128 MB DDR PNY nVidia GeForce FX 5500 (Direct X 9 compatible)

Black Mesa -- Software Mode: Direct X 8.0
* Forcing Direct X 9.0 results in gameplay that&#39;s too slow

(I know, I know: Get a computer that&#39;s _NOT_ from the turn of the century...)

====================

Aside from the unsupported Direct X 8.0/8.1 issues that others have noted elsewhere, this map loading error is the first major problem I&#39;ve encountered so far.  I&#39;ve made it to the Teleportation Labs last night after noclipping through some of the underwater coolant areas in the Lamba Complex.

Even when models and textures are set to &#39;High&#39; (which are their recommended settings), the gameplay is remarkably fluid most of the time for such an old machine, although I&#39;ve intentionally set several other enhancements lower than their recommended settings so as to not &quot;push my luck.&quot;

Thank you for your time, and even more for your wonderful Mod -- it takes me back to 1998 again...</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2012 16:34:46 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>In-game Issues (Mod)</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/map-bm-c3a1b-will-not-load/11318.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Map bm_c3a1b will not load</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Chuck_Finley]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="sersoft">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/user_avatar/leakfree.org/sersoft/40/5837_2.png" class="avatar"> sersoft:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>The 5500 is not bad for it’s age but I am thinking that particular level requires a CPU instruction set that’s not available on NetBurst cores.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Thanks for the information, Sersoft.  I have other AGP video cards, but they are all older, so that won’t help…</p>
<p>And sorry to hear you are having similar problems, Yuri.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/map-bm-c3a1b-will-not-load/11318/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/map-bm-c3a1b-will-not-load/11318/4</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2012 16:34:46 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11318-4</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/map-bm-c3a1b-will-not-load/11318.rss">Map bm_c3a1b will not load</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Map bm_c3a1b will not load</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[sersoft]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>The 5500 is not bad for it’s age but I am thinking that particular level requires a CPU instruction set that’s not available on NetBurst cores.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/map-bm-c3a1b-will-not-load/11318/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/map-bm-c3a1b-will-not-load/11318/3</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 04 Oct 2012 22:01:27 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11318-3</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/map-bm-c3a1b-will-not-load/11318.rss">Map bm_c3a1b will not load</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Map bm_c3a1b will not load</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Yuri_kalashnikov]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I’ve posted another post, but now I see there’s another person with the same problem:</p>
<p>I HAVE EXACTLY THE SAME PROBLEM!!!<br>
I’ve done the same as you: reinstalling the game, downloading another time the zip and the map, loading the map in the console etc. I can load the other maps too…</p>
<p>I hate that ladder… surface is so close, but so far :freeman:</p>
<p>I have no solutions, but well, at least I’ve found someone who shares my misfortune  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/smiley.png?v=9" title=":smiley:" class="emoji" alt=":smiley:"></p>
<p>Good Luck!</p>
<p>P.D : I have an old computer too, like yours, and the same GPU… but I’ve made the underwater parts with no cheats (but a lot of luck)</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/map-bm-c3a1b-will-not-load/11318/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/map-bm-c3a1b-will-not-load/11318/2</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 04 Oct 2012 21:35:59 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11318-2</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/map-bm-c3a1b-will-not-load/11318.rss">Map bm_c3a1b will not load</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Map bm_c3a1b will not load</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Chuck_Finley]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I haven’t found this one yet in the 44+ pages of bugs noted here so far nor in the off-site bug tracker…</p>
<p>====================</p>
<p>While climbing up the manhole ladder at the end of map bm_c3a1a, the next map – bm_c3a1b – will not load.  The screen holds at the “Loading…” background and locks-up the computer (ctrl-alt-del is rendered inoperative), forcing me to cold reboot the system.</p>
<p>Starting fresh at the game’s menu screen, it also fails to load using the developer’s console (typing “map bm_c3a1b”) – the system hangs the same as described above as if I were playing the game.  I can manually load the maps on either ‘side’ from the console (bm_c3a1a &amp; bm_c3b1a), so it appears to be something with that particular map.</p>
<p>I’ve reinstalled the game a second time, and even downloaded the install files a second time from a different mirror site; even though the MD5 checksum for the 7z download passed, it’s still a “no go.”</p>
<p>There is no mdump file generated for this problem.  Here is the information about the map size, but unlike others who have had similar load problems, the map seems to be about the same size as the others:</p>
<p>bm_c3a1b.bsp = 40.3 MB (42,261,692 bytes)</p>
<p>Here are my computer specs:<br>
(Please note that I am fully prepared for the laughter, scorn and derision that will certainly result.)</p>
<p>====================</p>
<p>CPU: Intel Pentium 4 / 2.4 GHz (from early 2002)<br>
RAM: 2 GB SDRAM DDR 333 PC2700 DIMM (two 1 GB chipsets)<br>
OS: Windows XP Home Edition v2002 SP3<br>
GPU: 128 MB DDR PNY nVidia GeForce FX 5500 (Direct X 9 compatible)</p>
<p>Black Mesa – Software Mode: Direct X 8.0</p>
<ul>
<li>Forcing Direct X 9.0 results in gameplay that’s too slow</li>
</ul>
<p>(I know, I know: Get a computer that’s <em>NOT</em> from the turn of the century…)</p>
<p>====================</p>
<p>Aside from the unsupported Direct X 8.0/8.1 issues that others have noted elsewhere, this map loading error is the first major problem I’ve encountered so far.  I’ve made it to the Teleportation Labs last night after noclipping through some of the underwater coolant areas in the Lamba Complex.</p>
<p>Even when models and textures are set to ‘High’ (which are their recommended settings), the gameplay is remarkably fluid most of the time for such an old machine, although I’ve intentionally set several other enhancements lower than their recommended settings so as to not “push my luck.”</p>
<p>Thank you for your time, and even more for your wonderful Mod – it takes me back to 1998 again…</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/map-bm-c3a1b-will-not-load/11318/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/map-bm-c3a1b-will-not-load/11318/1</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 04 Oct 2012 12:30:29 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11318-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/map-bm-c3a1b-will-not-load/11318.rss">Map bm_c3a1b will not load</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
