<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>VTFEdit keeps messing up my skins</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/vtfedit-keeps-messing-up-my-skins/13286</link>
    <description>I&#39;m not sure where to post this but I&#39;m getting the classic &quot;texture-made-out-of-shower-curtains&quot; issue when I import a .tga weapon texture to a .vtf file with VTFEdit and view it in BMS. I think this has something to do with VTFEdit&#39;s import settings or alpha channels, but I don&#39;t know how to fix it. Even if I turn all phong etc. values to 0 in the .vmt file it still looks shinier than the default skin. Does anybody know how to get rid of this?

(With VTFEdit&#39;s settings I mean the ones that say alpha format, normal format etc and where you have to pick between different formats when importing.)</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2014 07:14:58 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Help and Support</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/vtfedit-keeps-messing-up-my-skins/13286.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>VTFEdit keeps messing up my skins</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[boxbreaker]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I’m not sure where to post this but I’m getting the classic “texture-made-out-of-shower-curtains” issue when I import a .tga weapon texture to a .vtf file with VTFEdit and view it in BMS. I think this has something to do with VTFEdit’s import settings or alpha channels, but I don’t know how to fix it. Even if I turn all phong etc. values to 0 in the .vmt file it still looks shinier than the default skin. Does anybody know how to get rid of this?</p>
<p>(With VTFEdit’s settings I mean the ones that say alpha format, normal format etc and where you have to pick between different formats when importing.)</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/vtfedit-keeps-messing-up-my-skins/13286/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/vtfedit-keeps-messing-up-my-skins/13286/1</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2014 07:14:58 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13286-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/vtfedit-keeps-messing-up-my-skins/13286.rss">VTFEdit keeps messing up my skins</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
