<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Resource for PC and Video Game Enthusiasts</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/resource-for-pc-and-video-game-enthusiasts/14426</link>
    <description>Hey all.

I&#39;m not sure this is allowed here (if not, I sincerely apologize and will humbly bow out of this thread), but I&#39;ve developed a website that I hope will come to be a valuable resource for PC and video gaming enthusiasts.

That said, 90% of the content on the website is going to be user-generated articles, reviews, tech guides, and so forth. However, unlike sites like Metacritic where anyone can upload pretty much anything, I plan on editing and formatting each article to at least give it the appearance of a professional article (content aside).

With that in mind, I figured this would be a great place to have folks submit their content, as I&#39;m sure a large majority of you are into PC gaming at the very least.

If you want to contribute or just check it out: [url=&#39;https://www.pcbattlestation.com&#39;]PCBattleStation[/url]. At the very least, I suggest signing up for the forums and entering the giveaway contest--just post a pic of your computer rig/battle station.

Thanks!</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 30 Sep 2015 00:48:34 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Show Off</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/resource-for-pc-and-video-game-enthusiasts/14426.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Resource for PC and Video Game Enthusiasts</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Gunsrequiem]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Hey all.</p>
<p>I’m not sure this is allowed here (if not, I sincerely apologize and will humbly bow out of this thread), but I’ve developed a website that I hope will come to be a valuable resource for PC and video gaming enthusiasts.</p>
<p>That said, 90% of the content on the website is going to be user-generated articles, reviews, tech guides, and so forth. However, unlike sites like Metacritic where anyone can upload pretty much anything, I plan on editing and formatting each article to at least give it the appearance of a professional article (content aside).</p>
<p>With that in mind, I figured this would be a great place to have folks submit their content, as I’m sure a large majority of you are into PC gaming at the very least.</p>
<p>If you want to contribute or just check it out: <a href="https://www.pcbattlestation.com" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">PCBattleStation</a>. At the very least, I suggest signing up for the forums and entering the giveaway contest–just post a pic of your computer rig/battle station.</p>
<p>Thanks!</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/resource-for-pc-and-video-game-enthusiasts/14426/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/resource-for-pc-and-video-game-enthusiasts/14426/1</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 30 Sep 2015 00:48:34 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14426-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/resource-for-pc-and-video-game-enthusiasts/14426.rss">Resource for PC and Video Game Enthusiasts</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
