<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>I can&#39;t select my weapon.</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/i-cant-select-my-weapon/14269</link>
    <description>I&#39;m sorry to bother, but I cannot fully &quot;select&quot; a weapon. I can switch between them, but there seems to be no rhyme or reason. There is no HUD for the weapons and weapons only. I&#39;m not sure if it&#39;s an addon I installed because I&#39;ve checked &#39;em all and none of the descriptions say anything of the sort. I&#39;m not sure if it&#39;s a glitch, or if I just should verify game cache and delete local content and take the SAVES folder out and put it back in. I am extremely stuck and it is freakin&#39; annoying to use this idiotic weapon switch (Please GaBeN have it not be put in by the actual developers)</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 30 Jun 2015 03:24:24 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Help!</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/i-cant-select-my-weapon/14269.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>I can&#39;t select my weapon.</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Sage_J_Fox]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Did you tick on Fast Weapon Switch in the options?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/i-cant-select-my-weapon/14269/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/i-cant-select-my-weapon/14269/2</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 30 Jun 2015 03:24:24 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14269-2</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/i-cant-select-my-weapon/14269.rss">I can&#39;t select my weapon.</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>I can&#39;t select my weapon.</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Thefunny711]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I’m sorry to bother, but I cannot fully “select” a weapon. I can switch between them, but there seems to be no rhyme or reason. There is no HUD for the weapons and weapons only. I’m not sure if it’s an addon I installed because I’ve checked ‘em all and none of the descriptions say anything of the sort. I’m not sure if it’s a glitch, or if I just should verify game cache and delete local content and take the SAVES folder out and put it back in. I am extremely stuck and it is freakin’ annoying to use this idiotic weapon switch (Please GaBeN have it not be put in by the actual developers)</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/i-cant-select-my-weapon/14269/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/i-cant-select-my-weapon/14269/1</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jun 2015 23:54:53 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14269-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/i-cant-select-my-weapon/14269.rss">I can&#39;t select my weapon.</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
