<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>web-server kinda problem</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/web-server-kinda-problem/13291</link>
    <description>hey guys, I&#39;ve a problem with a web server and hope you may be able to help me out.

First of all, I&#39;m a total newbie regarding these things and don&#39;t really look behind all of this yet. We&#39;ve taken over a old webspace, where the CMS is Joomla 1.5.2.6 (yes, I know, pretty old) and got the data for administrator access (only for joomla it seems). I wanted to upload another template and also other media like other pictures etc. First I tried it via the Browser-Interface of Joomla but had seemingly no access (directory rights said all were write-protected), so I tried uploading it via SFTP (FileZilla) but permission was also denied (I could connect to the server though). Then I tried resetting the directory rights via file zilla to 755 but that didn&#39;t work either (permission denied as well).
Google led me to many 404 sites or some who didn&#39;t help me at all, howevs there were mentioned some terms like wwwrun problem and if php-connection is cgi or apache but I&#39;m not quite sure how to take on those terms or in what relation to my problems they are (as I already said, I have NO idea about setting up / managing / maintaining a web server, the FTP itself, php and so on) and right now I&#39;m totally like [img]https://mlkshk.com/r/97VP[/img]

Maybe I&#39;m just too stupid or haven&#39;t read me into this topic so well yet, so please forgive my lack of common net knowledge  :stuck_out_tongue: 

More information via pn as I&#39;m not too keen on letting out too much information to people to fuck with afterwards</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2014 16:58:17 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Help and Support</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/web-server-kinda-problem/13291.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>web-server kinda problem</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[yrr]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>ok, no reply after 3 days and I already got help, so @ mods \close thread plz</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/web-server-kinda-problem/13291/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/web-server-kinda-problem/13291/2</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2014 16:58:17 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13291-2</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/web-server-kinda-problem/13291.rss">web-server kinda problem</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>web-server kinda problem</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[yrr]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>hey guys, I’ve a problem with a web server and hope you may be able to help me out.</p>
<p>First of all, I’m a total newbie regarding these things and don’t really look behind all of this yet. We’ve taken over a old webspace, where the CMS is Joomla 1.5.2.6 (yes, I know, pretty old) and got the data for administrator access (only for joomla it seems). I wanted to upload another template and also other media like other pictures etc. First I tried it via the Browser-Interface of Joomla but had seemingly no access (directory rights said all were write-protected), so I tried uploading it via SFTP (FileZilla) but permission was also denied (I could connect to the server though). Then I tried resetting the directory rights via file zilla to 755 but that didn’t work either (permission denied as well).<br>
Google led me to many 404 sites or some who didn’t help me at all, howevs there were mentioned some terms like wwwrun problem and if php-connection is cgi or apache but I’m not quite sure how to take on those terms or in what relation to my problems they are (as I already said, I have NO idea about setting up / managing / maintaining a web server, the FTP itself, php and so on) and right now I’m totally like <span alt="" class="broken-image" title="This image is broken"><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-unlink svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#unlink"></use></svg></span></p>
<p>Maybe I’m just too stupid or haven’t read me into this topic so well yet, so please forgive my lack of common net knowledge  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=9" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"></p>
<p>More information via pn as I’m not too keen on letting out too much information to people to fuck with afterwards</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/web-server-kinda-problem/13291/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/web-server-kinda-problem/13291/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 08 Jun 2014 22:21:26 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13291-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/web-server-kinda-problem/13291.rss">web-server kinda problem</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
