<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>On Philosophy, Religion, and Genocide.</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/on-philosophy-religion-and-genocide/13093</link>
    <description>Dragging this little gem out of the Rage topic, to continue this discussion until it is probably just me and Bur tossing paragraphs at each other, as per usual.  :stuck_out_tongue: 

Rules of this thread:

1. We are all still friends at the end of the day.

2. No throwing of Bibles, Quran&#39;s, Tipitaka&#39;s or lab equipment.



To catch up anyone too lazy to read the other thread, it started with some pro-white genocide comments, and I made a comment on all the religious and atheistic implications of white genocide specifically, and the topic grew into a monster, so, to continue:
[quote=&quot;bur&quot;]
euhm no, if you hold to the evolution theory without higher power, any genocide is equally disastrous to the survival of the species. There is no reason why Europeans or Asians would be a better choice, not even because there are many of them or because they currently have great material wealth. Genetically, the distinction is arbitrary.
If anything, killing all Europeans or all Asians would free up more resources for the rest than any other &quot;race&quot;. Which is what Ramirezoid was getting at, I think.
[/quote]
I do not think this would be true. If everything is simply a mechanical entity with no other force behind it save the same physics that hurl asteroids through space and burn stars, if your intended goal is to keep such entities replicating, you would naturally use strains that have proven traits of high adaptability, though I agree culling any other races generally would come with more cons than pros.
[quote=&quot;bur&quot;]
It&#39;s also pretty much impossible to use &quot;race&quot; with any sort of accuracy, since superficial differences don&#39;t necessarily speak to genetic ones.
A white dude could be more closely related to some black dude than some other white dude, and vice versa. Or not. There&#39;s no way to know unless you do DNA testing, and even then it&#39;s subject to interpretation and error.
[/quote]
This sounds like you are measuring humans with a different scale than common animals. Pitbulls tend to be more violent, Greyhounds tend to be faster, Pomeranians tend to be more noisy, etc. As noted, they are all dogs, yet they all show physical as well as mental differences within each breed/race/strain. It is impossible for someone to be atheistic, believe in evolution and not believe in racial superiority in one form or another (by this I mean: Whites are superior in X, blacks are superior in Y, etc). It&#39;s one of the fundamental laws governing evolutionary theory.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 08 May 2014 22:53:48 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Off Topic</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/on-philosophy-religion-and-genocide/13093.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>On Philosophy, Religion, and Genocide.</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[bur]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>i dont think criminalizing natural behaviour has ever done anything good</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/on-philosophy-religion-and-genocide/13093/113">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/on-philosophy-religion-and-genocide/13093/113</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2014 22:53:48 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13093-113</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/on-philosophy-religion-and-genocide/13093.rss">On Philosophy, Religion, and Genocide.</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>On Philosophy, Religion, and Genocide.</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Chickenprotector]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Reviving the thread for this <a href="https://news.yahoo.com/california-city-aims-fight-bullying-criminalizing-022310216.html" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">thought provoking article I read.</a></p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Yahoo article By Alex Dobuzinskis">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Yahoo article By Alex Dobuzinskis:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>LOS ANGELES (Reuters) - A southern California city aims to fight back at bullies by making it a crime to pick on others, in a measure that would protect not only school children but anyone up to age 25 who is targeted for harassment.</p>
<p>City leaders in Carson, a suburb of Los Angeles, are poised to become among the first municipalities in the nation to make bullying a crime by treating it as an infraction or a misdemeanor, which are offenses less serious than a felony.</p>
<p>Carson Mayor Jim Dear said he expects the measure could be challenged in court but said he supports it.</p>
<p>“We’re not talking about putting a 5-year-old in jail, we’re talking about intervening in both the bully’s life, who is a person who is hurting too, and the victim’s life,” Dear said.</p>
<p>The Carson city council voted 5-0 on Tuesday to move forward with the anti-bullying ordinance, which needs to come back for a final vote on May 20. The text of the measure says it is modeled on a similar ordinance in Monona, Wisconsin.</p>
<p>Carson, a city of about 93,000 residents, contracts with the Los Angeles County Sheriff’s Department for policing, and the measure would call on sheriff’s deputies to enforce the ordinance. The measure defines bullying as “a willful course of conduct which involves harassment of a person(s) from kindergarten through age 25.”</p>
<p>The measure covers physical and verbal actions, as well as so-called cyberbullying.</p>
<p>It would require the parent of a suspected bully to attend a juvenile court hearing and hold parents partly responsible for actions of their children, Dear said.</p>
<p>Time in custody would not always be administered to children and young adults found to have committed bullying, and counseling and therapy would be part of the solution, he said.</p>
<p>But Brendan Hamme, staff attorney for the American Civil Liberties Union of Southern California, said the measure is too vague and does not even spell out how much jail time an offender could potentially face, although in California a misdemeanor crime can carry a maximum sentence of a year in jail.</p>
<p>Ross Ellis, founder and CEO of New York-based Stomp Out Bullying, said the measure appears to go too far.</p>
<p>“Do you want someone to go to jail if they’re calling someone a name?” Ellis said.</p>
<p>(Reporting by Alex Dobuzinskis; Editing by Ken Wills)</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Thoughts?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/on-philosophy-religion-and-genocide/13093/112">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/on-philosophy-religion-and-genocide/13093/112</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2014 16:34:43 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13093-112</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/on-philosophy-religion-and-genocide/13093.rss">On Philosophy, Religion, and Genocide.</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>On Philosophy, Religion, and Genocide.</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[GilCMassey]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>It’s my opinion that religions simply act as a way to convey the morality that is best for everyone’s sake. However, morality exists just as well without a God or Goddess to threaten others with punishment for not acting in a moral way.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/on-philosophy-religion-and-genocide/13093/111">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/on-philosophy-religion-and-genocide/13093/111</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2014 23:59:25 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13093-111</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/on-philosophy-religion-and-genocide/13093.rss">On Philosophy, Religion, and Genocide.</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>On Philosophy, Religion, and Genocide.</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[CatzEyes93]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Pyro">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/p/71e660/40.png" class="avatar"> Pyro:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Here’s a nice question to argue over, that I’ve seen crop up in a few places lately:</p>
<p>Is religion necessary to have an objective sense of morality? Can we determine any system of morals from a purely scientific viewpoint?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Absolutely not! Animals act on instinct regardless of whether it is moral or not. They are driven as a species to act a certain way usually as a means to ensure their own survival. But humans act on selfish/unselfish ideas regardless of whter it will ensure their own survival. As a result of their superior intellect, humans seem to be more about growth and expanding beyond what we were in the past and it think a moral code is reflected in that growth.</p>
<p>Recognizing a higher being is beside the point of a moral code.</p>
<p>At least that is my take on it.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/on-philosophy-religion-and-genocide/13093/110">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/on-philosophy-religion-and-genocide/13093/110</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 13 Apr 2014 22:39:19 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13093-110</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/on-philosophy-religion-and-genocide/13093.rss">On Philosophy, Religion, and Genocide.</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>On Philosophy, Religion, and Genocide.</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Chickenprotector]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I have a few female friends that I play with regularly and enjoy the company of when they play on the server I putz around on. Funny thing is, some of my closest gamer friends that I would consider “best friends” of mine because we’ve kept in touch even after quitting the title we both played are female.</p>
<p>I guess its too limiting of a topic, why not expand it to the market as a whole, the direction games are going in…</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/on-philosophy-religion-and-genocide/13093/109">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/on-philosophy-religion-and-genocide/13093/109</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 13 Apr 2014 18:42:05 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13093-109</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/on-philosophy-religion-and-genocide/13093.rss">On Philosophy, Religion, and Genocide.</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>On Philosophy, Religion, and Genocide.</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[bur]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>i wouldn’t really call myself a gamer anymore, so i couldnt say, but i had a few female friends on call of duty back in the day, i never really saw any sexism either, but since I’m not a woman that sort of makes sense really</p>
<p>racism and homophobia, yes, plenty</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/on-philosophy-religion-and-genocide/13093/108">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/on-philosophy-religion-and-genocide/13093/108</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 13 Apr 2014 18:12:50 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13093-108</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/on-philosophy-religion-and-genocide/13093.rss">On Philosophy, Religion, and Genocide.</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>On Philosophy, Religion, and Genocide.</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Chickenprotector]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Going to revive this thread with another topic. <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Q65fly5HXQw" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">The latest episode of Foamy the Squirrel covered the topic of “gamer girls.”</a> I personally treat everyone I play with with respect until someone starts acting like a dick (directly at me or toward someone else that I feel is getting harassed too much), regardless of gender, race, etc.</p>
<p>So, my question is: How do you feel about gamer culture as it is currently? Good, bad, terrible? How do you feel about women getting into gaming?</p>
<p>Edit: I forgot to add my opinion. I play with small multiplayer communities. The last LARGE community (1k+ players) I was apart of was Diablo II’s <a href="http://battle.net" rel="nofollow noopener">battle.net</a> when I PvP’d (it was hell usually since they bitched constantly). Fortress Forever has a tiny community, an upwards of, at most, 50 players (if that) - a majority of them are mature enough to keep their fucking mouth shut and don’t constantly bitch. L4D2 has 8 players only and I rarely pub on that game so it’s a non-issue there. I don’t like people who constantly bitch and spout “common” insults (racial slurs and the like) at people and just end up being douche bags. I can stand the common troll who cracks yo mamma jokes constantly for shits and giggles, and isn’t really serious.</p>
<p>I’ve never encountered Sexism in the servers I’ve played in that I can recall, which is kind of odd to me. Thoughts?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/on-philosophy-religion-and-genocide/13093/107">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/on-philosophy-religion-and-genocide/13093/107</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 13 Apr 2014 17:52:39 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13093-107</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/on-philosophy-religion-and-genocide/13093.rss">On Philosophy, Religion, and Genocide.</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>On Philosophy, Religion, and Genocide.</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[papernick]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Already been discussed on the first and second pages of this very thread. E.g:</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="danielsangeo">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/user_avatar/leakfree.org/danielsangeo/40/4347_2.png" class="avatar"> danielsangeo:</div>
<blockquote>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="(rot)(fodder">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 (rot)(fodder:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Without a God, morals have no value, which would put genocide on the same level as walking to the store and buying a piece of fruit</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>This is false.  Absolutely, undeniably, 100% false.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/on-philosophy-religion-and-genocide/13093/106">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/on-philosophy-religion-and-genocide/13093/106</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2014 00:38:42 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13093-106</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/on-philosophy-religion-and-genocide/13093.rss">On Philosophy, Religion, and Genocide.</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>On Philosophy, Religion, and Genocide.</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Pyroclase]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Here’s a nice question to argue over, that I’ve seen crop up in a few places lately:</p>
<p>Is religion necessary to have an objective sense of morality? Can we determine any system of morals from a purely scientific viewpoint?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/on-philosophy-religion-and-genocide/13093/105">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/on-philosophy-religion-and-genocide/13093/105</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2014 00:07:40 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13093-105</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/on-philosophy-religion-and-genocide/13093.rss">On Philosophy, Religion, and Genocide.</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>On Philosophy, Religion, and Genocide.</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[bur]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I guess the current nature of the debate just isn’t as interesting to me personally  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/smiley.png?v=9" title=":smiley:" class="emoji" alt=":smiley:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/on-philosophy-religion-and-genocide/13093/104">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/on-philosophy-religion-and-genocide/13093/104</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2014 15:13:42 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13093-104</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/on-philosophy-religion-and-genocide/13093.rss">On Philosophy, Religion, and Genocide.</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>On Philosophy, Religion, and Genocide.</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Han_Shot_First]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I mean these debates are not necessarily designed to convince the other side, rather it’s an exchange of ideas. These ideas are tested by the other side attempting to debunk it. It’s kind of for us, but people watching it unfold can benefit too.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/on-philosophy-religion-and-genocide/13093/103">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/on-philosophy-religion-and-genocide/13093/103</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2014 14:23:33 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13093-103</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/on-philosophy-religion-and-genocide/13093.rss">On Philosophy, Religion, and Genocide.</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>On Philosophy, Religion, and Genocide.</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Cheerios]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Bur, I think the conversation is going rather well actually. I may not be participating but this thread is awesome just as it is.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/on-philosophy-religion-and-genocide/13093/102">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/on-philosophy-religion-and-genocide/13093/102</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2014 13:24:48 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13093-102</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/on-philosophy-religion-and-genocide/13093.rss">On Philosophy, Religion, and Genocide.</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>On Philosophy, Religion, and Genocide.</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Tiki]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Pyro">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/p/71e660/40.png" class="avatar"> Pyro:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Even Adam Smith admitted that some degree of economic oversight is necessary.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Adam Smith was such a moderate.</p>
<p>By that I mean to suggest that economic oversight should be ubiquitous.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/on-philosophy-religion-and-genocide/13093/101">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/on-philosophy-religion-and-genocide/13093/101</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2014 21:55:39 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13093-101</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/on-philosophy-religion-and-genocide/13093.rss">On Philosophy, Religion, and Genocide.</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>On Philosophy, Religion, and Genocide.</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[bur]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>guys, debating politics with inane “examples” and hypothetical scenarios is counterproductive, at best you end up going in circles and at worst you end up just spouting generalized nonsense</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/on-philosophy-religion-and-genocide/13093/100">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/on-philosophy-religion-and-genocide/13093/100</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2014 07:46:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13093-100</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/on-philosophy-religion-and-genocide/13093.rss">On Philosophy, Religion, and Genocide.</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>On Philosophy, Religion, and Genocide.</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Han_Shot_First]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Danielsangeo: That’s why I’m a minarchist. I personally believe that, for example, your slaves example. The right of ownership of slaves is not as important as, say, the right to not be held against your will. Therefore, the government will in fact make it illegal to own slaves for that exact reason (but indentured servitude is fair game ).</p>
<p>Also, in what scenario is it the case that all the sellers of a product would not sell to a specific race or gender? In Nazi Germany, for example, shopkeepers not selling to jews was done because it was supported by the state. But under what historical circumstance is that the case, where the sellers of a good, on their own volition,  are not willing to sell to a minority?</p>
<p>That’s why I have a problem with strong centralized government. Racist people in government have a much larger capacity to harm minorities than a racist shopkeeper or a CEO. The ability to wield power still lies in someone’s hands, it’s just that it’s a lot more decentralized and the words of an individual does carry the same air of legitimacy than a government leader.</p>
<p>I do agree that there is place for government, but it must be heavily restricted. An an-cap society wouldn’t work for the exact same reason why an an-com society wouldn’t work: some people are asshats, and are willing to do some pretty shitty stuff to gain power/wealth. But a minarchist society, where the government’s place is to enforce law that directly pertain to the protection of the rights of the individual, then immediately, corporations can only truly rely on appeasement, not on fear, to profit, but are not restricted in methods and the positive side effects of their actions.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/on-philosophy-religion-and-genocide/13093/99">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/on-philosophy-religion-and-genocide/13093/99</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2014 05:39:47 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13093-99</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/on-philosophy-religion-and-genocide/13093.rss">On Philosophy, Religion, and Genocide.</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>On Philosophy, Religion, and Genocide.</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Pyroclase]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Even Adam Smith admitted that some degree of economic oversight is necessary - ‘the market’ is far from being a perfectly self-regulating system.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/on-philosophy-religion-and-genocide/13093/98">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/on-philosophy-religion-and-genocide/13093/98</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2014 02:22:52 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13093-98</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/on-philosophy-religion-and-genocide/13093.rss">On Philosophy, Religion, and Genocide.</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>On Philosophy, Religion, and Genocide.</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[danielsangeo]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>“determined by the market”</p>
<p>This seems like another “intangible idealism” to me.  Can “the market” ever be wrong?  What if the majority of the market suggests that homosexuals and transgenders should only be allowed to get jobs in sideshows?  How about if the majority of the market suggests black people should be slaves?  What if the majority of the market suggests that atheists should not be able to buy property?</p>
<p>It seems that you’re just moving the “initiation of force” off of the collection of people known as “government” and onto the collection of people known as “the market”.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/on-philosophy-religion-and-genocide/13093/97">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/on-philosophy-religion-and-genocide/13093/97</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2014 00:33:09 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13093-97</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/on-philosophy-religion-and-genocide/13093.rss">On Philosophy, Religion, and Genocide.</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>On Philosophy, Religion, and Genocide.</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[k3nny1550]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I’m not really an anything-ist, or at least identifying with any particular movement. I just happened to really like what I was reading. But yeah, thanks Han for helping explain!  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=9" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/on-philosophy-religion-and-genocide/13093/96">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/on-philosophy-religion-and-genocide/13093/96</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2014 19:20:18 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13093-96</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/on-philosophy-religion-and-genocide/13093.rss">On Philosophy, Religion, and Genocide.</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>On Philosophy, Religion, and Genocide.</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Han_Shot_First]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>The problem is that cooperation cannot be forced, and people cooperate via incentives. Instead of fighting that urge, capitalism tries to allow for incentives to benefit others.</p>
<p>Danielsangeo, Capitalism differs from the intangible idealism of communism because communism calls for self-motivated selflessness. Communism is supposed to be decentralized, yet as we can see from history, people just don’t act like that, at least the vast majority. Capitalism isn’t governed by anything except your own actions. People aren’t FORCED to sign a contract for a company, and isn’t threatened by death by companies (in a minarchist, not anachro-capitalist society), unlike the force of government experienced by socialism.</p>
<p>Also, Sangeo, the worth of someone is determined by the market, simply enough. The market (the average price of the collective prices) seems to determine this value much better than any government employee or village head. But also remember that value is subjective, and each vendor ultimately makes their own price based on how much they want labor, and how badly the employee needs to be hired.</p>
<p>K3nny, I don’t know if you are a minarchist, voluntaryist, or anachro-capitalist, but I do agree with you. By introducing these measures implemented by government to try to balance the playing field, in reality usually only flips the problem around, rather than actually solving the core of the problem.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/on-philosophy-religion-and-genocide/13093/95">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/on-philosophy-religion-and-genocide/13093/95</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2014 15:45:16 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13093-95</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/on-philosophy-religion-and-genocide/13093.rss">On Philosophy, Religion, and Genocide.</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>On Philosophy, Religion, and Genocide.</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[bur]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Maybe we don’t really need janitors. Maybe the concept of labour and wage isn’t the be all and end all of societal organization. Maybe a company or whatever which is run cooperatively could work out some sort of rotation so everyone cleans up some shit.</p>
<p>Ideology should die a horrible painful death already. Let’s try to run our society based on facts and numbers and deliberation and cooperation, instead of high minded ideals and abstract notions of an individual’s worth and of humanity’s nature.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/on-philosophy-religion-and-genocide/13093/94">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/on-philosophy-religion-and-genocide/13093/94</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2014 14:52:30 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13093-94</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/on-philosophy-religion-and-genocide/13093.rss">On Philosophy, Religion, and Genocide.</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>On Philosophy, Religion, and Genocide.</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[danielsangeo]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Still feels like a central authority dictating things that you just aren’t calling ‘government’.</p>
<p>However, I don’t believe that what you’re calling for can work in real life any more than “communism” or “socialism” can.  There’s a scene in Office Space that explains the problem perfectly.</p>
<p>Peter: Our high school guidance counselor used to ask us what you would do if you had a million dollars and didn’t have to work. And invariably, whatever you’d say, that was supposed to be your career. So if you wanted to fix old cars, then you’re supposed to be an auto mechanic.<br>
Samir: So what did you say?<br>
Peter: I never had an answer. I guess that’s why I’m working at Initech.<br>
Michael: No, you’re working at Initech because that question is bullshit to begin with. If everyone listened to her, there would be no janitors, because no one would clean shit up if they had a million dollars.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/on-philosophy-religion-and-genocide/13093/93">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/on-philosophy-religion-and-genocide/13093/93</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2014 12:50:31 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13093-93</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/on-philosophy-religion-and-genocide/13093.rss">On Philosophy, Religion, and Genocide.</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>On Philosophy, Religion, and Genocide.</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[k3nny1550]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Economic forces are not centrally planned. I’m talking about the whole “people buy what they want to buy” mentality where goods and services are provided at-will by both employee and employer. If you’re useful, you keep your job. If you aren’t, you don’t. No hiring quotas. No enforced diversity. No using of social status, race, or gender as a qualification for employment. I personally think that’s more fair than having affirmative action or any other similar type of preferential hiring.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/on-philosophy-religion-and-genocide/13093/92">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/on-philosophy-religion-and-genocide/13093/92</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2014 09:33:03 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13093-92</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/on-philosophy-religion-and-genocide/13093.rss">On Philosophy, Religion, and Genocide.</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>On Philosophy, Religion, and Genocide.</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[danielsangeo]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>But, isn’t that just an “abstract societal notion…delegated by a central authority like the society in ‘Anthem’’”?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/on-philosophy-religion-and-genocide/13093/91">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/on-philosophy-religion-and-genocide/13093/91</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2014 05:23:22 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13093-91</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/on-philosophy-religion-and-genocide/13093.rss">On Philosophy, Religion, and Genocide.</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>On Philosophy, Religion, and Genocide.</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[k3nny1550]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>See my edit. But if it’s tl;dr: market forces and common sense, basically.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/on-philosophy-religion-and-genocide/13093/90">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/on-philosophy-religion-and-genocide/13093/90</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2014 05:20:06 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13093-90</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/on-philosophy-religion-and-genocide/13093.rss">On Philosophy, Religion, and Genocide.</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>On Philosophy, Religion, and Genocide.</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[danielsangeo]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>You didn’t answer my question.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/on-philosophy-religion-and-genocide/13093/89">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/on-philosophy-religion-and-genocide/13093/89</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2014 05:08:46 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13093-89</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/on-philosophy-religion-and-genocide/13093.rss">On Philosophy, Religion, and Genocide.</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
