<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Nine Years Ago Today</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/nine-years-ago-today/5427</link>
    <description>It&#39;s amazing what sort of minor details you remember in a situation like that...

I was sitting in Math class when the phone rang. My teacher had a bad habit of being so engrossed in what she was doing that if there was a sudden noise, like a ringing phone or a door slamming, she&#39;d nearly jump out of her shoes. She didn&#39;t that time, and there was a lot of ribbing congratulations from the students. She answered the phone and said &quot;Oh my god!&quot; and then walked quickly out the door.

We didn&#39;t know what to think of it, maybe something had happened elsewhere in the school, or there was some family emergency. Eventually curiosity got the better of some of us and we filtered into the next room where a cluster of students and teachers were gathered around a finicky, staticky old analog TV set...The only one they could dredge up on short notice. The budget at this particular school at that time wasn&#39;t that great. One of the world trade center towers was burning. To get a better signal, some of us took turns standing behind it with a clothes hanger. I remember thinking, at first, that it was some kind of freak accident. I kept recalling the bomber that had run into the Empire State Building back in the 1940&#39;s.

Then the second plane hit.

The rest of the day was spent in a gaggle of other students and teachers just watching the news.

Though the first real sense that &#39;the times, they are a&#39;changing&#39; happened about a week later. I lived, and still currently do, in Richmond, VA. And we&#39;d often go up around DC to sightsee or to do some shopping. It was on one of these little excursions that we had a flight of F-16s buzz over our heads at low altitude when we were walking in a parking lot, in an obvious CAP pattern.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 14 Sep 2010 16:07:17 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Off Topic</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/nine-years-ago-today/5427.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Nine Years Ago Today</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[CatzEyes93]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>It seems some have missed the meaning of this whole thread.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/nine-years-ago-today/5427/78">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/nine-years-ago-today/5427/78</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Sep 2010 16:07:17 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-5427-78</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/nine-years-ago-today/5427.rss">Nine Years Ago Today</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Nine Years Ago Today</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Winged_One]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Mith">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/m/e36b37/40.png" class="avatar"> Mith:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Yes, and that’s basically what everyone else is saying to you. When you post in an <span class="bbcode-b">international</span> forum, don’t expect <span class="bbcode-b">everyone</span> to come crying about how tragic 9/11 was and how it changed their lives, because chances are most people won’t care, because “their lives weren’t affected”. But no, if anyone dare says 9/11 isn’t a big deal people get the ultimate butthurt and go on a flaming spree talking about how insensitive and disrespectful people are.</p>
<p>I’m plenty sensitive and respectful, but about the stuff that matters the most to me, much like you guys are, and to be honest a terrorist attack in the USA is just like a terrorist attack from the IRA in Ireland to most of us. Of course the proportions are larger, but as other mentioned there have been other attacks much worse than that, and as Bolteh (for once) rightfully stated, if there’s anything special (to <span class="bbcode-i">us</span>) about the 9/11 attacks is that they were much more “spectacular”, and not much more than that.</p>
<p>I’m not saying I’ll disrespect the people that were affected by it or any of that, but Americans (yes, I’m generalizing, I know not all of you fit this statement) should just learn to not expect anything more than apathy from people around the world when it comes to their own issues. And not just about 9/11 but everything tbh. For example, my brother went to Europe on vacation last year, and there were a few Americans in his hotel when he was staying in Italy through the first half of July. Then, on the 4th the Americans were going crazy in the lobby partying and stuff, and when my brother and a few of his friends asked them what was all that fuss about they were like outraged that people didn’t know what the 4th of July was or “what it represents”.</p>
<p>Seriously, stop thinking the world revolves around you (again, not meant to any individuals specifically, just the few American morons I’ve seen and met that think this way).</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I also said I understand how you all feel because that’s exactly what I would do.</p>
<p>It seems you missed the meaning of my post completely.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/nine-years-ago-today/5427/77">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/nine-years-ago-today/5427/77</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Sep 2010 13:02:59 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-5427-77</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/nine-years-ago-today/5427.rss">Nine Years Ago Today</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Nine Years Ago Today</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Comrade_Tiki]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="CatzEyes93">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/user_avatar/leakfree.org/catzeyes93/40/4402_2.png" class="avatar"> CatzEyes93:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>The 4 year old is now 13, and he specifically dvr’d a 9/11 special.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Wow, very impressive!<br>
I was the same unknowing age, actually a year younger, when seeing green footage of us bombing Baghdad (the first time) on television…</p>
<p>…and I wish i had the chance to record some Gulf War special to get a good grasp of its chronology. But with us in Afghanistan and the sort, there hasn’t been much interest in 1991. Television is obsessed with the things that look just like it… the things that happened more recently.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Flatline">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/f/b9bd4f/40.png" class="avatar"> Flatline:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>It doesn’t take a genius to realise she’s referring to the posts in this thread.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>A little broad, isn’t that?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/nine-years-ago-today/5427/76">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/nine-years-ago-today/5427/76</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Sep 2010 08:01:22 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-5427-76</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/nine-years-ago-today/5427.rss">Nine Years Ago Today</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Nine Years Ago Today</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Mith]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Winged One">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Winged One:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Yes, we care more about what happened here more than an earthquake in some random European city.  It’s tragic that people died in whatever tragedy you bring up, but the fact of the matter is I will never care as much about what happens in your nation as I care about what happens in mine.  Because no matter how many people die in some other nation, sure it will be a tragic loss of life, but my daily routine remains unchanged and I barely give it a thought because, quite frankly, it doesn’t affect my life.  9/11 resulted in the loss of thousands of fellow Americans, hell most of which were fellow New Yorkers.  So yeah, we care more about what happens on our soil, and we barely give two shits about what happens to you.  Just being brutally honest here.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Yes, and that’s basically what everyone else is saying to you. When you post in an <span class="bbcode-b">international</span> forum, don’t expect <span class="bbcode-b">everyone</span> to come crying about how tragic 9/11 was and how it changed their lives, because chances are most people won’t care, because “their lives weren’t affected”. But no, if anyone dare says 9/11 isn’t a big deal people get the ultimate butthurt and go on a flaming spree talking about how insensitive and disrespectful people are.</p>
<p>I’m plenty sensitive and respectful, but about the stuff that matters the most to me, much like you guys are, and to be honest a terrorist attack in the USA is just like a terrorist attack from the IRA in Ireland to most of us. Of course the proportions are larger, but as other mentioned there have been other attacks much worse than that, and as Bolteh (for once) rightfully stated, if there’s anything special (to <span class="bbcode-i">us</span>) about the 9/11 attacks is that they were much more “spectacular”, and not much more than that.</p>
<p>I’m not saying I’ll disrespect the people that were affected by it or any of that, but Americans (yes, I’m generalizing, I know not all of you fit this statement) should just learn to not expect anything more than apathy from people around the world when it comes to their own issues. And not just about 9/11 but everything tbh. For example, my brother went to Europe on vacation last year, and there were a few Americans in his hotel when he was staying in Italy through the first half of July. Then, on the 4th the Americans were going crazy in the lobby partying and stuff, and when my brother and a few of his friends asked them what was all that fuss about they were like outraged that people didn’t know what the 4th of July was or “what it represents”.</p>
<p>Seriously, stop thinking the world revolves around you (again, not meant to any individuals specifically, just the few American morons I’ve seen and met that think this way).</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/nine-years-ago-today/5427/75">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/nine-years-ago-today/5427/75</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Sep 2010 04:17:15 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-5427-75</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/nine-years-ago-today/5427.rss">Nine Years Ago Today</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Nine Years Ago Today</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[russilker]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Anybody retarded enough to believe the horrid stereotypes presented in Hollywood movies should not even be considered an “average” American.</p>
<p>Sure, there’s a LOT of stupidity in the USA (a <span class="bbcode-i">lot…</span>) but I honestly believe there are more normal people than fucktards; the latter just make themselves more noticeable.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/nine-years-ago-today/5427/74">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/nine-years-ago-today/5427/74</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Sep 2010 00:25:24 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-5427-74</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/nine-years-ago-today/5427.rss">Nine Years Ago Today</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Nine Years Ago Today</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[DansonDelta40]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Winged One">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Winged One:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>No where in our media do we imply the Middle East is all inhabited by backwards terrorists.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Maybe you should get a good overview about every Hollywood movie featuring people of Middle Eastern descent and make notes about what role these people play in the story, and then reconsider your thought. Just for the heck of it.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/nine-years-ago-today/5427/73">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/nine-years-ago-today/5427/73</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 13 Sep 2010 23:23:16 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-5427-73</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/nine-years-ago-today/5427.rss">Nine Years Ago Today</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Nine Years Ago Today</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[X_Mastershot_X]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>K.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/nine-years-ago-today/5427/72">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/nine-years-ago-today/5427/72</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 13 Sep 2010 22:56:21 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-5427-72</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/nine-years-ago-today/5427.rss">Nine Years Ago Today</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Nine Years Ago Today</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Winged_One]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="X_Mastershot_X">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/x/c5a1d2/40.png" class="avatar"> X_Mastershot_X:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>:facepalm: kids become racist if they are taught that 9/11 was the work of muslims. or if they are filled with the “all people who live in middle-east are stupid and terorists” propoganda I imply you misunderstand me.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Right, we should pretend that the people behind this weren’t part of an extremist Muslim faction.</p>
<p>And again, you tell me I’m wrong in my assumption of your intended meaning, then prove once more that you are an idiot.  Kids are taught about Al Qaeda.  They are taught they are an extremist Muslim terror cell and are very unlike the rest of the Muslim population.</p>
<p>There is no “propaganda” save for references that we are fighting a war in the Middle East against terrorists, but that’s mostly cause we are.  No where in our media do we imply the Middle East is all inhabited by backwards terrorists.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/nine-years-ago-today/5427/71">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/nine-years-ago-today/5427/71</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 13 Sep 2010 22:23:43 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-5427-71</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/nine-years-ago-today/5427.rss">Nine Years Ago Today</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Nine Years Ago Today</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[russilker]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>That wasn’t directed at you lol… it was to the ignorant dumbfucks who try to call Americans retarded for caring so much about 9/11</p>
<p>EDIT: <a class="mention" href="/u/x_mastershot_x">@X_Mastershot_X</a></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/nine-years-ago-today/5427/70">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/nine-years-ago-today/5427/70</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 13 Sep 2010 21:20:52 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-5427-70</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/nine-years-ago-today/5427.rss">Nine Years Ago Today</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Nine Years Ago Today</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[CatzEyes93]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Winged One">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Winged One:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Once again, Bolteh is going for that prestigious Troll Of The Year award.  Good luck!</p>
<p>But anyway, Fancy, and whoever else claims that the US and all it’s inhabitants are dicks for mourning 9/11 more than other attacks/disasters around the world…we care about your shitty countries and all their problems just about as much as you care about ours.  I find it ironic, Fancy, that you accused the US of being inconsiderate of the tragedies in other nations than went on to say you basically don’t give a rat’s ass about what happened on 9/11.  You are being a hypocrite.</p>
<p>Yes, we care more about what happened here more than an earthquake in some random European city.  It’s tragic that people died in whatever tragedy you bring up, but the fact of the matter is I will never care as much about what happens in your nation as I care about what happens in mine.  Because no matter how many people die in some other nation, sure it will be a tragic loss of life, but my daily routine remains unchanged and I barely give it a thought because, quite frankly, it doesn’t affect my life.  9/11 resulted in the loss of thousands of fellow Americans, hell most of which were fellow New Yorkers.  So yeah, we care more about what happens on our soil, and we barely give two shits about what happens to you.  Just being brutally honest here.</p>
<p>If you’re upset that we made a thread about 9/11 but no other tragedy received such recognition, I suggest you make use of your ability to type and make a thread about your respective disaster.  It’s an open forum.  The person who made this thread cared enough about what happened to want to discuss it.  It wasn’t a call to everyone who doesn’t care.  So how about you leave this thread alone and make a thread devoted to some other shitty worthless disaster so I can do my part and ignore it.</p>
<p>And that whole “The US doesn’t give a shit about anyone else” is bullshit.  Our news stations were absolutely <span class="bbcode-i">devoted</span> to Haiti for a month after it occurred.  There was nothing to gain by centering on it, we just happened to care about the amount of suffering going on there.  People I know actually went down to help, so do some research before making a conclusion.</p>
<p>Just out of curiosity, how long did they focus on 9/11 for?  A month or two?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>What he said. Probably with a bit less “!GRRR!” but basically, what he said.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/nine-years-ago-today/5427/69">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/nine-years-ago-today/5427/69</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 13 Sep 2010 21:20:39 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-5427-69</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/nine-years-ago-today/5427.rss">Nine Years Ago Today</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Nine Years Ago Today</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[X_Mastershot_X]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>ah! oh! well! I accept your victory russilker. You just owned me.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/nine-years-ago-today/5427/68">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/nine-years-ago-today/5427/68</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 13 Sep 2010 21:12:12 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-5427-68</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/nine-years-ago-today/5427.rss">Nine Years Ago Today</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Nine Years Ago Today</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[russilker]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>This thread reeks of so much stupidity.</p>
<p>Whether or not 9/11 was the “worst” terrorist attack in history is entirely irrelevant; to those that it affected, and even to those that live in the same country it happened in/find a way to connect to it <span class="bbcode-u">personally</span>, it is the “worst” terrorist attack.</p>
<p>Think of it this way: a truck full of young soldiers blows up somewhere in Afghanistan. That same day, you see on the local news that a toddler you’ve seen before was run over by a car. Which would affect you more?</p>
<p>Your retarded trolling could be compared to a police telling a rape victim and her family to quit QQing because children are being raped everyday in Africa.</p>
<p>Grow a pair and realize that 9/11 is a horrible event and shouldn’t be compared to others, because no terrorist attack is the same, and everybody is affected differently by each one.</p>
<p>EDIT: oh, and about the racist kids… i’d  say just the opposite, this generation of teenagers is (by and large) very much against racism of any kind. sure we might joke about the arabs in our neighborhood making bombs in their garage because we heard a ticking sound from across the street, but it in no way is evidence that most American children and adults think Muslims are terrorists</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/nine-years-ago-today/5427/67">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/nine-years-ago-today/5427/67</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 13 Sep 2010 21:00:02 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-5427-67</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/nine-years-ago-today/5427.rss">Nine Years Ago Today</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Nine Years Ago Today</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[X_Mastershot_X]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>:facepalm: kids become racist if they are taught that 9/11 was the work of muslims. or if they are filled with the “all people who live in middle-east are stupid and terorists” propoganda I imply you misunderstand me.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/nine-years-ago-today/5427/66">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/nine-years-ago-today/5427/66</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 13 Sep 2010 20:47:55 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-5427-66</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/nine-years-ago-today/5427.rss">Nine Years Ago Today</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Nine Years Ago Today</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Winged_One]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="X_Mastershot_X">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/x/c5a1d2/40.png" class="avatar"> X_Mastershot_X:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>The kids hate arabs and muslims. They see muslims as monsters So a new racist dumbfuck generation is born.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>This is quoted from you.  You imply that the children all hate Muslims (and that the learned to be racist from the older generation).  I imply you are a moron.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/nine-years-ago-today/5427/65">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/nine-years-ago-today/5427/65</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 13 Sep 2010 20:19:06 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-5427-65</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/nine-years-ago-today/5427.rss">Nine Years Ago Today</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Nine Years Ago Today</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[X_Mastershot_X]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I don’t think everyone in America hates muslims. Where did you get that idea? I HAVE to care about you because when something happens in America it’s repeated again and again. AND Again There have been many important attacks on many places. (not just terorist organisations. Countries do terorism, too). I can understand if it’s the Biggest attack you had</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/nine-years-ago-today/5427/64">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/nine-years-ago-today/5427/64</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 13 Sep 2010 20:16:41 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-5427-64</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/nine-years-ago-today/5427.rss">Nine Years Ago Today</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Nine Years Ago Today</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Winged_One]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>If you think everyone here hates Muslims, you are a moron.  The only reason these racist fucks get publicity and shit is because they are so unique to the rest of the US population.</p>
<p>And we make a big deal out of 9/11 because it is a big deal.  No other terrorist attack I know of in recent times has changed the course of history like this has.  Not to mention it was one of the, if not THE, largest terrorist attack on US soil.  So yeah, it’s sort of a big deal <span class="bbcode-i">to us</span>.</p>
<p>Again, you don’t care about us and we sure as hell don’t care about you.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/nine-years-ago-today/5427/63">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/nine-years-ago-today/5427/63</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 13 Sep 2010 20:07:09 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-5427-63</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/nine-years-ago-today/5427.rss">Nine Years Ago Today</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Nine Years Ago Today</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[X_Mastershot_X]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I raged because eventually some people like Pastor Jones will appear, bitch about so called 9/11 mosque, will start burning Qurans and the history will repeat itself. The problem is Lots of people is getting killed by terorism every week. America gets one attack and it is like the end of the world. Every Human life is priceless but parents teach their kids this event like it’s the apocalypse. The kids hate arabs and muslims. They see muslims as monsters So a new racist dumbfuck generation is born. It’s time to move on already. In America it’s still like 12/9. People are still angry, “The Ground-zero Mosque” discussion is the proof of this.,</p>
<p>I apologize from everybody ITT whose relatives or friends died at the twin-towers. may they rest in peace.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/nine-years-ago-today/5427/62">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/nine-years-ago-today/5427/62</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 13 Sep 2010 19:55:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-5427-62</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/nine-years-ago-today/5427.rss">Nine Years Ago Today</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Nine Years Ago Today</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Rossman]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I doubt even that long. On the Haiti thing. I know a guy that adopted 2 children from Haiti that had lost their mother and had no other family. They came to the pool one day and I taught them how to jump off the diving board. I loved those kids and they are so happy and lucky to live here.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/nine-years-ago-today/5427/61">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/nine-years-ago-today/5427/61</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 13 Sep 2010 18:40:47 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-5427-61</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/nine-years-ago-today/5427.rss">Nine Years Ago Today</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Nine Years Ago Today</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Winged_One]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Once again, Bolteh is going for that prestigious Troll Of The Year award.  Good luck!</p>
<p>But anyway, Fancy, and whoever else claims that the US and all it’s inhabitants are dicks for mourning 9/11 more than other attacks/disasters around the world…we care about your shitty countries and all their problems just about as much as you care about ours.  I find it ironic, Fancy, that you accused the US of being inconsiderate of the tragedies in other nations than went on to say you basically don’t give a rat’s ass about what happened on 9/11.  You are being a hypocrite.</p>
<p>Yes, we care more about what happened here more than an earthquake in some random European city.  It’s tragic that people died in whatever tragedy you bring up, but the fact of the matter is I will never care as much about what happens in your nation as I care about what happens in mine.  Because no matter how many people die in some other nation, sure it will be a tragic loss of life, but my daily routine remains unchanged and I barely give it a thought because, quite frankly, it doesn’t affect my life.  9/11 resulted in the loss of thousands of fellow Americans, hell most of which were fellow New Yorkers.  So yeah, we care more about what happens on our soil, and we barely give two shits about what happens to you.  Just being brutally honest here.</p>
<p>If you’re upset that we made a thread about 9/11 but no other tragedy received such recognition, I suggest you make use of your ability to type and make a thread about your respective disaster.  It’s an open forum.  The person who made this thread cared enough about what happened to want to discuss it.  It wasn’t a call to everyone who doesn’t care.  So how about you leave this thread alone and make a thread devoted to some other shitty worthless disaster so I can do my part and ignore it.</p>
<p>And that whole “The US doesn’t give a shit about anyone else” is bullshit.  Our news stations were absolutely <span class="bbcode-i">devoted</span> to Haiti for a month after it occurred.  There was nothing to gain by centering on it, we just happened to care about the amount of suffering going on there.  People I know actually went down to help, so do some research before making a conclusion.</p>
<p>Just out of curiosity, how long did they focus on 9/11 for?  A month or two?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/nine-years-ago-today/5427/60">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/nine-years-ago-today/5427/60</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 13 Sep 2010 18:36:24 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-5427-60</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/nine-years-ago-today/5427.rss">Nine Years Ago Today</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Nine Years Ago Today</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[E-Nelson]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>bait</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/nine-years-ago-today/5427/59">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/nine-years-ago-today/5427/59</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 13 Sep 2010 17:46:30 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-5427-59</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/nine-years-ago-today/5427.rss">Nine Years Ago Today</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Nine Years Ago Today</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Bolteh]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="k3nny1550">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/user_avatar/leakfree.org/k3nny1550/40/4952_2.png" class="avatar"> k3nny1550:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Every extraneous pollitical comment in this thread is an insult to those who died on 9/11.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>It’s funny when you realize that 9/11 was caused by extraneous political comments by the US.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/nine-years-ago-today/5427/58">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/nine-years-ago-today/5427/58</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 13 Sep 2010 17:09:38 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-5427-58</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/nine-years-ago-today/5427.rss">Nine Years Ago Today</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Nine Years Ago Today</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[CatzEyes93]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>thnx for the support k3nny1550.  My children were aged 14 and 4 and “sparkle in my eye”.  The 4 year old is now 13, and he specifically dvr’d a 9/11 special.  He watched it, but he didn’t talk much about it.  He was just quiet.  Which actually surprized me a lot that he not only recorded it but went out of his way to watch it, cuz normally he is the kind of person that avoids ‘death’ topics.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/nine-years-ago-today/5427/57">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/nine-years-ago-today/5427/57</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 13 Sep 2010 16:44:03 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-5427-57</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/nine-years-ago-today/5427.rss">Nine Years Ago Today</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Nine Years Ago Today</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[k3nny1550]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>This thread brought back so much. I remember to this day exactly where I was and what I was doing. The reason we remember it so vividly is that it’s analogous to the trauma of people finding out about the assassination of JFK- a national event that touches the lives of everyone living in it. Say what you will about the fallout from the event on international politics but this thread is about where we were and remembering what happened.</p>
<p>I for one am depressed that this thread, much like the conflicts started as a result of this heinous act of terrorism, have been unconscionably politicized by ignorant peons too sucked in by their own sense of righteousness. Every extraneous pollitical comment in this thread is an insult to those who died on 9/11.</p>
<p>As for where I was, my mom woke me up to watch the news. The second tower came down when I was eating waffles. I saw the towers fall when I got to school later in the day. Suddenly my world felt less safe. I guess that’s when I actually started paying attention to the world and what was going on. Being as I was in sixth grade at the time of the attacks though, it was a lot to take in at once. I had trouble sleeping that night.</p>
<p>@ CatzEyes- you are not alone in your sadness at this thread being taken over by politics and ignorance. It’s insensitive and cruel to do so in a thread like this. Those discussions are for another thread. So let’s just leave the politics out here, okay?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/nine-years-ago-today/5427/56">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/nine-years-ago-today/5427/56</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 13 Sep 2010 16:24:25 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-5427-56</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/nine-years-ago-today/5427.rss">Nine Years Ago Today</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Nine Years Ago Today</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[E-Nelson]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I remember the news folks saying that young children watching the footage may not realize that it is simply a replay, but that they may interpret as it happening over and over and over.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/nine-years-ago-today/5427/55">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/nine-years-ago-today/5427/55</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 13 Sep 2010 15:49:21 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-5427-55</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/nine-years-ago-today/5427.rss">Nine Years Ago Today</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Nine Years Ago Today</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[bur]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I challenge anyone here to read John Pilger’s <span class="bbcode-i">Heroes</span> and then come back and say that 9/11 was the worst tragedy in the past fifty years, or that the US itself has never been responsible for tragedies a thousand times worse.</p>
<p>And whoever posted that crap about the US spending billions of dollars on aid every year obviously doesn’t realize that in most of the cases it’s just a political ploy used to exercise power over so-called third world countries.</p>
<p>I do sympathize with people that lost loved ones on that day though, and I realize it was a big shock to Americans. I remember being at home watching television when they broadcast the planes crashing into the towers. My dad said something along the lines of “This is history in the making.”</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/nine-years-ago-today/5427/54">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/nine-years-ago-today/5427/54</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 13 Sep 2010 15:45:22 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-5427-54</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/nine-years-ago-today/5427.rss">Nine Years Ago Today</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
