<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Green &quot;radiation&quot; textures</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/green-radiation-textures/11579</link>
    <description>My only disappointment with this mod (disappointment is actually too harsh of a word, I just can&#39;t think of anything else) was the use of the &quot;green glowing&quot; textures for the radiation areas.  Unforunately, this is based on a misconception by the public that goes back to the 1940&#39;s.

The only exposure a lot of people had to radiation was &quot;radioactive&quot; watch dials.  Watch dials were made of flourescent materials and painted with a radium-laced paint.  There was not much radium (and in fact, the watches were safe to own and use - radioactivity was actually very low) - but it of course interacted with the flourescent materials and caused a green glow.  This is how early &quot;glow in the dark&quot; watches were made.  Unfortunately, it made a lasting correlation in the public mind, that sources of radiation glow green, when in fact they do not.

The original Half-Life sadly fell prey to this misconception.  However, Half-Life 2, which predates this mod by 8 years, did not.  I was actually pleasantly surprised when the &quot;radioactive&quot; areas of Half-Life 2 were given MUCH more realistic textures.  If you&#39;ve seen what REAL radioactive waste looks like, Half-Life 2 actually comes pretty close to the mark, or close enough considering the limits of 3D engines and hardware in 2004 when it was made.  There was actually a little bit of a glow to some of Half-Life 2&#39;s textures, where in real life there would not be, but it overall wasn&#39;t too bad.

What I&#39;m wondering is...since this is a Source game, if it would be possible to change/copy some files around and have it use the Half-Life 2 textures for the radioactive areas, rather than the green glow.  This is really nothing more than a minor nitpick in a very well done mod, but as someone who does understand radiation and KNOWS that radioactive substances do not glow green, I find the green glowing water to be a distraction.

Here is a video that shows what real radioactive waste looks like.  It&#39;s low resolution, but this is why I said Half-Life 2 came pretty close to the mark.  [url]https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=J2mYstiYhJs&amp;feature=endscreen&amp;NR=1[/url]</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 29 Jan 2013 05:36:17 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>The Cafeteria</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/green-radiation-textures/11579.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Green &quot;radiation&quot; textures</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[cdoublejj]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>don’t we have to keep generating this stuff to make more “fuel”? seems kind of counter productive.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/green-radiation-textures/11579/49">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/green-radiation-textures/11579/49</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jan 2013 05:36:17 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11579-49</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/green-radiation-textures/11579.rss">Green &quot;radiation&quot; textures</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Green &quot;radiation&quot; textures</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Akaihiryuu]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="cdoublejj">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/c/82dd89/40.png" class="avatar"> cdoublejj:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I found that very informative. TIL that what radioactive waste really looks like. As with all games, it is a game but, never the less he does have a point.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Well, when I wrote the original post, I didn’t realize that the lighting in those areas was dependent on the green glow.  So sadly that rules out using the HL2 textures.  And it wasn’t the lack of realism that bothered me…it was more the fact that it was in a way a step back from HL2 which used more realistic textures.  I was hoping for the mod to have more of a HL2 feel, while keeping the same story/tension as HL.</p>
<p>But if you want to learn more about radioactive waste, it’s neat to read about the processes that produce it.  It doesn’t come from nuclear power.  Spent fuel rods from nucelar power are usually stored underwater for a cooling period, and then moved to dry casks (filled with a noble gas like argon or xenon to prevent chemical reactions).</p>
<p>Radioactive waste is actually what is left over from producing plutonium for nuclear weapons.  The fuel pellets are dissolved in concentrated nitric acid, then mixed with a solution of tributyl phosphate in kerosene, this forms a complex which removes most of the uranium and plutonium from solution, leaving the other nasty radioisotopes behind (primarily Cs-137 and I-131, at least those are the most dangerous two).  This gunk left over (basically, a mixture of nitrate sales of Cs-137 and I-131 in nitric acid, mixed with kerosene) is dumped in underground tanks.  To prevent the acid from eating through the tanks (which it would eventually do), alkaline substances are added to neutralize the acid.  Unfortunately since acid + base = salt + water, this cases the radioactive salts to precipitate out and harden.  So what you are left with in the end: mounts of radioactive salt, mixed with water and kerosene.  That’s simplified a bit, but it’s a nasty organic soup that can undergo a lot of chemical reactions, and release all kinds of toxic organic substances (even if the radioactive material doesn’t escape).  At one point one of the vents on a Hanford tank was sampled, and there were over 1200 different chemicals coming out.  There are filters to trap all the radioactive particles, so no radioactivity escapes.  <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/PUREX" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/PUREX</a></p>
<p>So not only is it dangerously radioactive, it is also extremely chemically toxic.  This stuff is some of the most nasty material in existence in the universe, totally destrutive to all forms of life that we know of except for a couple species of extremophile bacteria (some have even been found living in the tanks), and a couple species of radiotrophic fungi that have actually evolved to live on gamma radiation.  Interestingly enough, some of the extremophile bacteria is capable of actually eating the organic waste and leaving chemically inert substances behind.  Obviously it’s still radioactive, but removing the chemical toxicity helps a lot.</p>
<p>But the waste is so dangerous that all work in the tanks has to be done by remote controlled robots.  There is literally NO shielding that could protect someone from direct exposure.  Thick concrete and distance (inverse square law) is the only protection.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/green-radiation-textures/11579/48">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/green-radiation-textures/11579/48</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jan 2013 03:20:22 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11579-48</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/green-radiation-textures/11579.rss">Green &quot;radiation&quot; textures</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Green &quot;radiation&quot; textures</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[cdoublejj]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Akaihiryuu">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/a/ee59a6/40.png" class="avatar"> Akaihiryuu:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>My only disappointment with this mod (disappointment is actually too harsh of a word, I just can’t think of anything else) was the use of the “green glowing” textures for the radiation areas.  Unforunately, this is based on a misconception by the public that goes back to the 1940’s.</p>
<p>The only exposure a lot of people had to radiation was “radioactive” watch dials.  Watch dials were made of flourescent materials and painted with a radium-laced paint.  There was not much radium (and in fact, the watches were safe to own and use - radioactivity was actually very low) - but it of course interacted with the flourescent materials and caused a green glow.  This is how early “glow in the dark” watches were made.  Unfortunately, it made a lasting correlation in the public mind, that sources of radiation glow green, when in fact they do not.</p>
<p>The original Half-Life sadly fell prey to this misconception.  However, Half-Life 2, which predates this mod by 8 years, did not.  I was actually pleasantly surprised when the “radioactive” areas of Half-Life 2 were given MUCH more realistic textures.  If you’ve seen what REAL radioactive waste looks like, Half-Life 2 actually comes pretty close to the mark, or close enough considering the limits of 3D engines and hardware in 2004 when it was made.  There was actually a little bit of a glow to some of Half-Life 2’s textures, where in real life there would not be, but it overall wasn’t too bad.</p>
<p>What I’m wondering is…since this is a Source game, if it would be possible to change/copy some files around and have it use the Half-Life 2 textures for the radioactive areas, rather than the green glow.  This is really nothing more than a minor nitpick in a very well done mod, but as someone who does understand radiation and KNOWS that radioactive substances do not glow green, I find the green glowing water to be a distraction.</p>
<p>Here is a video that shows what real radioactive waste looks like.  It’s low resolution, but this is why I said Half-Life 2 came pretty close to the mark.  <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=J2mYstiYhJs&amp;feature=endscreen&amp;NR=1" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=J2mYstiYhJs&amp;feature=endscreen&amp;NR=1</a></p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I found that very informative. TIL that what radioactive waste really looks like. As with all games, it is a game but, never the less he does have a point.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/green-radiation-textures/11579/47">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/green-radiation-textures/11579/47</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 26 Jan 2013 10:14:25 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11579-47</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/green-radiation-textures/11579.rss">Green &quot;radiation&quot; textures</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Green &quot;radiation&quot; textures</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[fuegerstef]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="NemetZzZ">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/n/8e8cbc/40.png" class="avatar"> NemetZzZ:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>If you think of it this way, you better know that barrels/crates full of something explosive/incendiary don’t go boom when you shoot them with a pistol or hit with a crowbar.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>This.</p>
<p>Also:<br>
You cannot carry all weapons at once without sticking it where the sun don’t shine.</p>
<p>Resonance Cascades haven’t been proven to be real either.</p>
<p>Have I mentioned that in real life you can move your arm to the left and right and it is not always aligned with the direction you look at?</p>
<p>Conclusion: If you want to mod a game to be realistic and take out everything that makes it interesting you will have to mod it until it is easier and more playable and more interesting to just go outside and take a walk.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/green-radiation-textures/11579/46">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/green-radiation-textures/11579/46</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jan 2013 11:05:34 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11579-46</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/green-radiation-textures/11579.rss">Green &quot;radiation&quot; textures</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Green &quot;radiation&quot; textures</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NemetZzZ]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>If you think of it this way, you better know that barrels/crates full of something explosive/incendiary don’t go boom when you shoot them with a pistol or hit with a crowbar.<br>
It’s more of a design element, you know.<br>
And the green glow may be just a safety measure after all, as proposed by Mr. Someguy.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/green-radiation-textures/11579/45">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/green-radiation-textures/11579/45</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jan 2013 18:55:35 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11579-45</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/green-radiation-textures/11579.rss">Green &quot;radiation&quot; textures</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Green &quot;radiation&quot; textures</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Dotard]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Mr. Someguy">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Mr. Someguy:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I’m just going to assume that for safety reasons, Black Mesa adds a glowing green chemical to hazardous waste so any leaks or spills are instantly recognised by even the dullest players.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>fixed</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/green-radiation-textures/11579/44">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/green-radiation-textures/11579/44</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2013 21:42:31 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11579-44</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/green-radiation-textures/11579.rss">Green &quot;radiation&quot; textures</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Green &quot;radiation&quot; textures</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Mr_Someguy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I’m just going to assume that for safety reasons, Black Mesa adds a glowing green chemical to hazardous waste so any leaks or spills are instantly recognised by even the dullest workers.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/green-radiation-textures/11579/43">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/green-radiation-textures/11579/43</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2013 18:23:55 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11579-43</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/green-radiation-textures/11579.rss">Green &quot;radiation&quot; textures</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Green &quot;radiation&quot; textures</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[ac3d]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>edit: quack</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/green-radiation-textures/11579/42">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/green-radiation-textures/11579/42</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 31 Oct 2012 10:35:45 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11579-42</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/green-radiation-textures/11579.rss">Green &quot;radiation&quot; textures</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Green &quot;radiation&quot; textures</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Hezus]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>The only way to get rid of the green glow is to set your display to black and white  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/wink.png?v=9" title=":wink:" class="emoji" alt=":wink:">  Or find an old CRT from the 80’s… although many of them where green on black, lol.</p>
<p>From a design standpoint, the great lighting effect of the green glow pretty much overrules the concern about realism, imho. And if you’re really concerned about realism, you shouldn’t play Half-life or probably any game at all. There is always something to complain about…</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/green-radiation-textures/11579/41">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/green-radiation-textures/11579/41</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 31 Oct 2012 10:02:58 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11579-41</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/green-radiation-textures/11579.rss">Green &quot;radiation&quot; textures</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Green &quot;radiation&quot; textures</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypt]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Cpl.1nsane">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/user_avatar/leakfree.org/cpl.1nsane/40/4631_2.png" class="avatar"> Cpl.1nsane:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Nope, the green glow is generated from the lights.rad file (the water is a texture light essentially) and baked when vrad is run.</p>
<p>So you would have to recompile all the maps to change the glow if you so desired.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>But no, all that recompile time wouldn’t be worth it, especially with having to fix up anything the decompile screwed up.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/green-radiation-textures/11579/40">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/green-radiation-textures/11579/40</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 31 Oct 2012 08:48:51 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11579-40</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/green-radiation-textures/11579.rss">Green &quot;radiation&quot; textures</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Green &quot;radiation&quot; textures</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[sgtpieman]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I don’t like it (Even though it looks much better in game due to it being animated), and I don’t think the green glow on the tubs can be removed either. So the message for the OP is that yes, it technically is semi-possible to change the radiation to something more realistic. But it really isn’t worth it…</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/green-radiation-textures/11579/39">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/green-radiation-textures/11579/39</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 30 Oct 2012 22:25:17 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11579-39</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/green-radiation-textures/11579.rss">Green &quot;radiation&quot; textures</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Green &quot;radiation&quot; textures</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypt]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>And then our problems were solved.<br>
Holy shit, though. That look awesome. I’d swim in it, provided it’s not toxic.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/green-radiation-textures/11579/38">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/green-radiation-textures/11579/38</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 30 Oct 2012 05:57:09 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11579-38</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/green-radiation-textures/11579.rss">Green &quot;radiation&quot; textures</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Green &quot;radiation&quot; textures</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[darkone]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><a href="https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-1346551/Goldstream-River-turns-bright-GREEN-Radioactive-disaster-hoax.html" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-1346551/Goldstream-River-turns-bright-GREEN-Radioactive-disaster-hoax.html</a></p>
<p>read above, now we can explain the green maybe be do to dyes used to test things, I can see the BM area using green dye combined with luminescent materiel to mark radioactive water flow through the facility, this would be a safety feature more than anything.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/green-radiation-textures/11579/37">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/green-radiation-textures/11579/37</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 30 Oct 2012 05:20:35 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11579-37</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/green-radiation-textures/11579.rss">Green &quot;radiation&quot; textures</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Green &quot;radiation&quot; textures</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[brokenfridgehinge]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>That looks like shit, quite literally.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/green-radiation-textures/11579/36">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/green-radiation-textures/11579/36</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 30 Oct 2012 04:58:02 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11579-36</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/green-radiation-textures/11579.rss">Green &quot;radiation&quot; textures</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Green &quot;radiation&quot; textures</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypt]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Wow, it’s just not the same. Fuck realism.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/green-radiation-textures/11579/35">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/green-radiation-textures/11579/35</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 30 Oct 2012 04:54:21 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11579-35</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/green-radiation-textures/11579.rss">Green &quot;radiation&quot; textures</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Green &quot;radiation&quot; textures</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Dragunov2]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I love the green glow  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/wink.png?v=9" title=":wink:" class="emoji" alt=":wink:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/green-radiation-textures/11579/34">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/green-radiation-textures/11579/34</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 30 Oct 2012 00:43:34 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11579-34</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/green-radiation-textures/11579.rss">Green &quot;radiation&quot; textures</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Green &quot;radiation&quot; textures</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[sgtpieman]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>aye yai yai, come on people! Some of us have different opinions. If the OP wants realistic looking toxic waste, that’s their call. I’ll take a look at the files to see if it’s possible, but I’m not making any promises.</p>
<p>EDIT:Well, I got some progress. Most of the radiation is done by a green type of water. All I did there was turn it blue somehow (I still can’t find the file where I did that, if any of the devs can please direct me to it.)<br>
BUT I did manage to edit one of the little tube things in Residue Processing. Also, whether you go below the water waste or the waste in this tub, you won’t see some green blotchy thing either. It’s similar to what is on the surface. The green light I don’t think I can change though. I still wish I could figure out that water waste as well.<br>
<span alt="" class="broken-image" title="This image is broken"><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-unlink svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#unlink"></use></svg></span></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/green-radiation-textures/11579/33">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/green-radiation-textures/11579/33</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 30 Oct 2012 00:10:40 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11579-33</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/green-radiation-textures/11579.rss">Green &quot;radiation&quot; textures</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Green &quot;radiation&quot; textures</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[ac3d]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I hated the look of the toxic waste in HL2, boring (and low res), it looks just the way I like it in Black Mesa, but I wish the sludge had its own effects instead of borrowing from the water one, perhaps the splash effect could be the same as the bullsquid’s acid spit, leaving a print on the wall and dealing damage to anyone nearby.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/green-radiation-textures/11579/32">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/green-radiation-textures/11579/32</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 29 Oct 2012 14:20:30 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11579-32</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/green-radiation-textures/11579.rss">Green &quot;radiation&quot; textures</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Green &quot;radiation&quot; textures</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Dragunov2]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>The water can contain a product who glows AND make it radioactive.</p>
<p>Chemical product, cause we have the Chemical Waste Facility aswell.</p>
<p>So the green is PERFECT!</p>
<p>It’s not cause it’s radioactive it’s green and vica versa…</p>
<p>BUT here it’s possible like I said in the first line!</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/green-radiation-textures/11579/31">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/green-radiation-textures/11579/31</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 29 Oct 2012 14:04:19 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11579-31</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/green-radiation-textures/11579.rss">Green &quot;radiation&quot; textures</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Green &quot;radiation&quot; textures</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[UnhingedMouse0]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>OP needs to learn the meaning of the word “<span class="bbcode-b">stylization</span>.”</p>
<p>And everyone who likes to nit-pick about things like this need to learn that: <span class="bbcode-b">REAL ≠[/SIZE] FUN</span></p>
<p>As far as replacing the textures goes, the BM textures have the liquid flowing, the HL2 ones do not. It wouldn’t look right even if it was as simple as swapping them out.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/green-radiation-textures/11579/30">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/green-radiation-textures/11579/30</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 29 Oct 2012 11:39:17 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11579-30</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/green-radiation-textures/11579.rss">Green &quot;radiation&quot; textures</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Green &quot;radiation&quot; textures</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[dky.tehkingd.u]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I liked Water Hazard… to an extent.  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/frowning.png?v=9" title=":frowning:" class="emoji" alt=":frowning:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/green-radiation-textures/11579/29">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/green-radiation-textures/11579/29</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 28 Oct 2012 22:03:39 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11579-29</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/green-radiation-textures/11579.rss">Green &quot;radiation&quot; textures</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Green &quot;radiation&quot; textures</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[warpedfreeman]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Crypt19">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Crypt19:</div>
<blockquote>
<p><a href="https://half-life.wikia.com/wiki/Half-Life_2_storyline#Water_Hazard" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://half-life.wikia.com/wiki/Half-Life_2_storyline#Water_Hazard</a></p>
<p>Man, screw that chapter, I hate it.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>well i liked it, though wasnt to good, offered a diferent gameplay <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/confused.png?v=9" title=":confused:" class="emoji" alt=":confused:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/green-radiation-textures/11579/28">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/green-radiation-textures/11579/28</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 28 Oct 2012 19:39:21 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11579-28</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/green-radiation-textures/11579.rss">Green &quot;radiation&quot; textures</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Green &quot;radiation&quot; textures</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypt]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><a href="https://half-life.wikia.com/wiki/Half-Life_2_storyline#Water_Hazard" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://half-life.wikia.com/wiki/Half-Life_2_storyline#Water_Hazard</a></p>
<p>Man, screw that chapter, I hate it.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/green-radiation-textures/11579/27">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/green-radiation-textures/11579/27</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 28 Oct 2012 19:24:11 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11579-27</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/green-radiation-textures/11579.rss">Green &quot;radiation&quot; textures</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Green &quot;radiation&quot; textures</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[warpedfreeman]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Crypt19">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Crypt19:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>that annoying chapter Water Hazard</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>wut?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/green-radiation-textures/11579/26">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/green-radiation-textures/11579/26</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 28 Oct 2012 18:12:52 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11579-26</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/green-radiation-textures/11579.rss">Green &quot;radiation&quot; textures</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Green &quot;radiation&quot; textures</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[dky.tehkingd.u]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Makes sense. So if you changed the texture, I’d imagine a whole bunch of things would look screwed up.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/green-radiation-textures/11579/25">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/green-radiation-textures/11579/25</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 28 Oct 2012 17:49:03 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11579-25</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/green-radiation-textures/11579.rss">Green &quot;radiation&quot; textures</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
