<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>L4D: General mapping questions</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/l4d-general-mapping-questions/2133</link>
    <description>I am working on a full L4D campaign, with the general layout for the first map completed in hammer.

I intend to use this thread multiple times, as I run into any problems...

My first questions is this:  What is the recommended height of a ventilation duct in Left 4 Dead?

Oh, and could somebody refresh my memory on rope... it doesn&#39;t seem to want to work...

EDIT: Solved the rope problem, hit a new one.  Is it possible to connect a prop_physics to a rope?  If so, how?  If not, how do I do something to that effect.

Update on the rope-light fail:  I can either have the rope show up with no light-prop, and MAYBE the actual light itself projected a couple feet away from its real location; no rope, light-prop on ground, and maybe a light; and finally nothing but possibly a bit of light in the wrong place.  It seems that setting the keyframe_rope&#39;s object causes the rope to never appear.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 22 Oct 2010 11:52:37 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Help and Support</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/l4d-general-mapping-questions/2133.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>L4D: General mapping questions</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Madcat1030]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Necro-ing again.  I’m back to work, and have seriously optimized this map.  Five minute compiles, the forests props are removed (I was using ALL real trees, stupidly), set up the barriers, have the underground section completed, and 90% of the rest of the map finished.  Now with zero FPS drops.  My next step is finishing the forest, setting the stage for the second panic event, and then populating the forest with a few trees near the edges and 2d tree-cards.  Then it’s a matter of figuring out panic events a little better, and navmapping.  I’ll have my first map.</p>
<p>Actually, before I navmap, I’ll make the starting saferoom for the second level and link them so there’s less possibility of losing my navmap when  I recompile with the level-link.</p>
<p>Once I do that, I’ll prolly put up a link for some feedback.  I’d expect a month (because I only get a few minutes a day until the quarters done, waaaay too much work, and this project is keeping me sane, giving me something to do when I just can’t flash any more).</p>
<p>Oh yeah, a reason for posting:  Any tips on making panic events work properly, lemme know here.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/l4d-general-mapping-questions/2133/30">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/l4d-general-mapping-questions/2133/30</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 22 Oct 2010 11:52:37 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2133-30</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/l4d-general-mapping-questions/2133.rss">L4D: General mapping questions</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>L4D: General mapping questions</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[RabidMonkey]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Keep in mind that you can reduce the fog <span class="bbcode-i">density</span> and make the end distance farther back to avoid completely fogging over transparent cards like those trees there, and to avoid the obvious ‘fog’ effect, while still providing some ambience. Of course this is not compatible with the far Z clipping plane, unless you can never see that far without fog (and in that case, far z clip seems unnecessary anyway)</p>
<p>There is no 2D sky fog in Source, so if you want an overcast effect, you have to create a custom skybox of flat color with the exact same hue as the fog.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/l4d-general-mapping-questions/2133/29">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/l4d-general-mapping-questions/2133/29</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 09 Jun 2010 16:45:56 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2133-29</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/l4d-general-mapping-questions/2133.rss">L4D: General mapping questions</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>L4D: General mapping questions</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Madcat1030]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>But that would make the sky a solid wall of fog…  Which might be good for some other levels, but I think for this one, I’m going to cut the fog and do my best to keep it looking good.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/l4d-general-mapping-questions/2133/28">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/l4d-general-mapping-questions/2133/28</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 09 Jun 2010 14:45:31 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2133-28</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/l4d-general-mapping-questions/2133.rss">L4D: General mapping questions</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>L4D: General mapping questions</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Cameron_D]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Or make a custom skybox set to the fog colour</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/l4d-general-mapping-questions/2133/27">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/l4d-general-mapping-questions/2133/27</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 09 Jun 2010 07:57:26 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2133-27</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/l4d-general-mapping-questions/2133.rss">L4D: General mapping questions</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>L4D: General mapping questions</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Madcat1030]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>And it will what? Fade into the skybox?  Blarg, now I have to go play with 3d-skyboxery.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/l4d-general-mapping-questions/2133/26">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/l4d-general-mapping-questions/2133/26</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 09 Jun 2010 07:54:59 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2133-26</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/l4d-general-mapping-questions/2133.rss">L4D: General mapping questions</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>L4D: General mapping questions</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Cameron_D]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>You need to have the fog set up the same for the 3D skybox</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/l4d-general-mapping-questions/2133/25">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/l4d-general-mapping-questions/2133/25</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 09 Jun 2010 07:27:08 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2133-25</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/l4d-general-mapping-questions/2133.rss">L4D: General mapping questions</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>L4D: General mapping questions</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Madcat1030]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>HAY.  Necro-ing my own thread out of the olden-pages, cuz it’s along the same lines.  Except the map I’m in is now a L4D2 map (same map, just ported over to the l4d2 authoring tools version of Hammer.</p>
<p>So I was fooling around, filling out the above-ground portion of the level, making it look like some woods, not just a flat bunch of dirt in the middle of the sky, figured out that Player Clip brushes are what you use to block survivors and not infected, did that all around the woods, played through for continuity, discovered how to properly use the farz thingamajig, and now have a 3/4 complete map (not even touching nav-mapping yet), half of which is decorated.</p>
<p>Anywho.  I attempted to put fog in, and the result is pretty… chilling.</p>
<p><span alt="" class="broken-image" title="This image is broken"><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-unlink svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#unlink"></use></svg></span></p>
<p>How do I do this properly so a wall of fog shows up once the “fog” effect on the entities has reached 100%.  Right now, I’m only using an env_fog_controller, I take it I’m missing something.  Or am I thinking fog works in a way it doesn’t really work, and I should really just be choosing a fog color closer to the sky-color?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/l4d-general-mapping-questions/2133/24">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/l4d-general-mapping-questions/2133/24</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 09 Jun 2010 06:07:46 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2133-24</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/l4d-general-mapping-questions/2133.rss">L4D: General mapping questions</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>L4D: General mapping questions</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Madcat1030]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Thanks a bunch.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/l4d-general-mapping-questions/2133/23">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/l4d-general-mapping-questions/2133/23</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 14 Jan 2010 20:41:16 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2133-23</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/l4d-general-mapping-questions/2133.rss">L4D: General mapping questions</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>L4D: General mapping questions</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Angdraug]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Yes.</p>
<p>Tools -&gt; Options… -&gt; 3D views -&gt; Model render distance</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/l4d-general-mapping-questions/2133/22">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/l4d-general-mapping-questions/2133/22</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 14 Jan 2010 09:52:20 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2133-22</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/l4d-general-mapping-questions/2133.rss">L4D: General mapping questions</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>L4D: General mapping questions</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Madcat1030]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I just have one last question:  When working in hammer, is there a way to make it so props and the likes will be visible from a higher distance?  Some props become difficult to work around when they turn into a giant yellow/purple/red box.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/l4d-general-mapping-questions/2133/21">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/l4d-general-mapping-questions/2133/21</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 14 Jan 2010 00:37:34 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2133-21</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/l4d-general-mapping-questions/2133.rss">L4D: General mapping questions</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>L4D: General mapping questions</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Madcat1030]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Hey, just got back to my computer after X-mas break, and I booted up the L4D2 Dev Kit, continued with hint-brushing and func_detailing, and got it to the point where the compiler (which must have been optimized to work with W7, because it no longer crashes or freezes when I move my mouse, and I can even to THIS now without it crashing!) goes through the PortalFlow faze in about 5 minutes…</p>
<p>HOWEVER:  PortalFlow gets caught at “9…”…  I’ve just about done all I can do as far as optimizing goes without compromising my map.  Has anybody else ever had this problem?<br>
It’s still running, and has been for approximately five minutes since it hit “9…”, and I plan on letting it run for another fifteen minutes, but figured I’d post this, because I doubt it’s gonna move on.</p>
<p>EDIT:  Still running…  In the time I’ve spent trying to get this damned MAP to compile, I’ve started work on a more successful, if not rather mundane HL2 mod…  I think its only a matter of time before I drop this entirely, heh…  I think my big problem with this map is really smaller than I’m making it out to be…  I just have to make a drop a bit longer and make a tunnel section no longer inside of the world, but outside…  If that makes any sense.  That will be tomorrow’s project!</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/l4d-general-mapping-questions/2133/20">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/l4d-general-mapping-questions/2133/20</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 03 Jan 2010 06:24:30 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2133-20</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/l4d-general-mapping-questions/2133.rss">L4D: General mapping questions</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>L4D: General mapping questions</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Madcat1030]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>That I know.  That is one of the few things I know.  That’s why I’m making the tunnels square BEFORE making the arch-parts details.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/l4d-general-mapping-questions/2133/19">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/l4d-general-mapping-questions/2133/19</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 17 Dec 2009 04:03:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2133-19</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/l4d-general-mapping-questions/2133.rss">L4D: General mapping questions</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>L4D: General mapping questions</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Cameron_D]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Just remember, func_detail does <span class="bbcode-i">not</span> seal the world (nor do any other entitys)</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/l4d-general-mapping-questions/2133/18">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/l4d-general-mapping-questions/2133/18</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 17 Dec 2009 00:49:42 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2133-18</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/l4d-general-mapping-questions/2133.rss">L4D: General mapping questions</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>L4D: General mapping questions</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Madcat1030]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Oh wow.  The whole friggen thing was details, lol.  I’mma work on that.  I’m gonna make all my tunnels square and func_detail out the arched portions, I think that’ll do something for it.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/l4d-general-mapping-questions/2133/17">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/l4d-general-mapping-questions/2133/17</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 16 Dec 2009 23:28:29 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2133-17</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/l4d-general-mapping-questions/2133.rss">L4D: General mapping questions</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>L4D: General mapping questions</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[RabidMonkey]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Madcat1030">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/m/9f8e36/40.png" class="avatar"> Madcat1030:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>New Question:  How are func_details treated differently, if at all, by lighting?<br>
Will I lose lighting quality on them or will making a tunnel a square and making the “arches” func_details keep all the light-y-goodness and cut down on leaf-splitting badness?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>They aren’t affected any differently by lighting. (although if you have huge wall sections tied to func_detail some light may seep through on the edges). For all intents and purposes they are standard world geometry with the exception that they don’t block visibility. Anything like door frames, window trimming, small barriers or railings etc should be tied to func_detail if they don’t block visibility significantly. Anything cylindrical or angular should also be tied to a func_detail unless it is gigantic and necessary for it to be part of the world (the curved silo walls in c2a2b is world geometry, for example.)</p>
<p>VIS should really be taking under a minute or two on a quad-core, and your portal files (if properly optimized) should be free of areas with lots of really tiny portal ‘clusters’ and look rather neat (<a href="https://images.rabidmnky.com/etc/detail_1.jpg" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">this</a> is what you’re trying to avoid). As mentioned it should take longer and longer with each dot it adds to the compile log but if it’s taking over 5 minutes and not finished then there are some optimization problems that should be fixed. (The compiler will often say ‘not responding’ during the compile process, but this is normal if you are compiling through Hammer). The reason it finished RAD and was playable in-game but everything is visible is that the VIS process didn’t get a chance to complete, so it’s just rendering everything because it the map has no visibility tables to use.</p>
<p>If it’s taking ages to compile, it probably needs more func_details! Good portions of maps are often constructed of them. Here are two examples, one by Valve;</p>
<p><a href="https://developer.valvesoftware.com/w/images/c/cb/C17plaza-worldbrush.jpg" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">C17 Trainstation</a></p>
<p>L4D map <a href="https://images.rabidmnky.com/WIP/l4d/visgroups_1.jpg" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">with</a> and <a href="https://images.rabidmnky.com/WIP/l4d/visgroups_2.jpg" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">without</a> func_detail and models</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/l4d-general-mapping-questions/2133/16">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/l4d-general-mapping-questions/2133/16</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 16 Dec 2009 22:20:49 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2133-16</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/l4d-general-mapping-questions/2133.rss">L4D: General mapping questions</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>L4D: General mapping questions</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Madcat1030]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Found another unhappy area in my map.  There was a…  specific hallway designed in a way to give off a certain feel in which the doors were made in a way other than regular L4D doors, they actually had a frame rather than a decal on the wall around them.  I simply turned the frames to func_details, and now the rooms are separated by visleaves, but no longer ripped to shreds by the visleaves flying out of the frames.</p>
<p>EDIT: My latest attempt to compile (cut short by an accidental iced-tea-bottle/power-button incident) was running a few minutes ago, and it was only taking 64-80% of my CPU…  I think the fact that it’s no longer raping my computer means I’m doing something right.</p>
<p>UPDATE:  visclustered the aboveground area, started compiling five minutes ago.  It was at 6 and one dot when I left the room a few moments ago.</p>
<p>UPDATE:  I just went back to my room.  It’s only been like 10 minutes, and its already at 9 and two dots.  That’s 10 minutes from starting.  I’m gonna viscluster the rest of the aboveground area AROUND the lone house, and that’ll make it even quicker, hopefully.  Right now it’s only on one side of the house.  By the way, 9 and three dots.</p>
<p>So, up to now I have reduced the portalclusters count from 5000 something to 2072, and the numportals count from 25,000 something down to 6356.  I think with a little more hint brushing, I could do even better.</p>
<p>Final update on this post unless it completes successfully:  Five minutes since my last post, and its still on 9 and three dots…  Is there possibly a known condition where it hangs on to the last tick before completing?  That would make me feel better…</p>
<p>I lied.  It didn’t work.  Got to 9 and three dots, sat there for like… 12 hours, then I ended it.  It moved onto VRAD, and finished.  In-game, lighting was fine, but I toggled mat_wireframe 1, and all objects were being rendered all the time.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/l4d-general-mapping-questions/2133/15">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/l4d-general-mapping-questions/2133/15</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 16 Dec 2009 14:51:35 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2133-15</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/l4d-general-mapping-questions/2133.rss">L4D: General mapping questions</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>L4D: General mapping questions</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Cameron_D]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Care to post a screenshot from in hammer with func details on and off?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/l4d-general-mapping-questions/2133/14">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/l4d-general-mapping-questions/2133/14</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 16 Dec 2009 12:59:12 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2133-14</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/l4d-general-mapping-questions/2133.rss">L4D: General mapping questions</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>L4D: General mapping questions</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Madcat1030]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Yeah, well it decided to crash at 9 and three dots, so I’mma go through and do some serious hint-work.  Make sure I didn’t leave any massive-polygon behemoth’s laying around…  I func_detailed the well, it’s base, and several gate-structures in the level, and that made it get to 5 in about five minutes, and from there it just took exponentially longer.  I have a feeling there is ONE LARGE thing that I’m missing.  Gonna take a closer look at the portal file today.</p>
<p>I feel like if I get this map to compile right, I won’t have trouble in the future.</p>
<p>New Question:  How are func_details treated differently, if at all, by lighting?<br>
Will I lose lighting quality on them or will making a tunnel a square and making the “arches” func_details keep all the light-y-goodness and cut down on leaf-splitting badness?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/l4d-general-mapping-questions/2133/13">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/l4d-general-mapping-questions/2133/13</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 16 Dec 2009 12:04:18 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2133-13</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/l4d-general-mapping-questions/2133.rss">L4D: General mapping questions</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>L4D: General mapping questions</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Cameron_D]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>If you have a 3.6ghz quad, and your map is taking that long to compile… You need some serious optimisation. I can compile most of the TF2 stock maps in 15-20 mins.</p>
<p>If you could easily take on board the link in my other post, maybe take a look at <a href="https://optimization.interlopers.net/" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://optimization.interlopers.net/</a> for a more detailed explanation on optimising. It also explains stuff like func_detail in more uhh… detail (no pun intended  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/wink.png?v=9" title=":wink:" class="emoji" alt=":wink:">  )</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/l4d-general-mapping-questions/2133/12">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/l4d-general-mapping-questions/2133/12</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 16 Dec 2009 09:00:45 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2133-12</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/l4d-general-mapping-questions/2133.rss">L4D: General mapping questions</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>L4D: General mapping questions</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Madcat1030]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Quad-core, and I think 3.33 gHz.  I’m not at it and can’t think too well at 2 in the morning, so if I’m far off, meh, I’m far off.  Maybe it was 3.66gHz…  maybe it wasn’t any of them.</p>
<p>Also, VVIS just eats up the whole damned thing.  100% usage all the time.</p>
<p>And it’s still “Not responding”.  Started not responding bout a half-hour ago.  I just turned off the monitor, set the volume up high, and am going to bed, hoping to be woken up by a really loud reloading sound some time in the next few hours…</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/l4d-general-mapping-questions/2133/11">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/l4d-general-mapping-questions/2133/11</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 16 Dec 2009 06:44:15 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2133-11</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/l4d-general-mapping-questions/2133.rss">L4D: General mapping questions</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>L4D: General mapping questions</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Cameron_D]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>How many CPU cores @ what speed?<br>
And yeah, as it progresses it takes longer and longer to do each calculation.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/l4d-general-mapping-questions/2133/10">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/l4d-general-mapping-questions/2133/10</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 16 Dec 2009 05:28:14 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2133-10</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/l4d-general-mapping-questions/2133.rss">L4D: General mapping questions</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>L4D: General mapping questions</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Madcat1030]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Thanks for the link, that’s a really nice and understandable explanation.</p>
<p>By the way… 9 and two dots.  ONLY 1 DOT TO GO!</p>
<p>9 and 3 dots…  I have a horrible feeling that this last dot is never going to finish…</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/l4d-general-mapping-questions/2133/9">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/l4d-general-mapping-questions/2133/9</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 16 Dec 2009 03:58:12 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2133-9</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/l4d-general-mapping-questions/2133.rss">L4D: General mapping questions</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>L4D: General mapping questions</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Cameron_D]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><a href="https://www.nodraw.net/2009/12/optimization-in-source-a-practical-demonstration/" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://www.nodraw.net/2009/12/optimization-in-source-a-practical-demonstration/</a></p>
<p>Practical uses of your hint/optimisation stuff.</p>
<p>The compiler stops responding in Vista/7. Try using VBCT (Although I don’t know if that supports L4D)</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/l4d-general-mapping-questions/2133/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/l4d-general-mapping-questions/2133/8</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 16 Dec 2009 00:53:16 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2133-8</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/l4d-general-mapping-questions/2133.rss">L4D: General mapping questions</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>L4D: General mapping questions</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Madcat1030]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Meant to say Func_detail.  Also, it just popped up to 6 and no dots.  It seems to be taking exponentially longer.  What is the general number of portalclusters and numportals?  Like, but general, I mean a max possibly.</p>
<p>I’m at 2837 portalclusters and 8597 numportals.</p>
<p>Oh, I also encountered something, on my computer, if I try to do ANYTHING other than move the mouse, the compiler will stop responding, but keep working, NEVER ending.  I’m using my netbook to write this post now.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/l4d-general-mapping-questions/2133/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/l4d-general-mapping-questions/2133/7</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 16 Dec 2009 00:48:11 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2133-7</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/l4d-general-mapping-questions/2133.rss">L4D: General mapping questions</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>L4D: General mapping questions</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[RabidMonkey]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I just checked and it’s there…just tie your brush to an entity and start typing ‘viscluster’ in the dropdown box and it should pull it up.</p>
<p>func_brush or any other brush-based entity won’t cause leaf splitting, but they also use up entdata as they have special functions (they can be toggled on and off, etc) and they also contribute to brush-based rendering costs significantly more - the preferable option is to tie them to a func_detail - this ‘entity’ won’t split the visleaves but it doesn’t take up entdata either as the entity data for details is discarded during the compile process - for all intents and purposes they’re standard world geometry with the exception that they don’t wreck your visleaves. Good portions of your map will probably end up being func_details.</p>
<p>Skip and nodraw serve different purposes - nodraw will seal the map from the void, will split leaves, block visibility etc; it basically acts as a normal world brush except it doesn’t get drawn. Skip doesn’t do anything at all and the faces are discarded immediately during BSP - it’s used on the sides of hint brushes where you don’t want to split leaves, for example.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/l4d-general-mapping-questions/2133/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/l4d-general-mapping-questions/2133/6</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 16 Dec 2009 00:35:07 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2133-6</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/l4d-general-mapping-questions/2133.rss">L4D: General mapping questions</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
