<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>BSP holes in the dam [Fixed]</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/bsp-holes-in-the-dam-fixed/10111</link>
    <description>Your dam is leaking.

[img]https://cloud.steampowered.com/ugc/938129520109277869/7941B85DF2DDEBCE329148E2E2C54B2FC993727F/[/img]

Also as a bonus, some other misc things:

1. It&#39;s REALLY hard to get the hat through the teleporters.  I would suggest NOT allowing the hat to teleport on its own if the player is carrying it, and instead when the player teleports the hat comes with them and the player is still holding it.  Alternatively, if the hat could be held similarly to how the gnome works in L4D2, this would also solve that problem.
2. MASSIVE slowdown while the second garg was chasing me (before you use the air strike to kill it).  Not sure why, maybe the physics from the garg messing with the cars?
3. Another MASSIVE slowdown in the final room when the teleporter particles are online (I think the single beam was OK, it was the secondary beams that really did it).  It makes the game near unplayable unless you are looking away but even that doesn&#39;t fully work. I suspect this is particle or lighting related slowdown.  These are the only two places where framerate really dropped for me and I reloaded in both cases and saw the slowdown happened at the same point.  I didn&#39;t know about the showbudget thing, if I find myself in game at those points I will record those values.
4. In the Lambda Core, the pump and tank rooms (4 total, IIRC) each have a set of doors with a connecting hallway on the upper level.  Some of the buttons for the doors (both sides) are really weird.  The buttons move vertically through the ceiling!  Lol.  I didn&#39;t take a screenshot since you wouldn&#39;t be able to see them moving.

Also I wanna say I love the stuff you did with the game.  Moving the crowbar pickup later was great (I like those &quot;improvisation&quot; gameplay bits in HL mods before you get weapons).  You really improved the NPCs to make them more integral to the storyline it seemed... at one point, you go and help a security officer find a weapons cache.  If he survives with you, the guard at the cache and him have a conversation.  If not (or he falls behind) the guard just talks to you in an entirely different conversation.  I thought that was awesome.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 16 Sep 2012 15:03:39 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>In-game Issues (Mod)</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/bsp-holes-in-the-dam-fixed/10111.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>BSP holes in the dam [Fixed]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[shef2010]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Map - <span class="bbcode-b">[COLOR=‘SeaGreen’]bm_c2a5a</span></p>
<p><div class="lightbox-wrapper"><a class="lightbox" href="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/original/3X/d/b/db5abd10f3c8e2ec781b68c05121f7da8f7880af.jpeg" data-download-href="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/db5abd10f3c8e2ec781b68c05121f7da8f7880af" title=""><img src="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/optimized/3X/d/b/db5abd10f3c8e2ec781b68c05121f7da8f7880af_2_690x431.jpeg" alt="" data-base62-sha1="viuYi6U7x2nD55psHRniiQrpgXZ" width="690" height="431" srcset="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/optimized/3X/d/b/db5abd10f3c8e2ec781b68c05121f7da8f7880af_2_690x431.jpeg, https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/optimized/3X/d/b/db5abd10f3c8e2ec781b68c05121f7da8f7880af_2_1035x646.jpeg 1.5x, https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/optimized/3X/d/b/db5abd10f3c8e2ec781b68c05121f7da8f7880af_2_1380x862.jpeg 2x" data-small-upload="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/optimized/3X/d/b/db5abd10f3c8e2ec781b68c05121f7da8f7880af_2_10x10.png"><div class="meta"><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-far-image svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#far-image"></use></svg><span class="filename"></span><span class="informations">1680×1050 299 KB</span><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-discourse-expand svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#discourse-expand"></use></svg></div></a></div> <div class="lightbox-wrapper"><a class="lightbox" href="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/original/3X/c/b/cb44b88f307166d82518abda2b5bdf2da7960da8.jpeg" data-download-href="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/cb44b88f307166d82518abda2b5bdf2da7960da8" title=""><img src="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/optimized/3X/c/b/cb44b88f307166d82518abda2b5bdf2da7960da8_2_690x431.jpeg" alt="" data-base62-sha1="t0c9WFNFwFbnwb0OOI0cZGkH3fi" width="690" height="431" srcset="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/optimized/3X/c/b/cb44b88f307166d82518abda2b5bdf2da7960da8_2_690x431.jpeg, https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/optimized/3X/c/b/cb44b88f307166d82518abda2b5bdf2da7960da8_2_1035x646.jpeg 1.5x, https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/optimized/3X/c/b/cb44b88f307166d82518abda2b5bdf2da7960da8_2_1380x862.jpeg 2x" data-small-upload="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/optimized/3X/c/b/cb44b88f307166d82518abda2b5bdf2da7960da8_2_10x10.png"><div class="meta"><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-far-image svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#far-image"></use></svg><span class="filename"></span><span class="informations">1680×1050 110 KB</span><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-discourse-expand svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#discourse-expand"></use></svg></div></a></div></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/bsp-holes-in-the-dam-fixed/10111/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/bsp-holes-in-the-dam-fixed/10111/3</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 16 Sep 2012 15:03:39 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-10111-3</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/bsp-holes-in-the-dam-fixed/10111.rss">BSP holes in the dam [Fixed]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>BSP holes in the dam [Fixed]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypt]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="The MAZZTer">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 The MAZZTer:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Your dam is leaking.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Haha! It’s funny from both a player and a developer’s point of view, heh heh.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/bsp-holes-in-the-dam-fixed/10111/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/bsp-holes-in-the-dam-fixed/10111/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 16 Sep 2012 02:30:44 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-10111-2</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/bsp-holes-in-the-dam-fixed/10111.rss">BSP holes in the dam [Fixed]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>BSP holes in the dam [Fixed]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[The_MAZZTer]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Your dam is leaking.</p>
<p><span alt="" class="broken-image" title="This image is broken"><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-unlink svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#unlink"></use></svg></span></p>
<p>Also as a bonus, some other misc things:</p>
<ol>
<li>It’s REALLY hard to get the hat through the teleporters.  I would suggest NOT allowing the hat to teleport on its own if the player is carrying it, and instead when the player teleports the hat comes with them and the player is still holding it.  Alternatively, if the hat could be held similarly to how the gnome works in L4D2, this would also solve that problem.</li>
<li>MASSIVE slowdown while the second garg was chasing me (before you use the air strike to kill it).  Not sure why, maybe the physics from the garg messing with the cars?</li>
<li>Another MASSIVE slowdown in the final room when the teleporter particles are online (I think the single beam was OK, it was the secondary beams that really did it).  It makes the game near unplayable unless you are looking away but even that doesn’t fully work. I suspect this is particle or lighting related slowdown.  These are the only two places where framerate really dropped for me and I reloaded in both cases and saw the slowdown happened at the same point.  I didn’t know about the showbudget thing, if I find myself in game at those points I will record those values.</li>
<li>In the Lambda Core, the pump and tank rooms (4 total, IIRC) each have a set of doors with a connecting hallway on the upper level.  Some of the buttons for the doors (both sides) are really weird.  The buttons move vertically through the ceiling!  Lol.  I didn’t take a screenshot since you wouldn’t be able to see them moving.</li>
</ol>
<p>Also I wanna say I love the stuff you did with the game.  Moving the crowbar pickup later was great (I like those “improvisation” gameplay bits in HL mods before you get weapons).  You really improved the NPCs to make them more integral to the storyline it seemed… at one point, you go and help a security officer find a weapons cache.  If he survives with you, the guard at the cache and him have a conversation.  If not (or he falls behind) the guard just talks to you in an entirely different conversation.  I thought that was awesome.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/bsp-holes-in-the-dam-fixed/10111/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/bsp-holes-in-the-dam-fixed/10111/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 16 Sep 2012 02:28:58 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-10111-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/bsp-holes-in-the-dam-fixed/10111.rss">BSP holes in the dam [Fixed]</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
