<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Biodude&#39;s bugs [Fixed]</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/biodudes-bugs-fixed/9986</link>
    <description>Found a few bugs while playing, just thought I&#39;d share.

In lambda core in the room with that circle that moves up and down around where all the portals are, I stood on there and went all the way up, then It got me stuck half way into the ceiling, couldn&#39;t move.

In the start of forget about freeman, I found that if you blow up the trip mine before the guy walks into it, the door will shut and the breakable glass to open the door button is unbreakable, thus making it impossible to progress

I see there is a normal reload for the pistol in the model viewer, but it isn&#39;t used. Any chances of adding it in?

I love the mod guys, really great work, just trying to help with any small things I find.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 15 Sep 2012 19:51:52 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>In-game Issues (Mod)</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/biodudes-bugs-fixed/9986.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Biodude&#39;s bugs [Fixed]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[biodude]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Found a few bugs while playing, just thought I’d share.</p>
<p>In lambda core in the room with that circle that moves up and down around where all the portals are, I stood on there and went all the way up, then It got me stuck half way into the ceiling, couldn’t move.</p>
<p>In the start of forget about freeman, I found that if you blow up the trip mine before the guy walks into it, the door will shut and the breakable glass to open the door button is unbreakable, thus making it impossible to progress</p>
<p>I see there is a normal reload for the pistol in the model viewer, but it isn’t used. Any chances of adding it in?</p>
<p>I love the mod guys, really great work, just trying to help with any small things I find.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/biodudes-bugs-fixed/9986/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/biodudes-bugs-fixed/9986/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 15 Sep 2012 19:51:52 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9986-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/biodudes-bugs-fixed/9986.rss">Biodude&#39;s bugs [Fixed]</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
