<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>What Game Should I Play Next?</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/what-game-should-i-play-next/11180</link>
    <description>This thread is intended for a personal inquiry as to which game I should play next (post Black Mesa, of course). But maybe it could also be a spin-off of the &quot;What Game Did You Play Today?&quot; thread. 
As I&#39;m sure some cant make up their minds in similar situations. What with our steam lists exponentially growing and limited time.

In any case, I&#39;m torn as to which Sp game I should play next. I&#39;ve narrowed it down to these 5 (games that are on my steam list that I&#39;ve never played).  

Batman: Arkham City
Metro 2033
Fable: Lost Chapters
Hitman Blood Money
Alan Wake.
--------------
Oh, and also MGS: Peace Walker for ps3

Obviously some of these cant even be compared but I&#39;m looking for the most enjoyment per time spent. Thanks for the input.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 28 Sep 2012 06:34:03 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Technology and Gaming</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/what-game-should-i-play-next/11180.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>What Game Should I Play Next?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[k3nny1550]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Peace Walker is probably my favorite out of that list. Alan Wake and Blood Money are good too. Arkham City was too samey for me- Arkham Asylum was great, though.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/what-game-should-i-play-next/11180/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/what-game-should-i-play-next/11180/2</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Sep 2012 06:34:03 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11180-2</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/what-game-should-i-play-next/11180.rss">What Game Should I Play Next?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>What Game Should I Play Next?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[TheKeeper]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>This thread is intended for a personal inquiry as to which game I should play next (post Black Mesa, of course). But maybe it could also be a spin-off of the “What Game Did You Play Today?” thread.<br>
As I’m sure some cant make up their minds in similar situations. What with our steam lists exponentially growing and limited time.</p>
<p>In any case, I’m torn as to which Sp game I should play next. I’ve narrowed it down to these 5 (games that are on my steam list that I’ve never played).</p>
<h2>Batman: Arkham City<br>
Metro 2033<br>
Fable: Lost Chapters<br>
Hitman Blood Money<br>
Alan Wake.</h2>
<p>Oh, and also MGS: Peace Walker for ps3</p>
<p>Obviously some of these cant even be compared but I’m looking for the most enjoyment per time spent. Thanks for the input.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/what-game-should-i-play-next/11180/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/what-game-should-i-play-next/11180/1</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Sep 2012 06:30:43 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11180-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/what-game-should-i-play-next/11180.rss">What Game Should I Play Next?</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
