<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Unofficial Official Game Chat</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/unofficial-official-game-chat/11208</link>
    <description>This is basically to help keep the threads from being cluttered with small topics that only get a few posts. Pretty much any topic relating to games and the technology around them. I&#39;m not sure why this hasn&#39;t been made yet.

Anyone remember when good graphics were made by good models and equally as good textures, instead of bad models with super bump mapped textures... good times, good times.


______
On a side note, anyone have a giftable copy of HL2: Episode Two sitting around? The Cinematic Mod requires the GCF&#39;s from it.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 29 Sep 2012 21:24:39 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Technology and Gaming</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/unofficial-official-game-chat/11208.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Unofficial Official Game Chat</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[MDIGN]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>This is basically to help keep the threads from being cluttered with small topics that only get a few posts. Pretty much any topic relating to games and the technology around them. I’m not sure why this hasn’t been made yet.</p>
<p>Anyone remember when good graphics were made by good models and equally as good textures, instead of bad models with super bump mapped textures… good times, good times.</p>
<hr>
<p>On a side note, anyone have a giftable copy of HL2: Episode Two sitting around? The Cinematic Mod requires the GCF’s from it.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/unofficial-official-game-chat/11208/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/unofficial-official-game-chat/11208/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 29 Sep 2012 21:24:39 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11208-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/unofficial-official-game-chat/11208.rss">Unofficial Official Game Chat</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
