<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Three NPC Sound Bugs - Abrams, Bullsquid, Zombie</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/three-npc-sound-bugs-abrams-bullsquid-zombie/13999</link>
    <description>I&#39;ve found three different sound bugs:

* [b]Abrams [/b]- Every Abrams tank in the game seems to constantly play its looping turret rotation sound, abrams_turret.wav, even if the turret isn&#39;t rotating.  The sound just keeps playing until the tank is destroyed. (Bug not in mod)
* [b]Bullsquid [/b]- Bullsquids play their spit sound effect twice, with a slight delay between, whenever the player tricks a bullsquid into having to stop its spit attack because the player hid behind an obstacle--out of sight of the bullsquid. (Bug not in mod)
* [b]Zombie [/b]- Zombies don&#39;t ever play their death sound effects.  If killed by gunfire, zombies simply play their pain sound as they turn into a ragdoll. [b](Bug *is* also in mod[/b])
[b]Edit[/b]: Using &quot;snd_visualize 1,&quot; I was able to see that in the mod too the Abrams does in fact keep looping its turret rotation sound.  [b]BUT, [/b]in the mod, the sound is only audible when the turret [i]is [/i]actually rotating.  According to what I can see then from &quot;snd_show 1,&quot; the sound of the rotation sound is drastically decreased, nearly to the point of silence, whenever the turret isn&#39;t moving--and then increases whenever it is.  [b]So it seems that the retail version simply isn&#39;t decreasing the volume of the turret sound whenever it&#39;s not rotating.[/b]</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 12 May 2015 18:30:07 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>In-game Issues</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/three-npc-sound-bugs-abrams-bullsquid-zombie/13999.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Three NPC Sound Bugs - Abrams, Bullsquid, Zombie</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[coldroll]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I’ve noticed the bugs above as well, also if I may add when the HECU soldiers are killed they don’t have any death sounds anymore as well.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/three-npc-sound-bugs-abrams-bullsquid-zombie/13999/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/three-npc-sound-bugs-abrams-bullsquid-zombie/13999/2</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 12 May 2015 18:30:07 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13999-2</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/three-npc-sound-bugs-abrams-bullsquid-zombie/13999.rss">Three NPC Sound Bugs - Abrams, Bullsquid, Zombie</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Three NPC Sound Bugs - Abrams, Bullsquid, Zombie</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Shask]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I’ve found three different sound bugs:</p>
<ul>
<li>
<span class="bbcode-b">Abrams </span>- Every Abrams tank in the game seems to constantly play its looping turret rotation sound, abrams_turret.wav, even if the turret isn’t rotating.  The sound just keeps playing until the tank is destroyed. (Bug not in mod)</li>
<li>
<span class="bbcode-b">Bullsquid </span>- Bullsquids play their spit sound effect twice, with a slight delay between, whenever the player tricks a bullsquid into having to stop its spit attack because the player hid behind an obstacle–out of sight of the bullsquid. (Bug not in mod)</li>
<li>
<span class="bbcode-b">Zombie </span>- Zombies don’t ever play their death sound effects.  If killed by gunfire, zombies simply play their pain sound as they turn into a ragdoll. <span class="bbcode-b">(Bug <em>is</em> also in mod</span>)<br>
<span class="bbcode-b">Edit</span>: Using “snd_visualize 1,” I was able to see that in the mod too the Abrams does in fact keep looping its turret rotation sound.  <span class="bbcode-b">BUT, </span>in the mod, the sound is only audible when the turret <span class="bbcode-i">is </span>actually rotating.  According to what I can see then from “snd_show 1,” the sound of the rotation sound is drastically decreased, nearly to the point of silence, whenever the turret isn’t moving–and then increases whenever it is.  <span class="bbcode-b">So it seems that the retail version simply isn’t decreasing the volume of the turret sound whenever it’s not rotating.</span>
</li>
</ul>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/three-npc-sound-bugs-abrams-bullsquid-zombie/13999/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/three-npc-sound-bugs-abrams-bullsquid-zombie/13999/1</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 12 May 2015 04:32:40 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13999-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/three-npc-sound-bugs-abrams-bullsquid-zombie/13999.rss">Three NPC Sound Bugs - Abrams, Bullsquid, Zombie</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
