<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>QE Crash; Fall dmg on map load</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/qe-crash-fall-dmg-on-map-load/15093</link>
    <description>The other night I was playing through Questionable Ethics and I got to the point where you burn a hole through the wall with the big laser. Upon going through the hole, the only way down is a steep drop down a pipe. It&#39;s very easy to take fall damage if you&#39;re not careful going down this pipe, which isn&#39;t an issue on it&#39;s own, it&#39;s just part of the game.

The problem I discovered is, upon taking fall damage, there is a chance you take that fall damage just as the map load transition is triggered. This caused the game to freeze up on that loading screen for about a minute before crashing to desktop. I&#39;m not sure how easily this can be repeated because I don&#39;t know how close the timing of the map load and fall damage have to be.

[url]https://drive.google.com/file/d/0B5OB2kbaznlKdlgtQnpjYlJodDQ/view?usp=sharing[/url]

--------------------------------

Windows 7 SP1 64-bit
GTX 570
i5-2400 3.1Ghz</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 09 Feb 2017 18:06:36 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>In-game Issues</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/qe-crash-fall-dmg-on-map-load/15093.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>QE Crash; Fall dmg on map load</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[MistaX88_COF]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>The other night I was playing through Questionable Ethics and I got to the point where you burn a hole through the wall with the big laser. Upon going through the hole, the only way down is a steep drop down a pipe. It’s very easy to take fall damage if you’re not careful going down this pipe, which isn’t an issue on it’s own, it’s just part of the game.</p>
<p>The problem I discovered is, upon taking fall damage, there is a chance you take that fall damage just as the map load transition is triggered. This caused the game to freeze up on that loading screen for about a minute before crashing to desktop. I’m not sure how easily this can be repeated because I don’t know how close the timing of the map load and fall damage have to be.</p>
<p><a href="https://drive.google.com/file/d/0B5OB2kbaznlKdlgtQnpjYlJodDQ/view?usp=sharing" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://drive.google.com/file/d/0B5OB2kbaznlKdlgtQnpjYlJodDQ/view?usp=sharing</a></p>
<hr>
<p>Windows 7 SP1 64-bit<br>
GTX 570<br>
i5-2400 3.1Ghz</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/qe-crash-fall-dmg-on-map-load/15093/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/qe-crash-fall-dmg-on-map-load/15093/1</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 09 Feb 2017 18:06:36 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-15093-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/qe-crash-fall-dmg-on-map-load/15093.rss">QE Crash; Fall dmg on map load</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
