<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Surface tension helicopter not appearing?</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/surface-tension-helicopter-not-appearing/63058</link>
    <description>Just purchased this and great job love the remake.
But I have a problem once you cleared out the storage facility as you come out you are supposed to be met by a helicopter  you take it out and can move on to the right but there is a large bolder which can not be passed so I guess the chopper blows that up but I can not move forward as no chopper appears????  reloaded game didn&#39;t help.  can you use NoClip to get pass the bolder and no chopper problem and move on if so how to use no clip as that is not working either! with cheats enabled thanks for any help anyone can suggest.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 23 Mar 2020 13:33:09 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Off Topic</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/surface-tension-helicopter-not-appearing/63058.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Surface tension helicopter not appearing?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[CitizenSmith]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Just purchased this and great job love the remake.<br>
But I have a problem once you cleared out the storage facility as you come out you are supposed to be met by a helicopter  you take it out and can move on to the right but there is a large bolder which can not be passed so I guess the chopper blows that up but I can not move forward as no chopper appears???  reloaded game didn’t help.  can you use NoClip to get pass the bolder and no chopper problem and move on if so how to use no clip as that is not working either! with cheats enabled thanks for any help anyone can suggest.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/surface-tension-helicopter-not-appearing/63058/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/surface-tension-helicopter-not-appearing/63058/1</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Mar 2020 13:33:09 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-63058-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/surface-tension-helicopter-not-appearing/63058.rss">Surface tension helicopter not appearing?</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
