<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Black Mesa themed TF2 workshop items</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/black-mesa-themed-tf2-workshop-items/13994</link>
    <description>[url]https://steamcommunity.com/id/bmworkshop/myworkshopfiles/?appid=440[/url]
Well, it&#39;s awesome and all, but seems that it doesn&#39;t have as many items as it could of have :/
Well, actually I had an idea about Half Life themed TF2 weapons a LONG time ago, even before the workshop, but I can&#39;t rally make those myself  :stuck_out_tongue:  So I&#39;ll just share some of them and hope that maybe somebody from BM workshop  picks them up :
1. &quot; Scientist&#39;s assistant&quot; - a spas 12 shotgun for engineer - Stats:  -15% firing rate; +10% more accurate; +Alt-Fire - Fire both barrels for some metal cost and decreased rate of fire
2. &quot; Browning&#39;s medicine&quot; - M2 .50 cal machine gun for heavy - Stats : -20% firing rate; -15% movement speed while deployed; -every bullet unit shoots 2 bullet instead of 4; *60% accuracy (neutral point because it reduces weapons effectiveness in close quarters) . +20% damage *damage ramp-up and fall-off  is reduced; + no spin-up noise
3. &quot;Crossed Assassin&quot; - black mesa crossbow for  sniper : + silent and produces no kill message ( optionally cloacks the body after a Headshot kill ); + 30% faster charge time; +20% damage on headshots; - projectiles aren&#39;t hitscan and have travel time according to the charge; - requires reload after every 5 shots ( basically has a magazine of 5 bolts); -does no damage to buildings ( - 10 ammo optionally)
4.  &quot; HECU PDA&quot; - replaces engineer&#39;s turret with 2 buildable HECU turrets. Stats: +10% faster build time * health and fire rate are exactly the half  normal LVL 2 turret. *requires 150 metal. * while scanning the area uses a visible laser beam of teams collour to aim, but aims a little faster. - can&#39;t be upgraded or ( maybe) resupplied.
5.  &quot; Snake&#39;s Hand Cannon &quot; - colt python for spy ( i know there is one already, but this is more similar to half-life one, having nickel plating and all  :smiley:   :stuck_out_tongue:  ) : +10% damage. - 25% fire rate ( to match the same rate as in Black mesa one), -20% reload speed; +30% damage on headshots.
6. &quot; Stalker&#39;s stinger&quot; - black mesa rocket launcher for the soldier :  - 3 clip capacity; + a laser guidance for the rocke t * can&#39;t be reloaded while the rocket is in the air. + rocket can be detonated midair;  + 15% rocket flying speed; + 30% damage on direct hits.
7.  &quot; Lazy Trapper&quot; - a sticky bomb launcher for the demo which launches trip mines -  * launched tripmines emit laser beams; tripmines detonate when the beam is crossed. - can only deploy 5 tripmines; *Alt fire detonates all tripmines set, but detonation is delayed a little and there is some noise indication. +20% damage and blast radius;  - tripmines travel 40% less the distance of ordinary stikies
8. &quot; Ghost Frier&quot; - a gluon gun for pyro - +100% range. - 75% afterburn damage; +15% direct damage; * disintegrates killed enemies similarly to Cow mangler; * alt fire creates a small field for 35 ammo which destroys all projectiles; +30% damage to buildings.
Feel free to discuss and write down your own ideas  :slight_smile:</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 11 May 2015 19:09:11 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>The Cafeteria</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/black-mesa-themed-tf2-workshop-items/13994.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Black Mesa themed TF2 workshop items</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Darth_Giorgi]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/id/bmworkshop/myworkshopfiles/?appid=440" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://steamcommunity.com/id/bmworkshop/myworkshopfiles/?appid=440</a><br>
Well, it’s awesome and all, but seems that it doesn’t have as many items as it could of have <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/confused.png?v=9" title=":confused:" class="emoji" alt=":confused:"><br>
Well, actually I had an idea about Half Life themed TF2 weapons a LONG time ago, even before the workshop, but I can’t rally make those myself  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=9" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:">  So I’ll just share some of them and hope that maybe somebody from BM workshop  picks them up :</p>
<ol>
<li>" Scientist’s assistant" - a spas 12 shotgun for engineer - Stats:  -15% firing rate; +10% more accurate; +Alt-Fire - Fire both barrels for some metal cost and decreased rate of fire</li>
<li>" Browning’s medicine" - M2 .50 cal machine gun for heavy - Stats : -20% firing rate; -15% movement speed while deployed; -every bullet unit shoots 2 bullet instead of 4; *60% accuracy (neutral point because it reduces weapons effectiveness in close quarters) . +20% damage *damage ramp-up and fall-off  is reduced; + no spin-up noise</li>
<li>“Crossed Assassin” - black mesa crossbow for  sniper : + silent and produces no kill message ( optionally cloacks the body after a Headshot kill ); + 30% faster charge time; +20% damage on headshots; - projectiles aren’t hitscan and have travel time according to the charge; - requires reload after every 5 shots ( basically has a magazine of 5 bolts); -does no damage to buildings ( - 10 ammo optionally)</li>
<li>" HECU PDA" - replaces engineer’s turret with 2 buildable HECU turrets. Stats: +10% faster build time * health and fire rate are exactly the half  normal LVL 2 turret. *requires 150 metal. * while scanning the area uses a visible laser beam of teams collour to aim, but aims a little faster. - can’t be upgraded or ( maybe) resupplied.</li>
<li>" Snake’s Hand Cannon " - colt python for spy ( i know there is one already, but this is more similar to half-life one, having nickel plating and all  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/smiley.png?v=9" title=":smiley:" class="emoji" alt=":smiley:">   <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=9" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:">  ) : +10% damage. - 25% fire rate ( to match the same rate as in Black mesa one), -20% reload speed; +30% damage on headshots.</li>
<li>" Stalker’s stinger" - black mesa rocket launcher for the soldier :  - 3 clip capacity; + a laser guidance for the rocke t * can’t be reloaded while the rocket is in the air. + rocket can be detonated midair;  + 15% rocket flying speed; + 30% damage on direct hits.</li>
<li>" Lazy Trapper" - a sticky bomb launcher for the demo which launches trip mines -  * launched tripmines emit laser beams; tripmines detonate when the beam is crossed. - can only deploy 5 tripmines; *Alt fire detonates all tripmines set, but detonation is delayed a little and there is some noise indication. +20% damage and blast radius;  - tripmines travel 40% less the distance of ordinary stikies</li>
<li>" Ghost Frier" - a gluon gun for pyro - +100% range. - 75% afterburn damage; +15% direct damage; * disintegrates killed enemies similarly to Cow mangler; * alt fire creates a small field for 35 ammo which destroys all projectiles; +30% damage to buildings.<br>
Feel free to discuss and write down your own ideas  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=9" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:">
</li>
</ol>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/black-mesa-themed-tf2-workshop-items/13994/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/black-mesa-themed-tf2-workshop-items/13994/1</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 11 May 2015 19:09:11 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13994-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/black-mesa-themed-tf2-workshop-items/13994.rss">Black Mesa themed TF2 workshop items</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
