<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Did you find Black Mesa &quot;scary enough?&quot;</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/did-you-find-black-mesa-scary-enough/11676</link>
    <description>Hey guys, new to the forum and I&#39;d like to share my thoughts so far on BMS.

First off, I really don&#39;t need to tell you guys what a brilliant job you&#39;ve done. So I&#39;ll just skip to what I intended to write.

Did you guys feel that Black Mesa Source is scary, or is scarier/less scarier than the original Half-Life? Here are my thoughts.

Although BMS is a great game, I just feel like it&#39;s not as scary as the original. Going through the tram ride in the original Half-Life and hearing that deeply depressing/ambient music really scared (and still scares) the fuck out of me, and really makes me feel like I&#39;m extremely... alone; that was something I didn&#39;t feel at the beginning of BMS. The music throughout the game is good, but it has more of a badass feel than a scary, more intense feeling; it&#39;s as if Gordon Freeman was the composer. Also, I&#39;m not sure if it&#39;s just the modeling of Half-Life, but it&#39;s imperfections almost make it scarier than a more realistic looking game. 

Anyways, just my thoughts. What do you think?</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2013 13:41:21 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>The Cafeteria</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/did-you-find-black-mesa-scary-enough/11676.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Did you find Black Mesa &quot;scary enough?&quot;</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[KyuuGryphon]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I don’t know if I’d call it scary.</p>
<p>A lot of the “scare” in HL1 for me was due to jump-scares. First time playing, finding headcrabs in vents was <span class="bbcode-i">not</span> fun.</p>
<p>Subsequent playthroughs of HL1 were nowhere near as frightening. There are some parts that actually still make me tense up (i.e. running from the Garg at the end of ST or PU), and there’s certainly still an “unsettling” vibe to the game.</p>
<p>With Black Mesa, I knew most of what was going to happen because I had played Half-Life. I don’t quite have a photographic memory of HL1, but in BM, even with areas that were extensively redesigned, a lot of the time I could go “oh hey, it’s this area”. I could “track” my position in a BM level vs. where I’d be in the HL1 equivalent and prepare myself for anything lying ahead because of it.</p>
<p>I don’t know if I worded that very well, bluh.</p>
<p>Having said that, though - Black Mesa was definitely a more empathic experience. I felt the same way about Half-Life, but Source’s capabilities only enhance it.</p>
<p>I don’t find myself jumping or going “OH SHIT” because of things happening in BM (not to be confused with an “aw crap” moment), but it does a lot more - for me at least - in the psychological horror aspect.</p>
<p>Even already knowing what would happen, I can’t think of anything in the Half-Life series that hit me as hard as walking out of the test chamber post-Cascade in BM. Just, the entirety of that section up until you meet the first (alive) Security Guard… I thought that was incredible.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/did-you-find-black-mesa-scary-enough/11676/50">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/did-you-find-black-mesa-scary-enough/11676/50</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2013 13:41:21 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11676-50</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/did-you-find-black-mesa-scary-enough/11676.rss">Did you find Black Mesa &quot;scary enough?&quot;</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Did you find Black Mesa &quot;scary enough?&quot;</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Lahey]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Well it’s hard to say if I find Black Mesa more or less scarier than Half-Life 1 since I knew what to expect. I did find Half-Life 1 a bit scary.<br>
I do want to say that I did not like the first introduction of the alien race at the anti-mass spectrometer. In comparison with Half-Life 1, it was too obvious we are dealing with aliens. (In Half-Life 1 it was darker thus I was confused and a bit frightened what I just saw).<br>
Speaking of darkness, darkness is a very important factor in making games scary. Here is a nice youtube that sums up 10 elements that makes games scary:<br>
<a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=0KIaZvu39Po" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=0KIaZvu39Po</a></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/did-you-find-black-mesa-scary-enough/11676/49">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/did-you-find-black-mesa-scary-enough/11676/49</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2013 04:13:07 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11676-49</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/did-you-find-black-mesa-scary-enough/11676.rss">Did you find Black Mesa &quot;scary enough?&quot;</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Did you find Black Mesa &quot;scary enough?&quot;</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[imadoofus]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="GPuzzle">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/g/858c86/40.png" class="avatar"> GPuzzle:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>the elevator flood caused my FPS to die</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Oh, thank God it’s not just my computer.</p>
<p>For me, Black Mesa isn’t as much scary or creepy as it is just giving you a feeling of apprehension - very slight, and you hardly know it’s there until a headcrab leaps out at you from a vent for the first time. In my humble opinion, Unforeseen Consequences was easily the scariest chapter. I probably don’t really have to explain why… at the beginning I lingered for a second to see if the scientist ended up reviving the guard like in the original. Then I moved on and CRASH and BOOM and FIZZLE and CREEPY MUSIC and THE FREAKING INTRODUCTION TO CROUCH-JUMPING WITH THAT FLIPPING HEADCRAB and MUFFINS and G-MAN… it was pretty terrifying, in the dark at an alien-infested, barely-operational facility, even when I had a security guard by my side.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/did-you-find-black-mesa-scary-enough/11676/48">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/did-you-find-black-mesa-scary-enough/11676/48</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 23 Feb 2013 02:54:27 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11676-48</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/did-you-find-black-mesa-scary-enough/11676.rss">Did you find Black Mesa &quot;scary enough?&quot;</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Did you find Black Mesa &quot;scary enough?&quot;</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[GPuzzle]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="FrontLineAssembly">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/f/ebca7d/40.png" class="avatar"> FrontLineAssembly:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Although HL2 is more like George Orwells book ‘1960’, or whatever it was called, while Deux Ex is more aiming at William Blake’s corporate dystopia</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>1984, and, together with Farenheith 451, Brave New World and Us, it’s one of the books that could or possibly have a straight up relationship with the HL2 storyline.</p>
<p>Anyway, I found Black Mesa to be actually not scary, but I was constantly training myself to use weapons such as the .357, the Crossbow and the Satchel Charge, due to my ability to set traps (in my co-op playthrough of Resident Evil 5 with a friend, I carried the explosives and a shotgun) and a slightly comfort with weapons that are insanely powerful in damage.<br>
I found myself in the dam to be sniping with the Crossbow (and believe me, I suck at sniping), just to the running with the .357 (already a few guys down - 4), shooting down 2 guys with it, throwing a Satchel and detonating it shortly after, destroying the Marine squad. That made me feel "oh, hey, this is more of a “keep supplies and good aim and you’ll be fine”, instead of a “Um, this is scary…”<br>
I found several moments to be scary in Black Mesa - the elevator flood caused my FPS to die, the tentacles were just THAT scary, I was insanely afraid and conforted at the same time when I picked up the Crossbow, the Assassin warehouse in Aprehension was kind of paranoic - it wasn’t exactly a terror à la Dead Space, it was more of a Edgar Allan Poe terror - mind terror. I was scared due to the flood and not knowing if I was going to drown in there, the tentacles were scary due to the fact that they dealed heavy damage, the Crossbow sequence was scary due to the goddamn Ichytosaur in the water, and the Warehouse was scary due to assassins being something that made me have trouble considering my terrible aim.</p>
<p>Black Mesa has that feel of “Fuck, what the hell happened? I’ll just fight my way through and be badass” and Half Life have that feel of “Shit, I NEED TO GET OUT OF HERE”. Mainly because we played Half Life first, then Black Mesa.<br>
We did not have the same amount of knowledge, so we were scared each time a new enemy showed up. Black Mesa fights against this with nothing but pure badassery. The Dam in ST, the Ambush in QE and the WHG finale (with the goddamn epic bass sequence) were awesome due to the fights, and I think that’s how they fought against a bigger player knowledge.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/did-you-find-black-mesa-scary-enough/11676/47">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/did-you-find-black-mesa-scary-enough/11676/47</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 23 Feb 2013 01:04:38 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11676-47</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/did-you-find-black-mesa-scary-enough/11676.rss">Did you find Black Mesa &quot;scary enough?&quot;</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Did you find Black Mesa &quot;scary enough?&quot;</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[karotiv]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>half life is not a scary game, so black mesa is not a scary game 2.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/did-you-find-black-mesa-scary-enough/11676/46">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/did-you-find-black-mesa-scary-enough/11676/46</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jan 2013 13:49:35 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11676-46</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/did-you-find-black-mesa-scary-enough/11676.rss">Did you find Black Mesa &quot;scary enough?&quot;</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Did you find Black Mesa &quot;scary enough?&quot;</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Serza]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>In my case, a bunch of Poison’s do. Not a second of “OH SHIT” rather than having occassional nightmares since summer holidays. Totally worth it.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/did-you-find-black-mesa-scary-enough/11676/45">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/did-you-find-black-mesa-scary-enough/11676/45</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jan 2013 17:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11676-45</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/did-you-find-black-mesa-scary-enough/11676.rss">Did you find Black Mesa &quot;scary enough?&quot;</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Did you find Black Mesa &quot;scary enough?&quot;</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[bulbman]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>IMO, fear isn’t being startled by a sudden movement, it’s being completely filled with dread of moving foward, fear builds up, it’s not one socond of “oh shit i wasnt expecting that!”, play amnesia in a dark room.alone.with headphones, then youll experience true fear, it’s not what you can see, it’s what you can’t see. But as far as BM being “scary”, i don’t know if scary applies, i never really thought of HL as scary. I think foreboding is a better word, seeing all the executed guards and scientists in QE sent a chill down my spine, especially because of the lack of HECU in the early areas. Pretty creepy.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/did-you-find-black-mesa-scary-enough/11676/44">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/did-you-find-black-mesa-scary-enough/11676/44</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jan 2013 05:38:08 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11676-44</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/did-you-find-black-mesa-scary-enough/11676.rss">Did you find Black Mesa &quot;scary enough?&quot;</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Did you find Black Mesa &quot;scary enough?&quot;</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[GenericPlayerX]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I have played BMS twice since I finally got the download to work and have yet to have an “OH S***!” moment. Sadly, that means I must declare that BMS is so far NOT as scary as HL1 was for me when I started playing in 2000. Even when I quit playing HL1 in 2008 (my computer died and I lost all my favorite mods as well) I still felt like I could die plenty of times.</p>
<p>So far, only one death in BMS and that was when my whiskey bottle fell over on my hand while I was making a jump onto a crate over an endless chasm. It was kinda fun watching my guy just run right off the edge into that chasm. Never really done that before in a game; a new experience. Funny how alcohol can change your life even when you are not drinking it.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/did-you-find-black-mesa-scary-enough/11676/43">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/did-you-find-black-mesa-scary-enough/11676/43</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Jan 2013 09:01:48 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11676-43</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/did-you-find-black-mesa-scary-enough/11676.rss">Did you find Black Mesa &quot;scary enough?&quot;</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Did you find Black Mesa &quot;scary enough?&quot;</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[MSKyuuni]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Vampire95">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/v/b2d939/40.png" class="avatar"> Vampire95:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>“If you’re smart, if you value your continued existance. If you have any plans of seeing tomorrow, there’s one thing you never, ever put in a trap. Me.”</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Oh I remember that</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/did-you-find-black-mesa-scary-enough/11676/42">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/did-you-find-black-mesa-scary-enough/11676/42</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jan 2013 03:15:38 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11676-42</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/did-you-find-black-mesa-scary-enough/11676.rss">Did you find Black Mesa &quot;scary enough?&quot;</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Did you find Black Mesa &quot;scary enough?&quot;</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Vampire95]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Oh yeah, almost as scary as Half-Life at some parts. At some parts more scary than the original, but whenever I felt trapped I just went on thinking<br>
“If you’re smart, if you value your continued existance. If you have any plans of seeing tomorrow, there’s one thing you never, ever put in a trap. Me.”</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/did-you-find-black-mesa-scary-enough/11676/41">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/did-you-find-black-mesa-scary-enough/11676/41</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 07 Jan 2013 23:55:47 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11676-41</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/did-you-find-black-mesa-scary-enough/11676.rss">Did you find Black Mesa &quot;scary enough?&quot;</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Did you find Black Mesa &quot;scary enough?&quot;</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[John_Lemon]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I’m not going to bother quoting all the people posting before me, but I’ll just chip in my two cents anyway.</p>
<ol>
<li>To the lad/ladette who said that BM devs were trying to make Black Mesa “like HL2” in the comparison and transitions of Lovecraftian/B-Movie Sci-Fi and Cyberpunk, I don’t think that’s the case. The devs are trying to make Half-Life as Valve would <em>with HL2’s technology.</em>
</li>
<li>ST was cut severely because the main mapper behind ST quit unexpectedly and no-one could really take over for him. (At least, that’s the story I heard)</li>
<li>The first encounter with the Marines was perfect, IMO. To say that now it’s “cheesy” and “predictable” is completely ridiculous, as if it was better in Half-Life. For me, it’s a perfect transition from old to new. And your main proof of the line “The military cleanup is just a paranoid rumor, isn’t it?” was in Half-Life 1, as a piece of random scientist chatter. I think that BM actually improved upon introducing the Marines and their threat with certain other events such as the VOX takeover (“Attention, this-[static]-ystem now under military command”) and the first few staff executions (Particularly the panicked and confused scientists, “If you’ll wait just a moment, I-I can show you my ID card!” Cue MP5)</li>
</ol>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/did-you-find-black-mesa-scary-enough/11676/40">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/did-you-find-black-mesa-scary-enough/11676/40</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 02 Jan 2013 21:45:46 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11676-40</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/did-you-find-black-mesa-scary-enough/11676.rss">Did you find Black Mesa &quot;scary enough?&quot;</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Did you find Black Mesa &quot;scary enough?&quot;</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Kaweebo]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>It was scary in how depressing it was. There weren’t really any jumpscare moments, but the music combined with the frantic, panicked voice acting of scientists trapped in elevators among other things, really contributed to the feel during those first few chapters.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/did-you-find-black-mesa-scary-enough/11676/39">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/did-you-find-black-mesa-scary-enough/11676/39</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 30 Dec 2012 01:14:01 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11676-39</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/did-you-find-black-mesa-scary-enough/11676.rss">Did you find Black Mesa &quot;scary enough?&quot;</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Did you find Black Mesa &quot;scary enough?&quot;</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Lumbergh]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>People have widely varying sensibilities about what it means to be frightened. I’m not surprised in the least about all the differences of opinion. For some people, the concept of supernatural involvement may be necessary for fear, thus the Ravenholm group. For others, danger itself is scary, so BM/HL1 may be quite frightening. Some people find science fiction elements frightening, etc., etc. Point is most of it is rather subjective, and thus so are our perceptions of all these games, Black Mesa included.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/did-you-find-black-mesa-scary-enough/11676/38">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/did-you-find-black-mesa-scary-enough/11676/38</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 26 Dec 2012 15:03:06 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11676-38</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/did-you-find-black-mesa-scary-enough/11676.rss">Did you find Black Mesa &quot;scary enough?&quot;</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Did you find Black Mesa &quot;scary enough?&quot;</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[herrington.t.bass]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I don’t think scary was ever a term I would for Half Life. Although, my first several trips through Ravenholm scared the bejesus out of me.</p>
<p>I have always been a science fiction nut, and the original Half Life filled me with wonder.</p>
<p>In my opinion, the Dead Space series is one of the scariest of all games. Especially the Church level in DS2! Those church acolyte necromorphs were the bomb <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=9" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/did-you-find-black-mesa-scary-enough/11676/37">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/did-you-find-black-mesa-scary-enough/11676/37</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 26 Dec 2012 04:07:12 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11676-37</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/did-you-find-black-mesa-scary-enough/11676.rss">Did you find Black Mesa &quot;scary enough?&quot;</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Did you find Black Mesa &quot;scary enough?&quot;</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Rex_Prime]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>In Half Life it kinda felt creepy at the first when we were almost completely lonely but we got used to it by time, In Half-Life 2 we don’t feel alone for most of the time but when that happens…</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/did-you-find-black-mesa-scary-enough/11676/36">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/did-you-find-black-mesa-scary-enough/11676/36</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 24 Dec 2012 11:11:54 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11676-36</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/did-you-find-black-mesa-scary-enough/11676.rss">Did you find Black Mesa &quot;scary enough?&quot;</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Did you find Black Mesa &quot;scary enough?&quot;</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[BendyBread]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="jpk">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/j/71e660/40.png" class="avatar"> jpk:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>The creepiest HL series level for me was Ravenholm in HL2. That level just really made my hair stand on end.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>^x100000</p>
<p>The atmosphere of being alone and isolated (I mean in HL you’re nearly always alone, but for short bursts in HL2 you’re not abandoned for once), seeing all the death and destruction, and then being stuck with all these crazy zombies that not only make generally scary sounds, but their screaming when you set them on fire, oh god.</p>
<p>Don’t even get me started on the fast zombies. -shudder-</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/did-you-find-black-mesa-scary-enough/11676/35">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/did-you-find-black-mesa-scary-enough/11676/35</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 24 Dec 2012 09:08:30 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11676-35</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/did-you-find-black-mesa-scary-enough/11676.rss">Did you find Black Mesa &quot;scary enough?&quot;</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Did you find Black Mesa &quot;scary enough?&quot;</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[jpk]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>The creepiest HL series level for me was Ravenholm in HL2. That level just really made my hair stand on end.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/did-you-find-black-mesa-scary-enough/11676/34">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/did-you-find-black-mesa-scary-enough/11676/34</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 22 Dec 2012 20:10:52 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11676-34</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/did-you-find-black-mesa-scary-enough/11676.rss">Did you find Black Mesa &quot;scary enough?&quot;</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Did you find Black Mesa &quot;scary enough?&quot;</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[AverageForumGuy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>imo the cut out parts of ST were mostly filler but they should have still added the  satchel pipe scene and some scenes of aliens fighting (and winning) against<br>
the HECU.</p>
<p>Also i don’t get all this “not lonely enough” stuff. Blast Pit and On a Rail felt really lonely to me</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/did-you-find-black-mesa-scary-enough/11676/33">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/did-you-find-black-mesa-scary-enough/11676/33</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2012 18:46:03 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11676-33</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/did-you-find-black-mesa-scary-enough/11676.rss">Did you find Black Mesa &quot;scary enough?&quot;</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Did you find Black Mesa &quot;scary enough?&quot;</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Dr_Maxwell]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I didn’t mean it was expected in the sense that I knew it was coming.  I knew it was coming when I played Half-Life for the first time; I was spoiled.  I meant it was expected in the sense that the game went out of its way to tell you what was going to happen before it was going to happen, with moments like the one I already pointed out (“the military coverup is just a rumor - right?”)</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/did-you-find-black-mesa-scary-enough/11676/32">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/did-you-find-black-mesa-scary-enough/11676/32</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2012 05:31:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11676-32</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/did-you-find-black-mesa-scary-enough/11676.rss">Did you find Black Mesa &quot;scary enough?&quot;</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Did you find Black Mesa &quot;scary enough?&quot;</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[M-Man]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Dr. Maxwell">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Dr. Maxwell:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I’d be careful not to go too far down that path, though, pRopaaNs.  One of the moments in Black Mesa that I thought was most disimproved from Half-Life was the first military encounter.  In half-Life, it was a total surprise, and a horrifying one.  In Black Mesa, it was insanely cheesily overly-built-up, with it all but stated that the military would be evil before they got here.  (“The military coverup is just a rumor - right?”)  As a result, the corresponding moment in Black Mesa isn’t horrifying, just disappointing.  It feels less like a betrayal and more like a “yup, as expected”.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>of course it wasn’t a surprise… you knew what was going to happen already. :facepalm: Anyone who’s played the first game knows what’s coming.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/did-you-find-black-mesa-scary-enough/11676/31">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/did-you-find-black-mesa-scary-enough/11676/31</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2012 03:59:53 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11676-31</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/did-you-find-black-mesa-scary-enough/11676.rss">Did you find Black Mesa &quot;scary enough?&quot;</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Did you find Black Mesa &quot;scary enough?&quot;</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Problematic_A-hole]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Half Life never was scary</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/did-you-find-black-mesa-scary-enough/11676/30">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/did-you-find-black-mesa-scary-enough/11676/30</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2012 22:37:33 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11676-30</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/did-you-find-black-mesa-scary-enough/11676.rss">Did you find Black Mesa &quot;scary enough?&quot;</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Did you find Black Mesa &quot;scary enough?&quot;</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[BendyBread]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I’m not sure why they cut parts out of ST.</p>
<p>Cutting most of OAR was fine (for me), it was long, frustrating and overall confusing. That’s fair enough. But cutting ST also cut some of the storyline down.</p>
<p>We don’t truly get to see the whole aliens vs humans war, where the aliens start to win and push back the human forces (leading into FAF).<br>
Not to mention the satchel in the pipe thing, that was the best thing ever. Quickly crawling back in a panic and hiding in the water just as the blast goes through the tunnel and over the water.</p>
<p>The only 2 fights I can remember in ST is the small fight with the OSPREY, and the. That was kind of depressing because you were too busy trying to destroy the osprey and survive at the same time. Also maybe this is just me, but the hecu annoyingly just ditched fighting the a-grunts and always came to kill me, even if I wasn’t in view.<br>
Second is the small fight where the manta goes over and 2 grunts spawn, then the human tank comes out behind them. That was also a poor fight.</p>
<p>I miss the full out “war” you see. The only one I witnessed probably in the entire game was near the end of FAF, and even then the hecu once again just ran for me the second they saw me and abandoned fighting the aliens.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/did-you-find-black-mesa-scary-enough/11676/29">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/did-you-find-black-mesa-scary-enough/11676/29</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2012 22:33:28 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11676-29</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/did-you-find-black-mesa-scary-enough/11676.rss">Did you find Black Mesa &quot;scary enough?&quot;</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Did you find Black Mesa &quot;scary enough?&quot;</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[GordonFreeManz]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>My problem with QE in Black Mesa and Half-Life is this…</p>
<p>There’s cryotubes and stuff… can’t there be more surprise moments and maybe make you feel abandoned ala DOOM 1 for PS1 or DOOM 64 or Halo 1 343 Guilty Spark?!</p>
<p>QE in Black Mesa has ways to kill the Alien Grunt in the cryotube… I don’t like that. I’d rather have the alien grunt bang on the glass and roar and then as soon as I break a button it comes charging at me and comes to kill me. I feel as though the Alien Grunt doesn’t really have a role anymore.</p>
<p>Also, devs… I had to download a Surface Tension map-pack because you guys cut out a lot…</p>
<p>Really?! Was it really necessary to cut out maps?! They were essential to the plot, atmosphere, and story of Black Mesa.</p>
<p>Also, I had to re-edit the Black Mesa skill.cfg and weapon.cfgs back to their old Half-Life 1 values via a small mod based off Half-Life 1 values.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/did-you-find-black-mesa-scary-enough/11676/28">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/did-you-find-black-mesa-scary-enough/11676/28</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2012 16:26:32 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11676-28</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/did-you-find-black-mesa-scary-enough/11676.rss">Did you find Black Mesa &quot;scary enough?&quot;</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Did you find Black Mesa &quot;scary enough?&quot;</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Gregorovich]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>The only ‘scary’ parts of HL were the Icthyosaur bits. So seeing as all the Icthyosaurs in BM were weakened severely (not to mention taking away the gurgling sound), no. BM is not as scary as HL.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/did-you-find-black-mesa-scary-enough/11676/27">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/did-you-find-black-mesa-scary-enough/11676/27</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 25 Nov 2012 02:07:49 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11676-27</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/did-you-find-black-mesa-scary-enough/11676.rss">Did you find Black Mesa &quot;scary enough?&quot;</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Did you find Black Mesa &quot;scary enough?&quot;</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[xalener]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>^ pretty much</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/did-you-find-black-mesa-scary-enough/11676/26">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/did-you-find-black-mesa-scary-enough/11676/26</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 25 Nov 2012 01:02:10 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11676-26</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/did-you-find-black-mesa-scary-enough/11676.rss">Did you find Black Mesa &quot;scary enough?&quot;</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
