<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Edit the scrolling speed of the credits?</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/edit-the-scrolling-speed-of-the-credits/13401</link>
    <description>Personally, I love Joel Nielsen&#39;s music in Black Mesa... However, there&#39;s one song I despise strongly... and that&#39;s end credit song #1. Maybe, I hate this song because when I beat Half-Life for the first time in 2003 - and after playing through the entire epic game... the cliff-hanger that  you were left with at the end was one of the most epic cliff-hangers I&#39;ve ever seen (including movies). 

So when the amazing end credits music by Kelly Bailey started playing... I got chills down my spine. The perfect song, for the perfect ending to the game. I sat there in awe as the credits scrolled across the screen... amazed by the fact that it felt so epic. Half-Life was the first game I ever played that made me feel like I was the main character, and that I had, personally, beaten nihilanth, and that I had personally survived the resonance cascade at Black Mesa. 

To honor that original feeling - I edited the credits song of BM to the original Kelly Bailey song, and mixed it with Joel Nielsen&#39;s end credits part 2 song. There&#39;s only one problem... The music is cut off (around) 10 seconds before it&#39;s supposed to end. And therefore... that kind of ruins the experience...  :frowning:  

So can anyone tell me which files I should edit to make it so the credits scroll a little slower? Thanks everyone!

P.S I also edited in the original alarm (instead of the school bell type ring) to the original &#39;Alien-like&#39; siren. I also put the original Fire Door closing warning sound beep back in, but other than that - everything else is perfect  :wink: 

At the moment - I&#39;m also attempting to mix the original HEV charge and Med-Charge &#39;initiate&#39; sounds with the new sounds. If I can get that done and change the above - I&#39;d post that for other who want to do the same  :slight_smile:</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2014 13:13:42 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>The Cafeteria</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/edit-the-scrolling-speed-of-the-credits/13401.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Edit the scrolling speed of the credits?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[JeffMOD]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>You could try adding some escape characters to the end of the credits before the final line of text. I don’t know if that will change the speed or just make everything go a bit faster, though. Worth a try.<br>
The file is scripts/credits.txt, there should also be some additional parameters you can try modifying.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/edit-the-scrolling-speed-of-the-credits/13401/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/edit-the-scrolling-speed-of-the-credits/13401/4</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2014 13:13:42 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13401-4</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/edit-the-scrolling-speed-of-the-credits/13401.rss">Edit the scrolling speed of the credits?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Edit the scrolling speed of the credits?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[BuzzKillington]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Flatline">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/f/b9bd4f/40.png" class="avatar"> Flatline:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>What a ridiculous thing to complain about. I don’t think you’re going to be able to do that. When part 2 is released there’ll be a whole new ending and whole new set of credits anyway.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>My understanding of the entire point of Black Mesa is to relive the Half-Life experience. That’s all I’m trying to do. Relive a part of my childhood.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/edit-the-scrolling-speed-of-the-credits/13401/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/edit-the-scrolling-speed-of-the-credits/13401/3</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2014 11:51:52 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13401-3</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/edit-the-scrolling-speed-of-the-credits/13401.rss">Edit the scrolling speed of the credits?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Edit the scrolling speed of the credits?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Flatline]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>What a ridiculous thing to complain about. I don’t think you’re going to be able to do that. When part 2 is released there’ll be a whole new ending and whole new set of credits anyway.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/edit-the-scrolling-speed-of-the-credits/13401/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/edit-the-scrolling-speed-of-the-credits/13401/2</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2014 09:08:28 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13401-2</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/edit-the-scrolling-speed-of-the-credits/13401.rss">Edit the scrolling speed of the credits?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Edit the scrolling speed of the credits?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[BuzzKillington]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Personally, I love Joel Nielsen’s music in Black Mesa… However, there’s one song I despise strongly… and that’s end credit song <span class="hashtag">#1</span>. Maybe, I hate this song because when I beat Half-Life for the first time in 2003 - and after playing through the entire epic game… the cliff-hanger that  you were left with at the end was one of the most epic cliff-hangers I’ve ever seen (including movies).</p>
<p>So when the amazing end credits music by Kelly Bailey started playing… I got chills down my spine. The perfect song, for the perfect ending to the game. I sat there in awe as the credits scrolled across the screen… amazed by the fact that it felt so epic. Half-Life was the first game I ever played that made me feel like I was the main character, and that I had, personally, beaten nihilanth, and that I had personally survived the resonance cascade at Black Mesa.</p>
<p>To honor that original feeling - I edited the credits song of BM to the original Kelly Bailey song, and mixed it with Joel Nielsen’s end credits part 2 song. There’s only one problem… The music is cut off (around) 10 seconds before it’s supposed to end. And therefore… that kind of ruins the experience…  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/frowning.png?v=9" title=":frowning:" class="emoji" alt=":frowning:"></p>
<p>So can anyone tell me which files I should edit to make it so the credits scroll a little slower? Thanks everyone!</p>
<p>P.S I also edited in the original alarm (instead of the school bell type ring) to the original ‘Alien-like’ siren. I also put the original Fire Door closing warning sound beep back in, but other than that - everything else is perfect  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/wink.png?v=9" title=":wink:" class="emoji" alt=":wink:"></p>
<p>At the moment - I’m also attempting to mix the original HEV charge and Med-Charge ‘initiate’ sounds with the new sounds. If I can get that done and change the above - I’d post that for other who want to do the same  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=9" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/edit-the-scrolling-speed-of-the-credits/13401/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/edit-the-scrolling-speed-of-the-credits/13401/1</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2014 01:38:53 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13401-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/edit-the-scrolling-speed-of-the-credits/13401.rss">Edit the scrolling speed of the credits?</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
