<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Minecraft LAN connection timeout</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/minecraft-lan-connection-timeout/11129</link>
    <description>So I&#39;m asking here first on the off chance someone has a clue what to do. I&#39;ve been using a minecraft LAN game (NOT internet) for the last while, and it has been working fine, up until last night, where one of the computers is suddenly unable to connect. If that computer sets up a game, the others can find the server but are unable to connect. If another computer sets up a game, that computer cannot even see it. I&#39;ve uninstalled/reinstalled minecraft, and I&#39;ve tried  allowing access through the firewall. When that didn&#39;t work, I thought maybe I did something wrong with the allow access somehow, and disabled the firewall completely, but still nothing seems to work.

I don&#39;t know shit about firewalls and the like, so if anyone has an idea of what might be going on here I would really appreciate the help. I&#39;d prefer to not make another account on another website just for a single fix if one of you guys might have the answer.  :smiley:</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 25 Sep 2012 06:28:19 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Help and Support</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/minecraft-lan-connection-timeout/11129.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Minecraft LAN connection timeout</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[_rot_fodder]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>So I’m asking here first on the off chance someone has a clue what to do. I’ve been using a minecraft LAN game (NOT internet) for the last while, and it has been working fine, up until last night, where one of the computers is suddenly unable to connect. If that computer sets up a game, the others can find the server but are unable to connect. If another computer sets up a game, that computer cannot even see it. I’ve uninstalled/reinstalled minecraft, and I’ve tried  allowing access through the firewall. When that didn’t work, I thought maybe I did something wrong with the allow access somehow, and disabled the firewall completely, but still nothing seems to work.</p>
<p>I don’t know shit about firewalls and the like, so if anyone has an idea of what might be going on here I would really appreciate the help. I’d prefer to not make another account on another website just for a single fix if one of you guys might have the answer.  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/smiley.png?v=9" title=":smiley:" class="emoji" alt=":smiley:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/minecraft-lan-connection-timeout/11129/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/minecraft-lan-connection-timeout/11129/1</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 25 Sep 2012 06:28:19 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11129-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/minecraft-lan-connection-timeout/11129.rss">Minecraft LAN connection timeout</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
