<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Error code 2</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/error-code-2/9697</link>
    <description>I have downloaded all three files and placed them in the same folder. Whenever I try to use the installer it says &quot;Failed to extract files, 7-zip returned error code: 2&quot; I have deleted and redownloaded all of the files multiple times.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 20 Sep 2012 02:28:31 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>In-game Issues (Mod)</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/error-code-2/9697.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Error code 2</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[lexa2]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="mgr.inz.player">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/m/e0b2c6/40.png" class="avatar"> mgr.inz.player:</div>
<blockquote>
<p><a class="mention" href="/u/lexa2">@lexa2</a>, you can take screenshots I made three days ago, from this <a href="https://forums.blackmesasource.com/showthread.php?p=495082#post495082" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">topic</a></p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>[COLOR=‘Gray’][offtopic]The site you used to host pictures don’t allow access unless you right-click on the picture, press “Open in a new window” and pass the CAPTCHA test there. As for using these screenshots: IMO we’re living in the age of google and there’re more than enough info on how to use torrents in general and uTorrent in particular all over the internet thus thre’s no point to create yet another “How to use torrents for dummies” page on the BM forums :-). People who want to learn something would do it, rest would continue to suffer and ask to help them endlessly. Sad but true :-(.[/offtopic][/SIZE]</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/error-code-2/9697/36">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/error-code-2/9697/36</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 20 Sep 2012 02:28:31 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9697-36</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/error-code-2/9697.rss">Error code 2</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Error code 2</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[mgr.inz.player]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><a class="mention" href="/u/lexa2">@lexa2</a>, you can take screenshots I made three days ago, from this <a href="https://forums.blackmesasource.com/showthread.php?p=495082#post495082" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">topic</a></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/error-code-2/9697/35">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/error-code-2/9697/35</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 19 Sep 2012 16:56:08 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9697-35</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/error-code-2/9697.rss">Error code 2</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Error code 2</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[lexa2]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Mods are here not to post help responses, they are here to prevent SPAM and all other nasty stuff from growing. And from what I see they are surprisingly tolerate on these forums towards swarms of newcomers refusing to read and follow posting gudelines and forum rules. On most other forums a lot of people would already been banned for behaving like they behave here in bug-reporting section.</p>
<p>Back to your problems, get it simple:<br>
a) Easiest, most robust and most bandwidth-consuming way to (re-)download BM is by using torrents.<br>
b) Using torrents is harder than simply clicking on the download link in browser and hoping for the best. You would have to learn some thing before you could get utorrent (or some other torrent client you prefer) to do what you request it to do. But that’s just how the things work on PC: if you want have mostly problems-free gaming on PC - you would have to learn a lot. It is not a game console where you insert one thing into another bigger thing and then the game just works - it does not work like that. You would have to learn things or would be facing troubles.<br>
c) Some people can’t use torrents with default configuration of the torrent client due to ISP trying to block it. This block is pretty easy to bypass if you spend some time and learn about enabling incoming/outgoing torrent protocol encryption and about using uTP (UDP-based torrent protocol extension).<br>
d) What benefits you get by using torrent download instead of ordinary HTTP/FTP based in-browser download:</p>
<ul>
<li>warranted download pause/resume capability - you won’t have to redownload entire thing in case you would like to pause/stop downloading for some time;</li>
<li>warranted integrity of the download - torrent by design checks that the data it had downloaded is not corrupt and automatically re-downloads corrupt parts of the file;</li>
<li>in case you’ve get files already downloaded by some other way (like interrupted/corrupted HTTP download) - torrent would allow you to fix your corrupted files by redownloading the minimum amount of data that is required to fix corruption; I.E. you won’t need to redownload entire 3GB in order to fix one byte error in the end of the file.</li>
<li>download speeds for popular torrents are usually several times higher compared to what you get with traditional HTTP/FTP downloads;</li>
</ul>
<p>That being said, I have to state that here is not a “teach how to use your PC and/or torrent client” forums. BM is available for download, and thousands of people all over the world had been able to do it successfully and now play the game. If you got the problem with downloading/installing on your setup - chances are 99% that it’s due to you doing something wrong. Overclocking, viruses/trojans or other malware, crappy anti-virus software and simply lack of required skills and refusal to learn - that are the usual causes of the problem this thread is about. It is as simple as that.</p>
<p>Have a problem? Google, try &amp; learn. Too lazy for that? Than simply <a href="https://forums.blackmesasource.com/showpost.php?p=498933&amp;postcount=31" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">try to follow the recommended troubleshooting procedure step by step and post a detailed report about all the messages you get on the way</a>.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/error-code-2/9697/34">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/error-code-2/9697/34</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 18 Sep 2012 20:53:31 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9697-34</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/error-code-2/9697.rss">Error code 2</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Error code 2</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Skull_the_Troll]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I thought desura would be great, but I cant get it from them either, I get to 4105 GB, and it says I’ve lost my internet connection. (I haven’t) Anyone got a working copy of their BMS folder posted somewhere. Downloading 7gb is better than downloading the 3.4gb for the 5th time. Also where the hell are the mods in this forum, I haven’t seen a posted response to a help request yet.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/error-code-2/9697/33">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/error-code-2/9697/33</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 18 Sep 2012 19:38:38 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9697-33</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/error-code-2/9697.rss">Error code 2</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Error code 2</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[vanacava]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Update: I managed to bypass the issue by using Desura to install the mod.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/error-code-2/9697/32">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/error-code-2/9697/32</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 18 Sep 2012 04:48:45 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9697-32</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/error-code-2/9697.rss">Error code 2</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Error code 2</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[lexa2]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Steps to troubleshoot:<br>
0) Remove any existing 7zip installation you have.</p>
<ol>
<li>Install latest 7zip from <a href="https://www.7-zip.org/" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://www.7-zip.org/</a> matching your windows version.</li>
<li>Run 7z File Manager, navigate to where you had downloaded the game and run integrity check on the archive. It should pass without errors. If not - try running it once again.<br>
3a) If both first and the second attemps to test BlackMesa.7z integrity failed with an error - most probably you have a corrupted download. Easiest way to fix - use torrent to redownload and tell it to download to the same folder you have your corrupted files stored in. In such case it would only redownload the corrupted parts saving you from having to redownload entire 3GB archive. After torrent would finish downloading - repeat step (2) - i.e. test the archive once again with 7zfm.<br>
3b) If you have second testing attempt went ok while first had given you an error: check your PC. It is either viruses/trojans, faulty memory or overclocking-related problems.</li>
<li>As soon as 7zfm would state that the archive is not corrupt - proceed with executing BlackMesa-Setup.exe. It should work fine now. If not - report back including all the exact steps you took before getting the error. Also don’t forget to provide the complete log of the installer output.</li>
</ol>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/error-code-2/9697/31">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/error-code-2/9697/31</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 18 Sep 2012 00:39:11 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9697-31</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/error-code-2/9697.rss">Error code 2</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Error code 2</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[vanacava]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="woohhaa">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/w/dc4da7/40.png" class="avatar"> woohhaa:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Do you have access to another computer and the means to transport 3gb of data from it to your machine? As best I could tell it was a problem with my file server.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Unfortunately I don’t, but thanks anyway.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/error-code-2/9697/30">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/error-code-2/9697/30</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 18 Sep 2012 00:21:04 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9697-30</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/error-code-2/9697.rss">Error code 2</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Error code 2</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[woohhaa]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="vanacava">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/v/ba8739/40.png" class="avatar"> vanacava:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Any ideas on fixing a potentially corrupted 7z file without using torrent?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Do you have access to another computer and the means to transport 3gb of data from it to your machine? As best I could tell it was a problem with my file server.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/error-code-2/9697/29">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/error-code-2/9697/29</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 17 Sep 2012 23:47:13 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9697-29</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/error-code-2/9697.rss">Error code 2</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Error code 2</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[vanacava]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="woohhaa">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/w/dc4da7/40.png" class="avatar"> woohhaa:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I reloaded the torrent anderson utorrent check the file against the tracker and it fixed the corrupt 7z file.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Any ideas on fixing a potentially corrupted 7z file without using torrent?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/error-code-2/9697/28">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/error-code-2/9697/28</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 17 Sep 2012 23:44:56 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9697-28</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/error-code-2/9697.rss">Error code 2</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Error code 2</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[woohhaa]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Nobuga">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/n/f4b2a3/40.png" class="avatar"> Nobuga:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Any fixes to this? I´m stuck with this error.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I reloaded the torrent and let utorrent check the file against the tracker and it fixed the corrupt 7z file.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/error-code-2/9697/27">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/error-code-2/9697/27</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 16 Sep 2012 22:48:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9697-27</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/error-code-2/9697.rss">Error code 2</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Error code 2</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Nobuga]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Any fixes to this? I´m stuck with this error.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/error-code-2/9697/26">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/error-code-2/9697/26</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 16 Sep 2012 22:41:24 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9697-26</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/error-code-2/9697.rss">Error code 2</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Error code 2</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[woohhaa]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I finally got it to install successfully! I had been doing all the downloading on my home file server then copying it over the network to my gaming rig. Well the install was failing on both boxes so I assumed it was the install sets or some weird compatibility issue. It occurred to me that my file server and network were the only constants so I loaded up the torrent file from my gaming rig. It started checking the install set and then proceeded to download a bit of additional data. I thought that was interesting so i tried to run the installer again.  Low and behold it worked!</p>
<p>So at this point I’d downloaded the install media from two different torrents, a http mirror,  and a buddies FTP site but ended up installing with the first install set I downloaded after getting the complete install set after having it fixed up by the torrent.</p>
<p>I’ll post the specs on my home file server later. Its nothing impressive but someone else having the issue may have some similar hardware.</p>
<p>Thanks to everyone who tried to help and made suggestions. I really appreciated and tried all your ideas.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/error-code-2/9697/25">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/error-code-2/9697/25</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 16 Sep 2012 20:51:58 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9697-25</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/error-code-2/9697.rss">Error code 2</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Error code 2</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[pantonio717]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>All,</p>
<p>I had the same issue but finally fixed it.  I’ll run you through my scenario and this should knock out some of the assumptions being made.</p>
<p>Running the setup file or manually extracting didn’t work.  I transferred the setup/7zip files to my laptop with windows vista (doesn’t have 7-zip installed) and ran the setup to see what would happen.  Surely enough it worked and extracted properly.  I decided to transfer the 7gb output folder back over to my steam folder on my gaming PC.  This actually worked.</p>
<p>That said, I doubt the files are corrupted.  If you get desperate and have another laptop/pc, you could do what I did as a last resort.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/error-code-2/9697/24">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/error-code-2/9697/24</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 16 Sep 2012 18:21:10 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9697-24</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/error-code-2/9697.rss">Error code 2</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Error code 2</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Mutto]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="sevenalive">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/s/f6c823/40.png" class="avatar"> sevenalive:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>For those that have a problem with a torrent download, stop the torrent and in uTorrent right click it and do a Force Recheck, it will verify the files.</p>
<p>I downloaded it on release day and it works fine for me, I downloaded it via torrent and ran the setup.exe</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>That’s always a good place to start.</p>
<p>However, I installed BMS on 2 computers with 1 torrent download and it took 6+ attempts to correctly install it on each machine, meaning my file downloaded just fine.  Something else is going on in addition to possible faulty downloads.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/error-code-2/9697/23">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/error-code-2/9697/23</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 16 Sep 2012 16:28:59 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9697-23</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/error-code-2/9697.rss">Error code 2</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Error code 2</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[sevenalive]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>For those that have a problem with a torrent download, stop the torrent and in uTorrent right click it and do a Force Recheck, it will verify the files.</p>
<p>I downloaded it on release day and it works fine for me, I downloaded it via torrent and ran the setup.exe</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/error-code-2/9697/22">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/error-code-2/9697/22</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 16 Sep 2012 10:21:13 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9697-22</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/error-code-2/9697.rss">Error code 2</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Error code 2</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[vanacava]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Kizza">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/k/e19adc/40.png" class="avatar"> Kizza:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Here is my success story with this error.</p>
<p>I tried extracting the BlackMesa.zip file with WinRAR and then proceeding to use the installer or 7-zip, but apparently this is the step that causes all the problems.</p>
<p>Here are the details of the successful method I used:</p>
<p>Uninstall 7-zip. Reinstall using freshly downloaded 7zip 9.20 x64 from their website (<a href="https://www.7-zip.org/download.html" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://www.7-zip.org/download.html</a>).<br>
Extract BlackMesa.zip (md5#: D0C72B16AA176D7FFFF57CB019C13267, size: 3,299,286,777 bytes) using freshly installed 7-zip. DO NOT USE ANY OTHER PROGRAM FOR THIS STEP.<br>
Use 7-zip to extract BlackMesa.7z (md5#: F1D86575816F4C6994A5657EEBF76409, size: 3,298,098,513 bytes) to \steamapps\sourcemods\BMS<br>
This process should be unremarkably error free.<br>
Restart Steam.<br>
Play.</p>
<p>I hope this helps. It seems as though the .zip file the installer is originally compressed in is non-standard and was compressed by 7-zip. Therefore it stands to reason that 7zip is the only program compatible with the file.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Thanks, but unfortunately, this didn’t work. Using 7zip to extract the BlackMesa.zip file only resulted in an apparently broken 7zip file.</p>
<p>I’d try redownloading, but I’ve already done that a few times from different mirrors.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/error-code-2/9697/21">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/error-code-2/9697/21</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 16 Sep 2012 09:44:40 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9697-21</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/error-code-2/9697.rss">Error code 2</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Error code 2</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Kizza]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Here is my success story with this error.</p>
<p>I tried extracting the BlackMesa.zip file with WinRAR and then proceeding to use the installer or 7-zip, but apparently this is the step that causes all the problems.</p>
<p>Here are the details of the successful method I used:</p>
<p>Uninstall 7-zip. Reinstall using freshly downloaded 7zip 9.20 x64 from their website (<a href="https://www.7-zip.org/download.html" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://www.7-zip.org/download.html</a>).<br>
Extract BlackMesa.zip (md5#: D0C72B16AA176D7FFFF57CB019C13267, size: 3,299,286,777 bytes) using freshly installed 7-zip. DO NOT USE ANY OTHER PROGRAM FOR THIS STEP.<br>
Use 7-zip to extract BlackMesa.7z (md5#: F1D86575816F4C6994A5657EEBF76409, size: 3,298,098,513 bytes) to \steamapps\sourcemods\BMS<br>
This process should be unremarkably error free.<br>
Restart Steam.<br>
Play.</p>
<p>I hope this helps. It seems as though the .zip file the installer is originally compressed in is non-standard and was compressed by 7-zip. Therefore it stands to reason that 7zip is the only program compatible with the file.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/error-code-2/9697/20">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/error-code-2/9697/20</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 16 Sep 2012 03:45:02 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9697-20</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/error-code-2/9697.rss">Error code 2</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Error code 2</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Skull_the_Troll]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I’ve tried a torrent and a direct download. Also checked with someone else on my steam friends list and he downloaded from the same mirror I did with out a problem. Like him I don’t have 7zip installed. (I dont like the crap that goes with it) but I do have the ability to unpack 7zip files. Before some one suggests that I download zip I’m just personally at a spot where I’d rather wait for it to come out on steam than download it again or install bloatware.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/error-code-2/9697/19">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/error-code-2/9697/19</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 16 Sep 2012 03:43:22 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9697-19</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/error-code-2/9697.rss">Error code 2</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Error code 2</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[The_MAZZTer]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Verify the MD5 of the 7zip file using a md5 hashing tool.</p>
<p>If it does not verify you will need to redownload.</p>
<p>I REALLY recommend torrent because it will do hashing verification for you as the file downloads.  Failed hashes result in only the corrupted piece being redownloaded.  Also the torrent will likely be faster now than HTTP downloads.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/error-code-2/9697/18">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/error-code-2/9697/18</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 16 Sep 2012 02:47:43 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9697-18</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/error-code-2/9697.rss">Error code 2</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Error code 2</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[vanacava]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I’m also having the same error. I could be wrong, but I think it has something to do with the 7zip file being corrupt.</p>
<p>I’ve tried downloading from gamefront, fileshack, moddb, and <a href="http://Chip.de" rel="nofollow noopener">Chip.de</a>. Unfortunately, I can’t download using torrent.</p>
<p>I either get an error 2 while using the installer, or can’t unzip all the files due to file corruption.</p>
<p>Any help would be appreciated.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/error-code-2/9697/17">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/error-code-2/9697/17</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 16 Sep 2012 00:45:53 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9697-17</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/error-code-2/9697.rss">Error code 2</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Error code 2</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Kiingy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="woohhaa">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/w/dc4da7/40.png" class="avatar"> woohhaa:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Using MD5 check v 2.1 I found that the checksum doesn’t match between the blackmesa.7z and blackmesa.md5 file. I’m not a file compression guru so I’m not sure what this tells you other than we’ve got CRC issues.</p>
<p>BlackMesa<br>
MD5 CDFBDD9E6C51BF4E98F4FF0BA18AB980<br>
7z 5F5B38F945FF7F52927A2AE664F48B15</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>[COLOR=‘PaleGreen’]<br>
Means that you’re probably going to have to download it again. You used torrents last time?</p>
<p>Try using one of the direct download mirrors.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/error-code-2/9697/16">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/error-code-2/9697/16</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 15 Sep 2012 21:42:03 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9697-16</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/error-code-2/9697.rss">Error code 2</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Error code 2</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[woohhaa]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Using MD5 check v 2.1 I found that the checksum doesn’t match between the blackmesa.7z and blackmesa.md5 file. I’m not a file compression guru so I’m not sure what this tells you other than we’ve got CRC issues.</p>
<p>BlackMesa<br>
MD5 CDFBDD9E6C51BF4E98F4FF0BA18AB980<br>
7z 5F5B38F945FF7F52927A2AE664F48B15</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/error-code-2/9697/15">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/error-code-2/9697/15</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 15 Sep 2012 21:25:43 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9697-15</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/error-code-2/9697.rss">Error code 2</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Error code 2</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[woohhaa]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>GORDON FREEMAN WHY HAVE YOU FORSAKEN ME!!!</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/error-code-2/9697/14">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/error-code-2/9697/14</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 15 Sep 2012 21:12:17 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9697-14</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/error-code-2/9697.rss">Error code 2</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Error code 2</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[woohhaa]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="V3R1TAS">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/v/65b543/40.png" class="avatar"> V3R1TAS:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Download and install 7-Zip (<a href="https://www.7-zip.org/download.html" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://www.7-zip.org/download.html</a>) and then be sure to extract the blackmesa zip file using Windows explorer (at least that’s how I did it) That fixed the issue for me. I was getting the same error.</p>
<p>Step by step:<br>
1- Download and install 7-Zip<br>
2- extract blackmesa.zip with Windows explorer<br>
3-Double click on Blackmesa setup</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I actually already tried using 7zip. I’ve been using the command line version of this for years to automate CNC downloads and other such non-sense but this is my first go at the GUI version.</p>
<p>When I extract using the 7zip GUI it it ends with 29409 Errors. Win Rar just tells me the file is corrupt. Same results from every version I’ve downloaded.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/error-code-2/9697/13">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/error-code-2/9697/13</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 15 Sep 2012 20:28:22 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9697-13</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/error-code-2/9697.rss">Error code 2</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Error code 2</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Kiingy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>[COLOR=‘PaleGreen’]Try installing WinRAR first, then run the setup exe.<br>
<a href="https://www.rarlab.com/download.htm" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://www.rarlab.com/download.htm</a></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/error-code-2/9697/12">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/error-code-2/9697/12</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 15 Sep 2012 18:46:46 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9697-12</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/error-code-2/9697.rss">Error code 2</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
