<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>New Tech</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/new-tech/3416</link>
    <description>This thread is basically a list I have compiled of all the new technology, everything from augmented reality to carbon nanotubes.
Unfortunately, most of these are still in the R&amp;D sector of corporate labs, but we could still see some of them within our lifetime.

*NOTE: This area of science is very sketchy. It is entirely possible that some of these are impossible.*

The reason we can see some of these within our lifetime is that medical research is advancing so fast that some people claim that, within the next forty years, scientists will be able to extend the human lifespan by more than 175 years. There are already one or two groups dedicated towards this goal, and more are on the way.
For you skeptics, it is entirely feasible. Several possible routes include gene therapy, limb/organ replacement, even uploading neural patterns into a robotic host body. (&lt;&lt; long way off)
There&#39;s really no way to tell when this is going to be available. The date that seems to get thrown around most is sometime in 2050, but there&#39;s no way to know.

The leading cause of death is disease or injury. This may not be the case for long.
Nanobots are incredibly tiny robots. To small to be seen with anything short of an electron microscope. They are, as their name suggest, robots. I&#39;m not sure exactly how they function, but basically they can break down or manipulate molecules. This clears up cancer, diabetes, most blood diseases, heart attacks, fat, pregnancy, sexual disease.....actually, pretty much any disease.
The reason is that they can be &quot;programmed&quot; to hunt down and destroy certain amounts of certain cells in certain areas. It&#39;s also possible that, somewhere down the line, they will be able to alter our genetics, but that&#39;s a long way off.
It&#39;s also been suggested that they could manipulate cells and molecules to speed up the healing process. They could also be used to turn off pain, increase neural activity, increase concentration, intelligence, and memory, as well as being able to stimulate certain emotions. Assuming you don&#39;t mind have trillions of tiny robots floating around in your bloodstream.
What happens if you get tasered?...
These will be available soon. They are being tested right now, and are expected to hit the market sometime next year.
Just like how episode 3 is going to be released in 2007.

Then there&#39;s carbon nanotubes.
These are very small, conductive tubes that are stronger than anything we have right now. They are so strong that, hypothetically, were you to drop a car from a mile up onto one, it would SLICE THE CAR IN FUCKING HALF.
Yeah.
The possible applications of this are literally endless. The most obvious one is combat armor that is more or less death proof. It could be used to reinforce any given structure, making it indestructible.

It could also build the space elevator.

Yup.

You&#39;re paying attention now, aren&#39;t you?

For those 1 or 2 people who don&#39;t know, the space elevator is a hypothetical.....elevator...that goes into space.
The way it works is that there&#39;s a platform/station on earth, usually proposed to be on a boat. On this platform there would be several entwined cables. Attached to those cables is a gigantic elevator, that either connects to the moon or to another platform that just sits there in orbit.
That&#39;s a very basic summary, and I don&#39;t really get the technicals, but there you go. I also have 2 images:
![](upload://6SM1JVR8HRaBhnjjJb03yQHy6vk.jpeg)
![](upload://lVuES9xk5VmlwcjT9mD1rW74YfJ.jpeg)
Carbon nanotubes are also supposed to make the smallest and most powerful computers to date, but I really don&#39;t know how.
There&#39;s one or two products with carbon nanotubes out already. They are being very rapidly developed, so expect to see more soon.

To change the subject, one company says they are going to have VR by 2014. &#39;Nuff said.

There&#39;s also exoskeletons. That term is used broadly, but in essence it means a semi-automated, full-body, mechanical device that assists/augments the human body.
There are more than enough examples of this in sci-fi. One is the lifter from aliens. Another is the H.E.V. suit. Yet another would be the nanosuit.
There are several of these in development.
My favorite is still in the design phase, but it can lift 220 pounds indefinitely.
It is worn by the user, and is connected in such a way that it simply mirror&#39;s the users movements.
I know there are several others in development, but I can only recall the specifics of one other.
It is done by a Japanese company. It is still in the R&amp;D phase, but it is significantly further along than the other ones. In fact, there was a video showing one of the workers using it to carry another worker across the office. I do not know how much this one can lift.
This is where it gets weird.
The company very stupidly got a website called skynet. I do not remember the rest of it-- it was something/something/.eu/es or something like that-- but for a company making robotic exoskeletons, that&#39;s pretty ominous.
Then there&#39;s the fact that the exoskeleton was made out of a smooth, white, chitinous casing with glowing blue centers. I shit you not. For those who don&#39;t get it, this pic is the thing that it looks like most:
[img]https://portalwiki.net/images/c/c6/GI_53_core1.jpg[/img]
If any knows the site, please post it.
This technology can be expected within the next 10 years.

Next is cars. I&#39;m not going to write much on this, as it depresses me, but here&#39;s the basics:
First, the manufacturers have decreed that priuses/hybrids/&quot;green&quot; cars are too quite. Supposedly, quite enough to be a menace.
The logical solution here would be to install louder horns, or, better yet, expect people to slow down when they are about to run someone over.
That&#39;s the LOGICAL solution.
The manufacturer&#39;s solution is to allow people to upload MP3&#39;s in place of horns. This seems like a good idea, until you realize that
A: Other people have different tastes in music, and
B: They are going to be blowing their horns for the hell of it.
This means that in the middle of a traffic jam it&#39;s going to be a regular lady gaga festival, leading to road rage, manslaughter, and general insanity.
It also means that you have no idea if someone&#39;s actually about to run you over, or if they&#39;re just being a douche.
The only plausible upshot is tailgating someone with the jaws theme.
Also with cars, they are developing cars that are:
covered in foam,
are painted green,
relay their location to ???,
are modular?
and, bizarrely enough, drive vertically and attach themselves to the balcony of your apartment.

We also have augmented reality.
This is an age-old concept where you have contacts/glasses/implants that let you see an &quot;enhanced&quot; version of reality. To explain, here are 2 pictures:
[img]https://thenextweb.com/wp-content/uploads/2009/06/augmented_reality.jpg[/img]
^^does not exist yet^^
![](upload://fecfqb0Eos8gXd9MQ6Gdr6WZ3rh.jpeg)
^^exists^^

Yes, ladies and gentlemen, this technology is here. Now. It&#39;s still in it&#39;s infancy, but it&#39;s here.
But only as iphone apps.
Yes, you can have it, but you will be perpetually holding up your Iphone in front of you, squinting at the readout.
Here are some links, if you want them:
[url]https://mashable.com/2009/12/05/augmented-reality-iphone/[/url]
[url]https://layar.com/[/url]

For those who still don&#39;t get it, augmented reality is the pinnacle of the information age. You glance at someone, and you immediately get their name, facebook page, twitter feed, phone number, DOB, Educational/sexual/criminal history....the list is endless.
You can also get directions to a location, link up with satellites, project images or webpages onto blank walls or really any surface.
If you are in the military, you can receive silent commands, get enemy locations, see what the enemy is wielding, where it&#39;s pointing the gun, where your squad is....again, the possibilities are endless.
&quot;But BMSMG,&quot; you ask, &quot;How could we use this when we&#39;re holding the Iphone up to our face all the time?&quot;
Here&#39;s how:
![](upload://1rAdbC7zEQU1wBVjYhN8GJ8L5UT.jpeg)
![](upload://hQY9ML7DaQ1T0YjzIDhhibYojlx.jpeg)
![](upload://9KQMDwfnA6h9sP7Yiq6QslJi2Kh.jpeg)
![](upload://ApbCRHyYTjeyY05wWBpdzwyizD4.jpeg)
It&#39;s called bionic vision, and it is the most awesome thing in all of recent frakking history. 
It is, in short, a monitor that overlays your vision. Anything you could display on a computer monitor is RIGHT IN FRONT OF YOU.
That, my friends, is how we will use augmented vision.

Now we also have another species to share augmented vision with!
Say hello to Jules.
[url]https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=kThr6CMLrvg[/url]
[url]https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=RNKLuXUh3M4[/url]
[url]https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=vArdTJfTOzo[/url]
[url]https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ysU56JzBjTY[/url]
[url]https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=elVdiboCa80[/url]
Jules is a conversational robot with facial recognition systems and lots of memory. He uses that memory to recall how people acted towards him in previous conversations, and then re-acts accordingly. In the words of his maker:
&quot;Be nice to jules or he may not treat you well&quot;
We have a word for that. You know what it is?
VENGEANCE.:fffuuu:
So if you see him, be nice.

Also it appears that we are soon going to be battling large, mechanical spiders just for the hell of it.
[url]https://www.lamachine.co.uk/index.php[/url]
You don&#39;t actually battle these, and there&#39;s nothing excitingly futuristic about this tech, but my steampunk obsessed mind would go crazy if I didn&#39;t post this.

Now that you have all these technology&#39;s buzzing throughout your head, read this article:
[url]https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Technological_singularity[/url]
Also, here are some links for the extended life tech:
[url]https://www.extended-eternallife.org/frame.html[/url]
[url]https://www.wired.com/wired/archive/8.01/forever.html[/url]
[url]https://www.nytimes.com/library/magazine/home/20000130mag-hall6.html[/url]

Images taken from /gajitz.com /portal wiki /thegamereviews.com /wikipedia
If you want to know more about any of this, just ask me, or, better yet, just freaking google it.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 24 Mar 2010 18:54:32 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Technology and Gaming</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/new-tech/3416.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>New Tech</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Bmsmg]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Fair point.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/new-tech/3416/42">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/new-tech/3416/42</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 24 Mar 2010 18:54:32 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3416-42</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/new-tech/3416.rss">New Tech</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>New Tech</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[sersoft]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Bmsmg">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/b/439d5e/40.png" class="avatar"> Bmsmg:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>And how long until we forget real life and just start playing thoughts over and over again like some perverse Ipod playlist?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>not long ago</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/new-tech/3416/41">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/new-tech/3416/41</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 23 Mar 2010 03:05:12 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3416-41</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/new-tech/3416.rss">New Tech</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>New Tech</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Bmsmg]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Ah. Here it is.<br>
<a href="https://www.cityweekly.net/utah/article-9318-brain-chip-may-help-the-blind-see.html" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://www.cityweekly.net/utah/article-9318-brain-chip-may-help-the-blind-see.html</a><br>
For those that didn’t understand that, this will allow you to download/upload thoughts onto a hard drive and, presumably, send them as an E-mail attachment in Yahoo!<br>
That seems simple enough, but if, for example, someone sells you a though of having sex with a hooker, is it just a though, porn, or prostitution?<br>
And how long until we forget real life and just start playing thoughts over and over again like some perverse Ipod playlist?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/new-tech/3416/40">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/new-tech/3416/40</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 20 Mar 2010 04:08:50 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3416-40</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/new-tech/3416.rss">New Tech</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>New Tech</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[sersoft]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="russilker">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/r/bbce88/40.png" class="avatar"> russilker:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I’m about 50% sure that I’ll die at the same time as the rest of humanity.<br>
Whether it be from AI growing too smart, from humans killing each other in war, from a natural disaster of some sort, etc; I’m pretty positive we don’t have much time left at this rate. We can’t handle our own progress.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I’m scared for the world if alot of people have your attitude, I am only about 0.03% sure of the world going to shit in my lifetime.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/new-tech/3416/39">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/new-tech/3416/39</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 19 Mar 2010 23:56:32 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3416-39</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/new-tech/3416.rss">New Tech</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>New Tech</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Spycrabz]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>tl;dr</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/new-tech/3416/38">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/new-tech/3416/38</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 19 Mar 2010 21:08:22 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3416-38</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/new-tech/3416.rss">New Tech</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>New Tech</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[taxi_evil]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Bmsmg">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/b/439d5e/40.png" class="avatar"> Bmsmg:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>How? I’ve tried shoving a CPU through it, teleporting myself, teleporting an object into another, but it seems invincible.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>You teleport something from the 2nd pad (the one that doesn’t start with a cactus on it) that’s too big to fit into the first pad.</p>
<p>A computer tower did the trick for me</p>
<p>Xbox version this was, got me a nice achievement  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=9" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/new-tech/3416/37">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/new-tech/3416/37</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 19 Mar 2010 21:05:11 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3416-37</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/new-tech/3416.rss">New Tech</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>New Tech</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Ibanez]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Muhb">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/m/ee7513/40.png" class="avatar"> Muhb:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Awesome grandpa rant</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Dude, after reading that, I was totally going to post that exact same Louis CK clip. He’s a champ. And absolutely right, I do the same damn thing with my cell phone, heh.  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=9" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/new-tech/3416/36">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/new-tech/3416/36</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 19 Mar 2010 06:08:50 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3416-36</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/new-tech/3416.rss">New Tech</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>New Tech</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[sersoft]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Bmsmg">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/b/439d5e/40.png" class="avatar"> Bmsmg:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>How? I’ve tried shoving a CPU through it, teleporting myself, teleporting an object into another, but it seems invincible.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=WlVBHvuSxyM" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=WlVBHvuSxyM</a></p>
<p>(you don’t have to jump on it, just teleport more than 1 object a few times back and forth until it breaks)</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/new-tech/3416/35">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/new-tech/3416/35</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 19 Mar 2010 03:19:18 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3416-35</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/new-tech/3416.rss">New Tech</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>New Tech</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Bmsmg]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Muhb">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/m/ee7513/40.png" class="avatar"> Muhb:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I can’t <span class="bbcode-i">wait</span> until I’m an old man and get to use the “when I was your age” card…</p>
<p>I’m going to be such a great luddite. My only hope is that I’ll be able to say “I told you so!” at least once to all of society before I die, when the Resonance Cascade happens at either the LHC or the NIF. :freeman:</p>
<p>(Not that I’m actually against technology or anything.  I find science fascinating.  Just that I personally believe that hopes and dreams for a technologically utopian, perfect, happy-go-lucky future, where all our problems will have been solved by GLaDOS/HAL/WOPR/GERTY/SkyNET/VIKI/Asimo/<span class="bbcode-i">&lt;&gt;</span>, are extremely unlikely.  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=9" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"> )</p>
<p>Also, I hate to say it, but part of me is actually kind of sad at the exponential rate at which technology is now increasing.  I think it makes it more difficult to <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=rOtEQB-9tvk" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">see or appreciate</a> each piece of the puzzle that helped to get us to where we are today.  It all becomes lost in one long massive stream of innovation.  I still like hearing/reading about new gadgets, but when you can start referring to science and technology collectively like that… “new gadgets…” I don’t know, something about it stops being special somehow.  Maybe I’m just weird like that though.  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/frowning.png?v=9" title=":frowning:" class="emoji" alt=":frowning:"></p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>An when I was your age, we didn’t have no stinkin telepathy! We had to put it on forums!<br>
By typing!<br>
WITH OUR HANDS!<br>
And if you got carpal tunnel, you were <span class="bbcode-i">[COLOR=‘White’]screwed. </span>:fffuuu:</p>
<p>In all seriousness, however, I don’t think this stuff is leading towards<br>
happy-go-lucky utopia. I think that people are going to try to make a utopia out of this, and that’s why it’s going to be hell. The only feasible way a utopia would work is if everyone thought exactly alike.<br>
Which, with some of this tech, could actually be possible…<br>
But let’s not go there.</p>
<p>And I, for one, actually don’t get any less excited with each new shiny tech.<br>
Of course, that could just be my steampunk-fanboy brain, but there you go.</p>
<p><span class="mention">@rusilker</span><br>
Naw. We can handle the tech.<br>
I’ll explain why tomorrow, as I need to download Prototype off steam now.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/new-tech/3416/34">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/new-tech/3416/34</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 19 Mar 2010 02:45:20 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3416-34</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/new-tech/3416.rss">New Tech</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>New Tech</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[russilker]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I’m about 50% sure that I’ll die at the same time as the rest of humanity.<br>
Whether it be from AI growing too smart, from humans killing each other in war, from a natural disaster of some sort, etc; I’m pretty positive we don’t have much time left at this rate. We can’t handle our own progress.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/new-tech/3416/33">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/new-tech/3416/33</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 19 Mar 2010 02:33:56 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3416-33</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/new-tech/3416.rss">New Tech</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>New Tech</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Bmsmg]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>How? I’ve tried shoving a CPU through it, teleporting myself, teleporting an object into another, but it seems invincible.</p>
<p>Also, more on eternal life:<br>
<a href="https://discovermagazine.com/2007/apr/how-to-grow-a-new-limb" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://discovermagazine.com/2007/apr/how-to-grow-a-new-limb</a></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/new-tech/3416/32">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/new-tech/3416/32</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 19 Mar 2010 02:31:06 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3416-32</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/new-tech/3416.rss">New Tech</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>New Tech</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Muhb]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I can’t <span class="bbcode-i">wait</span> until I’m an old man and get to use the “when I was your age” card…</p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>When I was your age, we didn’t have no stinkin’ “tello-porters,” you had to <span class="bbcode-b">manually drive</span>, or, (if you had the money,) you could hurl your frail body through the <span class="bbcode-b">sky</span> in an elongated <span class="bbcode-b">sardine can</span> towards the general direction where you wanted to go, using either a “car” or a “plane” that burned <span class="bbcode-b">combustible fuel</span>. <span class="bbcode-i">“What happened if you ran out of fuel, Grandpa?”</span> Then you were <span class="bbcode-b"><span class="bbcode-i">screwed!</span></span> :fffuuu:</p>
<p>When I was your age, we didn’t have no stinkin’ “space elevator,” no, we had to use a <span class="bbcode-b">giant metal bottle rocket</span> which burned <span class="bbcode-b">hydrogen</span> to get to the moon. <span class="bbcode-i">“Wow, really?!”</span> You bet, but if you ever had to take a dump right before takeoff, you were <span class="bbcode-b"><span class="bbcode-i">screwed.</span></span> :fffuuu:</p>
<p>When I was your age, we didn’t have no stinkin’ “hollow-deck” to play in, instead we had to watch movies and play video games on a <span class="bbcode-b">two-dimensional screen</span> using a controller <span class="bbcode-b"><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=bTR1L_B93Rg" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">with buttons and triggers</a></span> for fun, so quit your whining! <span class="bbcode-i">“But Grandp–”</span> (And if the power ever went out while you were fighting the final boss, you were <span class="bbcode-b"><span class="bbcode-i">screwed.</span></span>) :fffuuu:</p>
<p>When I was your age, we didn’t need no fancy stinkin’ contact lenses to help us identify our family members and friends, we actually had to <span class="bbcode-b">memorize</span> their <span class="bbcode-b">faces</span>. <span class="bbcode-i">“…”</span> And if you blanked out for a moment, and couldn’t remember someone’s name, you were <span class="bbcode-b"><span class="bbcode-i">screwed!</span></span> :fffuuu:</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I’m going to be such a great luddite. My only hope is that I’ll be able to say “I told you so!” at least once to all of society before I die, when the Resonance Cascade happens at either the LHC or the NIF. :freeman:</p>
<p>(Not that I’m actually against technology or anything.  I find science fascinating.  Just that I personally believe that hopes and dreams for a technologically utopian, perfect, happy-go-lucky future, where all our problems will have been solved by GLaDOS/HAL/WOPR/GERTY/SkyNET/VIKI/Asimo/<span class="bbcode-i">&lt;&gt;</span>, are extremely unlikely.  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=9" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"> )</p>
<p>Also, I hate to say it, but part of me is actually kind of sad at the exponential rate at which technology is now increasing.  I think it makes it more difficult to <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=rOtEQB-9tvk" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">see or appreciate</a> each piece of the puzzle that helped to get us to where we are today.  It all becomes lost in one long massive stream of innovation.  I still like hearing/reading about new gadgets, but when you can start referring to science and technology collectively like that… “new gadgets…” I don’t know, something about it stops being special somehow.  Maybe I’m just weird like that though.  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/frowning.png?v=9" title=":frowning:" class="emoji" alt=":frowning:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/new-tech/3416/31">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/new-tech/3416/31</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 19 Mar 2010 02:24:30 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3416-31</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/new-tech/3416.rss">New Tech</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>New Tech</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[sersoft]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Madcat1030">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/m/9f8e36/40.png" class="avatar"> Madcat1030:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>He was quoting Alyx… I think.  An inside joke for all HL2 players.  Which we all should be.  If you don’t own HL2, gtfo the forums.  nao. <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/expressionless.png?v=9" title=":expressionless:" class="emoji" alt=":expressionless:"> So says stoic smiley.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>this</p>
<p>did you know you can break the small teleporter in the same scene?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/new-tech/3416/30">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/new-tech/3416/30</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 18 Mar 2010 23:57:57 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3416-30</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/new-tech/3416.rss">New Tech</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>New Tech</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Bmsmg]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Jingles">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/j/46a35a/40.png" class="avatar"> Jingles:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>With the teleporter in hl2…</p>
<p>The cat got turned inside out during testing.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>This.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/new-tech/3416/29">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/new-tech/3416/29</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 18 Mar 2010 23:50:29 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3416-29</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/new-tech/3416.rss">New Tech</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>New Tech</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Madcat1030]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>He was quoting Alyx… I think.  An inside joke for all HL2 players.  Which we all should be.  If you don’t own HL2, gtfo the forums.  nao. <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/expressionless.png?v=9" title=":expressionless:" class="emoji" alt=":expressionless:"> So says stoic smiley.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/new-tech/3416/28">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/new-tech/3416/28</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 18 Mar 2010 20:16:37 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3416-28</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/new-tech/3416.rss">New Tech</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>New Tech</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Jingles]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>With the teleporter in hl2…</p>
<p>The cat got turned inside out during testing.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/new-tech/3416/27">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/new-tech/3416/27</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 18 Mar 2010 20:07:03 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3416-27</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/new-tech/3416.rss">New Tech</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>New Tech</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[sersoft]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>What cat?  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/expressionless.png?v=9" title=":expressionless:" class="emoji" alt=":expressionless:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/new-tech/3416/26">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/new-tech/3416/26</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 18 Mar 2010 20:03:21 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3416-26</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/new-tech/3416.rss">New Tech</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>New Tech</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Bmsmg]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Hey yeah, about that cat…</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/new-tech/3416/25">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/new-tech/3416/25</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 18 Mar 2010 18:29:37 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3416-25</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/new-tech/3416.rss">New Tech</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>New Tech</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Seth]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>We have complete confidence in you. :freeman:</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/new-tech/3416/24">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/new-tech/3416/24</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 18 Mar 2010 16:49:25 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3416-24</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/new-tech/3416.rss">New Tech</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>New Tech</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Madcat1030]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I’d perfer no packet loss, thank you.  I enjoy my package.</p>
<p>But seriously, I totally understand what you meant.  It we can’t have near perfect data retention through transfer, teleportation would be unsafe and unstable.</p>
<p>And the problem with Quantum-based teleportation (of course, as of right now, that’s the only feasible form of teleportation, anyway) is that it would be a strictly 1-to-1 system.</p>
<p>In order to teleport from my house to the moon, we would have to have a linked-Quantum pair set up and then have one put into* the teleport at my house and one at the moon teleport.  In order for my best friend in Russia (I don’t casually know anybody in Russia, by the way) to transport to the moon, there would need to be another linked pair, and it’s two would have to be put into* the teleport at his house and in another teleport on the moon.  Essentially, it would be likely that if this ever happens and becomes a mass-reality**, there would most likely be several teleport “hubs” around the world, each with a different porter to the other hubs, in several major cities.  Then space-faring corporations and institutions (NASA and the like, but probably not NASA, since they are already having trouble with funding) would have their linked pairs set up and installed at their base of operations and another in a teleport on a rocket or something, and then sent to the destination.</p>
<p>Of course, this is all if we can minimize packet loss to an acceptable level of safety.</p>
<p>*By “put in” I mean incorporate them into a teleportation device however it would be necessary.  As I am not a Quantum physicist, I do not know what the exact specifications of such a device would be.</p>
<p>**By “mass-reality” I mean becomes used in everyday life by more than researchers, rich people, and governments.  Example: Private helicopters =/= mass-reality.  Television = mass-reality, on the basis that a majority of people have a television or access to a television.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/new-tech/3416/23">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/new-tech/3416/23</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 18 Mar 2010 15:43:26 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3416-23</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/new-tech/3416.rss">New Tech</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>New Tech</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[russilker]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Until “packet loss” is minimized to a very low percentage teleportation will be impossible, as Soviet stated.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/new-tech/3416/22">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/new-tech/3416/22</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 18 Mar 2010 04:03:21 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3416-22</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/new-tech/3416.rss">New Tech</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>New Tech</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Soviet]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Speaking of teleportation, quantum teleportation is a reality, if only in very rudimentary stages. It essentially copies the properties of one particle to another instantaneously. Of course, as stated in the link below, it only works 25% of the time and the idea of moving this up to anything larger like actual objects is very unlikely.</p>
<p><a href="https://www.aip.org/png/html/teleport.htm" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://www.aip.org/png/html/teleport.htm</a></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/new-tech/3416/21">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/new-tech/3416/21</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 18 Mar 2010 03:50:10 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3416-21</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/new-tech/3416.rss">New Tech</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>New Tech</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Bmsmg]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Expect new links within the next 1 or 2 days.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/new-tech/3416/20">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/new-tech/3416/20</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 18 Mar 2010 03:10:09 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3416-20</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/new-tech/3416.rss">New Tech</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>New Tech</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[sersoft]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>in the spirit of this thread, I’m guessing that by the time the space elevator is complete, technology will allow people to teleport via the internet anywhere(even out to space) as long as there’s decent signal and low packet loss.  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=9" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"></p>
<p>Seriously though, I bet people will pay good money just to ride the elevator up and down.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/new-tech/3416/19">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/new-tech/3416/19</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 17 Mar 2010 17:40:46 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3416-19</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/new-tech/3416.rss">New Tech</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>New Tech</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Madcat1030]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="sersoft">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/user_avatar/leakfree.org/sersoft/40/5837_2.png" class="avatar"> sersoft:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I always thought that the space elevator is to avoid fighting with gravity on takeoff, so at the other end would be a space station with all the space ships and shit, but they won’t have to take off from earth and waste half the fuel reserve just to take off.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Yes, the space elevator would provide an alternative to the massive amounts of rocket fuel required to escape earth’s orbit each launch, but ships would have to be built in space (not a bad thing, just different, because we’d have to ship up the construction parts piece by piece), around some sort of theoretical space-dock, which would be the end-point of what would most likely be the MAIN space lift, if not the only.  They’d be massively expensive, require extensive maintenance to keep them from snapping, and some sort of epic shielding.  Even on a track, the atmosphere’s gonna put up a fight against anything passing through, so the cabins would likely have to be replaced every couple of years.  I’d suspect if we ever got a space elevator, it would be the only one for a very long time.</p>
<p>That, and the space elevator’s track could house cables, allowing for any station on the end to hook into Earth’s internet.  As with the interplaNET on mars, they’re working on getting ready to launch a few satellites around the ISS to provide it with it’s own internet and flimsy direct downlink to Earth’s internet.  The space-elevator would get rid of this need by extending Earth’s own internet.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="OBNOXIUs">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/o/edb3f5/40.png" class="avatar"> OBNOXIUs:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>You say it will be connected to a moon or gigantic satellite…That isn’t necessary.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Well, yeah, it isn’t necessary, but the pod would just go flying off into space.  Yeah, that MIGHT be useful if you just sat a rocket on it and used the lift to get it through the atmosphere, and just letting it coast the rest of the way, but we’d get much more use out of it if we used it to build in space.  If we got this theoretical elevator hooked up to a ‘small’ space station, we could use it to send the supplies to create an geosynchronous superstation, see space-dock above.</p>
<p>Also, because this elevator would likely span many Earth-radii beyond our atmosphere, there would have to be defense stations along the span, with some sort of mounted turrets to ward off meteorites.  They would be a real danger to the spans.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/new-tech/3416/18">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/new-tech/3416/18</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 17 Mar 2010 17:21:25 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3416-18</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/new-tech/3416.rss">New Tech</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
