<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crash in c1a4e</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/crash-in-c1a4e/9813</link>
    <description>After blast pit I was going down the ladder and the game kept crashing after loading c1a4e. Turns out if I look towards the wall it would crash, but if I look outwards from the ladder it wouldn&#39;t. Now that I managed to get down and swim out backwards I still can&#39;t continue because everytime I turn around it would crash. Don&#39;t really want to play the entire level in reverse.

I now tried to lower all graphic settings to lowest which seems to have helped. Then I set them back to their previous value one by one and it worked. Seems to be an issue with the graphics settings when the level is loaded or something like that</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 15 Sep 2012 13:30:27 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>In-game Issues (Mod)</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/crash-in-c1a4e/9813.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Crash in c1a4e</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[RiscIt]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Managed to proceed. While standing on the pipe to cross the goo (first time, over the rotating paddle vat) I would crash every time I looked back. When I crossed it, I crashed when I looked to the path left.</p>
<p>Eventually I dropped all advanced video options to the minimum, and have been able to proceed, and look all around me.</p>
<p>EDIT: When I climbed up on to the final catwalk/pipe frame which leads to the pipe you need to move in to place, I began restoring advanced video options 1 at a time. After each I would walk back to the area I had just come from and look around. I never crashed again in that level, and I was able to restore all of my settings to max. I can’t explain it. Particularly frustrating since it was crashing so consistently before.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/crash-in-c1a4e/9813/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/crash-in-c1a4e/9813/3</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 15 Sep 2012 13:30:27 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9813-3</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/crash-in-c1a4e/9813.rss">Crash in c1a4e</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Crash in c1a4e</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[RiscIt]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="ccMatrix">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/c/47e85d/40.png" class="avatar"> ccMatrix:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>After blast pit I was going down the ladder and the game kept crashing after loading c1a4e.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Same here. I can not continue as it crashes on loading the next level as I climb down in to the pit.</p>
<p>EDIT: On reading the above post I tried looking up at the ceiling as I descended. I could load the level after that. As I turned around the framerate stuttered (texture loading I presume). I fell in to the water (scripted) and climbed out. I crashed looking at some orange barrels right in front of me.</p>
<p>EDIT: next attempt. Was able to land on solid ground (ouch). Crashed while looking around (panning) the room.</p>
<p>EDIT: Ok… I can look anywhere in the room, except behind me. I’m standing under the ladder drop point. If I turn counter-clockwise I don’t get far enough to see the ladder. If I turn clock-wise just ladder rungs are just in view, and then it crashes.</p>
<p>EDIT: I was on very high texture detail. Dropping to medium did not help.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/crash-in-c1a4e/9813/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/crash-in-c1a4e/9813/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 15 Sep 2012 13:04:50 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9813-2</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/crash-in-c1a4e/9813.rss">Crash in c1a4e</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Crash in c1a4e</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[ccMatrix]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>After blast pit I was going down the ladder and the game kept crashing after loading c1a4e. Turns out if I look towards the wall it would crash, but if I look outwards from the ladder it wouldn’t. Now that I managed to get down and swim out backwards I still can’t continue because everytime I turn around it would crash. Don’t really want to play the entire level in reverse.</p>
<p>I now tried to lower all graphic settings to lowest which seems to have helped. Then I set them back to their previous value one by one and it worked. Seems to be an issue with the graphics settings when the level is loaded or something like that</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/crash-in-c1a4e/9813/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/crash-in-c1a4e/9813/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 15 Sep 2012 10:44:24 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9813-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/crash-in-c1a4e/9813.rss">Crash in c1a4e</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
