<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Text and Chapter Titles being cut of, not scaling properly.</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/text-and-chapter-titles-being-cut-of-not-scaling-properly/14488</link>
    <description>I just decided to give Black Mesa another run through after I purchased it (last play through was when it was released on the website before), when I noticed a rather strange bug.

I&#39;m just doing Black Mesa Inbound and every time there is text past a certain point, it is being cut off.  For example, when the game is indicating Black Mesa is in New Mexico, it cuts off partway through the text and indicates its Mexi. Physics is being cut of to just Ph, and Sector  C Laboratory is being reported as Sector C Labo.

It seems obvious to me that the text box is being restricted, or not scaling properly with my monitor.

I&#39;m currently using a 3440 x 1440 monitor, so that may play a part in it.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 04 Dec 2015 08:22:47 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>In-game Issues</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/text-and-chapter-titles-being-cut-of-not-scaling-properly/14488.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Text and Chapter Titles being cut of, not scaling properly.</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Bel]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I just decided to give Black Mesa another run through after I purchased it (last play through was when it was released on the website before), when I noticed a rather strange bug.</p>
<p>I’m just doing Black Mesa Inbound and every time there is text past a certain point, it is being cut off.  For example, when the game is indicating Black Mesa is in New Mexico, it cuts off partway through the text and indicates its Mexi. Physics is being cut of to just Ph, and Sector  C Laboratory is being reported as Sector C Labo.</p>
<p>It seems obvious to me that the text box is being restricted, or not scaling properly with my monitor.</p>
<p>I’m currently using a 3440 x 1440 monitor, so that may play a part in it.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/text-and-chapter-titles-being-cut-of-not-scaling-properly/14488/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/text-and-chapter-titles-being-cut-of-not-scaling-properly/14488/1</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 04 Dec 2015 08:22:47 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14488-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/text-and-chapter-titles-being-cut-of-not-scaling-properly/14488.rss">Text and Chapter Titles being cut of, not scaling properly.</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
