<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Ask an Objectivist</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/ask-an-objectivist/6487</link>
    <description>Derp.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 19 Feb 2011 23:22:07 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Off Topic</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/ask-an-objectivist/6487.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Ask an Objectivist</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[k3nny1550]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Okay, I’ve got a question for the OP:</p>
<ul>
<li>
<p>How would an implementation of Objectivist principles assist the current US economy?</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>A core tenant of Objectivism is in the free economic principles. Considering that most of the US economy has been outsourced to other countries in the name of cutting expenditures, how would such principles be applied to bring jobs back to America? Would this come from venture capital? (Which currently is scarce due to said economic conditions)</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>The current administration’s actions with regards to the economy have been very much against the tenants of Objectivism. How would an Objectivist be able to fix these problems? (Historically, attempting to repeal <span class="bbcode-i">any</span> act of Congress is like pulling steel teeth four inches thick with tweezers and no anisthetic)</p>
</li>
</ul>
<p>EDIT: My background for Objectivist theory is based on my reading sections of “The Virtue of Selfishness” and, at present, reading the entirety of “Atlas Shrugged.” A fine novel, but drags in description. The ideas presented within are revolutionary, but the presentation of said ideas occasionally comes across as ham-fisted into the dialog. Hopefully the core philosophy will be implemented more seamlessly into the film due out this year.)</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/ask-an-objectivist/6487/125">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/ask-an-objectivist/6487/125</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 19 Feb 2011 23:22:07 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-6487-125</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/ask-an-objectivist/6487.rss">Ask an Objectivist</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Ask an Objectivist</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[danielsangeo]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>sersoft: Tell that to Agrajag!</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/ask-an-objectivist/6487/124">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/ask-an-objectivist/6487/124</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Feb 2011 13:02:42 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-6487-124</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/ask-an-objectivist/6487.rss">Ask an Objectivist</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Ask an Objectivist</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[sersoft]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Everybody’s evil. I killed a fly today, I am evil. I deserve to be punished (from the point of view of the fly). But who knows, maybe when you die and become one with the universe again you feel grateful for whatever your cause of death was, nobody knows.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/ask-an-objectivist/6487/123">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/ask-an-objectivist/6487/123</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Feb 2011 06:47:25 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-6487-123</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/ask-an-objectivist/6487.rss">Ask an Objectivist</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Ask an Objectivist</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[danielsangeo]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Triage: This is the Mass-Debating Hall and you posted this topic in the open.  PM kinda negates the purpose, don’t it?</p>
<p>As for the concept of evil, back to the Star Wars rebels.  They destroy the Death Star, yes?  Well, a lot of people were killed on the Death Star.  Those that were killed were supporting evil, yes?  The Death Star killed a lot of people, yes?</p>
<p>So, the Empire is an either-or scenario.  You are either a member of the Empire or you’re part of the rebels.  The rebels are an outlaw organization.  There are support staff (such as janitors who clean the toilets) that were killed following the law.  They were “innocent”, weren’t they?  The janitors?</p>
<p>Aren’t the rebels, then, evil, or at least supporting evil acts and either way you go, you’re evil?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/ask-an-objectivist/6487/122">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/ask-an-objectivist/6487/122</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Feb 2011 06:29:49 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-6487-122</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/ask-an-objectivist/6487.rss">Ask an Objectivist</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Ask an Objectivist</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[bur]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>“He is evil because he is hurting others.”</p>
<p>He is hurting others. Applying the term “evil” is completely arbitrary.</p>
<p>btw before you say that i’m close-minded or angry or something, this is mass <span class="bbcode-i">debating</span> hall, i’m <span class="bbcode-i">debating</span> (trying to) what you’re saying</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/ask-an-objectivist/6487/121">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/ask-an-objectivist/6487/121</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 17 Feb 2011 20:31:11 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-6487-121</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/ask-an-objectivist/6487.rss">Ask an Objectivist</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Ask an Objectivist</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Triage]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Cat_Fuzz">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/c/7bcc69/40.png" class="avatar"> Cat_Fuzz:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I hate to say I’ve my doubts on this idea of Objectivism. Here’s why:</p>
<p>This statement essentially says that there is good and that there is evil. That good is objective, and that evil is born through ignorance from objective values.</p>
<p>But then what defines good and evil.</p>
<p>Take your earlier quote.</p>
<p>The good man works a well paid job for a buisness which is also responsible for exploiting child labourers. He can’t challenge this though, as he may lose his job and, ergo, his happy lifestyle. He is, in the eyes of Objectivism evil for willingly ignoring something that is objective.</p>
<p>[b]Here are some things wrong with that scenario:</p>
<p>-Say that yes, the company is exploiting children and making them work in harsh conditions. The owner of that company knows what he is doing but doesn’t care. He is evil because he is hurting others. In Objectivism, it is wrong to hurt others for any reason except if THEY are the ones who first harm others. In other words, that man, if he is claiming to be Objectivist, and is using the argument that he is only using them for his own selfish end, he is lying because: It is unreasonable and MORALLY INCORRECT to do such things to innocent children.</p>
<p>-The ‘good man’, in this scenario, is no longer a good man. He is supporting somebody who is exploiting and harming others.</p>
<p>-I assume that the public does not know about what’s going on in that business? If they do, but nobody gives a damn about it, then those people are also evil. However, I doubt that this scenario would occur in an Objectivist society, or ANY society for that matter. When the American public discovered the horrors of child labor in the late nineteenth century, they were disgusted. However, the mistake that the public made was that they called for regulation of business, when they could have just boycotted the companies that were responsible for the exploitation. Why punish all businesses by not allowing them to flourish, just because some businesses do cruel things?[/b]</p>
<p>Terrorists, on the other hand, could also be seen as good in the eyes of objectivism. Whilst they neglect western values, they believe in their own values. <span class="bbcode-u">To these people, intending harm in whatever form on those who do not follow their path of self-potential is a good thing. Aside from that, they are often big pillars within their communities and help and provide for those who share the same values.</span> While yes, most of these people are religious extremists who, with your logic, would render them nothing more than subjective extremists. What’s to stop them from saying we’re greedy, ignorant b*******s.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">What I underlined is the ruin of your own scenario. You’re saying that these people are selfish, but you also say that they help others in need because they consider it to be a must (again, different from perhaps helping the children being exploited because in their case, they are being hurt by someone directly). This implies altruism, the exact opposite of Objectivism. Therefore, to call them greedy is incorrect. </span></p>
<p>The point I’m trying to make is that I’m unconvinced that Objectivism can be followed to it’s extreme. The idea that evil exists as ignorance of objective values is somewhat contrived: as burbinator said, good people do bad stuff, bad people do good stuff. This is through circumstance, not ignorance.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>My responses are in bold.</p>
<p>I can tell that you, unlike some people who post here, have an openness to my philosophy, even if it’s small. If you would like, send me a PM with any questions that you have. I’d rather you speak to me directly than in the thread.</p>
<p>The above also applies to people who are genuinely curious about Objectivism, and don’t just want to ask a few questions before getting seemingly angry.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/ask-an-objectivist/6487/120">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/ask-an-objectivist/6487/120</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 17 Feb 2011 18:58:53 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-6487-120</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/ask-an-objectivist/6487.rss">Ask an Objectivist</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Ask an Objectivist</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Cat_Fuzz]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="From Lexicon">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 From Lexicon:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>The spread of evil is the symptom of a vacuum. Whenever evil wins, it is only by default: by the moral failure of those who evade the fact that there can be no compromise on basic principles.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I hate to say I’ve my doubts on this idea of Objectivism. Here’s why:</p>
<p>This statement essentially says that there is good and that there is evil. That good is objective, and that evil is born through ignorance from objective values.</p>
<p>But then what defines good and evil.</p>
<p>Take your earlier quote.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Triage">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/t/d6d6ee/40.png" class="avatar"> Triage:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Good and evil are not some sort of supernatural or unseen forces. They’re states of the human mind. If a man leads a happy life without causing harm to others (this is different from altruism, because he knows his limits and that each man or woman on earth has their own goals and values) then he is arguably a good man. If a terrorist leads a life of torturing and killing others either for entertainment or for his so-called “god” then he is an evil man.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>The good man works a well paid job for a buisness which is also responsible for exploiting child labourers. He can’t challenge this though, as he may lose his job and, ergo, his happy lifestyle. He is, in the eyes of Objectivism evil for willingly ignoring something that is objective.</p>
<p>Terrorists, on the other hand, could also be seen as good in the eyes of objectivism. Whilst they neglect western values, they believe in their own values. To these people, intending harm in whatever form on those who do not follow their path of self-potential is a good thing. Aside from that, they are often big pillars within their communities and help and provide for those who share the same values. While yes, most of these people are religious extremists who, with your logic, would render them nothing more than subjective extremists. What’s to stop them from saying we’re greedy, ignorant b*******s.</p>
<p>The point I’m trying to make is that I’m unconvinced that Objectivism can be followed to it’s extreme. The idea that evil exists as ignorance of objective values is somewhat contrived: as burbinator said, good people do bad stuff, bad people do good stuff. This is through circumstance, not ignorance.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/ask-an-objectivist/6487/119">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/ask-an-objectivist/6487/119</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 17 Feb 2011 08:08:28 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-6487-119</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/ask-an-objectivist/6487.rss">Ask an Objectivist</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Ask an Objectivist</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[bur]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Burbinator">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Burbinator:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>evil</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Triage">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/t/d6d6ee/40.png" class="avatar"> Triage:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>if you STILL cannot figure out what it means, then ask me.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Burbinator">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Burbinator:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>tell me then</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>three successive posts…</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/ask-an-objectivist/6487/118">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/ask-an-objectivist/6487/118</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 16 Feb 2011 23:10:50 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-6487-118</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/ask-an-objectivist/6487.rss">Ask an Objectivist</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Ask an Objectivist</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[papernick]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I’m not saying your ideals are worthless, I’m saying that this discussion is just philosophical bullshit.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/ask-an-objectivist/6487/117">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/ask-an-objectivist/6487/117</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 16 Feb 2011 22:03:50 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-6487-117</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/ask-an-objectivist/6487.rss">Ask an Objectivist</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Ask an Objectivist</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Triage]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Burbinator">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Burbinator:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>im not gonna bother copy pasting shit</p>
<p>tell me then</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>No.</p>
<p>Unless you actually give me an example of something you want explained, I can’t do anything. You’re pretty much asking me to answer a question for you, but you’re not giving me the question.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="acade366">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 acade366:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>you are discussing meaningless and redundant concepts.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>How so? Are you saying that my ideals are worthless? If so, what gives you the authority to say so?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/ask-an-objectivist/6487/116">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/ask-an-objectivist/6487/116</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 16 Feb 2011 21:33:53 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-6487-116</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/ask-an-objectivist/6487.rss">Ask an Objectivist</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Ask an Objectivist</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[papernick]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>you are discussing meaningless and redundant concepts.</p>
<p>And for the record, I’ve never played cod4.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/ask-an-objectivist/6487/115">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/ask-an-objectivist/6487/115</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 16 Feb 2011 19:09:36 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-6487-115</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/ask-an-objectivist/6487.rss">Ask an Objectivist</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Ask an Objectivist</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[BrAndi]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="acade366">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 acade366:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>what the fuck is this clusterfuck of a thread</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Yeah, thinking, building an opinion and admitting the other one may have a point. WHAT A CRAZY THING TO DO ACADE! LET’S GO AND FRAG IMAGES OF REAL SOLDIERS ON COD4!!!</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/ask-an-objectivist/6487/114">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/ask-an-objectivist/6487/114</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 16 Feb 2011 13:27:24 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-6487-114</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/ask-an-objectivist/6487.rss">Ask an Objectivist</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Ask an Objectivist</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[papernick]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>what the fuck is this clusterfuck of a thread</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/ask-an-objectivist/6487/113">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/ask-an-objectivist/6487/113</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 16 Feb 2011 02:48:46 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-6487-113</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/ask-an-objectivist/6487.rss">Ask an Objectivist</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Ask an Objectivist</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[bur]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>im not gonna bother copy pasting shit</p>
<p>tell me then</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/ask-an-objectivist/6487/112">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/ask-an-objectivist/6487/112</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 16 Feb 2011 00:39:46 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-6487-112</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/ask-an-objectivist/6487.rss">Ask an Objectivist</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Ask an Objectivist</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Triage]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Burbinator">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Burbinator:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>it repeatedly refers to evil as something tangible, as a sort of entity</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Give me a specific example of where it says that; however, I want you to first read it over again, and if you STILL cannot figure out what it means, then ask me.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/ask-an-objectivist/6487/111">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/ask-an-objectivist/6487/111</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 15 Feb 2011 23:17:36 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-6487-111</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/ask-an-objectivist/6487.rss">Ask an Objectivist</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Ask an Objectivist</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[bur]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>it repeatedly refers to evil as something tangible, as a sort of entity</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/ask-an-objectivist/6487/110">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/ask-an-objectivist/6487/110</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 15 Feb 2011 21:14:29 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-6487-110</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/ask-an-objectivist/6487.rss">Ask an Objectivist</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Ask an Objectivist</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Triage]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Burbinator">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Burbinator:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>i just did, and all i can say is: what a load of bullshit</p>
<p>it <span class="bbcode-i">does</span> seem to consider evil as some sort of force, at least partly so, and it all just sounds ridiculous</p>
<p>PERSON DOES BAD THING HE IS EVIL HURDUR</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Where does it say that evil is some sort of force?</p>
<p>And yes, if someone does things that are evil over and over again, or even thinks that they are good, then he is evil.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/ask-an-objectivist/6487/109">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/ask-an-objectivist/6487/109</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 15 Feb 2011 20:22:43 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-6487-109</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/ask-an-objectivist/6487.rss">Ask an Objectivist</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Ask an Objectivist</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[bur]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>i just did, and all i can say is: what a load of bullshit</p>
<p>it <span class="bbcode-i">does</span> seem to consider evil as some sort of force, at least partly so, and it all just sounds ridiculous</p>
<p>PERSON DOES BAD THING HE IS EVIL HURDUR</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/ask-an-objectivist/6487/108">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/ask-an-objectivist/6487/108</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 15 Feb 2011 16:39:05 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-6487-108</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/ask-an-objectivist/6487.rss">Ask an Objectivist</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Ask an Objectivist</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Triage]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Burbinator">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Burbinator:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>okay so basically that definition of evil has nothing to do with the classic understanding of the word</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Read. It. Again.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/ask-an-objectivist/6487/107">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/ask-an-objectivist/6487/107</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 15 Feb 2011 12:10:42 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-6487-107</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/ask-an-objectivist/6487.rss">Ask an Objectivist</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Ask an Objectivist</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[bur]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>okay so basically that definition of evil has nothing to do with the classic understanding of the word</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/ask-an-objectivist/6487/106">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/ask-an-objectivist/6487/106</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 15 Feb 2011 01:17:06 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-6487-106</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/ask-an-objectivist/6487.rss">Ask an Objectivist</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Ask an Objectivist</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[danielsangeo]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>So, the rebels were evil?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/ask-an-objectivist/6487/105">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/ask-an-objectivist/6487/105</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 15 Feb 2011 00:34:39 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-6487-105</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/ask-an-objectivist/6487.rss">Ask an Objectivist</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Ask an Objectivist</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Triage]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Burbinator">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Burbinator:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Tell me, what is your objective definition of evil?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p><a href="https://aynrandlexicon.com/lexicon/evil.html" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://aynrandlexicon.com/lexicon/evil.html</a></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/ask-an-objectivist/6487/104">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/ask-an-objectivist/6487/104</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 14 Feb 2011 23:40:41 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-6487-104</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/ask-an-objectivist/6487.rss">Ask an Objectivist</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Ask an Objectivist</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[bur]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Tell me, what is your objective definition of evil?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/ask-an-objectivist/6487/103">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/ask-an-objectivist/6487/103</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 14 Feb 2011 21:26:03 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-6487-103</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/ask-an-objectivist/6487.rss">Ask an Objectivist</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Ask an Objectivist</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Triage]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="danielsangeo">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/user_avatar/leakfree.org/danielsangeo/40/4347_2.png" class="avatar"> danielsangeo:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>The one example I always like to use is the end of Star Wars: Episode IV.  SPOILERS (in case you’re one of the last one on the planet that hasn’t seen it):</p>
<p>Luke and the Rebel Alliance go in and destroy the Death Star.  The first Death Star had a compliment of over a million (including crew, troops, pilots, support staff, etc).</p>
<p>Are the Rebels “evil”?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Well, was the empire using the Death Star as a weapon of mass destruction to destroy planets that were home to hundreds of millions people and aliens? Yes. Was the empire trying to tighten its grip on its colonies? Yes. Was it corrupt? Yes.</p>
<p>Were the rebels fighting against the people who allowed all this to be possible? Yes.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/ask-an-objectivist/6487/102">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/ask-an-objectivist/6487/102</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 14 Feb 2011 20:45:23 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-6487-102</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/ask-an-objectivist/6487.rss">Ask an Objectivist</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Ask an Objectivist</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[danielsangeo]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>The one example I always like to use is the end of Star Wars: Episode IV.  SPOILERS (in case you’re one of the last one on the planet that hasn’t seen it):</p>
<p>Luke and the Rebel Alliance go in and destroy the Death Star.  The first Death Star had a compliment of over a million (including crew, troops, pilots, support staff, etc).</p>
<p>Are the Rebels “evil”?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/ask-an-objectivist/6487/101">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/ask-an-objectivist/6487/101</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 14 Feb 2011 18:39:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-6487-101</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/ask-an-objectivist/6487.rss">Ask an Objectivist</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
