<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Very end of &quot;Unforseen Consequences&quot; Elevator Issue [Fixed]</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/very-end-of-unforseen-consequences-elevator-issue-fixed/10449</link>
    <description>The elevator you get on that takes you to the beginning of the &quot;Office Complex&quot; statue has a slight bug, in my opinion.  If you get on the elevator and press &quot;e&quot; to start your descent, but quickly get off the elevator before the doors close, you won&#39;t be open the doors back from the outside.  Essentially, you&#39;d be stuck in that warehouse room forever if you saved your game at this point.  Luckily, I had backup saves.

I know most people would never press &quot;e&quot; and then exit the elevator, but I was just messing around and found that you couldn&#39;t get back in.

Thanks.

P.S.  AMAZING job on this.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 17 Sep 2012 01:32:34 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>In-game Issues (Mod)</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/very-end-of-unforseen-consequences-elevator-issue-fixed/10449.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Very end of &quot;Unforseen Consequences&quot; Elevator Issue [Fixed]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[hybridmajik]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>The elevator you get on that takes you to the beginning of the “Office Complex” statue has a slight bug, in my opinion.  If you get on the elevator and press “e” to start your descent, but quickly get off the elevator before the doors close, you won’t be open the doors back from the outside.  Essentially, you’d be stuck in that warehouse room forever if you saved your game at this point.  Luckily, I had backup saves.</p>
<p>I know most people would never press “e” and then exit the elevator, but I was just messing around and found that you couldn’t get back in.</p>
<p>Thanks.</p>
<p>P.S.  AMAZING job on this.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/very-end-of-unforseen-consequences-elevator-issue-fixed/10449/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/very-end-of-unforseen-consequences-elevator-issue-fixed/10449/1</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 17 Sep 2012 01:32:34 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-10449-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/very-end-of-unforseen-consequences-elevator-issue-fixed/10449.rss">Very end of &quot;Unforseen Consequences&quot; Elevator Issue [Fixed]</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
