<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>ET:QW Modification: Tribal Wars Released</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/et-qw-modification-tribal-wars-released/3418</link>
    <description>[url]https://www.tribalwar.com/forums/showthread.php?t=558062[/url]
[quote]
The Modification for ETQW which brings in some of the classic elements of Starsiege: Tribes is now complete and available to the general public. The modification features Jetpacks, New Weapons, two new Maps, and a CTF Gametype.

This project has been in development for quite some time, and it&#39;s involved a lot of help from many individuals. They&#39;ve really put in a quality effort over the months of development, and their knowledge and talent has really made this mod possible. I&#39;d really like to thank everyone who was involved with the development of this project, I doubt I could have done it without you. I&#39;ve invested a good amount of my own time into this project and I&#39;ve really enjoyed some of the struggles and successes along the way. In the end though, I&#39;ve come away with a feeling of satisfaction and accomplishment. I hope that many of you enjoy playing the mod, as much as I did developing it.

There are many people from different communities that have expressed some interest in playing the mod, and even creating content for it. It&#39;s only fitting that there is a place to gather and share information about this unique project. We&#39;ve established a set of forums specifically for this mod where you can get all of the resources and support for Tribal Wars:

[url=&#39;https://twars.org/forums/&#39;]Tribal Wars Forums - Index page[/url]

Additionally we have an irc channel. You can find us on irc.quakenet.org, [url=&#39;https://webchat.quakenet.org/?nick=&amp;channels=twars&amp;prompt=1&#39;]#twars[/url]

Last but not least, a list of mirrors and locations you can download the mod from:

Windows Only Installers:

Mod-DB:
[url=https://www.moddb.com/mods/tribal-wars/downloads/tribal-wars-v10]Tribal Wars v1.0 download - Mod DB[/url]

Fileplanet:
[url=&#39;https://www.fileplanet.com/210636/210000/fileinfo/Tribal-Wars-Mod&#39;]FilePlanet: Tribal Wars Mod[/url]

Mega Upload:
[url=&#39;https://www.megaupload.com/?d=WMUJGRZ8&#39;]MEGAUPLOAD - The leading online storage and file delivery service[/url]
 
[/quote]</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 17 Mar 2010 04:44:08 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Technology and Gaming</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/et-qw-modification-tribal-wars-released/3418.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>ET:QW Modification: Tribal Wars Released</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[snob]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><a href="https://www.tribalwar.com/forums/showthread.php?t=558062" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://www.tribalwar.com/forums/showthread.php?t=558062</a></p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>The Modification for ETQW which brings in some of the classic elements of Starsiege: Tribes is now complete and available to the general public. The modification features Jetpacks, New Weapons, two new Maps, and a CTF Gametype.</p>
<p>This project has been in development for quite some time, and it’s involved a lot of help from many individuals. They’ve really put in a quality effort over the months of development, and their knowledge and talent has really made this mod possible. I’d really like to thank everyone who was involved with the development of this project, I doubt I could have done it without you. I’ve invested a good amount of my own time into this project and I’ve really enjoyed some of the struggles and successes along the way. In the end though, I’ve come away with a feeling of satisfaction and accomplishment. I hope that many of you enjoy playing the mod, as much as I did developing it.</p>
<p>There are many people from different communities that have expressed some interest in playing the mod, and even creating content for it. It’s only fitting that there is a place to gather and share information about this unique project. We’ve established a set of forums specifically for this mod where you can get all of the resources and support for Tribal Wars:</p>
<p><a href="https://twars.org/forums/" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Tribal Wars Forums - Index page</a></p>
<p>Additionally we have an irc channel. You can find us on <a href="http://irc.quakenet.org" rel="nofollow noopener">irc.quakenet.org</a>, <a href="https://webchat.quakenet.org/?nick=&amp;channels=twars&amp;prompt=1" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">#twars</a></p>
<p>Last but not least, a list of mirrors and locations you can download the mod from:</p>
<p>Windows Only Installers:</p>
<p>Mod-DB:<br>
<a href="https://www.moddb.com/mods/tribal-wars/downloads/tribal-wars-v10" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Tribal Wars v1.0 download - Mod DB</a></p>
<p>Fileplanet:<br>
<a href="https://www.fileplanet.com/210636/210000/fileinfo/Tribal-Wars-Mod" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">FilePlanet: Tribal Wars Mod</a></p>
<p>Mega Upload:<br>
<a href="https://www.megaupload.com/?d=WMUJGRZ8" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">MEGAUPLOAD - The leading online storage and file delivery service</a></p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/et-qw-modification-tribal-wars-released/3418/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/et-qw-modification-tribal-wars-released/3418/1</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 17 Mar 2010 04:44:08 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3418-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/et-qw-modification-tribal-wars-released/3418.rss">ET:QW Modification: Tribal Wars Released</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
