<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>How should the government do their job?</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/how-should-the-government-do-their-job/2497</link>
    <description>Let&#39;s tell them how to do their jobs.

What do you think the government should do? and how?

Conspiracy theories about the government being corrupt lazy fat-asses.

Propose a new form of government.

Current issues that you think you could solve if you were in charge.

This all needs to be pointlessly discussed. (In before uneducated opinions- oh wait  :frowning:  )</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 20 Aug 2011 18:31:28 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Off Topic</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/how-should-the-government-do-their-job/2497.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>How should the government do their job?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Guzzi]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Shit NecroPost… I’m gonna let it die.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/how-should-the-government-do-their-job/2497/28">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/how-should-the-government-do-their-job/2497/28</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 20 Aug 2011 18:31:28 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2497-28</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/how-should-the-government-do-their-job/2497.rss">How should the government do their job?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How should the government do their job?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Zuul]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Shadi">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/s/858c86/40.png" class="avatar"> Shadi:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>you’ve been “necrothreading” a lot recently…</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>ah shit man…I really need glasses.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/how-should-the-government-do-their-job/2497/27">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/how-should-the-government-do-their-job/2497/27</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 11 Aug 2011 09:30:06 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2497-27</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/how-should-the-government-do-their-job/2497.rss">How should the government do their job?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How should the government do their job?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Shadi]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>you’ve been “necrothreading” a lot recently…</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/how-should-the-government-do-their-job/2497/26">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/how-should-the-government-do-their-job/2497/26</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 08 Aug 2011 16:50:10 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2497-26</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/how-should-the-government-do-their-job/2497.rss">How should the government do their job?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How should the government do their job?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Zuul]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="PlausibleSarge">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/p/db5fbb/40.png" class="avatar"> PlausibleSarge:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>if a government is doing it’s job properly, you will never know its there (while living a normal life of course)</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>exactly…the swedish goverment had plans for nuclear bomb in the 50’s … and the general public hated the idea 'cause of “immediate destruction upon pressing the button”…so they scrapped that. The Finnish government however…they looked like it could be the hallmark of democracy, and all they did to protect the general population was to be ass-fucked by the russians. I’m a Finn. the finnish president Kekkonen invited russian highranking officials to his sauna…and practically made them sign treatis under the threat of 100+ degrees in the sauna, but the finnish ppl never heard of this …so because of this Finland is still “a free country” ehum…small lol…some shit is better to be not told or otherwise tha ppl will go apeshit</p>
<p>EDIT: sorry to revive a dead thread but democracy is important…even if it’s not all that I hoped for</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/how-should-the-government-do-their-job/2497/25">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/how-should-the-government-do-their-job/2497/25</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 06 Aug 2011 23:05:03 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2497-25</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/how-should-the-government-do-their-job/2497.rss">How should the government do their job?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How should the government do their job?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[PlausibleSarge]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>if a government is doing it’s job properly, you will never know its there (while living a normal life of course)</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/how-should-the-government-do-their-job/2497/24">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/how-should-the-government-do-their-job/2497/24</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jan 2010 00:54:41 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2497-24</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/how-should-the-government-do-their-job/2497.rss">How should the government do their job?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How should the government do their job?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[gwgmer]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="JohnKiller118">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 JohnKiller118:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>For example: I loved how, on the subject of health care reform, John McCain <span class="bbcode-i">(who is against the reform)</span> said he will <span class="bbcode-i">“fight for the American people”</span> along with a bunch of other lame patriot bullshit, yet a majority of Americans are for all for health care reform.<br>
<a href="https://www.gallup.com/poll/121664/majority-favors-healthcare-reform-this-year.aspx" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://www.gallup.com/poll/121664/majority-favors-healthcare-reform-this-year.aspx</a><br>
I can’t find a link to where McCain said that, but I heard it on a news channel while getting ready for school, and remember it fondly.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Few comments on this.<br>
First, the poll in question asked if Americans wanted reform this year, period. Not necessarily the reform bill in Congress at the time.<br>
This poll - by the same organization - may clarify what I’m saying: <a href="https://www.gallup.com/poll/121997/americans-healthcare-reform-top-takeaways.aspx" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://www.gallup.com/poll/121997/americans-healthcare-reform-top-takeaways.aspx</a><br>
It appears that most people want to change the health care system, but didn’t like the changes put forth in this particular bill. Not that it matters, because it passed anyways.</p>
<p>It also doesn’t matter, at least pertaining to McCain, however, because it’s not McCain’s job to fight “for the American people.” It’s McCain’s job to fight for the people of Arizona, his electorate. So, to determine what he should or shouldn’t have done, it would be better to find a poll on what Arizonans think. Considering Arizona is a fairly conservative state, I would guess that they’d be against the congressional bill. I can’t really be screwed to find a poll, but if you’d like to look, feel free.</p>
<p>If you want to talk about how the American republic is supposed to work, it’s worth looking into what the founders originally intended.</p>
<p>One of the things the founders most feared was the tyranny of the majority - that a group would take control of their government and reform it to their own ends. This is why they created a republic instead of a pure democracy: the idea being that while a pure democracy could fall to tyranny by creating a situation where someone could take control of the “unwashed masses” of the public and use it to overpower the government. They felt that a republic was better because the elected representatives - ideally, the best and brightest that the nation could produce - would resist such things. Well, that didn’t work out so well (see: political parties.)</p>
<p>The other thing they were really big on was trying to get things to move slowly when being passed into law - which makes sense. Better one thinks things through instead of heedlessly passing something that turns out to be garbage (see: stimulus.) The way they tried to do this was to create as much gridlock as possible in the congress by having people elected to represent, not the American people as a whole, but a set electorate. A senator was to represent only the people of his state, and a congressman (i.e. member of the House of Representatives) was to represent an even smaller area - his own district. In this way, they would be representing very diverse groups of people, and the idea was that - seeing as the interests the people of a state like Massachusettes would conflict greatly with the interests of the people of a state like South Carolina - it would take a very long time and much negotiation for the two to agree on anything. Thus a bill could only be passed after it was truly good and helped the people of both states.</p>
<p>As can be seen, the idea was not, as we see it today, to pass as much legislation as possible, as quickly as possible. It was to pass very LITTLE legislation, so as to ensure that the legislation was of good quality. If we MUST have government passing legislation, this is the way it ought to be.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/how-should-the-government-do-their-job/2497/23">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/how-should-the-government-do-their-job/2497/23</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Jan 2010 21:39:19 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2497-23</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/how-should-the-government-do-their-job/2497.rss">How should the government do their job?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How should the government do their job?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[mattemuse]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I don’t think it’s practical to have referendums on every subject. Representation works fine, if you can be sure your representatives aren’t voting the way their campaign financiers tell them to. That’s why the <span class="hashtag">#1</span> priority has to be campaign finance reform and lobby reform.</p>
<p>Everything else follows logically from not allowing industries to buy politicians. Forget the State owning industries, just make it impossible for industries to give politicians money or favors. Forget public control of media companies, just (through public financing of elections) ensure that all political candidates can buy the same amount of airtime.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/how-should-the-government-do-their-job/2497/22">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/how-should-the-government-do-their-job/2497/22</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Jan 2010 20:43:02 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2497-22</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/how-should-the-government-do-their-job/2497.rss">How should the government do their job?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How should the government do their job?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[DansonDelta40]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>A real democracy would have to give power to the people. That would mean letting the people decide over important decision like whether or not going to war, whether or not to change a certain law etc.</p>
<p>In other words, there ought to be public votes on every important subject that is likely to have a large impact on the general population.</p>
<p>For that to function there would have to be a huge raise in general education first, so that the population would have the ability to choose wisely.</p>
<p>Public representatives would have to be shielded from bribery and possible corruption. They should have to consult psychologists regularly and be under constant observation by differing public agencies to ensure they act in the best interest of the people, not of a certain lobby.</p>
<p>Instead of being dependent on sales, certain industries with a dangerous potential, such as weapon manufacturers and pharmacy companies, should be owned by the state and funded publicly, so that nobody gets stupid ideas like starting wars in foreign countries or poisoning people’s food to make them sick, just for the sake of boosted sales figures.</p>
<p>All media companies should be under public control constantly, making it impossible for mass media campaigns to significantly influence and manipulate the attitude of the population’s majority.</p>
<p>And many, maaaany more stuff would be necessary for a real democracy to actually work. Changes so radical that they will probably never occur.</p>
<p>And, as always, the disappearance of religion would massively help speeding up the whole process.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/how-should-the-government-do-their-job/2497/21">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/how-should-the-government-do-their-job/2497/21</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Jan 2010 20:30:53 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2497-21</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/how-should-the-government-do-their-job/2497.rss">How should the government do their job?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How should the government do their job?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[JohnKiller118]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="DansonDelta40">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/d/bbce88/40.png" class="avatar"> DansonDelta40:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Give every politician a soldier’s equipment and drill, bring them over to Iraq and Afghanistan and let them cover the retreat of your/our troops.</p>
<p>Wooozaa!</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Sempi-Fi, bitches!</p>
<p>Anyway, I think a Representative Democracy simply fails to do what it was designed to do: Have politicians represent the people.<br>
Politicians don’t look out for the people. They look out for their own agendas and whoever pays them well enough.</p>
<p>For example: I loved how, on the subject of health care reform, John McCain <span class="bbcode-i">(who is against the reform)</span> said he will <span class="bbcode-i">“fight for the American people”</span> along with a bunch of other lame patriot bullshit, yet a majority of Americans are for all for health care reform.<br>
<a href="https://www.gallup.com/poll/121664/majority-favors-healthcare-reform-this-year.aspx" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://www.gallup.com/poll/121664/majority-favors-healthcare-reform-this-year.aspx</a><br>
I can’t find a link to where McCain said that, but I heard it on a news channel while getting ready for school, and remember it fondly.</p>
<p>So, how SHOULD we run this country?<br>
Well, to be honest, I have no idea. I don’t think anyone really knows for sure. All I know is that it’s not working the way it is.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/how-should-the-government-do-their-job/2497/20">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/how-should-the-government-do-their-job/2497/20</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Jan 2010 20:06:26 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2497-20</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/how-should-the-government-do-their-job/2497.rss">How should the government do their job?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How should the government do their job?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Mr.Shadow]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>It was a joke.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/how-should-the-government-do-their-job/2497/19">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/how-should-the-government-do-their-job/2497/19</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Jan 2010 19:43:06 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2497-19</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/how-should-the-government-do-their-job/2497.rss">How should the government do their job?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How should the government do their job?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[mattemuse]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Why discuss constructive solutions when we can fantasize about wildly implausible violence? :facepalm:</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/how-should-the-government-do-their-job/2497/18">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/how-should-the-government-do-their-job/2497/18</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Jan 2010 19:40:45 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2497-18</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/how-should-the-government-do-their-job/2497.rss">How should the government do their job?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How should the government do their job?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Mr.Shadow]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>OR…just start a revolution.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/how-should-the-government-do-their-job/2497/17">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/how-should-the-government-do-their-job/2497/17</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Jan 2010 19:29:17 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2497-17</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/how-should-the-government-do-their-job/2497.rss">How should the government do their job?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How should the government do their job?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[mattemuse]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Mr.Shadow">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/m/43a26b/40.png" class="avatar"> Mr.Shadow:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Bring back the democracy. And I mean REAL democracy.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>The only way to do that is to get corporate influence (read: bribery) out of government.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/how-should-the-government-do-their-job/2497/16">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/how-should-the-government-do-their-job/2497/16</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Jan 2010 19:27:04 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2497-16</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/how-should-the-government-do-their-job/2497.rss">How should the government do their job?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How should the government do their job?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Mr.Shadow]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>First of all, get them to be killed. Second of all: Bring back the democracy. And I mean REAL democracy. Not some half-assed attempt to be a democracy, like we now have.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/how-should-the-government-do-their-job/2497/15">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/how-should-the-government-do-their-job/2497/15</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Jan 2010 19:06:40 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2497-15</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/how-should-the-government-do-their-job/2497.rss">How should the government do their job?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How should the government do their job?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[DansonDelta40]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Give every politician a soldier’s equipment and drill, bring them over to Iraq and Afghanistan and let them cover the retreat of your/our troops.</p>
<p>Wooozaa!</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/how-should-the-government-do-their-job/2497/14">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/how-should-the-government-do-their-job/2497/14</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jan 2010 22:50:10 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2497-14</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/how-should-the-government-do-their-job/2497.rss">How should the government do their job?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How should the government do their job?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Codgin]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>sounds like to much hardwork getting them to the top, why not get them in the lobby, and bring the building down on 'em</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/how-should-the-government-do-their-job/2497/13">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/how-should-the-government-do-their-job/2497/13</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jan 2010 21:32:17 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2497-13</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/how-should-the-government-do-their-job/2497.rss">How should the government do their job?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How should the government do their job?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Imonfire]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Garcian Smith">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Garcian Smith:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>You’ll need quite a few steps if they’re to reach the top of the building.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Or they could just take the elevator!</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/how-should-the-government-do-their-job/2497/12">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/how-should-the-government-do-their-job/2497/12</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jan 2010 20:27:33 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2497-12</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/how-should-the-government-do-their-job/2497.rss">How should the government do their job?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How should the government do their job?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[gwgmer]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>This question is flawed because it assumes that a government should “do” anything.</p>
<p>The only legitimate action of a government should be law enforcement and, by extension, national defense. Protect its citizens from breaches of strictly defined rights.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/how-should-the-government-do-their-job/2497/11">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/how-should-the-government-do-their-job/2497/11</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jan 2010 20:20:29 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2497-11</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/how-should-the-government-do-their-job/2497.rss">How should the government do their job?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How should the government do their job?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Garcian_Smith]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>You’ll need quite a few steps if they’re to reach the top of the building.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/how-should-the-government-do-their-job/2497/10">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/how-should-the-government-do-their-job/2497/10</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jan 2010 18:49:05 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2497-10</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/how-should-the-government-do-their-job/2497.rss">How should the government do their job?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How should the government do their job?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[brokenfridgehinge]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Firstly they can start by finding the closest tall building and jumping off it. There does not need to be a second step.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/how-should-the-government-do-their-job/2497/9">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/how-should-the-government-do-their-job/2497/9</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jan 2010 15:47:36 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2497-9</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/how-should-the-government-do-their-job/2497.rss">How should the government do their job?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How should the government do their job?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Alcator]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>“The best form of government is Enlightened Dictatorship. Sadly, we don’t have enough Enlightened Dictators available.”</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/how-should-the-government-do-their-job/2497/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/how-should-the-government-do-their-job/2497/8</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jan 2010 15:43:36 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2497-8</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/how-should-the-government-do-their-job/2497.rss">How should the government do their job?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How should the government do their job?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Codgin]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>while I’d agree money is a factor, I’d say it’s a small one, the iraq and afghastein war was simply a case of, if you hit a big dog with a stick  its going to turn round and bite “someone”. I do agree with the Goverment that Alqueda need to be crushed like the cockroaches they are, but how excatly do you fight an enemy, that isn’t a country, but a radical group spread all over the world?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/how-should-the-government-do-their-job/2497/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/how-should-the-government-do-their-job/2497/7</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jan 2010 10:49:49 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2497-7</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/how-should-the-government-do-their-job/2497.rss">How should the government do their job?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How should the government do their job?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[mga]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Of course we should get out of the Middle East because we shouldn’t have gone in the first place.</p>
<p>The war, in both Afghanistan and Iraq, is all about money.  Money from oil, from running Iraq, from the drug trade which we watch over in Afghanistan.</p>
<p>Our government is completely corrupt and I don’t see it changing unless it falls.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/how-should-the-government-do-their-job/2497/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/how-should-the-government-do-their-job/2497/6</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jan 2010 02:57:21 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2497-6</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/how-should-the-government-do-their-job/2497.rss">How should the government do their job?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How should the government do their job?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[mattemuse]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I have a whole list of things I’d like to see the American government do, but they all start with just one thing:</p>
<p>Exclusive public financing of all state and national elections. No more corporate financing of elections! Remove profit motive from government through stricter oversight and regulation of lobbies. Stricter oversight of conflict-of-interest in government. Regulating the ‘revolving door’ between government and lobbyists.</p>
<p>Removing profit motive from government is the only way to insure the people have a voice. Any other progressive goals are secondary and will never happen without the abolition of institutionalized greed in government.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/how-should-the-government-do-their-job/2497/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/how-should-the-government-do-their-job/2497/5</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jan 2010 02:53:08 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2497-5</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/how-should-the-government-do-their-job/2497.rss">How should the government do their job?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How should the government do their job?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Zerego]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>@ Thread: Properly.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/how-should-the-government-do-their-job/2497/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/how-should-the-government-do-their-job/2497/4</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jan 2010 01:17:16 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2497-4</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/how-should-the-government-do-their-job/2497.rss">How should the government do their job?</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
