<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>BM Creation Assistance</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/bm-creation-assistance/11525</link>
    <description>Hi guys. Since BM has been released I&#39;ve been throwing myself back into Hammer and various other tools to create custom content. However I&#39;ve not yet found a standard introduction to the new features and was hoping to get some guidance. I was hoping that people in the know would be able to answer some questions or point mew in the right direction if answers already exist. I might be posting a few of these (sorry) but I&#39;m addressing issues as they come up.

I apologise if this isn&#39;t in the right section, but it seemed the most appropriate.

1.) Is it possible to create another file in the scripts folder that does the same as the character_manifesto.txt file? I want to create new faces/face groups for npc but I&#39;m wary of altering the scripts that came with bm.

2.) In Hammer, is there any way to set which group the npcs choose from IN the manifesto document? say in a certain map I want all of the security guards to have vests, but don&#39;t want a specific named entity (like grd00_Door), how would I tell the engine which set to choose from?

3.) This one is kind of cheeky. As a hugely fan based and community driven mod, is there any indication that the source code will be released to encourage mod development where new npcs, entities or features could be included? I understand if it&#39;s a no, but there&#39;s always been this little part of me that liked the OpFor npcs and I would love to bring them in somehow.

Thanks in advance!</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 27 Oct 2012 17:28:14 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Black Mesa</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/bm-creation-assistance/11525.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>BM Creation Assistance</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[D3lta]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>For the 1st one I think you’re gonna need the Source code.<br>
For the second one I think you need to use choreography but I’m not sure.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/bm-creation-assistance/11525/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/bm-creation-assistance/11525/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 27 Oct 2012 17:28:14 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11525-2</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/bm-creation-assistance/11525.rss">BM Creation Assistance</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>BM Creation Assistance</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[mad.array]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Hi guys. Since BM has been released I’ve been throwing myself back into Hammer and various other tools to create custom content. However I’ve not yet found a standard introduction to the new features and was hoping to get some guidance. I was hoping that people in the know would be able to answer some questions or point mew in the right direction if answers already exist. I might be posting a few of these (sorry) but I’m addressing issues as they come up.</p>
<p>I apologise if this isn’t in the right section, but it seemed the most appropriate.</p>
<p>1.) Is it possible to create another file in the scripts folder that does the same as the character_manifesto.txt file? I want to create new faces/face groups for npc but I’m wary of altering the scripts that came with bm.</p>
<p>2.) In Hammer, is there any way to set which group the npcs choose from IN the manifesto document? say in a certain map I want all of the security guards to have vests, but don’t want a specific named entity (like grd00_Door), how would I tell the engine which set to choose from?</p>
<p>3.) This one is kind of cheeky. As a hugely fan based and community driven mod, is there any indication that the source code will be released to encourage mod development where new npcs, entities or features could be included? I understand if it’s a no, but there’s always been this little part of me that liked the OpFor npcs and I would love to bring them in somehow.</p>
<p>Thanks in advance!</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/bm-creation-assistance/11525/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/bm-creation-assistance/11525/1</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 19 Oct 2012 20:12:24 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11525-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/bm-creation-assistance/11525.rss">BM Creation Assistance</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
