<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>The Gerson Nonsense</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/the-gerson-nonsense/3102</link>
    <description>Responding to this:
[quote=&quot;Cup o Joe&quot;]
1. Here&#39;s information on the clinical trials done in the past 40 years:

[url]https://www.gerson.org/pdfs/Surviving%20Against%20All%20Odds.pdf[/url]
[/quote]
These are test aren&#39;t peer reviewed, if I&#39;m correct
[quote=&quot;Cup o Joe&quot;]
2. liver function being restored and fat being removed from the liver counts as a healthy procedure. (The only 2 Enema related deaths ever were because 1 patient overdosed the enema, and the other was allergic to caffeine)
[/quote]
What have enemas got to with the liver?
[quote=&quot;Cup o Joe&quot;]
3. The juice is from concentrate, and evidence shows that it pours out up to 8x more juice from leafy greens than centrifugal juicers, there&#39;s probably someone in your area that has a Norwalk, call Norwalk to ask who has one. Try a juice it&#39;s really good. 
[/quote]
Why does that matter? It&#39;s still juice. Why not keep the $4,000 and just drink eight times the amount of juice you usually do?
[quote=&quot;Cup o Joe&quot;]
4. Look again at the article about the research Dr. Eileen White from Rutger University who is the Associate Director for Basic Science, at The Cancer Institute of New Jersey, Professor in Molecular Biology and Biochemistry, at Rutgers University is doing about cell death, her research shows evidence that cancer is caused by a protein deficiency, resulting in acidity and a lack of Autophagy. 
[/quote]
What&#39;s that got to with Gerson&#39;s nonsense?
[quote=&quot;Cup o Joe&quot;]
What the Gerson Therapy does is it nourishes your body so much that the cancer cells cannot absorb what it needs to survive. Cancer is literally damaged cells, feeding off of the unused acidic nutrients in the blood.
[/quote]
That&#39;s just stupid. Not only is that stuff about &quot;acidic nutrients&quot; rubbish (it&#39;s just misunderstanding how proteins and such work), you&#39;re saying the cancer cells have so much nutrience that they absorb less nutrience.

Yeah, they&#39;re [i]damaged cells[/i], not waste as Gerson says. The only differences are that they don&#39;t have a function and when malign multiply profusely.
[quote=&quot;Cup o Joe&quot;]
Here&#39;s where the liver comes in, because the body is being fed correctly with an alkaline diet, the blood is completely filtered by the liver and the kidneys from the acids excreted by the healthy cells in your body which the cancer feeds on. The Liver is one of the most important filtration system in the body to keep in health.  cf. [url=&#39;https://www.britishlivertrust.org.uk/home/the-liver/summary-of-the-livers-functions.aspx&#39;]liver functions[/url] 
[/quote]
As I&#39;ve said, that acid stuff is just rubbish and based on nothing but what Gerson claims. Show me the evidence for it.
[quote=&quot;Cup o Joe&quot;]
If the body feeds itself properly with an alkaline diet and is well filtered by the liver, colon, and kidneys, the cancer cells cannot consume the acids it needs to survive since it needs an acidic environment to survive. so the cancer starts to literally eat ITSELF (autophagy), until there is nothing left to feed on and thus the DNA breaks apart so much that the cell dies. cf. [url=&#39;https://cancerres.aacrjournals.org/cgi/content/full/66/19/9349&#39;]Autophagy in Cancer paragraph 2 sentence 3.[/url]
[/quote]
That link just explains Autophagy, it doesn&#39;t mention needing an alkaline diet or anything of the sort.

Please stop posting links you haven&#39;t read/irrelevant links.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 23 Feb 2010 15:53:42 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Off Topic</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/the-gerson-nonsense/3102.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>The Gerson Nonsense</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[X_Mastershot_X]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>we are saved! Mga i hope you are reading this</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/the-gerson-nonsense/3102/16">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/the-gerson-nonsense/3102/16</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 23 Feb 2010 15:53:42 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3102-16</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/the-gerson-nonsense/3102.rss">The Gerson Nonsense</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The Gerson Nonsense</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[mattemuse]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>This is the real cure <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=OrU0EG0inuM&amp;feature=related" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=OrU0EG0inuM&amp;feature=related</a></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/the-gerson-nonsense/3102/15">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/the-gerson-nonsense/3102/15</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 22 Feb 2010 17:21:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3102-15</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/the-gerson-nonsense/3102.rss">The Gerson Nonsense</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The Gerson Nonsense</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[danielsangeo]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>What I meant was that it didn’t conclude what Cup o Joe tried to conclude:  That the study ITSELF was evidence of the success of the Gerson therapy.</p>
<p>What the study said is that it merited a full study.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/the-gerson-nonsense/3102/14">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/the-gerson-nonsense/3102/14</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 22 Feb 2010 17:11:58 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3102-14</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/the-gerson-nonsense/3102.rss">The Gerson Nonsense</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The Gerson Nonsense</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[mattemuse]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>The review you linked to doesn’t dispute their conclusion. It concluded that the results suggest that the Gerson method had enough merit to warrant a full study.</p>
<p>I’m not arguing either case, I’m just stating what your link says.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/the-gerson-nonsense/3102/13">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/the-gerson-nonsense/3102/13</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 22 Feb 2010 17:09:38 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3102-13</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/the-gerson-nonsense/3102.rss">The Gerson Nonsense</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The Gerson Nonsense</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[danielsangeo]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I’m not sure it was, though.  It was simply a study released.  The study, upon peer-review, did not conclude what Cup o Joe (and Gerson) tried to conclude.</p>
<p>I do not dispute that the study was done (and a paper released about it).  The do dispute, however, the conclusion, and peer-review backs that up.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/the-gerson-nonsense/3102/12">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/the-gerson-nonsense/3102/12</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 22 Feb 2010 17:05:53 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3102-12</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/the-gerson-nonsense/3102.rss">The Gerson Nonsense</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The Gerson Nonsense</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[mattemuse]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>The point was that it had been peer reviewed, I think. Not that it was the sole proof.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/the-gerson-nonsense/3102/11">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/the-gerson-nonsense/3102/11</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 22 Feb 2010 17:02:17 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3102-11</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/the-gerson-nonsense/3102.rss">The Gerson Nonsense</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The Gerson Nonsense</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[danielsangeo]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Soup">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/s/977dab/40.png" class="avatar"> Soup:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I’ll read these later, right now I have an essay to do for Uni.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>No need.   The paper referenced was a non-randomized study with too small a sample size.</p>
<p><a href="https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pubmed/8795907" data-bbcode="true">https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pubmed/8795907</a></p>
<p>Summary, according to the <a href="https://www.cancer.gov/cancertopics/pdq/cam/gerson/HealthProfessional/page6" data-bbcode="true">National Cancer Institute</a>:<br>
[i]"The study looked at records of 153 patients with stage I–IV melanoma treated with the Gerson diet. Of the 14 stage I–II patients, all were disease-free at 17 years posttreatment; however, this number was too small for a statistical comparison with other cohorts. For stage III patients, the 5-year survival rate was 71% compared with rates of 27% to 42% reported in the literature. The stage IV patients had the largest survival advantage. The 5-year survival rate for these 18 patients was 39%, compared with 6% in the published literature. The analysis did not include 53 patients who were lost to follow-up, which could have influenced the survival comparisons.</p>
<p>A small best-case series suggests that the evidence presented supports the development and conduct of a more definite clinical study on the Gerson regimen.</p>
<p>No conclusions about the effectiveness of the Gerson therapy, either as an adjuvant to other cancer therapies or as a cure, can be drawn from any of the studies reported above."[/i]</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/the-gerson-nonsense/3102/10">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/the-gerson-nonsense/3102/10</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 22 Feb 2010 16:04:34 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3102-10</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/the-gerson-nonsense/3102.rss">The Gerson Nonsense</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The Gerson Nonsense</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[X_Mastershot_X]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>oh god</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/the-gerson-nonsense/3102/9">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/the-gerson-nonsense/3102/9</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 22 Feb 2010 15:49:03 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3102-9</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/the-gerson-nonsense/3102.rss">The Gerson Nonsense</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The Gerson Nonsense</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[mattemuse]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>redacted</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/the-gerson-nonsense/3102/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/the-gerson-nonsense/3102/8</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 22 Feb 2010 15:41:03 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3102-8</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/the-gerson-nonsense/3102.rss">The Gerson Nonsense</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The Gerson Nonsense</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[hercule_poirots_nuts]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>this thread rules</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/the-gerson-nonsense/3102/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/the-gerson-nonsense/3102/7</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 22 Feb 2010 09:38:05 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3102-7</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/the-gerson-nonsense/3102.rss">The Gerson Nonsense</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The Gerson Nonsense</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Soup]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Cup o Joe">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Cup o Joe:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>It is peer reviewed, <a href="https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pubmed/9359807" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pubmed/9359807</a></p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I’ll read these later, right now I have an essay to do for Uni.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Cup o Joe">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Cup o Joe:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>The coffee (which is filtered and a body temperature) goes into the liver opening the bile ducts to get the liver to excrete the bile accumulated.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Adding ingredients to enemas is not proven to do anything superior to the effects of plain saline enemas. Hot liquid in the rectum can result in serious burns. It’s not proven to remove cancer causing toxins.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Cup o Joe">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Cup o Joe:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Because having something less would actually cost more in groceries, to make the 13 pints of juice, the patients use about 20 pounds of fruits and vegetables in total every day. If it were a centrifugal juicer, instead of pressure, it would be about 3 to 5 times more expensive for groceries.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Uh, no it wouldn’t. It would be the same amount of groceries either way, just one would be more concentrated. The only difference would be that there’d be more water in the regular pressed squash.</p>
<p>Also, it’s a bad idea to drink that much squash anyway. Regularly consuming large amounts of citric acid will harm the stomach.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Cup o Joe">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Cup o Joe:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>It is an acidity problem in the cell, the gerson therapy balances all the cells in the body, the cancer, because it’s damaged can’t completely heal and wants acidic nutrients, but because the blood becomes more alkaline through the therapy, the cancer starves.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I told you before that that’s rubbish. Cancer is caused by many, many different things, from radiation to heat damage.</p>
<p>The acids it needs are the same ones normal cells need, i.e. amino acids, fatty acids and the like. Making your blood more alkaline isn’t going to do much.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Cup o Joe">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Cup o Joe:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>My grammar was wrong there. What I was saying is that the blood has the nutrients the body needs in alkaline form. Some of the Cancer takes it in and heals. Other parts of the Cancer cannot absorb it and go into autophagy, causing the cell to die after some time.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>What? That’s nonsense. Why would only <span class="bbcode-i">some</span> of the cancer absorb it? Blood goes everywhere in the body, you know and unless those cells are utterly dead, they will absorb nutrients.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Cup o Joe">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Cup o Joe:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>It is waste because it is damaged, there is acidic waste inside the cell that damaged it.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>As I’ve said, there are many causes for cancer.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Cup o Joe">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Cup o Joe:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>WRONG, Dr. Otto Warburg was awarded the Nobel Prize in 1931 for the discovery that, unlike healthy cells in the human body, cancer cells do not “breathe” oxygen and excretes sodium salts rather than potassium salts, sodium salts being more what again? oh ACIDIC!<br>
cf. <a href="https://www.canceractive.com/cancer-active-page-link.aspx?n=1025" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Acidic bodies</a></p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>That’s what normal cells do when they don’t use oxygen. Your point being?</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Cup o Joe">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Cup o Joe:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>If you would have read the sentence you would see that the cancerous cell feeds on acidic protein and fat.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>So do normal cells.</p>
<p>Also, please respond to <a href="https://forums.blackmesasource.com/showpost.php?p=154698&amp;postcount=165" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">this</a> (obviously in this thread).</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Bolteh">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/b/ecae2f/40.png" class="avatar"> Bolteh:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>And in comes Soup with the thinly veiled “uh ur stupit” replies.</p>
<p>I admire your debating skills.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I would say they aren’t veiled at all, but thanks anyway.</p>
<p>Also, insulting =/= debating.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/the-gerson-nonsense/3102/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/the-gerson-nonsense/3102/6</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 21 Feb 2010 12:36:04 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3102-6</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/the-gerson-nonsense/3102.rss">The Gerson Nonsense</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The Gerson Nonsense</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Cup_o_Joe]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Soup">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/s/977dab/40.png" class="avatar"> Soup:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>These are test aren’t peer reviewed, if I’m correct</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>It is peer reviewed, <a href="https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pubmed/9359807" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pubmed/9359807</a></p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>What have enemas got to with the liver?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>The coffee (which is filtered and a body temperature) goes into the liver opening the bile ducts to get the liver to excrete the bile accumulated.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>Why does that matter? It’s still juice. Why not keep the $4,000 and just drink eight times the amount of juice you usually do?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Because having something less would actually cost more in groceries, to make the 13 pints of juice, the patients use about 20 pounds of fruits and vegetables in total every day. If it were a centrifugal juicer, instead of pressure, it would be about 3 to 5 times more expensive for groceries.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>What’s that got to with Gerson’s nonsense?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>It is an acidity problem in the cell, the gerson therapy balances all the cells in the body, the cancer, because it’s damaged can’t completely heal and wants acidic nutrients, but because the blood becomes more alkaline through the therapy, the cancer starves.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>That’s just stupid. Not only is that stuff about “acidic nutrients” rubbish (it’s just misunderstanding how proteins and such work), you’re saying the cancer cells have so much nutrients that they absorb less nutrients.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>My grammar was wrong there. What I was saying is that the blood has the nutrients the body needs in alkaline form. Some of the Cancer takes it in and heals. Other parts of the Cancer cannot absorb it and go into autophagy, causing the cell to die after some time.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>Yeah, they’re <span class="bbcode-i">damaged cells</span>, not waste as Gerson says. The only differences are that they don’t have a function and when malign multiply profusely.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>It is waste because it is damaged, there is acidic waste inside the cell that damaged it.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>As I’ve said, that acid stuff is just rubbish and based on nothing but what Gerson claims. Show me the evidence for it.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>WRONG, Dr. Otto Warburg was awarded the Nobel Prize in 1931 for the discovery that, unlike healthy cells in the human body, cancer cells do not “breathe” oxygen and excretes sodium salts rather than potassium salts, sodium salts being more what again? oh ACIDIC!<br>
cf. <a href="https://www.canceractive.com/cancer-active-page-link.aspx?n=1025" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Acidic bodies</a></p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>That link just explains Autophagy, it doesn’t mention needing an alkaline diet or anything of the sort.</p>
<p>Please stop posting links you haven’t read/irrelevant links.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>If you would have read the sentence you would see that the cancerous cell feeds on acidic protein and fat.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/the-gerson-nonsense/3102/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/the-gerson-nonsense/3102/5</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 20 Feb 2010 23:57:03 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3102-5</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/the-gerson-nonsense/3102.rss">The Gerson Nonsense</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The Gerson Nonsense</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Bolteh]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>And in comes Soup with the thinly veiled “uh ur stupit” replies.</p>
<p>I admire your debating skills.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/the-gerson-nonsense/3102/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/the-gerson-nonsense/3102/4</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 20 Feb 2010 23:37:59 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3102-4</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/the-gerson-nonsense/3102.rss">The Gerson Nonsense</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The Gerson Nonsense</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Soup]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Uh, that’s what I responded to in this thread. Didn’t you read my post?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/the-gerson-nonsense/3102/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/the-gerson-nonsense/3102/3</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 20 Feb 2010 22:59:11 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3102-3</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/the-gerson-nonsense/3102.rss">The Gerson Nonsense</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The Gerson Nonsense</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Cup_o_Joe]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Soup">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/s/977dab/40.png" class="avatar"> Soup:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Respond to <a href="https://forums.blackmesasource.com/showpost.php?p=121176&amp;postcount=400" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">this</a>.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<ol>
<li>Here’s information on the clinical trials done in the past 40 years:</li>
</ol>
<p><a href="https://www.gerson.org/pdfs/Surviving%20Against%20All%20Odds.pdf" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://www.gerson.org/pdfs/Surviving%20Against%20All%20Odds.pdf</a></p>
<ol start="2">
<li>
<p>liver function being restored and fat being removed from the liver counts as a healthy procedure. (The only 2 Enema related deaths ever were because 1 patient overdosed the enema, and the other was allergic to caffeine)</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>The juice is from concentrate, and evidence shows that it pours out up to 8x more juice from leafy greens than centrifugal juicers, there’s probably someone in your area that has a Norwalk, call Norwalk to ask who has one. Try a juice it’s really good. cf. <a href="https://www.nwjcal.com/comparison.htm" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Norwalk Juicer California</a></p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Look again at the article about the research Dr. Eileen White from Rutger University who is the Associate Director for Basic Science, at The Cancer Institute of New Jersey, Professor in Molecular Biology and Biochemistry, at Rutgers University is doing about cell death, her research shows evidence that cancer is caused by a protein deficiency, resulting in acidity and a lack of Autophagy. cf1. <a href="https://www.scienceblog.com/cms/waste-disposal-protein-mechanism-behind-cancer-tumor-suppression-22143.html" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">waste disposal</a> cf2. <a href="https://lifesci.rutgers.edu/~molbiosci/faculty/white.html" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Eileen White</a></p>
</li>
</ol>
<p>What the Gerson Therapy does is it nourishes your body so much that the cancer cells cannot absorb what it needs to survive. Cancer is literally damaged cells, feeding off of the unused acidic nutrients in the blood. cf <a href="https://www.cancer.gov/dictionary/?CdrID=45333" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">definition of cancer</a></p>
<p>Here’s where the liver comes in, because the body is being fed correctly with an alkaline diet, the blood is completely filtered by the liver and the kidneys from the acids excreted by the healthy cells in your body which the cancer feeds on. The Liver is one of the most important filtration system in the body to keep in health.  cf. <a href="https://www.britishlivertrust.org.uk/home/the-liver/summary-of-the-livers-functions.aspx" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">liver functions</a></p>
<p>If the body feeds itself properly with an alkaline diet and is well filtered by the liver, colon, and kidneys, the cancer cells cannot consume the acids it needs to survive since it needs an acidic environment to survive cf. <a href="https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pubmed/6522424?dopt=Abstract" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">national library of medicine</a>. so the cancer starts to literally eat ITSELF (autophagy), until there is nothing left to feed on and thus the DNA breaks apart so much that the cell dies. cf. <a href="https://cancerres.aacrjournals.org/cgi/content/full/66/19/9349" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Autophagy in Cancer paragraph 2 sentence 3.</a></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/the-gerson-nonsense/3102/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/the-gerson-nonsense/3102/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 20 Feb 2010 22:37:28 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3102-2</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/the-gerson-nonsense/3102.rss">The Gerson Nonsense</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The Gerson Nonsense</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Soup]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Responding to this:</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Cup o Joe">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Cup o Joe:</div>
<blockquote>
<ol>
<li>Here’s information on the clinical trials done in the past 40 years:</li>
</ol>
<p><a href="https://www.gerson.org/pdfs/Surviving%20Against%20All%20Odds.pdf" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://www.gerson.org/pdfs/Surviving%20Against%20All%20Odds.pdf</a></p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>These are test aren’t peer reviewed, if I’m correct</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Cup o Joe">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Cup o Joe:</div>
<blockquote>
<ol start="2">
<li>liver function being restored and fat being removed from the liver counts as a healthy procedure. (The only 2 Enema related deaths ever were because 1 patient overdosed the enema, and the other was allergic to caffeine)</li>
</ol>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>What have enemas got to with the liver?</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Cup o Joe">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Cup o Joe:</div>
<blockquote>
<ol start="3">
<li>The juice is from concentrate, and evidence shows that it pours out up to 8x more juice from leafy greens than centrifugal juicers, there’s probably someone in your area that has a Norwalk, call Norwalk to ask who has one. Try a juice it’s really good.</li>
</ol>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Why does that matter? It’s still juice. Why not keep the $4,000 and just drink eight times the amount of juice you usually do?</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Cup o Joe">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Cup o Joe:</div>
<blockquote>
<ol start="4">
<li>Look again at the article about the research Dr. Eileen White from Rutger University who is the Associate Director for Basic Science, at The Cancer Institute of New Jersey, Professor in Molecular Biology and Biochemistry, at Rutgers University is doing about cell death, her research shows evidence that cancer is caused by a protein deficiency, resulting in acidity and a lack of Autophagy.</li>
</ol>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>What’s that got to with Gerson’s nonsense?</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Cup o Joe">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Cup o Joe:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>What the Gerson Therapy does is it nourishes your body so much that the cancer cells cannot absorb what it needs to survive. Cancer is literally damaged cells, feeding off of the unused acidic nutrients in the blood.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>That’s just stupid. Not only is that stuff about “acidic nutrients” rubbish (it’s just misunderstanding how proteins and such work), you’re saying the cancer cells have so much nutrience that they absorb less nutrience.</p>
<p>Yeah, they’re <span class="bbcode-i">damaged cells</span>, not waste as Gerson says. The only differences are that they don’t have a function and when malign multiply profusely.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Cup o Joe">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Cup o Joe:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Here’s where the liver comes in, because the body is being fed correctly with an alkaline diet, the blood is completely filtered by the liver and the kidneys from the acids excreted by the healthy cells in your body which the cancer feeds on. The Liver is one of the most important filtration system in the body to keep in health.  cf. <a href="https://www.britishlivertrust.org.uk/home/the-liver/summary-of-the-livers-functions.aspx" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">liver functions</a></p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>As I’ve said, that acid stuff is just rubbish and based on nothing but what Gerson claims. Show me the evidence for it.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Cup o Joe">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Cup o Joe:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>If the body feeds itself properly with an alkaline diet and is well filtered by the liver, colon, and kidneys, the cancer cells cannot consume the acids it needs to survive since it needs an acidic environment to survive. so the cancer starts to literally eat ITSELF (autophagy), until there is nothing left to feed on and thus the DNA breaks apart so much that the cell dies. cf. <a href="https://cancerres.aacrjournals.org/cgi/content/full/66/19/9349" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Autophagy in Cancer paragraph 2 sentence 3.</a></p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>That link just explains Autophagy, it doesn’t mention needing an alkaline diet or anything of the sort.</p>
<p>Please stop posting links you haven’t read/irrelevant links.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/the-gerson-nonsense/3102/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/the-gerson-nonsense/3102/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 20 Feb 2010 22:31:11 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3102-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/the-gerson-nonsense/3102.rss">The Gerson Nonsense</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
