<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Couple bugs, that occurs everytime</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/couple-bugs-that-occurs-everytime/11892</link>
    <description>I&#39;ve played the game though couple times and found couple bugs:


1. -When riding a train, player slowly moves behind in the corners and uphills, and sometimes you lose the control of the train.

2. -When encountering the helicopter second time, it takes sometimes a great amount of rockets to be destroyed and it&#39;s incredibly hard, even on easy difficult and one time I did shoot over 20 rockets to it and it didn&#39;t destruct (maybe a bug itself ?). And when you are positioning yourself behind the rocks on the left, in the cave, where you find the rocket launcher, when the helicopter is in your sight, shoot a rocket and it stucks horizonally in front of you. (EDIT: You are able to destroy it, if you&#39;re outside of the cave, when I was in the cave and shooting from there, it didn&#39;t blow up. Still, it did take up to 9 rockets up to blow.)

3. In the area, where are those sticky mines in fields, where is the hatch, behind the hatch is a problem. If you go there, where seems to be just brown rock, you will drop inside of it and it&#39;s hard to get out of there.


And I&#39;m sure, that the list will continue...



...but don&#39;t worry, it&#39;s still a amazing game.  :stuck_out_tongue:</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 07 Jan 2013 19:33:35 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>In-game Issues (Mod)</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/couple-bugs-that-occurs-everytime/11892.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Couple bugs, that occurs everytime</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Dirrrrty_Harry]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Bug number four:</p>
<p>After the ‘‘laserbomb-labyrinth’’, when you get down with the elevator and go to the tunnel, where is couple military trucks and the security guard runs and yells help, do not go near to the truck at right, between it and the platform in front of you is a triangle-shaped hole. If you drop there, can’t jump up, you’ll be stuck at there.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/couple-bugs-that-occurs-everytime/11892/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/couple-bugs-that-occurs-everytime/11892/4</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 07 Jan 2013 19:33:35 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11892-4</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/couple-bugs-that-occurs-everytime/11892.rss">Couple bugs, that occurs everytime</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Couple bugs, that occurs everytime</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Dirrrrty_Harry]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Yea I’ve been doing in that way and the rockets hit the helicopter, but still it’s sometimes difficult. But restarting the game will sometimes solve the problem, sometimes not.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/couple-bugs-that-occurs-everytime/11892/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/couple-bugs-that-occurs-everytime/11892/3</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Dec 2012 15:44:47 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11892-3</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/couple-bugs-that-occurs-everytime/11892.rss">Couple bugs, that occurs everytime</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Couple bugs, that occurs everytime</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Cheerios]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Are you sure you are actually hitting the helicopter? It can be deceiving at first due to the helicopter shooting down your rockets before they hit it. The lesson in this is to learn to shoot to the side, the guide the missile into the helicopter.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/couple-bugs-that-occurs-everytime/11892/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/couple-bugs-that-occurs-everytime/11892/2</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 26 Dec 2012 15:29:27 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11892-2</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/couple-bugs-that-occurs-everytime/11892.rss">Couple bugs, that occurs everytime</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Couple bugs, that occurs everytime</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Dirrrrty_Harry]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I’ve played the game though couple times and found couple bugs:</p>
<ol>
<li>
<p>-When riding a train, player slowly moves behind in the corners and uphills, and sometimes you lose the control of the train.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>-When encountering the helicopter second time, it takes sometimes a great amount of rockets to be destroyed and it’s incredibly hard, even on easy difficult and one time I did shoot over 20 rockets to it and it didn’t destruct (maybe a bug itself ?). And when you are positioning yourself behind the rocks on the left, in the cave, where you find the rocket launcher, when the helicopter is in your sight, shoot a rocket and it stucks horizonally in front of you. (EDIT: You are able to destroy it, if you’re outside of the cave, when I was in the cave and shooting from there, it didn’t blow up. Still, it did take up to 9 rockets up to blow.)</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>In the area, where are those sticky mines in fields, where is the hatch, behind the hatch is a problem. If you go there, where seems to be just brown rock, you will drop inside of it and it’s hard to get out of there.</p>
</li>
</ol>
<p>And I’m sure, that the list will continue…</p>
<p>…but don’t worry, it’s still a amazing game.  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=9" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/couple-bugs-that-occurs-everytime/11892/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/couple-bugs-that-occurs-everytime/11892/1</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 24 Dec 2012 00:14:36 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11892-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/couple-bugs-that-occurs-everytime/11892.rss">Couple bugs, that occurs everytime</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
