<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Glock Not Ejecting Shells/Getting Weapon_assassin_glock</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/glock-not-ejecting-shells-getting-weapon-assassin-glock/14525</link>
    <description>I&#39;m sure this isn&#39;t an important issue, since it only seems to occur when using cheats, but sometimes the glock will straight up not eject shells.
I [i]think[/i] I&#39;ve tracked down the issue to Impulse 101 also giving the player a weapon_assassin_glock, which takes up the same inventory slot as the weapon_glock and seems to be missing a shell definition entry, judging by the error message.
This could also potentially become a balance issue (again, not a high priority one due to it&#39;s necessity on cheats to occur, but may be a small issue for people working on adjusting the balance of their own singleplayer maps) depending on what the cvars for the assassin&#39;s glock damage are set to.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 24 Dec 2015 00:35:41 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>In-game Issues</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/glock-not-ejecting-shells-getting-weapon-assassin-glock/14525.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Glock Not Ejecting Shells/Getting Weapon_assassin_glock</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[JeffMOD]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I’m sure this isn’t an important issue, since it only seems to occur when using cheats, but sometimes the glock will straight up not eject shells.<br>
I <span class="bbcode-i">think</span> I’ve tracked down the issue to Impulse 101 also giving the player a weapon_assassin_glock, which takes up the same inventory slot as the weapon_glock and seems to be missing a shell definition entry, judging by the error message.<br>
This could also potentially become a balance issue (again, not a high priority one due to it’s necessity on cheats to occur, but may be a small issue for people working on adjusting the balance of their own singleplayer maps) depending on what the cvars for the assassin’s glock damage are set to.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/glock-not-ejecting-shells-getting-weapon-assassin-glock/14525/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/glock-not-ejecting-shells-getting-weapon-assassin-glock/14525/1</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 24 Dec 2015 00:35:41 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14525-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/glock-not-ejecting-shells-getting-weapon-assassin-glock/14525.rss">Glock Not Ejecting Shells/Getting Weapon_assassin_glock</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
