<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Water placement issue</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/water-placement-issue/596</link>
    <description>I&#39;ve read that when using expensive water on different heights the water brushes are not allowed see each other. But I need some additional information. (I&#39;ve tried to search for the information and failed :[)

My problem is this:
I have a swimming pool with a hole in bottom and a pipe that runs underneath the pool. The player can dive from the pool straight down to the pipe.

Is it enough if the water surfaces don&#39;t see each other? That way I could have water in the pipe with the surface touching the ceiling and one tall water brush where the hole is to connect the pipe to the pool.

PS. My graphics card bit the dust and I&#39;m using a older one so the water reverts back to cheap water hence I can&#39;t really test it myself.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 16 Jun 2009 15:01:30 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Help and Support</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/water-placement-issue/596.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Water placement issue</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Angdraug]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Thanks. I couldn’t think outside the box enough to use different kind of water in the same water volume.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/water-placement-issue/596/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/water-placement-issue/596/3</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jun 2009 15:01:30 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-596-3</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/water-placement-issue/596.rss">Water placement issue</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Water placement issue</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Solokiller]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Expensive water is different from cheap water in its shaders, which is what you see up top as the reflection and refraction. If you want to have water go down a pipe, use a nodraw brush tied to func_water_analog, it’ll behave just like the water in the pool. If you use a water texture, it could create a weird, second layer of water in the pipe.</p>
<p>The different heights only matter with water that has expensive shaders on top, and another expensive water brush with a different height in the same rendered area.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/water-placement-issue/596/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/water-placement-issue/596/2</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jun 2009 13:21:27 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-596-2</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/water-placement-issue/596.rss">Water placement issue</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Water placement issue</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Angdraug]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I’ve read that when using expensive water on different heights the water brushes are not allowed see each other. But I need some additional information. (I’ve tried to search for the information and failed :[)</p>
<p>My problem is this:<br>
I have a swimming pool with a hole in bottom and a pipe that runs underneath the pool. The player can dive from the pool straight down to the pipe.</p>
<p>Is it enough if the water surfaces don’t see each other? That way I could have water in the pipe with the surface touching the ceiling and one tall water brush where the hole is to connect the pipe to the pool.</p>
<p>PS. My graphics card bit the dust and I’m using a older one so the water reverts back to cheap water hence I can’t really test it myself.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/water-placement-issue/596/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/water-placement-issue/596/1</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jun 2009 09:20:49 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-596-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/water-placement-issue/596.rss">Water placement issue</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
