<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Hammering away again...</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/hammering-away-again/2674</link>
    <description>Been playing around with hammer again...  This time with HL2.  I found an old write-up monologue that seemed like it would provide good back story for a mod set in the HL Universe.

I&#39;ve only been playing with the first map for a few days...  A train ride.  Here&#39;s some pics I just took.  Sorry for the high file sizes, I didn&#39;t compress them!

[img]https://img6.imageshack.us/img6/6579/hl22010011702051412.png[/img]
[img]https://img16.imageshack.us/img16/2996/hl22010011719234128.png[/img]
[img]https://img6.imageshack.us/img6/3407/hl22010011801400030.png[/img]
[img]https://img12.imageshack.us/img12/7535/hl22010011801391075.png[/img]

The first two shots are older (about 1 hammer-hour), and the water has been changed, and attention paid to empty spots in the background.


Um, yeah.  Lots of trees.  Besides being a bit bland, how does it look?  Also, the train doesn&#39;t have wheels because the player would be IN the train.  That last shot is just because it looked cool.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 19 Mar 2010 17:39:28 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Technology and Gaming</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/hammering-away-again/2674.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Hammering away again...</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Madcat1030]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Regarding fast VIS, I wasn’t saying that it would do for final version, I meant that it went through and worked without crashing.  I understand that my final version shouldn’t need it.</p>
<p>And thanks for the info about the giant props.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/hammering-away-again/2674/34">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/hammering-away-again/2674/34</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 19 Mar 2010 17:39:28 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2674-34</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/hammering-away-again/2674.rss">Hammering away again...</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Hammering away again...</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Omega_Absolute]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Madcat1030">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/m/9f8e36/40.png" class="avatar"> Madcat1030:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I’m just going to touch it up a bit (remove overhanging world-boxes (I don’t know if that’s a real term, but I’m using it to describe the box that contains the world.  Maybe I’ll find something…  I just don’t know why I’m getting leak-type in-game issues without any compile errors.  If I run them on fast, like I said, it all works well, and… and…  Hm…</p>
<p>I have giant props (cliffs), with giant boxes (the yellow representations if you move too far away) that go REAL high.  I automatically assumed that that meant the entire box had to be in the world.  Is that true?</p>
<p>I might take you up on your offer if I can’t get it fixed today.</p>
<p>Things are going to go soooo much better once I finish this map.  City level = less displacements.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Yea the boxes <span class="bbcode-i">generally</span> have to be in the world. Just lemme know what you want to do.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/hammering-away-again/2674/33">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/hammering-away-again/2674/33</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 19 Mar 2010 07:39:58 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2674-33</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/hammering-away-again/2674.rss">Hammering away again...</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Hammering away again...</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Madcat1030]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I’m just going to touch it up a bit (remove overhanging world-boxes (I don’t know if that’s a real term, but I’m using it to describe the box that contains the world.  Maybe I’ll find something…  I just don’t know why I’m getting leak-type in-game issues without any compile errors.  If I run them on fast, like I said, it all works well, and… and…  Hm…</p>
<p>I have giant props (cliffs), with giant boxes (the yellow representations if you move too far away) that go REAL high.  I automatically assumed that that meant the entire box had to be in the world.  Is that true?</p>
<p>I might take you up on your offer if I can’t get it fixed today.</p>
<p>Things are going to go soooo much better once I finish this map.  City level = less displacements.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/hammering-away-again/2674/32">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/hammering-away-again/2674/32</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 18 Mar 2010 12:52:44 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2674-32</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/hammering-away-again/2674.rss">Hammering away again...</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Hammering away again...</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Omega_Absolute]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Seems like your having quite a few problems and it’d be best to get them fixed before continuing. If you want, send me a pm and the vmf and I could take a look at it. I’ve been working with hammer (and worldcraft) since HL1 and have quite a bit of experience.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/hammering-away-again/2674/31">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/hammering-away-again/2674/31</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 18 Mar 2010 10:23:36 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2674-31</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/hammering-away-again/2674.rss">Hammering away again...</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Hammering away again...</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Madcat1030]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I don’t know what’s going on now.  I fast VIS and RAD’d it just to get it running, and…</p>
<p>Compiled correctly, all space outside the map should be “solid”, right?  As in, turn off noclip and you are stuck where you stand?  Because that’s not happening.  I’m not getting any leak errors, but the space is infinite…</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/hammering-away-again/2674/30">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/hammering-away-again/2674/30</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 17 Mar 2010 20:39:43 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2674-30</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/hammering-away-again/2674.rss">Hammering away again...</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Hammering away again...</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Ibanez]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>holy shit mediaz :3</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/hammering-away-again/2674/29">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/hammering-away-again/2674/29</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 17 Mar 2010 18:15:47 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2674-29</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/hammering-away-again/2674.rss">Hammering away again...</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Hammering away again...</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Madcat1030]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>So, in that first picture, all of the visible walls (in the outside and inside of the circular hallway) are details?</p>
<p>…That might help, considering I have an angle heavy area…  Very similar, in fact, to the area you just showed.  Thanks, I’mma work on that.  I’ve always had trouble with VVIS optimization…</p>
<p>By the way, fast VVIS works fine, with no visual or performance difference, and the water works.  I think the lack of performance drop might just be my computer, it’s pretty high end, so I miss alot of performance bugs that some other people get due to large/undefined vis-areas.</p>
<p>Was thinking:  Perhaps this would better fit in the Help and Support section?  If it’s fine here, leave it, though.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/hammering-away-again/2674/28">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/hammering-away-again/2674/28</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 17 Mar 2010 14:09:51 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2674-28</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/hammering-away-again/2674.rss">Hammering away again...</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Hammering away again...</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Madcat1030]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><span alt="" class="broken-image" title="This image is broken"><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-unlink svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#unlink"></use></svg></span><br>
Conceptual test.  For some reason, prior to this, I could never get dynamic lights to work properly.  I’ll probably go through and actually light the interior of the tram now…  In its static form, now that it actually lights stuff up as it goes by, it doesn’t have to be pitch black inside!  yay.</p>
<p>Also, I’ve run into a problem, a new problem:  VVIS is failing again…  not failing, but not finishing.  From within skyboxes, I can see some extremely random bits in OTHER sky boxes.  For example, looking up from the second area, I can see one displacement and two regular brush stairs in the first area, and looking down (I know there shouldn’t be skybox on the ground, but I’ll get around to it), I can see a long straight brush and all but one steps in a stairwell in the next area.  That, and water isn’t visible from the top anymore, but I suspect that has something to do with VVIS failing before completion.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Raminator">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/r/6bbea6/40.png" class="avatar"> Raminator:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>You’ll need your trigger_teleport, an info_teleport_destination and an info_target.</p>
<p>…</p>
<p>Alternatively, you can use only one train, parent the trigger volume and teleport destination to it, and set the train to teleport to the destination path_track (check the “teleport to THIS path track” flag). That way if the player shoots the train or somehow applies any other decals to it, they’ll won’t mysteriously disappear when you reach your destination.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>In the meantime, I’m working to try and get that to work, as my next step.  If I can get one train to work, then I’ll just need to light it once, and keep those dynamic’s parented to it for the entire ride.  Hopefully that’ll make things look better.  I’ll just have to make sure tunnel textures line up so to reduce the visual jump as much as possible.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Raminator">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/r/6bbea6/40.png" class="avatar"> Raminator:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Alternatively, you can use only one train, parent the trigger volume and teleport destination to it, and set the train to teleport to the destination path_track (check the “teleport to THIS path track” flag).</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Just one question on that:  How do I actually activate the teleport the way it’s layed out?  Trigger the trigger with another trigger?  Or as an output of the path_track, and if that, then which path_track, the one before or after the “teleport”.</p>
<p>WOAH.  FUCKED UP.  I just compiled again…  And now…  I have a massive leak (The entire side of a skybox that I guess I didn’t cut off when I tried to make it smaller, and all the lighting compiled.  Everything except the water worked fine.  Except I could fall into forever through a massive hole in my map.  I thought leaks made lighting fail…[/SIZE]</p>
<p>Fixed.  There was actually a very tiny hole under a door, that in turn, made the leftover skybox ‘ground’ a physical object, yet allowed it to drop off into oblivion.  Found and fixed, recompiling.</p>
<p>Ahem.  Now I don’t get any errors, but VVIS still won’t finish.  I can end the process and everything will be fine in game, but it just won’t finish the water.  The water’s never given me problems before, I haven’t even touched the skybox area it’s in in… forever!  I’m working in a completely separate (ie: NO connection whatsoever to the water’s area) area.<br>
Wait…  I did turn the docks into a func_detail…  They touch the water, and that’s the only thing I can think of that I’ve done anywhere near there…</p>
<p>That wasn’t it…  Duh…  I can’t believe this.  I took a GIANT skybox, totally excessive in size, and cut it down to just fit the area it was needed.  That involved giving it an akward corner, so to avoid cutting BACK into a tunnel.  That’s the only thing left I can even think that would be causing this damned VVIS stupidity.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/hammering-away-again/2674/27">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/hammering-away-again/2674/27</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 16 Mar 2010 17:36:45 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2674-27</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/hammering-away-again/2674.rss">Hammering away again...</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Hammering away again...</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Madcat1030]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I have a big problem.  I formatted my hard-drive, and in replacing my backup files, I guess I forgot the hammer map files.  I have the HL2 map files that can be loaded in game, but I guess I forgot the others.  Is there any way to recover the hammer-editable files from these map files?</p>
<p>If you can do it, I’d send the file to you, if you can explain to me, all the better.</p>
<p>Er, nevermind…  found it.  Let the search function sit on its ass for an hour, so nevermind.</p>
<p>My model viewer’s majorly fucked up.  I can only see the upper left hand quadrant.  And I can’t resize the boxes themselves to fit, they just slide away whenever I mouse over the barriers.</p>
<p>Well, I managed to get the top-right (model view area) to show back up, but the bottom area is below where I can possibly resize the box to.<br>
[/size]</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/hammering-away-again/2674/26">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/hammering-away-again/2674/26</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 09 Mar 2010 15:29:42 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2674-26</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/hammering-away-again/2674.rss">Hammering away again...</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Hammering away again...</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Madcat1030]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><span alt="" class="broken-image" title="This image is broken"><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-unlink svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#unlink"></use></svg></span></p>
<p>New area, going to spruce it up with crates, a vending machine (it’s going to be the basement of some building up above, and it just happens to be alongside the train’s tunnel),  and various other things (Light fixtures!).  Maybe a forklift or something.  That picture doesn’t really get the shape of the room.  It is located on the outside of the middle of a 90 degree turn in the tracks.  The walls just off the track go off at apprx 90 degrees from the track (45 degrees off NSEW in hammer), then goes in another 45 degrees, then has a jog in (tunnel in middle of image), goes back to flat (lift), then back around to the track, by where the image was taken.  The red light is at a door that leads up to the door you can actually see in the photo.</p>
<p>Also: Wtf is up with my hud.  All the words are choppy and the numbers 0 and 1 are choppy as well.  The other numbers are fine though…</p>
<p>Fortunate news:  Turns out that in my stupidity, I accidentally made the tunnel alot bigger than I meant post-teleportation-to-third-train, so a razor-combine-train would probably fit later.</p>
<p>Who thinks the words “teleporter” “teleportation” and “teleported” need to be added to Mozilla’s stock dictionary?  I know I can just add to dictionary, but why aren’t they there already…  They are used so comonly.  Other words get into the dictionary, and nobody likes them, so why can’t teleport and his friends get in…  come on, it can’t be THAT exclusive, doohickey’s in there!<br>
/offtopic, sorry</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/hammering-away-again/2674/25">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/hammering-away-again/2674/25</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 16 Feb 2010 21:40:52 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2674-25</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/hammering-away-again/2674.rss">Hammering away again...</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Hammering away again...</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Madcat1030]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>In the case of one-train teleporting, do a assign an output to the last path node (the one that it teleports FROM) triggering the trigger_teleport?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/hammering-away-again/2674/24">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/hammering-away-again/2674/24</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 12 Feb 2010 23:52:36 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2674-24</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/hammering-away-again/2674.rss">Hammering away again...</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Hammering away again...</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Madcat1030]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>It’s for a person.<br>
You are in a train car, it goes into a dimly (but not quite black) lit tunnel, and a couple good feet into it, you hit a teleport trigger which dumps you out onto another train, farther down in the map, on the other side, so it can keep going.  I’m trying to get it so it will spawn you in the same place on the new train that you were on the old train.  My problem is that kind of positioning requires a landmark on the first train, and since you can’t assign a parent to an info_landmark, I can’t do that.</p>
<p>My question now is:  Is the landmark the trigger_teleport is looking for an info_landmark or simply any entity to ACT as a landmark?</p>
<p>EDIT: Didn’t see solokillers response.  I’mma try that nao.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/hammering-away-again/2674/23">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/hammering-away-again/2674/23</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 12 Feb 2010 00:08:47 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2674-23</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/hammering-away-again/2674.rss">Hammering away again...</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Hammering away again...</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Angdraug]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>What are you teleporting? If you’re going to teleport the player use info_teleport_destination. I’m not sure if it work for props.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/hammering-away-again/2674/22">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/hammering-away-again/2674/22</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 11 Feb 2010 23:19:17 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2674-22</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/hammering-away-again/2674.rss">Hammering away again...</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Hammering away again...</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Solokiller]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>You can use an info_target if it’s not moving, and you can try using the prop_dynamic’s name.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/hammering-away-again/2674/21">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/hammering-away-again/2674/21</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 11 Feb 2010 22:50:39 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2674-21</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/hammering-away-again/2674.rss">Hammering away again...</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Hammering away again...</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Madcat1030]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I was hoping to use it as a teleportation landmark.  Or can I use anything as a local landmark for a trigger teleport?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/hammering-away-again/2674/20">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/hammering-away-again/2674/20</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 11 Feb 2010 22:32:55 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2674-20</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/hammering-away-again/2674.rss">Hammering away again...</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Hammering away again...</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Solokiller]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>It would only work if the entity supports the parent system, and an info_landmark obviously doesn’t, since it links 2 (or more) maps together.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/hammering-away-again/2674/19">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/hammering-away-again/2674/19</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 11 Feb 2010 21:07:06 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2674-19</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/hammering-away-again/2674.rss">Hammering away again...</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Hammering away again...</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Madcat1030]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Question:  If I leave “smart edit” mode and create a parameter called “parent” and assign it to a given object, can I make a info_landmark parented to a prop_dynamic?  Or will it just not recognize it as a valid parameter and ignore it.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/hammering-away-again/2674/18">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/hammering-away-again/2674/18</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 11 Feb 2010 18:49:49 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2674-18</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/hammering-away-again/2674.rss">Hammering away again...</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Hammering away again...</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Madcat1030]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Working on the tunnel.  It was getting a bit boring, so I had it turn a bit, and added a maintenance area, seen below, in all its unadorned and completely barren beauty.<br>
<span alt="" class="broken-image" title="This image is broken"><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-unlink svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#unlink"></use></svg></span></p>
<p>Floor texture for the track area isn’t important as you are currently unable to see down that far.</p>
<p>I just did some reading up on HL2’s original design plan, and this is going to end up being a lot like the intro sequence to HL2 was originally going to be (Gordon walking up to a vista of a beautiful city through a squeaky-happy-green-landscape, then the city morphing into C17 as we know it).  Except its going to happen in stages here.</p>
<p>UPDATE:  Working on the highway-canyon area.  Gotta make it a bit longer to go around a corner out of sight.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/hammering-away-again/2674/17">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/hammering-away-again/2674/17</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 22 Jan 2010 20:34:10 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2674-17</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/hammering-away-again/2674.rss">Hammering away again...</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Hammering away again...</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Madcat1030]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Lol.  Pointless post is pointless.  Yet made me smile…</p>
<p>Anywho:  Filled the emptiness of the basin with a processing plant.  Looks like the foundation is going to have to spread, cuz they don’t exactly look right, sticking right out of the earth.  Maybe if I make the earth rock instead, it will look a bit better than grass…</p>
<p>EDIT:  I can already tell this area is going to go through MANY iterations…  But here it is, FOR NOW.<br>
<span alt="" class="broken-image" title="This image is broken"><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-unlink svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#unlink"></use></svg></span><br>
Shot from across the “track” (next to the closest crane in the last photo) facing the new industrial area.  Yellow building on left is the same as the last photo, only from the opposite side.<br>
<span alt="" class="broken-image" title="This image is broken"><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-unlink svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#unlink"></use></svg></span><br>
Other side of the yellow building, facing same direction.</p>
<p>Definitely thinking of putting a giant gravel elevator (the long ramped enclosed conveyor buildings?) in the empty space on the bottom/left of the last image…</p>
<p>A reminder:  These are all things that are only going to be seen in passing, and that the player will have zero chance to interact with.  In later levels (the player may pass through some areas), barriers will be made by the environment (crashed trains, fallen buildings, etc), and areas will be optimized where needed.</p>
<p>UPDATED CONCEPT IDEA<br>
I was thinking…  maybe I should remove the props and put more piles of mined-rocks and maybe a few raised sheet-metal-walled buildings.  Like in the picture on this site:<br>
<a href="https://www.victoryminerals.com/about.html" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://www.victoryminerals.com/about.html</a><br>
Funny how I got there, reading an article on Half-life removed levels, found my way to episode 2, a translation of Waxta Nobeabl (the mine sines), googled it, and found Victory Minerals, but that’s totally irrelevant</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/hammering-away-again/2674/16">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/hammering-away-again/2674/16</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jan 2010 01:26:49 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2674-16</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/hammering-away-again/2674.rss">Hammering away again...</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Hammering away again...</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Ibanez]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="MaxTheLimit">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/m/0ea827/40.png" class="avatar"> MaxTheLimit:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I have a small thing.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>:3</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/hammering-away-again/2674/15">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/hammering-away-again/2674/15</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jan 2010 00:07:28 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2674-15</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/hammering-away-again/2674.rss">Hammering away again...</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Hammering away again...</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Madcat1030]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I fixed that actually, now there’s a new displacement in the valley left by the main grass displacement.  There’s a bit of a visual eye-stopper between them, but as you will be moving the whole time, it’s not a big problem.</p>
<p><a class="mention" href="/u/solokiller">@Solokiller</a>: Simply place a large brush, select the top face with the texture tool, and in the texture interface, click the “Displacement” tab, then click create, and add some noise.  Then copy it to the surrounding areas (can’t make one too large or it will look very jagged as you can only have up to a power of 4 cuts), highlight them all, and click Sew.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/hammering-away-again/2674/14">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/hammering-away-again/2674/14</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 19 Jan 2010 23:44:19 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2674-14</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/hammering-away-again/2674.rss">Hammering away again...</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Hammering away again...</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[MaxTheLimit]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I have a small thing.</p>
<p>In the second picture it looks as though the grass leads right up to, and than into the water. This wouldn’t typically happen as grass doesn’t grow underwater, or in areas where the soil is constantly battered with water. I would expect to see mud or rocks underwater and in the area leading up to that little lake thingy.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/hammering-away-again/2674/13">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/hammering-away-again/2674/13</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 19 Jan 2010 21:55:45 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2674-13</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/hammering-away-again/2674.rss">Hammering away again...</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Hammering away again...</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Solokiller]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>How did you create those displacements? I’m just wondering, since i’ve never actually seen how another person does it.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/hammering-away-again/2674/12">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/hammering-away-again/2674/12</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 19 Jan 2010 21:35:42 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2674-12</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/hammering-away-again/2674.rss">Hammering away again...</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Hammering away again...</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Madcat1030]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Brother Shrike, yeah, this is just a bunch of displacements thrown together.  I’mma fill the basin area of the quarry zone up with more details once I’ve finished the map up.</p>
<p>Well, I just did the math, and the track is about 1 mile long!  (that’s using 1 hammerunit = aprx .75 inches).  Oh, and the quarry’s really coming together.  Regarding the rock pile…  I’m working on placing an overlay that seems to work perfectly, but am having trouble finding a good balance between too much and too little.  I’ll just need to play around a bit more.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/hammering-away-again/2674/11">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/hammering-away-again/2674/11</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 19 Jan 2010 18:51:48 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2674-11</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/hammering-away-again/2674.rss">Hammering away again...</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Hammering away again...</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Zerego]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>This is looking great! Keep it up :3</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/hammering-away-again/2674/10">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/hammering-away-again/2674/10</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 19 Jan 2010 18:44:42 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2674-10</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/hammering-away-again/2674.rss">Hammering away again...</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
