<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Heliocentric</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/heliocentric/1664</link>
    <description>Yah, just thought I might as well just post a link to my music here.
The music project is called Heliocentric, so far I&#39;ve released two free albums with it, the first album is a mix of trip-hop and ambient (so it&#39;s a calm and smooth album), while the second one is more a mix of different up-tempo electronic genres. Apart from a few tracks that are more rock-oriented.
[url]https://www.myspace.com/heliocentricmusicproductions[/url]

There&#39;s also a facebook page with different tracks on it, just hit the search function there, IF you like the music that&#39;s on the myspace already.

Reason why I&#39;m posting this here, is because it&#39;s been used in several projects and it can be classified under &quot;game-related&quot;  :slight_smile: 

Cheers
Ice</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 26 Oct 2009 12:03:53 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Show Off</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/heliocentric/1664.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Heliocentric</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Dr_icecream]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I know music comes from passion, that’s what the point of both albums I’ve made so far is. But like it goes with every artist (and that’s something that can’t be denied), the more popular pieces are being exposed more. Besides, i’m not doing anything for money, I put up music for free, so the attention is not on purpose of getting signed (a thing I never dreamt about or desired), but more of getting my music to more people who actually might like this style. Besides, I wouldn’t call Channel 7, Ensnared or Scars lacking Substance, there’s plenty of variation there and the harmonies fit perfectly  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=9" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"><br>
I have plenty of rock tracks I wrote in the process of my second album, but I won’t release those untill they’re worked out for the full 100%, it’s just something that takes more time and will probably be less interesting for people since it’s going to be more about the progression of the songs than it’s about “having a kick-ass song”, like it seems to be the standard nowadays.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/heliocentric/1664/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/heliocentric/1664/6</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 26 Oct 2009 12:03:53 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-1664-6</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/heliocentric/1664.rss">Heliocentric</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Heliocentric</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Patonki]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Are you saying you’re already whoring out for money when you don’t make money yet?<br>
Music comes from passion, man. When you don’t enjoy creating it, it shows.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/heliocentric/1664/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/heliocentric/1664/5</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 26 Oct 2009 09:58:01 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-1664-5</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/heliocentric/1664.rss">Heliocentric</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Heliocentric</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Dr_icecream]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>What can I say? Most stuff I put up there is the more “popular” genres they’re playing around here nowadays. I have songs like Scream, Scars, Channel 7, Anywhere else but home etc… That are actually built up towards a climax and fade out in the end, but those songs are more for the people who listen to music to check out what kind of harmonies you can create. Te stuff I put up here is rather to satisfy people who’d go like “Oh yeah, that sounds kewl”</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/heliocentric/1664/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/heliocentric/1664/4</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 26 Oct 2009 07:28:04 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-1664-4</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/heliocentric/1664.rss">Heliocentric</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Heliocentric</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Patonki]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>It’s okay. Kinda lacking in substance. Some songs seem drawn out (and this is coming form a person who loves drone)</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/heliocentric/1664/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/heliocentric/1664/3</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 22 Oct 2009 20:55:48 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-1664-3</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/heliocentric/1664.rss">Heliocentric</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Heliocentric</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Android11x]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I much rather prefer geocentric.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/heliocentric/1664/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/heliocentric/1664/2</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 22 Oct 2009 20:32:26 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-1664-2</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/heliocentric/1664.rss">Heliocentric</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Heliocentric</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Dr_icecream]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Yah, just thought I might as well just post a link to my music here.<br>
The music project is called Heliocentric, so far I’ve released two free albums with it, the first album is a mix of trip-hop and ambient (so it’s a calm and smooth album), while the second one is more a mix of different up-tempo electronic genres. Apart from a few tracks that are more rock-oriented.<br>
<a href="https://www.myspace.com/heliocentricmusicproductions" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://www.myspace.com/heliocentricmusicproductions</a></p>
<p>There’s also a facebook page with different tracks on it, just hit the search function there, IF you like the music that’s on the myspace already.</p>
<p>Reason why I’m posting this here, is because it’s been used in several projects and it can be classified under “game-related”  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=9" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
<p>Cheers<br>
Ice</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/heliocentric/1664/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/heliocentric/1664/1</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 22 Oct 2009 09:48:14 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-1664-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/heliocentric/1664.rss">Heliocentric</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
