<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Blank screen</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/blank-screen/7985</link>
    <description>Hi guys, I&#39;m kind of a new guy here but a problem just came up and I need help.

A couple of days ago, when I boot up my computer my monitor just stays black. I know the monitor turns on and works (I&#39;m using it right now), but sometimes when I start up my computer it&#39;ll just stay black. I&#39;ve checked all the connections and everything seems to be in order. I did notice that when the monitor would stay black, my graphics card fan would rev up to 100% speed.

Pretty sure it&#39;s not a software problem, as the monitor wouldn&#39;t even show the POST screen half of the time. It&#39;s a very finicky problem that doesn&#39;t always appear; for example, I can put the computer in sleep mode and it&#39;ll come back on fine. Or I can restart the computer from Windows and it&#39;ll come back on okay. 

Can you guys help me out? I have a feeling it&#39;s a video card issue, but I want to be sure before I go out and get a new one. Is it possible it could be a motherboard or power supply issue?</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2011 17:53:27 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Help and Support</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/blank-screen/7985.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Blank screen</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[TickTock]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>How are you connecting the monitor to the PC? HDMI, DVI, VGA?<br>
What kind of video card?</p>
<p>I have seen things in the past when using HDMI on an ATI card that if the monitor is not powered up and out of sleep before the computer is turned on the monitor does not get the power on signal and will not come on until you restart or the computer changes video modes. If I am not mistaken this same type of thing can happen with DVI as well due to similar signaling and security standards.</p>
<p>To correct the problem I had I updated the video card drivers and I have not had any issues since.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/blank-screen/7985/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/blank-screen/7985/6</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2011 17:53:27 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7985-6</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/blank-screen/7985.rss">Blank screen</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Blank screen</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[mental2k]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Another diagnostic tool at your disposal may be your BIOS.  Google the beep codes for your BIOS, there will be a certain beep sequence for a defective graphics card.</p>
<p>Also it could be a defective cable, I’d try replacing that first before spending ££££ on a new graphics card or monitor.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/blank-screen/7985/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/blank-screen/7985/5</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 20 Oct 2011 11:45:49 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7985-5</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/blank-screen/7985.rss">Blank screen</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Blank screen</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Kairouseki]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I’m not sure if it’s the same thing but when I go to use my computer and turn the monitor back on, it doesn’t pick up a signal until I move my mouse or press a key. Just throwing that out there even though it’s probably not the same.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/blank-screen/7985/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/blank-screen/7985/4</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 20 Oct 2011 01:15:24 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7985-4</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/blank-screen/7985.rss">Blank screen</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Blank screen</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Delta]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I do get startup sounds, the keyboard and mouse light up and everything. The monitor shows that it’s searching for a video signal, but after a while of searching it gives up and stays blank. It doesn’t seem to be a connection issue between the monitor and the PC, because when the monitor is unplugged from the PC it displays a connection error message. I will try your tactic next time it happens though.</p>
<p>I have tried reseating and replugging in the power in my video card and it worked, although I’m not sure if it was that or if it just decided to work again. Could it be a PSU problem?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/blank-screen/7985/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/blank-screen/7985/3</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 20 Oct 2011 01:11:55 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7985-3</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/blank-screen/7985.rss">Blank screen</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Blank screen</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Jim_DiGriz]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>It could also be a monitor issue. Do you get startup sounds when the monitor stays black? A friend of mine had an Acer LCD display go out on him. It had been doing some strange things for a couple days, but was usable after power cycling it. He got some glitching in a game, rebooted his macine, and the monitor didn’t come out of sleep mode. He tested with his wifes monitor, and his machine was fine. He gave me the old monitor (I used to do component level repair on monitors and printers a few years ago), and I found a blown capacitor (1000 micro-farad, 10 volt). I replaced it, and it’s working fine now.</p>
<p>If you have access to another monitor of the same resolution, try switching the next time it stays black. If the second monitor comes on properly, it’s a bad monitor. If not, probably the video card. If your video card has to have power connected seperately, make sure the connection is good. Also, reseating the card never hurts (make sure the machine is off when you do these things).</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/blank-screen/7985/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/blank-screen/7985/2</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 20 Oct 2011 00:05:18 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7985-2</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/blank-screen/7985.rss">Blank screen</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Blank screen</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Delta]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Hi guys, I’m kind of a new guy here but a problem just came up and I need help.</p>
<p>A couple of days ago, when I boot up my computer my monitor just stays black. I know the monitor turns on and works (I’m using it right now), but sometimes when I start up my computer it’ll just stay black. I’ve checked all the connections and everything seems to be in order. I did notice that when the monitor would stay black, my graphics card fan would rev up to 100% speed.</p>
<p>Pretty sure it’s not a software problem, as the monitor wouldn’t even show the POST screen half of the time. It’s a very finicky problem that doesn’t always appear; for example, I can put the computer in sleep mode and it’ll come back on fine. Or I can restart the computer from Windows and it’ll come back on okay.</p>
<p>Can you guys help me out? I have a feeling it’s a video card issue, but I want to be sure before I go out and get a new one. Is it possible it could be a motherboard or power supply issue?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/blank-screen/7985/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/blank-screen/7985/1</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 19 Oct 2011 20:24:47 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7985-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/blank-screen/7985.rss">Blank screen</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
