<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>The life of a Headcrab</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/the-life-of-a-headcrab/3561</link>
    <description>Headcrabology. 

For some reason it interests me the various forms of the headcrab, what they are, how they come to be, how they live, how they grow, etc.

Of course we all know we have several types of headcrab: the standard headcrab, the &quot;fast&quot; headcrab, the poison headcrab, and the gonarch. 

Are they all the same species? Are they subspecies? Gonarchs seem to create standard headcrabs, so is there a gonarch-type for every type of headcrab? A giant speedy gonarch running around somewhere at 80mph spewing out fast headcrabs?

I think all headcrabs are members of the same species in various states of development. This is for two reasons. First, the gonarch was seen &quot;giving birth&quot; to only one physically identical type of headcrab which bears obvious resemblence to the &quot;standard&quot; headcrab type. Also, there is (at least IMHO) an obvious physical gradiation effect from normal headcrab to gonarch. See below:

[img]https://forums.blackmesasource.com/attachment.php?attachmentid=613&amp;d=1269811683[/img]

First we have the baby headcrab; quite pale, flat and elonged. By the time it matures to a &quot;standard&quot; headcrab it has shortened and rounded out. Maturing to &quot;fast&quot; headcrabs, its colouration grows darker, its legs become symmetrical both in appearance and placement. By the time it reaches &quot;poison&quot; headcrab it has become even darker, its body has become more squared and segmented as opposed to the smooth roundness of its younger forms and it develops some sort of poison. Then ??? happens, it grows exponentially larger and develops the reproductive sac.

It is likely that the transformation from one biological state to the next (except for baby headcrabs-&gt;&quot;standard&quot; headcrabs) is a near-instant biological process similar to insects, as no &quot;inbetween&quot; specimens have ever been found. 

The next question of course is how these different states relate to their symbiotic nature with host creatures (namely humans). Do headcrabs attach in their first stages and then develop into the later stages while attached to their host? I don&#39;t believe so; the states of their host bodies seems to varied to be of the same lineage as their development; &quot;normal&quot; headcrab hosts are relatively unchanged, while &quot;fast&quot; headcrab hosts become quite thin and fast, and &quot;poison&quot; headcrab hosts large, slow and lumbering; transformation of the host from one to the next to the next is biologically unlikely, but not impossible. 

Likely, the symbiotic relationship is the primary form of feeding for headcrabs and likely is a necessary act necessary for transformation, similar to how animals lay eggs in other animals to feed on and grow. So as not to become completely defenseless during the coupling process, the host victim is kept alive, but under the control of brutal, violent instinct, with only basic motor functions and reasoning ability. It is very unlikely the headcrab &quot;mind-controls&quot; its victims due to observed instances of a coupled victim carrying out actions native to its former pre-coupled existence that headcrabs would have no comprehension of (such as the use of grenades). It is also unlikely that hosts have any cognitive understanding of what they are doing, and are acting more like mindless rabies-infected &quot;zombies&quot; with extremely violent tendencies and will attack any non-headcrab organisms it detects. 

Headcrab social organization is hard to determine, but is likely similar to native social insect species such as ants. This is due to the fact that the &quot;gonarch&quot; state of development is nowhere near as plentiful and widespread as the other stages. The one gonarch we&#39;ve encountered was seen giving birth to undersized headcrabs at a prodigious rate; if these plentiful headgrabs would each (naturally) grow into a gonarch equipped with similar reproductive powers then the population explosion would be absolutely immense and far, far, far greater than what we actually see. Likely, most headcrabs do not &quot;make&quot; it to gonarch-dom, either due to high mortality rates in native populations (perhaps it takes years and years for a poison headcrab to develop into a gonarch, and most do not live anywhere near that long due to a variety of reasons), or lack of some food source required to power the immense transformation, or simply because very few headgrabs are actually born with the [i]ability[/i] to become gonarchs (similar to how the vast majority of ants are born as workers and soldiers as opposed to queens and males).

However, beyond this there does not appear to be any form of social interaction or unification between headcrabs. When multiple headcrabs exist in the same environment they almost completely ignore one another, and will pursue prey in an individualistic manner. This is contrary to the behaviour of other social insects who live, work, build, forage and hunt as one community with each member playing specific roles to a greater end. 

&quot;You bring up a good point identifying the similarities between headcrabs and social insect species. Doesn&#39;t this support each type of headcrab being &quot;born&quot; in its current state, rather than transforming from one to the next?&quot; No. Again, the only recorded gonarch was observed giving birth to a *single* type of headcrab. It is entirely possible that this &quot;baby headcrab&quot; can develop into any of the different kinds of headcrabs once it is born and simply looks the same because this is a common biological feature (young human fetuses look almost identical; baby birds regardless of gender look identical but the differences between adult males and females can often be quite mind-boggling; and ant larvae looks identical when laid but can hatch into a variety of different types of ant). However I like the idea that there is a clear link from baby&gt;standard&gt;fast&gt;poison&gt;gonarch, visually.

That is all.
![headcrabgrowth.jpg|138x500](upload://umBEVapbNQMA6sROnwERgKlB7Hs.jpeg)</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Apr 2010 16:40:03 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Half-Life Series</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/the-life-of-a-headcrab/3561.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>The life of a Headcrab</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[sekoshiba]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>o_O i thought that…</p>
<p>headcrab + host = zombie + time/exposure to headcrab’s mutagen = gonarch<br>
and…<br>
fast/poison headcrabs = biological weaponry made by the combine to fight the resistance</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/the-life-of-a-headcrab/3561/37">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/the-life-of-a-headcrab/3561/37</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 03 Apr 2010 16:40:03 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3561-37</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/the-life-of-a-headcrab/3561.rss">The life of a Headcrab</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The life of a Headcrab</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[baconeggs]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>We never find poison or fast variations in abundance amongst the headcrab population anyway. Even ignoring HL1, vanilla headcrabs still outnumber their mutated counterparts.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/the-life-of-a-headcrab/3561/36">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/the-life-of-a-headcrab/3561/36</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 03 Apr 2010 06:03:18 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3561-36</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/the-life-of-a-headcrab/3561.rss">The life of a Headcrab</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The life of a Headcrab</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Eric_Fong]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Doedel">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/d/c68b51/40.png" class="avatar"> Doedel:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>This could be, but then why do we never see headcrab mortars dropping the obviously more deadly fast and poison headcrab types, but find them in relative abundance throughout the headcrab population?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>It did, near the end of hl2 ep1, there is a containment full of headcrab shell, when the strider attack the containment, the headcrab shell release full of fast headcrab.</p>
<p>For poison headcrab, you must play Half-Life 2: Lost coast, in the church where you must destroy the headcrab shell cannon, when you does, it will release poison headcrab.</p>
<p>Edit: damn ninja.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/the-life-of-a-headcrab/3561/35">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/the-life-of-a-headcrab/3561/35</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 03 Apr 2010 04:15:58 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3561-35</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/the-life-of-a-headcrab/3561.rss">The life of a Headcrab</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The life of a Headcrab</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Muhb]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="baconeggs">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/b/43a26b/40.png" class="avatar"> baconeggs:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I suppose, although I do feel that there must be some link between zombification and gonarch development, otherwise the whole life cycle seems to be off kilter. Bear in mind that while a zombie bears no resemblance to a gonarch, the headcrab is still very much intact. Is it not unthinkable that the headcrab assimilate and reform material from the host?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Nope, not unthinkable at all, in fact it’s entirely possible.  Who knows, we could see evidence of that in EP3, if Valve decides to take things in that direction.  I just didn’t personally interpret it that way while playing through the series so far, I guess.  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=9" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"></p>
<p>In real Earth nature, there are plenty of examples of creatures bonding together (although the processes aren’t necessarily as “dramatic” as the headcrab bonding process…) for mutual benefit.  My guess is that this is what the headcrab was accustomed to doing prior to reaching Xen/Earth: Bonding with something else from its homeworld (since supposedly nothing is native to Xen) for the purpose of mutual benefit and growth. The Gonarch has a certain symmetry to it, suggesting to me that it could possibly be the result of what “should” happen in nature on its homeworld.  On the other hand, when a headcrab bonds with a human, the overall process isn’t nearly as symmetrical (at least not at first… judging by the mutation of the human’s arms) and overall, seems (to me, at least) to be far more degenerative, rather than productive or beneficial, to <span class="bbcode-i">both</span> parties involved. (Especially considering the fact that the headcrabs, after bonding with a human, really only accomplish the feat of make themselves bigger and more vulnerable targets to a particularly deadly crowbar-weilding, zombie-hating predator. :freeman <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=9" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
<p>The more I think about it, the more I’m actually convinved that humans are probably something headcrabs were never intended to bond with, and that the grisly end result is simply due to a lack of a genetic compatibility between the host and the headcrab, a genetic compatibility that the “right” creature most likely has with headcrabs.  As for <span class="bbcode-i">why</span> headcrabs bond with humans, and supposedly <span class="bbcode-i">not</span> with Vorts, (though this may change in the future) who knows?  It could be something as simple as similar pheromones between humans and the headcrabs’ typical host, or, maybe you are right, and maybe headcrabs just bond with whatever the heck they feel like, humans included, in order to reorganize their hosts’ DNA and use the extra tissue mass for their own benefit.  It could go either way, I think.</p>
<p>All I really know for certain, is that I wouldn’t want one on <span class="bbcode-i">my</span> head!  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=9" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"></p>
<p>(…random thought… we totally need a :headcrabbed: smiley!!  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/smiley.png?v=9" title=":smiley:" class="emoji" alt=":smiley:"> )</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/the-life-of-a-headcrab/3561/34">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/the-life-of-a-headcrab/3561/34</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 03 Apr 2010 03:34:03 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3561-34</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/the-life-of-a-headcrab/3561.rss">The life of a Headcrab</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The life of a Headcrab</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[baconeggs]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Muhb">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/m/ee7513/40.png" class="avatar"> Muhb:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I’ll have to agree with Coozins on this one, I see little resemblance between a (human) zombie and a Gonarch.  I suppose it’s possible, but I guess this is just something we’ll have to agree to disagree on.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I suppose, although I do feel that there must be some link between zombification and gonarch development, otherwise the whole life cycle seems to be off kilter. Bear in mind that while a zombie bears no resemblance to a gonarch, the headcrab is still very much intact. Is it not unthinkable that the headcrab assimilate and reform material from the host?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/the-life-of-a-headcrab/3561/33">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/the-life-of-a-headcrab/3561/33</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Apr 2010 04:18:46 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3561-33</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/the-life-of-a-headcrab/3561.rss">The life of a Headcrab</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The life of a Headcrab</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Ajax]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I tried to do something similar, but for all Xenofauna species. The entry I made for headcrabs went like this:</p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>Headcrabs - Headcrabs are a unique creature. They are omnivorous, but have seemed to develop very carnivorous habits upon teleporting to Earth. This may be that their primary food source on Xen <a>url=‘https://images4.wikia.nocookie.net/half-life/en/images/thumb/5/56/Fungus_on_Xen.jpg/800px-Fungus_on_Xen.jpg’</a>[/url] is roughtly the same size and color of most of the humans found upon entry in the Black Mesa Research Facility, and, indeed, all over the world. The openings on the top of the fungus, combined with the headcrab’s “beak,” suggest that the fungus has a hard skin, and that the beak is needed to break it open to take the neutrients out.</p>
<p>Upon “feeding” on a human, however, the effects are quite different <a>url=‘https://images3.wikia.nocookie.net/half-life/en/images/thumb/a/a0/Zombie_fire_arms_raised.jpg/418px-Zombie_fire_arms_raised.jpg’</a>[/url], leading us to believe that the Xen fungus may be poisonous, and the antibodies produced by the headcrab are fed into the fungus, as well as acting passively within the headcrab’s own body. These antibodies are most definately lethal to a human, causing a parisitic symbiosis of headcrab/human relations. The human body is sustained by the headcrab, and the “zombie,” as the combined form is called, must take in neutrients at the expense of all other activities.</p>
<p>This change is not present in just the human body, however. Fluids ingested from the human body by the headcrab causes a mutation within the headcrab itself as well, creating an addiction to feed on proteins only present in Earth animals. If a headcrab cannot feed on humans, eventually, we imagine, they may return to their original state, though not unharmed, mentally. Studies of Dr. Kleiner’s pet headcrab could be of use <a>url=‘https://images1.wikia.nocookie.net/half-life/en/images/c/c4/Lamarr_and_Kleiner.jpg’</a>[/url].</p>
<p>Since the Black Mesa incident, other variations of headcrab have evolved. Whether these mutations were present in the headcrab’s “native”* environment or not remains to be seen, though some have argued that it is not too far fetched that these variations could have begun on Earth. The “Fast” headcrab <a>url=‘https://images3.wikia.nocookie.net/half-life/en/images/6/6c/Headcrab_Fast.jpg’</a>[/url] and the “Poison” headcrab <a>url=‘https://images2.wikia.nocookie.net/half-life/en/images/e/e5/Headcrab_poison.jpg’</a>[/url].</p>
<p>The Headcrab life cycle is still a mystery, though we know that a creature called the “Gonarch” <a>url=‘https://images4.wikia.nocookie.net/half-life/en/images/2/2a/Gonarch_model.jpg’</a>[/url] is resposible for their birth, we have no idea as to whether or not they are born asexually or if the Gonarch has a mate. We also do not know how long it takes a headcrab to reach the Gonarch stage, though the current estimation is under 20 years, if the Fast and Poison headcrab variations were born on Earth. It is assumed, as well, that very few headcrabs make it to the Gonarch stage.</p>
<p>Headcrabs tend to stay near to their “mother” at the early stages of their life <a>url=‘https://images1.wikia.nocookie.net/half-life/en/images/a/a3/Headcrab_baby.jpg’</a>[/url]. They do not appear to leave their nest until after they’ve reached their main developmental stage. After they reach their main life stage, they leave the nest and find their own little caves to live out their lives. Headcrabs seem to live in mostly cavernous areas, often with very little room to move, but almost always with a food and water source nearby.</p>
<p>Further observations on this species are needed to determine timespans and mating habits.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/the-life-of-a-headcrab/3561/32">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/the-life-of-a-headcrab/3561/32</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 31 Mar 2010 18:20:51 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3561-32</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/the-life-of-a-headcrab/3561.rss">The life of a Headcrab</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The life of a Headcrab</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[X_Mastershot_X]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>…and i see a resemblance between a headcrab and Xen funghi</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/the-life-of-a-headcrab/3561/31">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/the-life-of-a-headcrab/3561/31</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 31 Mar 2010 17:35:21 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3561-31</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/the-life-of-a-headcrab/3561.rss">The life of a Headcrab</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The life of a Headcrab</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Muhb]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="baconeggs">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/b/43a26b/40.png" class="avatar"> baconeggs:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>For what I can see with the gonome’s mutation I hypothesised that the host’s body was used as “building material” for the gonarch’s form.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I’ll have to agree with Coozins on this one, I see little resemblance between a (human) zombie and a Gonarch.  I suppose it’s possible, but I guess this is just something we’ll have to agree to disagree on.</p>
<p>I actually think it’s much more likely that the Gonarch could possibly be the result of a headcrab coupling with another Xenian creature of some sort (probably followed by long years of eating/sleeping/growing/etc.) rather than with a human, as has already been suggested.  I mean, judging by size alone (which isn’t <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=zPu4f-F_pdM" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">necessarily accurate</a> I suppose, but just roll with me here for a sec  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=9" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"> ) the Gonarch from HL1 had probably existed for a number of Earth years, (before Gordon effectively ended it,) so whatever it had bonded with (assuming it bonded with anything at all, in the course of its life) most likely <span class="bbcode-i">wasn’t</span> human.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Doedel">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/d/c68b51/40.png" class="avatar"> Doedel:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>This could be, but then why do we never see headcrab mortars dropping the obviously more deadly fast and poison headcrab types, but find them in relative abundance throughout the headcrab population?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>But… we <span class="bbcode-i">do</span> see them… at least, I think we did… didn’t we…?  Maybe I’m remember wrong, but I thought that there were a few instances of mortar use where poison or fast headcrabs popped out (or where it was implied that poison or fast headcrabs had been housed inside, through indication of a poison/fast zombie lurking near a vacant mortar or something).  At least, I think so…</p>
<p>Lost Coast had poison headcrabs pop out of the mortars in the church, if I remember correctly.  And Episode One had that sea-faring shipping crate near the end of the game that Gordon was crawling through, which the strider blew up, causing the mortars that were inside with Gordon to open up, revealing two poison headcrabs (again, if I’m remembering correctly… I could just be bullshitting this, but I’m pretty sure there were poison guys in there).  I think I also recall a mortar hitting a building somewhere in Episode One which revealed a few fast headcrabs, but again, clearly I need to play the game(s) again to make sure…</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/the-life-of-a-headcrab/3561/30">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/the-life-of-a-headcrab/3561/30</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 31 Mar 2010 17:26:05 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3561-30</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/the-life-of-a-headcrab/3561.rss">The life of a Headcrab</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The life of a Headcrab</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Frozen_Cham]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><span alt="" class="broken-image" title="This image is broken"><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-unlink svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#unlink"></use></svg></span></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/the-life-of-a-headcrab/3561/29">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/the-life-of-a-headcrab/3561/29</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 30 Mar 2010 04:37:18 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3561-29</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/the-life-of-a-headcrab/3561.rss">The life of a Headcrab</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The life of a Headcrab</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Jerakal]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I think that the reason why most of the headcrabs on earth are so confused and disorganized is because they don’t have any contact with a “queen” or gonarch as the case may be, if we’re going with the theory that they function like ants.</p>
<p>If they also have multiple sub-species like the ants do, then we can assume that the regular head crabs are the drones, which might use their ability to control a host’s nervous system to take control of a host and take it back to the nest for food for the queen or other headcrabs.</p>
<p>The fast headcrabs destroy their hosts body for the most part, making them poorly suited for foraging, but their agility lends them superior combat abilities, making them much like soldier ants.</p>
<p>As for the poison headcrabs, their neuro-toxins would benefit the hive by poisoning and subduing larger opponents.</p>
<p>Apologies in advance if anyone else made these exact points, I kinda skimmed the thread.</p>
<p>Just my musings on the topic.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/the-life-of-a-headcrab/3561/28">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/the-life-of-a-headcrab/3561/28</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 29 Mar 2010 21:36:50 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3561-28</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/the-life-of-a-headcrab/3561.rss">The life of a Headcrab</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The life of a Headcrab</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[X_Mastershot_X]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Alyx will make another motherfuckin’ joke and will introduce<br>
the vortigaunt-zombie = ZORTİE!<br>
alien grunt-zombie<br>
Alien Mushroom-zombie<br>
Polar bear Zombie<br>
advisor-zombie<br>
houndeye-zombie</p>
<p>ANY GOD DAMN THİNG YOU CAN İMAGİNE!!!</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/the-life-of-a-headcrab/3561/27">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/the-life-of-a-headcrab/3561/27</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 29 Mar 2010 18:35:19 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3561-27</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/the-life-of-a-headcrab/3561.rss">The life of a Headcrab</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The life of a Headcrab</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Pettifogg]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>That’s what I meant. They probably did something similar to something else before they encountered humans. But the result may not have been zombification - it depends on what their original hosts were.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/the-life-of-a-headcrab/3561/26">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/the-life-of-a-headcrab/3561/26</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 29 Mar 2010 18:27:41 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3561-26</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/the-life-of-a-headcrab/3561.rss">The life of a Headcrab</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The life of a Headcrab</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Jingles]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Zombies do not have to be human!!! Do you think that headcrabz suddenly realised they were able to do that when humans appeareD?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/the-life-of-a-headcrab/3561/25">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/the-life-of-a-headcrab/3561/25</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 29 Mar 2010 18:23:46 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3561-25</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/the-life-of-a-headcrab/3561.rss">The life of a Headcrab</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The life of a Headcrab</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Pettifogg]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Doedel">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/d/c68b51/40.png" class="avatar"> Doedel:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>This could be, but then why do we never see headcrab mortars dropping the obviously more deadly fast and poison headcrab types, but find them in relative abundance throughout the headcrab population?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>We do see them drop fast and poison headcrabs. <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/expressionless.png?v=9" title=":expressionless:" class="emoji" alt=":expressionless:"></p>
<p>As far as Gonarchs go, I doubt it has much to do with zombies, as there weren’t any humans on Xen before very recently. Although, maybe their instinct for zombification comes from attaching to something else, and the gonome is the result of trying to develop using the wrong type of host?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/the-life-of-a-headcrab/3561/24">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/the-life-of-a-headcrab/3561/24</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 29 Mar 2010 18:14:24 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3561-24</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/the-life-of-a-headcrab/3561.rss">The life of a Headcrab</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The life of a Headcrab</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Frozen_Cham]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>XEN doesn’t be a name of a planet,solar-like system,galaxy,or nebular.<br>
But I think that it is a name of another dimension, same position in 3D-coordinate to the earth but in different position of forth(or fifth)-coordinate.<br>
|<br>
|<br>
V</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/the-life-of-a-headcrab/3561/23">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/the-life-of-a-headcrab/3561/23</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 29 Mar 2010 17:03:27 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3561-23</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/the-life-of-a-headcrab/3561.rss">The life of a Headcrab</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The life of a Headcrab</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[HumanParadoxx]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Coozins">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/c/f07891/40.png" class="avatar"> Coozins:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>How? I see very little resemblance between a gonome and a gonarch, whereas I do see an obvious resemblance between a headcrab on its own and a gonarch. Why would the stage go quadruped to biped host back to quadruped again? Plus, this would mean that headcrabs would need humans on Xen to mutate into a gonarch, which would make no sense.<br>
My guess is that gonarchs are created in a similar way to queen ants and queen bees, i.e. juvenile headcrabs will be fed a special diet to make them sexually mature.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>But they are fed by who?<br>
Of course, I believe that what we saw on HL was a restricted part of Xen. There can be lots of xenians species that we don’t saw.</p>
<p>Personally, I think that the gonarch is an advanced stage of the evolution of the zombies. Why? Headcrabs feeds on humans and start mutating they organic systems.<br>
Like this: that mouth of the zombies, in the future, is going to create some sort of tissue that will house the host’s internal organs - modified, of course. The arms and legs could keep themselves continually growing.</p>
<p>But, there’s a point: how the gonarch got that armor? If I remember, the only vulnerability of the monster was it’s reproductive sack.</p>
<p>ah, I don’t know. Tried.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/the-life-of-a-headcrab/3561/22">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/the-life-of-a-headcrab/3561/22</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 29 Mar 2010 16:50:57 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3561-22</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/the-life-of-a-headcrab/3561.rss">The life of a Headcrab</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The life of a Headcrab</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Coozins]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="baconeggs">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/b/43a26b/40.png" class="avatar"> baconeggs:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>For what I can see with the gonome’s mutation I hypothesised that the host’s body was used as “building material” for the gonarch’s form.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>How? I see very little resemblance between a gonome and a gonarch, whereas I do see an obvious resemblance between a headcrab on its own and a gonarch. Why would the stage go quadruped to biped host back to quadruped again? Plus, this would mean that headcrabs would need humans on Xen to mutate into a gonarch, which would make no sense.<br>
My guess is that gonarchs are created in a similar way to queen ants and queen bees, i.e. juvenile headcrabs will be fed a special diet to make them sexually mature.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/the-life-of-a-headcrab/3561/21">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/the-life-of-a-headcrab/3561/21</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 29 Mar 2010 16:40:21 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3561-21</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/the-life-of-a-headcrab/3561.rss">The life of a Headcrab</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The life of a Headcrab</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Scrab_on_mars]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Um… I think it’s like this: Baby Headcrab&gt;Classic, or Standard if you want, Headcrab, Poison Headcrab, Fast Headcrab&gt;Death. I think it’s like with the bees. A Gonarch gives birth to another, “Baby” version of it ,then dies, which in turn grows to a full-sized Gonarch, and the cycle continues.</p>
<p>Edit: Ninja’d by λdam  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/smiley.png?v=9" title=":smiley:" class="emoji" alt=":smiley:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/the-life-of-a-headcrab/3561/20">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/the-life-of-a-headcrab/3561/20</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 29 Mar 2010 16:34:38 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3561-20</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/the-life-of-a-headcrab/3561.rss">The life of a Headcrab</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The life of a Headcrab</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[_amp_955_dam]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>There has to be some sort of link between the Headcrab and the Gonarch.</p>
<p>However, I believe that fast headcrabs and poison headcrabs are either very quick evolution, (Unless they’ve been evolving on Xen for years, and then evolved on Earth), or genetically modified by the Combine.</p>
<p>I do agree with the Ants part though, maybe some Headcrabs have the ability to grow into Gonarch’s, and others just don’t.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/the-life-of-a-headcrab/3561/19">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/the-life-of-a-headcrab/3561/19</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 29 Mar 2010 16:32:58 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3561-19</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/the-life-of-a-headcrab/3561.rss">The life of a Headcrab</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The life of a Headcrab</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Doedel]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>How would a headcrab go from having a beak to having no beak at all to having a beak again?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>If the fast headcrab didn’t have a beak it wouldn’t be able to couple. I can’t find any pics now but perhaps the mandible-type things of its “mouth” are more inward in this form (lol to make it more aerodynamic amirite)</p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>the variations were simply genetically modified by the combine, like Ramirezoid said.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>This could be, but then why do we never see headcrab mortars dropping the obviously more deadly fast and poison headcrab types, but find them in relative abundance throughout the headcrab population?</p>
<p>I suppose one conclusion could be that the only times we see the combine using headcrab mortars is when launching them at the aquaducts to flush out resistance members in the city, and they’d probably prefer using the more controllable standard headcrab so that this population they’re creating is easily managed once it (presumably) infests the areas.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>You said it yourself: they don’t seem to cooperate. This is a proof that they are not a colony, therefore they are not an ant-like society!</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Socially, no, they are not like the more obvious antlions. But then again, what exactly are the behavioural differences between antlions and headcrabs? In both cases members of the species can be observed attacking threats together, both live in abundant numbers within the same environment with no observable competition or friction between members of the species, etc. The only essential difference between antlions  and headcrabs is that antlions can modify their environment through the creation of tunnels and chambers and whatnot whereas headcrabs seem completely content living in whatever environment they happen to find themselves in.</p>
<p>Of course it is entirely possible that the gonarch does spew out different types of headcrab, it’s not like we were able to observe the Gonarch in its natural environment for a long period of time.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>I think Valve just didn’t care for it and just wanted different types of headcrabs for gameplay values.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>shhhhhhhh, i’m trying to apply scientific explanations to arbitrary fantasy design choices here, tyvm.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/the-life-of-a-headcrab/3561/18">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/the-life-of-a-headcrab/3561/18</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 29 Mar 2010 15:25:54 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3561-18</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/the-life-of-a-headcrab/3561.rss">The life of a Headcrab</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The life of a Headcrab</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[QuakerMan]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Doedel">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/d/c68b51/40.png" class="avatar"> Doedel:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I think all headcrabs are members of the same species in various states of development.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Maybe you’re right, maybe not. Sometimes the same specie allows vastly different phenotypes, but I can’t find any argument that can refute or prove this theory</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Doedel">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/d/c68b51/40.png" class="avatar"> Doedel:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>if these plentiful headgrabs would each (naturally) grow into a gonarch equipped with similar reproductive powers then the population explosion would be absolutely immense</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Not at all: sea turtles use to make hundreds of eggs, but only a few animals are effectively able to become adults.<br>
I suppose that headcrabs are like turtles or snakes for our environment: they are predators of lesser animals, but they are still quite at the bottom of the food chain</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Doedel">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/d/c68b51/40.png" class="avatar"> Doedel:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Headcrab social organization is hard to determine, but is likely similar to native social insect species such as ants.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Doedel">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/d/c68b51/40.png" class="avatar"> Doedel:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>However, beyond this there does not appear to be any form of social interaction or unification between headcrabs. When multiple headcrabs exist in the same environment they almost completely ignore one another, and will pursue prey in an individualistic manner. This is contrary to the behaviour of other social insects who live, work, build, forage and hunt as one community with each member playing specific roles to a greater end.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>You said it yourself: they don’t seem to cooperate. This is a proof that they are not a colony, therefore they are not an ant-like society!<br>
Maybe, for gameplay reasons, we can’t see headcrabs cooperate but at the present state we can assume they simply don’t</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/the-life-of-a-headcrab/3561/17">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/the-life-of-a-headcrab/3561/17</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 29 Mar 2010 13:46:46 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3561-17</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/the-life-of-a-headcrab/3561.rss">The life of a Headcrab</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The life of a Headcrab</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[baconeggs]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Muhb">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/m/ee7513/40.png" class="avatar"> Muhb:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I personally never thought that headcrabs were capable of maturing into a later stage in their “regular” development (like a gonarch, or whatever) once they had attached to a host, though.  I always figured that zombification was an irreversible, one-way process (for human and headcrab alike…)</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>For what I can see with the gonome’s mutation I hypothesised that the host’s body was used as “building material” for the gonarch’s form.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/the-life-of-a-headcrab/3561/16">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/the-life-of-a-headcrab/3561/16</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 29 Mar 2010 12:18:31 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3561-16</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/the-life-of-a-headcrab/3561.rss">The life of a Headcrab</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The life of a Headcrab</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[ManlyStump]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I always thought it went Baby Headcrab =&gt; Headcrab =&gt; Gonarch =&gt; G-Man</p>
<p>Bet none of you thought G-Man would be the final FINAL evolutionary step of the headcrab did you!</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/the-life-of-a-headcrab/3561/15">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/the-life-of-a-headcrab/3561/15</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 29 Mar 2010 11:18:53 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3561-15</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/the-life-of-a-headcrab/3561.rss">The life of a Headcrab</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The life of a Headcrab</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[mrfohlin]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="awsgames">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/a/a3d4f5/40.png" class="avatar"> awsgames:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I love the idea of poison and fast gonarchs.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Splendid answer \o/</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/the-life-of-a-headcrab/3561/14">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/the-life-of-a-headcrab/3561/14</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 29 Mar 2010 10:12:35 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3561-14</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/the-life-of-a-headcrab/3561.rss">The life of a Headcrab</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The life of a Headcrab</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Muhb]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>An interesting theory. Only problem I see is that of the beak disappearing during the fast headcrab stage (something I honestly hadn’t even noticed until it was brought up here, good catch guys… guess I was always preoccupied with filling those freaks full of holes  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=9" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"> ).</p>
<p>Personally I was under the impression while playing that the variations were simply genetically modified by the combine, like Ramirezoid said.  I also figured that regular headcrabs, assuming they don’t manage to attach to a host (or die prematurely) would inevitably develop into a gonarch eventually.  Although I kind of like your queen ant analogy, maybe most headcrabs simply aren’t born to become gonarchs. Would make sense.</p>
<p>I personally never thought that headcrabs were capable of maturing into a later stage in their “regular” development (like a gonarch, or whatever) once they had attached to a host, though.  I always figured that zombification was an irreversible, one-way process (for human and headcrab alike…)</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/the-life-of-a-headcrab/3561/13">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/the-life-of-a-headcrab/3561/13</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 29 Mar 2010 06:52:33 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3561-13</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/the-life-of-a-headcrab/3561.rss">The life of a Headcrab</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
