<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>&quot;The Perfect Game&quot;</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/the-perfect-game/3041</link>
    <description>Hey! 

 Just curious about this, but I&#39;m interested into what your guys&#39; dream games are. If you were given the chance to wish a video game, it comes true; what would it be like? It can be anything, no limits. I&#39;ll be happy to share mine later, but I&#39;m in a rush.  :wink:  

 Thanks.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 28 Feb 2010 19:42:40 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Technology and Gaming</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/the-perfect-game/3041.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>&quot;The Perfect Game&quot;</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Ajax]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I didn’t play much, but the little I did play, I played like a stealth game. I didn’t play it again because it didn’t impress me that much.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/the-perfect-game/3041/108">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/the-perfect-game/3041/108</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 28 Feb 2010 19:42:40 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3041-108</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/the-perfect-game/3041.rss">&quot;The Perfect Game&quot;</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>&quot;The Perfect Game&quot;</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[JohnKiller118]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Ajax">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/a/a87d85/40.png" class="avatar"> Ajax:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>No first-person cutscenes, though. <span class="bbcode-b">And from what little I’ve played</span>, it’s not that great.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>:hmph:</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/the-perfect-game/3041/107">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/the-perfect-game/3041/107</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 28 Feb 2010 19:41:19 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3041-107</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/the-perfect-game/3041.rss">&quot;The Perfect Game&quot;</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>&quot;The Perfect Game&quot;</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Ajax]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I DID play it like a stealth game. Stop assuming things. And holding down a button to view some parts of a cutscene in first person does not make it a first-person cutscene. It’s a third person cutscene with a first person alternate perspective.</p>
<p>A full first-person cutscene example would be Crysis or F.E.A.R. 2: Project Origin.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/the-perfect-game/3041/106">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/the-perfect-game/3041/106</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 28 Feb 2010 19:24:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3041-106</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/the-perfect-game/3041.rss">&quot;The Perfect Game&quot;</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>&quot;The Perfect Game&quot;</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[JohnKiller118]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Ajax">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/a/a87d85/40.png" class="avatar"> Ajax:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>No first-person cutscenes, though.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>There are times where you can hold down R1 and you’ll see things from Snake’s perspective.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Ajax">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/a/a87d85/40.png" class="avatar"> Ajax:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>And from what little I’ve played, it’s not that great.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Stop killing people and play it like a stealth game.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/the-perfect-game/3041/105">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/the-perfect-game/3041/105</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 28 Feb 2010 15:50:06 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3041-105</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/the-perfect-game/3041.rss">&quot;The Perfect Game&quot;</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>&quot;The Perfect Game&quot;</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Ajax]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>No first-person cutscenes, though. And from what little I’ve played, it’s not that great.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/the-perfect-game/3041/104">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/the-perfect-game/3041/104</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 28 Feb 2010 14:55:58 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3041-104</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/the-perfect-game/3041.rss">&quot;The Perfect Game&quot;</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>&quot;The Perfect Game&quot;</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[JohnKiller118]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="SeriesOfTubes">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/s/ecae2f/40.png" class="avatar"> SeriesOfTubes:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Seriously, I like any game that has multiplayer that will keep me playing, a single player that will make you play again after you beat it. and it has to look as real as possible, almost like if the character was you and you are in the game at this moment, posting on this forum. I also like first person cut scenes to see it in the character’s eyes.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p><a href="https://img121.imageshack.us/i/24017272751494dd5c2f.jpg/" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener"><span alt="" class="broken-image" title="This image is broken"><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-unlink svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#unlink"></use></svg></span></a><br>
This game comes to mind.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/the-perfect-game/3041/103">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/the-perfect-game/3041/103</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 28 Feb 2010 14:37:12 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3041-103</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/the-perfect-game/3041.rss">&quot;The Perfect Game&quot;</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>&quot;The Perfect Game&quot;</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[SeriesOfTubes]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><span alt="" class="broken-image" title="This image is broken"><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-unlink svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#unlink"></use></svg></span><br>
TEH BEST GAEM EVAR!:retard:</p>
<p>Seriously, I like any game that has multiplayer that will keep me playing, a single player that will make you play again after you beat it. and it has to look as real as possible, almost like if the character was you and you are in the game at this moment, posting on this forum. I also like first person cut scenes to see it in the character’s eyes.<br>
If story was concerned, then it would be like this:</p>
<p>In the year 2025, you are in a city of no freedom, it’s basically anarchy. All major corporations and government powers are dubbed unfair and tyrannical according to the common people. No one decided to change the system (or RIP THE SYSTEM  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/smiley.png?v=9" title=":smiley:" class="emoji" alt=":smiley:"> ) so a small group of assassins were united to take out the corporations and the government. The assassins are like the runners on mirror’s edge, but they are not pussies that don’t use guns, they actually HAVE A MOTHERFUCKIN ARSENAL OF GUNS AND THEY ARE NOT AFRAID TO GO ON THE STREETS BITCH! They can also manipulate movement, such as when they shoot a gun, they can curve the bullet (like from Wanted) and kill multiple enemies, but you only have one bullet. The ability to go into a Corporation’s main lobby, pull out 2 Uzis and take out everyone sounds quite awesome to me.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/the-perfect-game/3041/102">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/the-perfect-game/3041/102</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 28 Feb 2010 06:51:38 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3041-102</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/the-perfect-game/3041.rss">&quot;The Perfect Game&quot;</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>&quot;The Perfect Game&quot;</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Orpheon]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><img src="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/original/2X/e/ea2c19d3deaa25f2ee7630ef662b1469b35ff70b.png" alt="" data-base62-sha1="xpAdfRxHComB8IZgDFYoyquFZ11" width="300" height="250"></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/the-perfect-game/3041/101">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/the-perfect-game/3041/101</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 28 Feb 2010 06:40:49 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3041-101</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/the-perfect-game/3041.rss">&quot;The Perfect Game&quot;</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>&quot;The Perfect Game&quot;</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Ajax]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Another example of what would be my perfect game would be a war-based action shooter. Not exactly accurate, maybe use it as a play on gaming itself, having the different armies representing online gaming clans, and making the game basically an online tactical clan war, even in the singleplayer story.</p>
<p>You join a clan, and it puts you through a series of basic training tests, then through shooting tests, and using these results, it determines if you are better placed in the “Assault” platoon, where you move from place to place, high-speed, low-drag, attacking enemy positions, and being general-use grunts. In the “Defence” platoon, where you move in after the Assault teams have cleared an area and secure it, or stay at the base and defend certain areas, or even provide escort for a moving Assault convoy. Or in the “Recon” platoon, where you are either in small numbered squads scouting the areas, or, if you’re a good shot, get placed in a scout/sniper squad, and deploy with only one dude helping you to either scout an area, or eliminate one specific foe. There is also a fourth platoon, but you can’t join it immediately, called “Spec Ops.” They do EVERYTHING, and they do it in seemingly-impossible situations and scenarios. The player can join it, but they have to be real good to join, and prove themselves worthy. Rarely do the Spec Ops deploy into a combat zone with more than four people.</p>
<p>Then you meet your squad, a randomly selected group of 8-10 men and women that will help you through the first few missions. These people can be killed at any point, and HEAVY scripting for on-base AI would be needed to make sure that every death is an emotional one, and every replacement is treated differently, depending on how good the replacement is, the replacement’s personality, the deceased’s personality, the deceased’s speciality, how good the deceased was, and how the deceased died, AND the squad members’ relationship with the deceased. And ALL squads, even the ones that the player is not a part of, would have this enabled, creating a living, breathing unit.</p>
<p>The game would start off with roughly 90 people in your unit, and by the end would have grown to 300 men and women. At the beginning you have small numbers of people and limited vehicles and supplies, so everything counts. You lose points for every bullet fired (but a hit is worth three points, and a kill is worth 10). You’re engaged in a series of small-scale skirmishes with smaller clans until your unit’s rising star gains the attention of one of three big-name clans. They begin to target your clan, and one of the other big clans, the one already in a war with the one that attacked you, decides to lend a hand. Eventually, all three big clans, and your clan, all are engaged in a VERY large war. The smaller clans may, under certain conditions, even ally with you in your fight. This all leads up into, depending how the game goes, a MASSIVE offensive against the enemy command centers with you and your allies, or a covert offensive with limited supplies and personel in your clan.</p>
<p>You can also rank up in your unit. You start as a Private, where you are just following orders. You can then be made a Corporal, where you are given command of a fire team, and that adds a strategy basis in the game, making in Ghost Recon-esque. At Sargeant, you’re given command of the entire squad, and can either micromanage the other fireteam, or give the fireteam general orders and let them run otherwise autonimously while you run your fireteam. Next, Master Sargeant gives you command of two squads, controlling them in either a Full Spectrum Warrior sort of interface, or an RTS-type interface. And it keeps going until you can become the leader of the ENTIRE unit. You can be demoted, as well, and there is no garantee that you will get promoted. It would be entirely possible to remain a Private until the end of the game.</p>
<p>The game would also have a “character bank” of roughly 1200 characters. These are basically just basic profiles to pull from (Such as Voice Type, Pitch, Specialty…the sort of things that would define the basics of a char, but not flesh out the whole thing, that is in a seperate bank with more limited options, like region of origin, and stuff…with gender decided from the model randomly selected to be used), and with 2000 faces (made similarly to Black Mesa’s face creation system) to pull from, would ensure that no two squads are ever alike in look or behavior. Basically, making a modular AI system that controlls only a couple aspect of the character, then letting other AI aspect modules form other parts of the AI system…leading to roughly 10 AI modules with up to three of four things decided upon by that module alone. No two playthoughs are ever alike at that point, then.</p>
<p>No such system is in place for any of the other clans, though. No need. Very little, if any character-based AI is shown through anything but dialogue and basic actions and behaviors (Like reaction to someone getting attacked, reactions to ambushes, deaths, and squad placement [a couple in a ‘relationship’ may take adjacent spots in formation, for example], but actual combat and movement AI is universal). Character behavios for squads that are not the player squads would not have character AI activated on a mission unless it is an important group, or the group is in downtime.</p>
<p>And all of that is just single player. In multiplayer you have your standard Deathmatch, Team Deathmatch, Capture the Flag, Capture the Bases, Objective Assault, and Us-Against-The-Horde type game modes, but you also have stuff like Squad Deathmatch and Unit Deathmatch, where it’s like Deathmatch/Team Deathmatch, but each person is in control of a fireteam, thus quadrupuling the amount of firepower you can lay down on the enemy. You also have a full co-op campaign that runs side-by-side with the main one (possibly a prologue?), and Convoy Assault/Defence, where one team is tasked with destroying a mobile Convoy while the other team has to defend said convoy.</p>
<p>Obviously, the game would have clan support, and you would be able to select your clan’s own standard gear (individual players can customise their weapon loadouts if you give them permission to), and select who is in what unit (Assault, Defence, Recon, Spec Ops), and make your own camoflague and unit insignia.</p>
<p>This would give us a realistic modern warfare game, without any actual modern countries or conflicts, without any country getting offended, and without any politics getting in the way.</p>
<p>EDIT:<br>
I forgot a couple things…<br>
First, a single player skirmish mode. This mode would allow the player to craft his own missions, as simple or as complex as they might be. They can choose from any map in the game (default or custom) and allow inexperianced creators to create complex campaigns with simple controls. These missions can be saved and exported to be shared with the online community. The player can decide if he or she wants to be in control of an entire faction, lead a squad, fireteam…basically, they get to pick the rank they play at during the mission.</p>
<p>Secondly, I left out a key gaming element from the multiplay listings. I forgot to add that there would be RTS-style Campaign Missions, where the players must command their unit to complete certain objectives before the opponant(s) do(es)…Attack/Defend, where one person is under attack and it’s up to him and his team (if there are more than two people in the server) to withstand the attack. Covert Defence, where one player is in RTS view, and has to defend him(her)self from up to five Spec Ops teams commanded by other players. High Command, where one player on each team is in RTS view and everyone else is in First Person view, and they have to capture differing objectives, or assault the other team, or a variety of mission objectives.</p>
<p>Every single player map would be avalable in Multiplayer, even the ones the player did not see. The various platoons all have a completely different set of campaign missions, and they are so varied based on mission preformance that you will never play all the maps in one campaign, though you may play one or two maps more than once.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/the-perfect-game/3041/100">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/the-perfect-game/3041/100</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 27 Feb 2010 16:36:46 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3041-100</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/the-perfect-game/3041.rss">&quot;The Perfect Game&quot;</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>&quot;The Perfect Game&quot;</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Orpheon]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Mastershot, that was an amazing game.</p>
<p>Wafflewarrior, you just reminded me: I really want a remake of Jet Force Gemini. But unfortunately I doubt thats likely.  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/frowning.png?v=9" title=":frowning:" class="emoji" alt=":frowning:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/the-perfect-game/3041/99">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/the-perfect-game/3041/99</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 27 Feb 2010 07:09:07 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3041-99</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/the-perfect-game/3041.rss">&quot;The Perfect Game&quot;</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>&quot;The Perfect Game&quot;</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[JohnKiller118]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>The perfect game, is…<br>
<a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Zk_OxVqNCzg&amp;NR=1&amp;feature=fvwp" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Zk_OxVqNCzg&amp;NR=1&amp;feature=fvwp</a></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/the-perfect-game/3041/98">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/the-perfect-game/3041/98</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 27 Feb 2010 04:05:33 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3041-98</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/the-perfect-game/3041.rss">&quot;The Perfect Game&quot;</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>&quot;The Perfect Game&quot;</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[CTID]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="X_Mastershot_X">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/x/c5a1d2/40.png" class="avatar"> X_Mastershot_X:</div>
<blockquote>
<p><a href="https://www.newgrounds.com/portal/view/467574" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://www.newgrounds.com/portal/view/467574</a> : The perfect game</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Holy shit that kicked ass.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/the-perfect-game/3041/97">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/the-perfect-game/3041/97</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 27 Feb 2010 04:02:19 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3041-97</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/the-perfect-game/3041.rss">&quot;The Perfect Game&quot;</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>&quot;The Perfect Game&quot;</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Kairouseki]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>A longer version of Heavy Rain with many many more choices and you play it by mimicking the motions with your entire body.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/the-perfect-game/3041/96">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/the-perfect-game/3041/96</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 27 Feb 2010 02:40:56 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3041-96</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/the-perfect-game/3041.rss">&quot;The Perfect Game&quot;</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>&quot;The Perfect Game&quot;</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[JohnKiller118]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I’m sorry. I started this mess by posting <span class="bbcode-i">“Ocarina of Time”</span> as my perfect game.<br>
This thread had great potential.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/the-perfect-game/3041/95">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/the-perfect-game/3041/95</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 26 Feb 2010 21:11:28 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3041-95</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/the-perfect-game/3041.rss">&quot;The Perfect Game&quot;</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>&quot;The Perfect Game&quot;</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Zachy_180]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Ajax">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/a/a87d85/40.png" class="avatar"> Ajax:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>My perfect game…hmmm…</p>
<p>I have a lot of ideas, but my main two are a zombie apocalypse shooter with a full open-ended fully-destructable city…with a wide variety of cities to choose from. Zombies that be in groups as small as 5 or as large as 1000. The game would start like a Zombie Sim, with only a handfull of zombies and a lot of humans, but slowly and surely the zombies begin overpowering the humans…basically Zombie Panic: Source in a Grand Theft Auto scale, with the destructiveness of Red Faction Guerilla and The Force Unleashed (Though the destroyed buildings and rubble doesn’t dissapear, it just stays there, being in the way, so you have to mold your tactics), and a complexity of human group behavior that allows them to make and form groups, wander the city, fight or flee zombies, create safehouses, call for help, and do a wide variety of other activities all without any scripting whatsoever. All of this on a game engine that is either the Source engine (impossible, I know), the UT3 Engine, CryEngine 2 or 3, Real Virtuality 3, or an engine developed with all the desired features from the previous engines.</p>
<p>I’ll post my other idea later.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>At least someone here can follow directions; thus, playing the game correctly.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/the-perfect-game/3041/94">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/the-perfect-game/3041/94</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 26 Feb 2010 20:50:12 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3041-94</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/the-perfect-game/3041.rss">&quot;The Perfect Game&quot;</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>&quot;The Perfect Game&quot;</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Mr.Shadow]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Half-Life and Oblivion are the 2 perfect games.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/the-perfect-game/3041/93">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/the-perfect-game/3041/93</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 26 Feb 2010 16:02:32 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3041-93</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/the-perfect-game/3041.rss">&quot;The Perfect Game&quot;</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>&quot;The Perfect Game&quot;</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[xalener]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>That was fucking awesome.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/the-perfect-game/3041/92">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/the-perfect-game/3041/92</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 26 Feb 2010 15:58:02 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3041-92</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/the-perfect-game/3041.rss">&quot;The Perfect Game&quot;</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>&quot;The Perfect Game&quot;</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[JohnKiller118]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="X_Mastershot_X">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/x/c5a1d2/40.png" class="avatar"> X_Mastershot_X:</div>
<blockquote>
<p><a href="https://www.newgrounds.com/portal/view/467574" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://www.newgrounds.com/portal/view/467574</a> : The perfect game</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>That was incredible.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/the-perfect-game/3041/91">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/the-perfect-game/3041/91</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 26 Feb 2010 14:38:11 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3041-91</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/the-perfect-game/3041.rss">&quot;The Perfect Game&quot;</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>&quot;The Perfect Game&quot;</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[X_Mastershot_X]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><a href="https://www.newgrounds.com/portal/view/467574" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://www.newgrounds.com/portal/view/467574</a> : The perfect game</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/the-perfect-game/3041/90">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/the-perfect-game/3041/90</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 26 Feb 2010 14:31:22 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3041-90</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/the-perfect-game/3041.rss">&quot;The Perfect Game&quot;</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>&quot;The Perfect Game&quot;</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Neon_Impulse]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>oh, the perfect game? it’s already been made… I don’t what it’s called, it’s either daikatana or ET: the game…</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/the-perfect-game/3041/89">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/the-perfect-game/3041/89</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 25 Feb 2010 23:49:43 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3041-89</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/the-perfect-game/3041.rss">&quot;The Perfect Game&quot;</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>&quot;The Perfect Game&quot;</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[SoaringScout]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><div class="lightbox-wrapper"><a class="lightbox" href="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/original/2X/3/3b9f5bae529ff9e830e3b8a6fc4711a7becf99de.jpeg" data-download-href="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/3b9f5bae529ff9e830e3b8a6fc4711a7becf99de" title=""><img src="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/optimized/2X/3/3b9f5bae529ff9e830e3b8a6fc4711a7becf99de_2_349x500.jpeg" alt="" data-base62-sha1="8vrAPeiWA3pMQvKWSxImJ1m7Eku" width="349" height="500" srcset="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/optimized/2X/3/3b9f5bae529ff9e830e3b8a6fc4711a7becf99de_2_349x500.jpeg, https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/optimized/2X/3/3b9f5bae529ff9e830e3b8a6fc4711a7becf99de_2_523x750.jpeg 1.5x, https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/optimized/2X/3/3b9f5bae529ff9e830e3b8a6fc4711a7becf99de_2_698x1000.jpeg 2x" data-small-upload="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/optimized/2X/3/3b9f5bae529ff9e830e3b8a6fc4711a7becf99de_2_10x10.png"><div class="meta"><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-far-image svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#far-image"></use></svg><span class="filename"></span><span class="informations">1024×1463 306 KB</span><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-discourse-expand svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#discourse-expand"></use></svg></div></a></div></p>
<p>and</p>
<p><span alt="" class="broken-image" title="This image is broken"><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-unlink svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#unlink"></use></svg></span></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/the-perfect-game/3041/88">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/the-perfect-game/3041/88</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 25 Feb 2010 23:30:28 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3041-88</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/the-perfect-game/3041.rss">&quot;The Perfect Game&quot;</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>&quot;The Perfect Game&quot;</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[wafflewarrior7]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><span alt="" class="broken-image" title="This image is broken"><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-unlink svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#unlink"></use></svg></span><br>
and<br>
<span alt="" class="broken-image" title="This image is broken"><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-unlink svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#unlink"></use></svg></span><br>
and<br>
<span alt="" class="broken-image" title="This image is broken"><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-unlink svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#unlink"></use></svg></span><br>
and<br>
<img src="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/original/2X/a/a6a9dc873f47e3cf7c0f9034462b28bd665590e1.jpeg" alt="" data-base62-sha1="nMnbz5KgOQqri1oljwWObbJKrnz" width="620" height="433"><br>
and Finnaly,<br>
<span alt="" class="broken-image" title="This image is broken"><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-unlink svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#unlink"></use></svg></span> (zombie panic source)</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/the-perfect-game/3041/87">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/the-perfect-game/3041/87</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 22 Feb 2010 18:33:53 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3041-87</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/the-perfect-game/3041.rss">&quot;The Perfect Game&quot;</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>&quot;The Perfect Game&quot;</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Ajax]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>My perfect game…hmmm…</p>
<p>I have a lot of ideas, but my main two are a zombie apocalypse shooter with a full open-ended fully-destructable city…with a wide variety of cities to choose from. Zombies that be in groups as small as 5 or as large as 1000. The game would start like a Zombie Sim, with only a handfull of zombies and a lot of humans, but slowly and surely the zombies begin overpowering the humans…basically Zombie Panic: Source in a Grand Theft Auto scale, with the destructiveness of Red Faction Guerilla and The Force Unleashed (Though the destroyed buildings and rubble doesn’t dissapear, it just stays there, being in the way, so you have to mold your tactics), and a complexity of human group behavior that allows them to make and form groups, wander the city, fight or flee zombies, create safehouses, call for help, and do a wide variety of other activities all without any scripting whatsoever. All of this on a game engine that is either the Source engine (impossible, I know), the UT3 Engine, CryEngine 2 or 3, Real Virtuality 3, or an engine developed with all the desired features from the previous engines.</p>
<p>I’ll post my other idea later.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/the-perfect-game/3041/86">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/the-perfect-game/3041/86</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 22 Feb 2010 16:48:36 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3041-86</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/the-perfect-game/3041.rss">&quot;The Perfect Game&quot;</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>&quot;The Perfect Game&quot;</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Kairouseki]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>A Call of Cthulhu DCotE sequel made with modern graphics and incredibly terrifying. It should be extremely long too with an incredibly epic story.</p>
<p>Edit: Now that I think about it, they should summon the spirit of Lovecraft to write the story for the game.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/the-perfect-game/3041/85">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/the-perfect-game/3041/85</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 22 Feb 2010 02:55:25 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3041-85</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/the-perfect-game/3041.rss">&quot;The Perfect Game&quot;</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>&quot;The Perfect Game&quot;</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[D4RKN3SS]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Zachy_180">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/z/e495f1/40.png" class="avatar"> Zachy_180:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Hey!</p>
<p>Just curious about this, but I’m interested into what your guys’ dream games are. If you were given the chance to wish a video game, it comes true; what would it be like? It can be anything, no limits. I’ll be happy to share mine later, but I’m in a rush.  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/wink.png?v=9" title=":wink:" class="emoji" alt=":wink:"></p>
<p>Thanks.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>THE ORANGE BOX BUY IT NOW!!!</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/the-perfect-game/3041/84">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/the-perfect-game/3041/84</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 22 Feb 2010 02:45:04 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3041-84</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/the-perfect-game/3041.rss">&quot;The Perfect Game&quot;</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
