<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>UK Riots.</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/uk-riots/7652</link>
    <description>[url=&#39;https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/uk-14449675&#39;]hundreds of people take the the street and smash up shops and houses.[/url] :meh:

Thoughts on the rioters and reasons?</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 09 Sep 2011 13:28:02 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Off Topic</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/uk-riots/7652.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>UK Riots.</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[JayJay]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>tl;dr</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/uk-riots/7652/131">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/uk-riots/7652/131</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Sep 2011 13:28:02 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7652-131</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/uk-riots/7652.rss">UK Riots.</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>UK Riots.</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Mented]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Actually I did follow the majority of the discussion, even if trying to empathise with your nieve mentality and trying to word a reply you might actually have to answer in full, without going off on a self righteous cavalade of psuedo-political gibberish is extremelly irritating.</p>
<p>So for starters we’l begin with you.</p>
<p>Your clearly of quite the high opinion of yourself. Shown by your clear need to denounce others as mouth breathers to validate your own intelectual self worth. Shown time and time again on how you deal with people and their points. You attack the perception you have of people eg. ‘afraid to see the truth’ yet wonder why people get so irritated by you. Your false assumptions fueling their assumptions of your generalising ignornace.</p>
<p>Your also quite the hipocrite, as shown…</p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>Also, your comment is somewhat disrespectful towards the French.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Coming from the guy who opened with…</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Jeannotvb">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/j/90ced4/40.png" class="avatar"> Jeannotvb:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Look at it from the bright side, it’s better to have this then having your city bombed by V1 rockets.</p>
<p>Also lol’d @ “government that looks after us”</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Which in turn is where I brought the ‘conspiracy theorist’ label from. Wording like this only makes me assume you think 9/11 was an inside job. Confirmation please?</p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>That’s how the system remains the way it is, that’s why people thought slavery was ok, that’s why it took so long for the Roman Empire to finally collapse.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>No there were numerous reasons for why those things changed, not for the sole reason of ‘people didn’t know any better’. You can’t go through life with such a generalising view of people, otherwise you’l come to the same idiotic conclussions you already have.</p>
<p>Now, moving on to your view of how criminals should be treated, and in general why the government doesn’t work with its use of force as a means to control.</p>
<p>You start off with a very obvious and simple point in order to ‘prove’ your theory, yet don’t actually come to any conclussion on how to actually go about doing such a thing. Showing your complete lack of deep thought into the subject matter.</p>
<p>So criminals become criminals because of their environment ( I’l agree for the most part, I won’t go into your nievity to believe this as universally applicable ) meaning that before or during your transition to a free market anarcho-capitalist world we would need to end every single source of negativity a child could recieve till its maturity.<br>
This would be ( anarcho-capitalist ) in a world completely devoid of regulation to those who are inherently evil ( something that I’m sorry to tell you, does exist ) in a world created around corporate buisness and ( you’ve admitted ) monopolies. The same world that uses human nature and its arbitrary morality to enforce an unforceful ‘punishment’ that consists of ‘routing out the problem’, which in turn completely negates any responsibility the ‘criminal’ ( or done hard too person in your case ) has.</p>
<p>I’l tell you a few things your utopian theory forgets.</p>
<p>People crave power, groups of people crave more power. Unregulated groups not accountable to a universal set of laws without even the regulations to make sure they do things at least partially by the book ( which reaches through to every aspect of buisness, least of all the way it is required to treate employees ) would in the end innevitably prove disasterous to the progression of the species and society as a whole.</p>
<p>It would be great if people were as kind as they are in your fantasy world, and completely devoid of need at elevating ones own status at the expense of others. Unfortunately for you and your ignorant view of the world, it quite simply isn’t the case. Will to power is just as alive today as it was in Roman times.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>A free market would solve any problem, thousands of times more efficiently than any government could ever do.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>It COULD solve any problem, it doesn’t mean it would, it would do it well, or that it would do it fairly. Which is something our governments at least try and do.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>The free market is more than capable of providing energy when there’s a demand. That’s how a free market works, if there’s demand for something then someone will supply that demand.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>They can also charge what they like for it too.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>He (OD used an extreme example of supposedly anarcho-capitalism being a horrible system, so I used extreme examples of world war two to show the ruthlessness of the state/government.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Your a fucking idiot to even bring up that ‘point’, let alone to actually explain to someone why your doing it without realising how retarded it is.</p>
<p>You would actually argue for an anarcho-capitalist state by arguing against Communist Russia? You could argue against just about anything and bring up Communist Russia as an example of the bad side. Doesn’t make your point any stronger.</p>
<p>Anyway, as for wikipedia…</p>
<p>You constantly refer to it and nothing else, and have in one occasion referred to it because you literally couldn’t put it better, indicating you’ve never heard it put any other way.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>Humans are <span class="bbcode-i">evil</span> by nature? That’s your argument? And I’m the one who has no grasp on human nature? :lol:</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Did I say that? Is that you putting words in my mouth?</p>
<p>Rather ignorant of you to assume such a thing, and rather fucking retarded to completely over look the point I was trying to make.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>You do realize that the <span class="bbcode-i">anarcho</span> part in <span class="bbcode-i">anarcho-capitalism</span> stands for anarchism. Anarchism means [COLOR=‘Red’]no state. You just lost whatever credibility you may have had. Also, please refer to my post where I claimed that a free market would not have monopolies.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>How did I lose any credibility? In what way have I missinterperated anarcho-capitalism?</p>
<p>You only write that because you’ve got nothing else to fall back on. You have no rebuttal so instead attack my understanding of the concept.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>Anyway, I really don’t understand all the fuss towards a free market society with no state. Most of the things would stay the same, except that you remove any government influence on the free market. The things your government ‘takes care of’ can be done through the free market without any need for government. It would be more efficient, and you would truly be free with no leaders, no taxation and so on. Everything is voluntary. Most people like a free market and capitalism, because they know it’s good, but they need to take the next step which is to remove the cancer that is government. Such a society would prosper and create a lot of wealth, just like the USA during the earlier years. Except this time, the government isn’t lurking around the corner like a cancer waiting to feed on wealth through taxation.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>This is by far the most idiotic, ignorant, disjointed, most unsupported, arrogantly diffinitive view of how the world could work I’ve ever heard. You sir live in a complete fantasy world. You have my pity.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="danielsangeo">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/user_avatar/leakfree.org/danielsangeo/40/4347_2.png" class="avatar"> danielsangeo:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>EDIT: Also, yes, private industry could do everything government does. But, why would they do it?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>Supply and demand, this is basic economics.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>[/quote]<br>
Oh wait…</p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>You’re just pulling that out of your ass, I never claimed any of that.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Of course you didn’t, I did. Interesting you go on the defensive, without actually denying it. Intriguing response.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>hurr durrrr</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Oh I’m sorry? Would your response to these PoS who burn down their neighbours cars, houses and entire livelihoods be something along the lines of</p>
<p>‘LOOK WHAT YOU DID! Ok bye! Don’t do it again!’</p>
<p>Because personally I’d have them shot. Humanity simply doesn’t have the time to waste on these people.</p>
<p><span class="mention">@OldDirtyBasdard</span>: Go fuck yourself. Oh sorry, I didn’t realise you were in charge of who gets to say what around here.</p>
<p>Well that was fun. If not a waste of time.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/uk-riots/7652/130">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/uk-riots/7652/130</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Sep 2011 12:50:37 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7652-130</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/uk-riots/7652.rss">UK Riots.</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>UK Riots.</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[DansonDelta40]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="OldDirtyBastard">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/o/dec6dc/40.png" class="avatar"> OldDirtyBastard:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>People aren’t stupid</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Ahahahahahahahahaha!!!</p>
<p>Wrong.</p>
<p><img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/expressionless.png?v=9" title=":expressionless:" class="emoji only-emoji" alt=":expressionless:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/uk-riots/7652/129">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/uk-riots/7652/129</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 27 Aug 2011 12:29:08 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7652-129</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/uk-riots/7652.rss">UK Riots.</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>UK Riots.</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[OldDirtyBastard]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I don’t think they’ll be getting away with that for long. People aren’t stupid</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/uk-riots/7652/128">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/uk-riots/7652/128</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 19 Aug 2011 05:03:51 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7652-128</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/uk-riots/7652.rss">UK Riots.</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>UK Riots.</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[bur]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="OldDirtyBastard">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/o/dec6dc/40.png" class="avatar"> OldDirtyBastard:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I’ll help ya.</p>
<p>What do you think about twitter revolutions in M.East and these two guys getting arrested?</p>
<p>The current state mechanism evolved into something so lame and awkward it’s fucking ridiculous.<br>
And people having 1-day long memory too - they can’t even remember what happened a couple weeks ago. It amazes me how someone up high can change his positions 4 times a day and no one would give a fuck. It’s retarded.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>i think the government isnt even making excuses anymore for its police state policies</p>
<p>the worst thing is that most people seem to approve of it, even call for it</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/uk-riots/7652/127">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/uk-riots/7652/127</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 19 Aug 2011 04:12:21 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7652-127</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/uk-riots/7652.rss">UK Riots.</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>UK Riots.</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[OldDirtyBastard]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>And sorry for that, I know it’s hard when you’re in half and equator around the globe and this shit happens back home.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/uk-riots/7652/126">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/uk-riots/7652/126</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 19 Aug 2011 02:54:31 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7652-126</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/uk-riots/7652.rss">UK Riots.</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>UK Riots.</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[OldDirtyBastard]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I’ll help ya.</p>
<p>What do you think about twitter revolutions in M.East and these two guys getting arrested?</p>
<p>The current state mechanism evolved into something so lame and awkward it’s fucking ridiculous.<br>
And people having 1-day long memory too - they can’t even remember what happened a couple weeks ago. It amazes me how someone up high can change his positions 4 times a day and no one would give a fuck. It’s retarded.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/uk-riots/7652/125">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/uk-riots/7652/125</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 19 Aug 2011 02:50:56 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7652-125</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/uk-riots/7652.rss">UK Riots.</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>UK Riots.</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[OldDirtyBastard]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Sure, darling, play a martyr.<br>
That’s what (not only) I want - more satisfaction from you getting banned.</p>
<p>P.S. And really, we did let you talk. So once again, go fuck yourself, nancy.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/uk-riots/7652/124">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/uk-riots/7652/124</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 19 Aug 2011 02:42:21 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7652-124</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/uk-riots/7652.rss">UK Riots.</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>UK Riots.</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Jeannotvb]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Silencing the competition by force, the way of the state. You complete my work in this thread.</p>
<p><span alt="" class="broken-image" title="This image is broken"><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-unlink svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#unlink"></use></svg></span></p>
<p>[COLOR=‘Black’]That’s you, on the left.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/uk-riots/7652/123">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/uk-riots/7652/123</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 19 Aug 2011 02:33:28 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7652-123</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/uk-riots/7652.rss">UK Riots.</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>UK Riots.</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[OldDirtyBastard]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>voteban your ass for cretinism and derailing threads, cretinism being the piority? [COLOR=‘Black’]I’ll happily go down with you</p>
<p>btw, popular demand, y/n</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/uk-riots/7652/122">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/uk-riots/7652/122</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 19 Aug 2011 02:16:23 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7652-122</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/uk-riots/7652.rss">UK Riots.</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>UK Riots.</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Jeannotvb]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="OldDirtyBastard">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/o/dec6dc/40.png" class="avatar"> OldDirtyBastard:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Fuck off, Jeannot.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>What ya gonna do about it, ape man.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/uk-riots/7652/121">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/uk-riots/7652/121</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 19 Aug 2011 02:13:22 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7652-121</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/uk-riots/7652.rss">UK Riots.</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>UK Riots.</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Rossman]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Oh! Oh! Oh! Let me go and get my pistol and camera!</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/uk-riots/7652/120">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/uk-riots/7652/120</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 19 Aug 2011 01:13:33 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7652-120</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/uk-riots/7652.rss">UK Riots.</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>UK Riots.</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[OldDirtyBastard]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Fuck off, Jeannot.</p>
<p>Mented, it’s your fucking fault too. Do humanity a favor, both of you - find a nine 9mm and shoot yourself in the head.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/uk-riots/7652/119">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/uk-riots/7652/119</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 19 Aug 2011 00:46:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7652-119</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/uk-riots/7652.rss">UK Riots.</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>UK Riots.</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Jeannotvb]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Mented">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/m/9de0a6/40.png" class="avatar"> Mented:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Anyone else amused that a ‘conspiracy theorist’ uses wikipedia as source material?</p>
<p>Anyone else not realise he has no grasp of human nature? Like if we get rid of the evil doers in government they won’t be in the rest of society anyway?</p>
<p>Like these ‘evil’ people would instantly have no power and no means to monopolise things to their own ends in an anarcho-capitalist state? Lol. Whos deluded?</p>
<p>The government is a tool in order to be better organised in a the larger, modern structure of society, regulating the bad seeds in order to let the others flourish. Ridding ourselves of it because of its inevitable problems due to the bad side of human nature is the kind of short sighted mentality that innevitably does more harm then good. As for tax, that is an entirely comparitive topic, comparative to what the taxes are spent on.</p>
<p>I honestly can’t believe this went on for 6 pages. Dude reads a book ( read: Wikipedia ) on an anarchistic form of anti government when he’s a teenager and goes on a self righteous rant. How original.</p>
<p>Rioters should be jailed, looters should be shot.</p>
<p>Sean Locke ( a comedian ) put it best with…<br>
‘I was watching the news and they were interviewing a girl on the streets, she said “Yeah well I iz jus lootin ma taxes bak innit”…<br>
They don’t tax crack you idiot!’</p>
<p>They are opportunistic scum, end of. You want a real discussion, try why the hell have channel 4 put on a series of shows glorifying these people. Adverts for their ‘urban season’ depict thieves running away from police and gangs of self obsessed wannabe gangsters rapping about generally being pricks and how awesome they are for it.</p>
<p>When you start mainstreaming and selling out to these people, then you know things are wrong.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Just when I think it’s getting quite this muppet shows up spouting all his bullshit about me, not reading anything of what has been posted and just comes here to show off how smart he thinks he is. Well I do read a discussion before I partake in it, so here goes (again).</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Mented">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/m/9de0a6/40.png" class="avatar"> Mented:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Anyone else amused that a ‘conspiracy theorist’ uses wikipedia as source material?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I’m not a conspiracy theorist, but please quote any posts I might have made that refer to an existing conspiracy theory. I have never claimed to use Wikipedia as my primary source of information, you’re just pulling that out of your ass. It’s useful for quickly introducing others to a subject without telling them they should just read a few books about it. That’s what encyclopedias are for you know.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Mented">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/m/9de0a6/40.png" class="avatar"> Mented:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Anyone else not realise he has no grasp of human nature? Like if we get rid of the evil doers in government they won’t be in the rest of society anyway?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Humans are <span class="bbcode-i">evil</span> by nature? That’s your argument? And I’m the one who has no grasp on human nature? :lol:</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Mented">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/m/9de0a6/40.png" class="avatar"> Mented:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Like these ‘evil’ people would instantly have no power and no means to monopolise things to their own ends in an <span class="bbcode-b">anarcho-capitalist state</span>? Lol. Whos deluded?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>You do realize that the <span class="bbcode-i">anarcho</span> part in <span class="bbcode-i">anarcho-capitalism</span> stands for anarchism. Anarchism means [COLOR=‘Red’]no state. You just lost whatever credibility you may have had. Also, please refer to my post where I claimed that a free market would not have monopolies.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Mented">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/m/9de0a6/40.png" class="avatar"> Mented:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>The government is a tool in order to be better organised in a the larger, modern structure of society, regulating the bad seeds in order to let the others flourish. Ridding ourselves of it because of its inevitable problems due to the bad side of human nature is the kind of short sighted mentality that innevitably does more harm then good. As for tax, that is an entirely comparitive topic, comparative to what the taxes are spent on.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>How nice of you to show your opinion, unfortunately all of this has already been talked about by ODB and I. If you don’t want to read it because it’s boring, fine, just don’t come in here trying to look like a smartass to those who haven’t read the thread.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Mented">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/m/9de0a6/40.png" class="avatar"> Mented:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I honestly can’t believe this went on for 6 pages. Dude reads a book ( read: Wikipedia ) on an anarchistic form of anti government when he’s a teenager and goes on a self righteous rant. How original.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>You’re just pulling that out of your ass, I never claimed any of that.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Mented">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/m/9de0a6/40.png" class="avatar"> Mented:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Rioters should be jailed, looters should be shot.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>hurr durrrr :retard:</p>
<ul>
<li>
</li></ul>
<p>What a disappointment. :facepalm:</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/uk-riots/7652/118">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/uk-riots/7652/118</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 18 Aug 2011 17:47:21 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7652-118</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/uk-riots/7652.rss">UK Riots.</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>UK Riots.</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[bur]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>what you mean to say is, those who are intellectually lazy can’t read through this thread through and understand it completely</p>
<p>or, more accurately, those who recognize that discussions on this forum are pretty stupid and pointless will read this thread through</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/uk-riots/7652/117">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/uk-riots/7652/117</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 18 Aug 2011 12:37:30 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7652-117</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/uk-riots/7652.rss">UK Riots.</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>UK Riots.</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[calhoun_freeman]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>No one who is not interested in politics/human nature/complex discussions/UK can read this thread through and understand it completely.</p>
<p>Too much text.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/uk-riots/7652/116">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/uk-riots/7652/116</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 18 Aug 2011 11:36:01 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7652-116</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/uk-riots/7652.rss">UK Riots.</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>UK Riots.</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Mented]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Anyone else amused that a ‘conspiracy theorist’ uses wikipedia as source material?</p>
<p>Anyone else not realise he has no grasp of human nature? Like if we get rid of the evil doers in government they won’t be in the rest of society anyway?</p>
<p>Like these ‘evil’ people would instantly have no power and no means to monopolise things to their own ends in an anarcho-capitalist state? Lol. Whos deluded?</p>
<p>The government is a tool in order to be better organised in a the larger, modern structure of society, regulating the bad seeds in order to let the others flourish. Ridding ourselves of it because of its inevitable problems due to the bad side of human nature is the kind of short sighted mentality that innevitably does more harm then good. As for tax, that is an entirely comparitive topic, comparative to what the taxes are spent on.</p>
<p>I honestly can’t believe this went on for 6 pages. Dude reads a book ( read: Wikipedia ) on an anarchistic form of anti government when he’s a teenager and goes on a self righteous rant. How original.</p>
<p>Rioters should be jailed, looters should be shot.</p>
<p>Sean Locke ( a comedian ) put it best with…<br>
‘I was watching the news and they were interviewing a girl on the streets, she said “Yeah well I iz jus lootin ma taxes bak innit”…<br>
They don’t tax crack you idiot!’</p>
<p>They are opportunistic scum, end of. You want a real discussion, try why the hell have channel 4 put on a series of shows glorifying these people. Adverts for their ‘urban season’ depict thieves running away from police and gangs of self obsessed wannabe gangsters rapping about generally being pricks and how awesome they are for it.</p>
<p>When you start mainstreaming and selling out to these people, then you know things are wrong.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/uk-riots/7652/115">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/uk-riots/7652/115</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 18 Aug 2011 09:14:03 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7652-115</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/uk-riots/7652.rss">UK Riots.</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>UK Riots.</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Mont_Blanc]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>So, is it done ? Can we travel safely to see the Olympic games ?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/uk-riots/7652/114">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/uk-riots/7652/114</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 16 Aug 2011 18:07:13 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7652-114</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/uk-riots/7652.rss">UK Riots.</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>UK Riots.</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[jerry]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Didn’t BART also jam up cellphone signals without a warrant?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/uk-riots/7652/113">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/uk-riots/7652/113</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 16 Aug 2011 16:25:06 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7652-113</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/uk-riots/7652.rss">UK Riots.</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>UK Riots.</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[thomas_c]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I’m not going to read up on all that’s been said in this here thread, but this article raises quite a few points that are not just valid/of importance in Britain:<br>
<a href="https://kenanmalik.wordpress.com/2011/08/12/moral-poverty-and-the-riots/#more-2640" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://kenanmalik.wordpress.com/2011/08/12/moral-poverty-and-the-riots/#more-2640</a><br>
Most importantly “the introduction of the market ethos into every area of life”.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/uk-riots/7652/112">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/uk-riots/7652/112</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 16 Aug 2011 16:13:18 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7652-112</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/uk-riots/7652.rss">UK Riots.</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>UK Riots.</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Scrue]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Medevilae">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/m/aca169/40.png" class="avatar"> Medevilae:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>It’s a US thing.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>No it’s not. We have it here in the UK</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/uk-riots/7652/111">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/uk-riots/7652/111</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 12 Aug 2011 15:45:27 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7652-111</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/uk-riots/7652.rss">UK Riots.</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>UK Riots.</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Medevilae]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="SassyRobot">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 SassyRobot:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I don’t actually remember having a Black History Month at school in England.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>It’s a US thing.</p>
<p>But yeah racial tension will remain regardless of how well we know the past. Simply and vaguely put, people’s differences are the cause of most if not all of the worlds problems.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/uk-riots/7652/110">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/uk-riots/7652/110</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 12 Aug 2011 14:46:23 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7652-110</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/uk-riots/7652.rss">UK Riots.</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>UK Riots.</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Scrue]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I’m not too sure how it will effect people as I don’t have a vast knowledge of the benefit system, though I would like to see any convicted rioters to have any privileges taken away.<br>
As a young person who has recently just come out of the education system I have been to school with the type of people who make up most of the riot mob and I feel like most of them don’t understand that if you actually pay attention in school and focus on what you want to become in the long term then just thinking you should be entitled to everything with no price.</p>
<p>The way the “badman” thing works is that the more people are scared of you and the more you show disregard towards the authorities, or people who in normal society are seen as people with most respect and control, then the more badman you are. There is an easy way of combating this, show them that you aren’t scared and they have no control over you. where as normal society works off respect the grime scene works of fear and this has to stop. Schools need to be more hard in punishment.</p>
<p>My school I feel was not at all good at punishment. I was bullied for quite some time quite severely and the bullies got nothing more then a “oh don’t do that again” while a boy who slashed another student with a razor blade got excluded for a mere month.</p>
<p>These people need to be shown while young that you cannot rule with fear.</p>
<p>I would also like to shoot down the argument that for black youths, there are no role models. As if role models are race specific. But if we keep saying that “it’s because there’s no one for black youth” Then we’re just making the gap between races ever more prevalent. I also think that black history month needs to be taken away and black history to be woven into the rest of the year. In black history month, we learn about the american civil rights movement, which I know is a huge part of world history, however we only need to cover this subject once. Black history month simply does nothing do help ease racial tension in schools.</p>
<p>I feel that teachers could help make students understand what they have done wrong and why. Many times I have seen a student do something wrong and a teacher call them out for it but not actually say what they did wrong, this confuses the student and can make the student feel discriminated (no matter the race or background).</p>
<p>Not that any of this justifies looting and rioting, it’s only suggestions of how to prevent people thinking they can just mess up the town because it’s the fault of everyone else.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/uk-riots/7652/109">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/uk-riots/7652/109</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 12 Aug 2011 12:41:46 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7652-109</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/uk-riots/7652.rss">UK Riots.</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>UK Riots.</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[bur]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>how about they are tried and convicted just like anyone else that commits a crime?</p>
<p>taking special measures would be very, very wrong</p>
<p>edit: at the ‘take away the benefits’ people</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/uk-riots/7652/108">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/uk-riots/7652/108</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 12 Aug 2011 11:55:50 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7652-108</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/uk-riots/7652.rss">UK Riots.</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>UK Riots.</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[OldDirtyBastard]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="SassyRobot">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 SassyRobot:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I don’t know how you’d put something like this into force though.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Sass, don’t bother, people can’t read, business as usual.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="OldDirtyBastard">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/o/dec6dc/40.png" class="avatar"> OldDirtyBastard:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>good luck with bookkeeping on that one.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/uk-riots/7652/107">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/uk-riots/7652/107</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 12 Aug 2011 11:53:14 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7652-107</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/uk-riots/7652.rss">UK Riots.</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
