<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Two bugs: Bullsquid attack crash and missing soldier textures</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/two-bugs-bullsquid-attack-crash-and-missing-soldier-textures/11360</link>
    <description>I&#39;ve done various searches for information on this first bug, but found nothing.  As the title says, every time I have been attacked by a bullsquid (meaning, whenever its attack actually hits me), I experience an instant CTD (&quot;hl2.exe has stopped working...&quot;).  I assume this may result from a problem with the visual effect that&#39;s supposed to be superimposed over my vision whenever this happens?  In any case, I&#39;ve attached the .mdmp file that was produced when it happened last.

Also, the second issue is that some soldiers seem to be missing/have glitched textures.  For example, some of the soldiers&#39; helmets are just plain white, with only the lighting/shaders working on them, while I&#39;ve seen one or two with blue hands (which looks like a normal map transparency issue).  I&#39;ll admit, I haven&#39;t looked this up, but my main issue was the bullsquid bug, anyway.

EDIT: I checked the integrity of the downloaded archive (all fine), and my DirectX is currently at 9.0 (according to the game, whereas the missing textures are apparently problems in versions before that), so I&#39;m thinking that it&#39;s not a problem with either of those.
&lt;a class=&#39;attachment&#39; href=&#39;/uploads/default/original/2X/9/9faf007a0ae304e94ffa4305be568548a3b09225.mdmp&#39;&gt;hl2_4104_crash_2012_10_6T7_38_34C0.mdmp&lt;/a&gt; (90.3 KB)</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 06 Oct 2012 07:51:44 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>In-game Issues (Mod)</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/two-bugs-bullsquid-attack-crash-and-missing-soldier-textures/11360.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Two bugs: Bullsquid attack crash and missing soldier textures</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Sinndogg]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I’ve done various searches for information on this first bug, but found nothing.  As the title says, every time I have been attacked by a bullsquid (meaning, whenever its attack actually hits me), I experience an instant CTD (“hl2.exe has stopped working…”).  I assume this may result from a problem with the visual effect that’s supposed to be superimposed over my vision whenever this happens?  In any case, I’ve attached the .mdmp file that was produced when it happened last.</p>
<p>Also, the second issue is that some soldiers seem to be missing/have glitched textures.  For example, some of the soldiers’ helmets are just plain white, with only the lighting/shaders working on them, while I’ve seen one or two with blue hands (which looks like a normal map transparency issue).  I’ll admit, I haven’t looked this up, but my main issue was the bullsquid bug, anyway.</p>
<p>EDIT: I checked the integrity of the downloaded archive (all fine), and my DirectX is currently at 9.0 (according to the game, whereas the missing textures are apparently problems in versions before that), so I’m thinking that it’s not a problem with either of those.<br>
<a class="attachment" href="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/original/2X/9/9faf007a0ae304e94ffa4305be568548a3b09225.mdmp">hl2_4104_crash_2012_10_6T7_38_34C0.mdmp</a> (90.3 KB)</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/two-bugs-bullsquid-attack-crash-and-missing-soldier-textures/11360/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/two-bugs-bullsquid-attack-crash-and-missing-soldier-textures/11360/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 06 Oct 2012 07:51:44 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11360-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/two-bugs-bullsquid-attack-crash-and-missing-soldier-textures/11360.rss">Two bugs: Bullsquid attack crash and missing soldier textures</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
