<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>So I want to get a bachelors in a foreign language...</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/so-i-want-to-get-a-bachelors-in-a-foreign-language/7581</link>
    <description>I want to get a bachelors in a foreign language, but the problem is I want to major in accounting and minor in a foreign language. Is it possible to get a bachelors in foreign language while doing this. Secondly I know I want to come out of college wanting to speak a language other than English fluently, but I don&#39;t know what. I was leaning towards Spanish seeing as how I have had more experience in it and it just might become the US&#39;s second language (If not already), or Chinese seeing as how whether we like it or not we&#39;re (Meaning the US) going to be getting really close in the next few years. I&#39;ve studied Chinese over the summer and the language is really easy to learn, its just the drawing of the characters that kills me. Please give concise and constructive feedback.

Thanks</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 28 Jul 2011 22:10:58 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Off Topic</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/so-i-want-to-get-a-bachelors-in-a-foreign-language/7581.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>So I want to get a bachelors in a foreign language...</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Veritas]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>But what language is currently in the most demand? And btw thanks, hadn’t thought of that.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/so-i-want-to-get-a-bachelors-in-a-foreign-language/7581/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/so-i-want-to-get-a-bachelors-in-a-foreign-language/7581/3</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 28 Jul 2011 22:10:58 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7581-3</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/so-i-want-to-get-a-bachelors-in-a-foreign-language/7581.rss">So I want to get a bachelors in a foreign language...</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>So I want to get a bachelors in a foreign language...</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[geekofalltrades]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>ITT: OP wants a degree in unemployment.</p>
<p>If you major in accounting, you will have a bachelor’s in accounting.  The only way to get a B.A. in foreign language is to major in it.  You could double major, but if you apply yourself and your only goal is to speak fluently, then a minor and some strict discipline will serve you just fine.</p>
<p>What you <span class="bbcode-i">don’t</span> want to do is major in foreign language and not major in anything else, because you will end up at the local McDonald’s.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/so-i-want-to-get-a-bachelors-in-a-foreign-language/7581/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/so-i-want-to-get-a-bachelors-in-a-foreign-language/7581/2</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 28 Jul 2011 20:41:13 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7581-2</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/so-i-want-to-get-a-bachelors-in-a-foreign-language/7581.rss">So I want to get a bachelors in a foreign language...</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>So I want to get a bachelors in a foreign language...</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Veritas]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I want to get a bachelors in a foreign language, but the problem is I want to major in accounting and minor in a foreign language. Is it possible to get a bachelors in foreign language while doing this. Secondly I know I want to come out of college wanting to speak a language other than English fluently, but I don’t know what. I was leaning towards Spanish seeing as how I have had more experience in it and it just might become the US’s second language (If not already), or Chinese seeing as how whether we like it or not we’re (Meaning the US) going to be getting really close in the next few years. I’ve studied Chinese over the summer and the language is really easy to learn, its just the drawing of the characters that kills me. Please give concise and constructive feedback.</p>
<p>Thanks</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/so-i-want-to-get-a-bachelors-in-a-foreign-language/7581/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/so-i-want-to-get-a-bachelors-in-a-foreign-language/7581/1</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 28 Jul 2011 20:28:11 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7581-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/so-i-want-to-get-a-bachelors-in-a-foreign-language/7581.rss">So I want to get a bachelors in a foreign language...</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
