<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>ac3d&#39;s Weapon Feedback</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/ac3ds-weapon-feedback/14327</link>
    <description>[b]Crosshair[/b]

[img]https://i.imgur.com/i0LQ3v2.jpg[/img]
* Make the crosshair grow larger during movement and firing to show reduced accuracy (similar to Counter-Strike)
* Make the normal four dash crosshair the default for all weapons
[b]Sprinting[/b]

* Remove the sprint activation sound
* Make weapons sway in the direction the player is sprinting (strafing left or right)
* Make the sprinting animation start straight away
* Make the sprinting animations less graceful and more reacting to the player’s steps hitting the ground
* Sync all animations to the player’s footsteps
[b]Iron Sights[/b]

* Give all appropriate weapons the ability to aim
* Reduce weapon accuracy while moving and aiming
* Make the weapon tilt and sway when moving while aiming
[b]Balance[/b]

* Reduce the accuracy of all appropriate weapons to make aiming a more viable choice
[b]Weapon Models[/b]

* Make all night sights on weapons glow in the dark similar to Half-Life 2
[b]Weapon Functionality[/b]

* Give ability to melee with selected weapon
* Implement a switch fire mode for all appropriate weapons
* Reduce the time from finishing a reload sequence and being able to fire
* Allow all appropriate weapons to keep a round in the chamber when reloading
[b]Player Models[/b]

* Make a first person view model for Gordon with all the appropriate movement animations
* Make animations for swimming
[b]Player Movement[/b]

* Give the ability to prone
* Add toggle crouch option
* Add toggle prone option
[b]Immersion[/b]

* Add option to drop empty clips on the ground when reloading
* Add option to enable realistic reloading, disable magazine pool
[b]Gameplay[/b]

* Increase the amount of crates that spawn ammo or weapons
[b]Crowbar[/b]

* Remove the screen tilting when swinging and hitting an object
* Make a charge swing secondary fire mode
* Implement ability to throw the crowbar, similar to SMOD but less comical, this can be used to knock out NPC’s in one hit
[b]Glock[/b]

[img]https://i.imgur.com/QBzKWTA.png[/img]

* Change the sprinting animation to two hands on the weapon similar to the .357

[img]https://i.imgur.com/6dzFCYn.png[/img]
* Change the alternate fire button to toggle burst fire mode
[b]357[/b]
[img]https://i.imgur.com/4JgNNTM.jpg[/img]

* Center the iron sights position
* Zoom in the weapon while aiming down sights more
* Make the sprinting animations clumsy and more uniform
* Reduce the time to zoom in the fov


[b]MP5[/b]

* Increase fire rate
* Increase short reload time
[b]Shotgun[/b]

* Reduce reload time
* Increase time between firing and pumping
* Reduce time between double firing and pumping
[b]Crossbow[/b]

* Reduce reload time
* Implement a quick animation for pulling back the string for the next arrow
[b]RPG[/b]

* Make the rocket fire instantly
* Reduce/improve the quality of the muzzle flash effect
* Give players the ability to use the scope
* Give the led screen a function e.g. Sensing heat signatures
[b]Tau Cannon[/b]

* Reduce the time between firing shots
* Give the ability to gib NPC’s
[b]Gluon Gun[/b]

* Give the alternate fire a function e.g. Charge
* Give the ability to gib NPC’s instead of the disintegrating effect
* Give the led screen a function e.g. Sensing heat signatures
[b]Hive Hand[/b]

* Reduce the ammo recharge time
* Increase the effectiveness of tracking enemies around corners
[b]Grenade[/b]

* Center the positon of the grenade being thrown more to reduce hitting walls by accident
* Add Half-Life 2’s crouch and roll ability
[b]C4[/b]

* Swap the buttons around for throwing the C4 and detonating
* Increase the delay between detonating and explosion
[b]Trip mine[/b]

* Implement an alternate fire ability to throw the mine in front of the player similar to the grenade, when the mine stops rolling it always activates facing straight up
* Reduce the time from planting and activation
[b]Snark[/b]

* Implement a charge alternate fire, charging increases the throw speed, the snark explodes on impact creating a puff of spore particles which stuns human enemies, similar to Half-Life 2’s Bug bait</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 07 Aug 2015 11:01:14 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>The Cafeteria</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/ac3ds-weapon-feedback/14327.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>ac3d&#39;s Weapon Feedback</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[fury]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>about aiming down sights: I don’t want this feature because it would basicly only be interessting for SMG, pistol and maybe shotgun. You would also need 1 more keybinding (i need all my buttons for direct (faster) weapon switch, fast teamchat and things like dropping weapons etc.) and really it’s not worth it unless they mess up the whole weapon mechanics. Why should I aim down sights if it doesn’t do anything except looking different? The only thing I could imagine would be to replace the suit-zoom with aim-down-sights. This aim feature would not change weapon behaviour, but it would show the sights and give a mini-zoom (maybe about 65 fov). They could do that, but still I don’t really like the idea to be able to zoom in with every weapon. In my opinion it disturbs the weapon balance, because zooming should be exclusive to 357 and crossbow. That’s why I don’t like suit-zoom either. It can get abused by gaussers to hit high range shots easier. So yea… for me aiming down sights in BM would be only a really unneeded gimmick that could affect gameplay in a negative way.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/ac3ds-weapon-feedback/14327/16">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/ac3ds-weapon-feedback/14327/16</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Aug 2015 11:01:14 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14327-16</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/ac3ds-weapon-feedback/14327.rss">ac3d&#39;s Weapon Feedback</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>ac3d&#39;s Weapon Feedback</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[fury]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>The glock is your spawn weapon in MP. It shouldn’t be too strong. If you was able to shoot as fast as you click, the glock needed appropriate bulletspread. This isn’t counter-strike and not wolfenstein either… and seriously… Who likes clickspam? I think the HL1 style firemodes are compfortable and  make sense. Either you shoot slow and precise (primary) or you shoot fast and inaccurate (secondary). In my opinion it could still get tweaked a bit (screenshake, firerate and damage) to become closer to HL1. Because in BMDM you can easily die by close spawnprotected respawners. The MP5 needs adjustments, too. In my opinion both need damage reduction, because MP5 damage is absolutely deadly. In current version of BMDM you mostly do not even need to go for headshots… MP5 recoil should get removed. The MP5 should only have some bulletspread and screenshake to make it less random. In multiplayer the MP5 should get used for spamming shots and tracking the enemies head for maximum damage. The effectivity of this should depend only on the range (because of bulletspread you hit less on high ranges), your mouseaim and your enemies ability to dodge. I am speaking about multiplayer here. For singleplayer mode I think the recoil and higher damage (like now) is fine. I think the current pistol is quite useful in BMSP (mainly against vorts, zombies, headcrabs, bullsquids and houndeyes). Still you shouldn’t use pistol when you have MP5, 357 or crossbow  (unless you have high range, want to shoot very precisely and want to save ammo)…</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/ac3ds-weapon-feedback/14327/15">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/ac3ds-weapon-feedback/14327/15</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Aug 2015 05:30:38 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14327-15</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/ac3ds-weapon-feedback/14327.rss">ac3d&#39;s Weapon Feedback</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>ac3d&#39;s Weapon Feedback</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Slendgy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I do feel that most of the visual changes were valid, and Wolfenstein: The New Order had aim-down sights AND secondary fire modes for most of the weapons by having a toggle fire mode key. And I do think that the glock should fire as fast as you click, and the general consensus is that it should get some sort of change as it’s only useful for killing barnacles after getting other weapons.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/ac3ds-weapon-feedback/14327/14">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/ac3ds-weapon-feedback/14327/14</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Aug 2015 02:10:25 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14327-14</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/ac3ds-weapon-feedback/14327.rss">ac3d&#39;s Weapon Feedback</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>ac3d&#39;s Weapon Feedback</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Dragunov2]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I also wonder why Gordon cannot run WITHOUT the suit!!!???</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/ac3ds-weapon-feedback/14327/13">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/ac3ds-weapon-feedback/14327/13</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jul 2015 21:05:07 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14327-13</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/ac3ds-weapon-feedback/14327.rss">ac3d&#39;s Weapon Feedback</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>ac3d&#39;s Weapon Feedback</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[TextFAMGUY1]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I always love it when people object to me asking them to use <span class="bbcode-i">reasoning</span> in almost entirely subjective feedback. It’s always fun to watch. Here’s why:</p>
<p>I don’t think the Shotgun pump is too slow. I don’t think the MP5 needs a slower reload time or a faster fire rate. I don’t think the Crossbow needs a faster reload.</p>
<p>Where do we go from here? I disagree with most of your balancing suggestions, but if you provide zero reasoning for any of them, there’s literally no argument to be had. I can just disagree. That’s it. Not exactly a productive or useful discussion. Sure, I can go through and point out all the ones I specifically disagree with, but the onus shouldn’t really be on me to decipher feedback like that.</p>
<p>The reason people don’t like the feedback is because it basically amounts to “completely change your core gameplay because reasons.” We’re all for any kind of feedback but you’re asking for a huge amount of work and a nearly completely different game. Realistically, that won’t happen. If you have more precise feedback about the weapon values and mechanics which you are able to explain, I’m all ears.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/ac3ds-weapon-feedback/14327/12">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/ac3ds-weapon-feedback/14327/12</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jul 2015 01:06:36 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14327-12</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/ac3ds-weapon-feedback/14327.rss">ac3d&#39;s Weapon Feedback</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>ac3d&#39;s Weapon Feedback</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[dky.tehkingd.u]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>The .357 is one of the few weapons in the original HL singleplayer that didn’t already have an alternate function. The MP5 already has an alternate function.</p>
<p>In addition, there WAS a zoom feature in HL multiplayer for the .357, so zooming in with it in Black Mesa is not completely out of the question if you want to keep it in faithful style to the original. They simply changed it so that there’s a physically explainable reason for the zoom, i.e. Gordon focusing down on the ironsights, whereas in HL, it was complete magic.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/ac3ds-weapon-feedback/14327/11">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/ac3ds-weapon-feedback/14327/11</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 29 Jul 2015 16:15:35 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14327-11</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/ac3ds-weapon-feedback/14327.rss">ac3d&#39;s Weapon Feedback</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>ac3d&#39;s Weapon Feedback</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[ac3d]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote group-black-mesa-devs" data-username="TextFAMGUY1">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/user_avatar/leakfree.org/textfamguy1/40/4294_2.png" class="avatar"> TextFAMGUY1:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Our game is inspired by Half-Life, not by modern or more realistic shooters.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Then why add aiming down sights to the .357? Seems like a suspiciously <span class="bbcode-b">realistic </span>mechanic to add to the game to me, if you can add that in, I don’t see why you can’t do it for something like the MP5 as well.</p>
<aside class="quote group-black-mesa-devs" data-username="TextFAMGUY1">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/user_avatar/leakfree.org/textfamguy1/40/4294_2.png" class="avatar"> TextFAMGUY1:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Also, for completely subjective judgements like “reduce pump time” for Shotgun, it helps to explain why you think those changes are necessary, rather than just state them like known fact.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I thought it was too slow, there’s a good second after the shotgun has finished kicking back from the double fire where the gun is doing nothing. I can provide more information for my suggestions at your request, but since you’ve already flat out said you’re not going to take <span class="bbcode-b">any</span> of them to heart, I feel very little reason to do so.</p>
<p>Regardless of how some of you have responded, I will continue to provide feedback on Black Mesa because I love the game and feel the need give something back to the developers that could potentially help to improve it, the next will be for the individual chapters.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/ac3ds-weapon-feedback/14327/10">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/ac3ds-weapon-feedback/14327/10</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 29 Jul 2015 15:29:23 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14327-10</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/ac3ds-weapon-feedback/14327.rss">ac3d&#39;s Weapon Feedback</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>ac3d&#39;s Weapon Feedback</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[TextFAMGUY1]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>We won’t be doing any of these, sorry. Our game is inspired by Half-Life, not by modern or more realistic shooters. We have no desire to be more like them.</p>
<p>Also, for completely subjective judgements like “reduce pump time” for Shotgun, it helps to explain why you think those changes are necessary, rather than just state them like known fact.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/ac3ds-weapon-feedback/14327/9">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/ac3ds-weapon-feedback/14327/9</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 29 Jul 2015 11:04:35 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14327-9</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/ac3ds-weapon-feedback/14327.rss">ac3d&#39;s Weapon Feedback</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>ac3d&#39;s Weapon Feedback</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[_rot_fodder]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><img src="https://38.media.tumblr.com/tumblr_lyogi5aHGz1r8g7gyo3_400.gif" alt="" width="400" height="227"></p>
<p>/thread</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/ac3ds-weapon-feedback/14327/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/ac3ds-weapon-feedback/14327/8</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jul 2015 23:34:40 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14327-8</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/ac3ds-weapon-feedback/14327.rss">ac3d&#39;s Weapon Feedback</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>ac3d&#39;s Weapon Feedback</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[vamp]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>at the time of hl1 there was medal of honour on the psone which if im not mistaken allowed ironsights.</p>
<p>Read over this feedback globally, the jest im getting is indeed black mesa black ops.<br>
That sounds horrible to its player base, theres call of duty or battlefield or csgo or whatever if you wish that sort of game.<br>
I would be disgusted and instantly give up on ever playing this game again apart from the single player perhaps.<br>
The other games are great in their own respects I play zombies on COD and I’m legendary eagle on csgo.<br>
I follow that competitive scene and take joy from watching top teams compete their LAN tournaments via stream.<br>
But thats really missing the feel of half-life.</p>
<p>If im bored I might come back here and read again to fish out some good suggestions, there usually are at least a few.</p>
<p>Sorry it just isn’t my cup of tea.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/ac3ds-weapon-feedback/14327/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/ac3ds-weapon-feedback/14327/7</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jul 2015 21:34:37 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14327-7</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/ac3ds-weapon-feedback/14327.rss">ac3d&#39;s Weapon Feedback</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>ac3d&#39;s Weapon Feedback</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Roadkill]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I agree with :</p>
<ul>
<li>swimmig animation<br>
-disabling sprint sound since not everyone uses HEV suit model<br>
-clips stay on floor for short time when discarded like in CS GO<br>
-also crowbar swings are too fast if you ask me</li>
</ul>
<p>Adding all what you said would change the feel of the game.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/ac3ds-weapon-feedback/14327/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/ac3ds-weapon-feedback/14327/6</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jul 2015 13:50:50 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14327-6</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/ac3ds-weapon-feedback/14327.rss">ac3d&#39;s Weapon Feedback</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>ac3d&#39;s Weapon Feedback</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[MG1231]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Many of the changes suggested seem pretty unnecessary, and even if these changes were to be taken account by the Black Mesa team, they would most likely be at a very low priority.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/ac3ds-weapon-feedback/14327/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/ac3ds-weapon-feedback/14327/5</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 25 Jul 2015 12:14:59 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14327-5</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/ac3ds-weapon-feedback/14327.rss">ac3d&#39;s Weapon Feedback</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>ac3d&#39;s Weapon Feedback</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[fury]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Dude… If Valve wanted ironsights in their games they would have them already… at the time when HL2 was developed, there were already games that allowed you to go to phrone and aim down sights. The point is that Half-Life has it’s focus on simple and fast paced action… tbh I like CoD4 Promod, which has ironsights, “realistic” sprint and phrone… but these features have nothing to do with Half-Life gameplay. I can’t imagine to fire my Egon, RPG or Tau-Cannon through ironsights… it would be fun as a Mod maybe, but seriously Half-Life is great because of it’s simplicity, easy and fast gameplay.<br>
Adrenaline Gamer was the perfect Multiplayer experience for me. It was unique and perfectly balanced. I really hope the team will continue to make their design decisions upon what Half-Life 1 really was and what it played like. In my opinion there are already enaugh unneeded changes that require to rebalance multiplayer maps and weapons. I don’t really care much about singleplayer but I don’t get the point why would we need features like that in a game that already works super nice the original way…</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/ac3ds-weapon-feedback/14327/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/ac3ds-weapon-feedback/14327/4</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 25 Jul 2015 10:40:53 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14327-4</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/ac3ds-weapon-feedback/14327.rss">ac3d&#39;s Weapon Feedback</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>ac3d&#39;s Weapon Feedback</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[ac3d]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Sage J. Fox">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Sage J. Fox:</div>
<blockquote>
<p><span class="bbcode-i">Call of Duty: Black Mesa Ops</span></p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Actually most of my suggestions were based on Battlefield, can’t you tell the difference? they’re totally different /sarcasm</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Sage J. Fox">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Sage J. Fox:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>a lot of these suggestions (beyond stat tweaks) are very… non-Half-Life.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>And what exactly <span class="bbcode-i">is </span>Half-Life? Assuming you’re referring to the iron sights mechanic, I think Valve would have put them in the game, had they actually thought of the idea at the time, besides I’m requesting it to be <span class="bbcode-i">optional, </span>you don’t have to use iron sights if you don’t want to, but putting them in would make it easier for people new to series to feel accustomed to the controls, and for people like me who find it ridiculous to think a scientist killed hundreds of soldiers and aliens without once aiming down the barrel of his gun, guess I’m the odd one out.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Sage J. Fox">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Sage J. Fox:</div>
<blockquote>
<ul>
<li>Gluon Gun screen has power, temperature, and radiation level readings on it, no idea what you’re going for with a heat signature detector.</li>
</ul>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Yes but do they actually read the power, temperature, and radiation levels? or are they just painted on to look pretty? Any simple function, an <span class="bbcode-i">actual </span>function  would be fine,  just a bit more attention to detail, that’s all I’m asking.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Sage J. Fox">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Sage J. Fox:</div>
<blockquote>
<ul>
<li>Thought Black Mesa did have rolling grenades when you lob (right click) them on the floor.</li>
</ul>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>No,  alt fire simply lobs them in front of you, even when crouching and looking at the ground</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Sage J. Fox">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Sage J. Fox:</div>
<blockquote>
<ul>
<li>Satchel buttons make sense to me, right click for right hand, left click for left hand. Always found having them switch once you’ve thrown one to be more confusing.</li>
</ul>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Personal preference, having the option to switch them around  can’t hurt anyone</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Sage J. Fox">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Sage J. Fox:</div>
<blockquote>
<ul>
<li>Don’t see what use the trip mine would be facing straight up. The enemy would need to walk directly over it.</li>
</ul>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>That’s the point, it essentially turns itself into a  claymore, for when you’re being chased and don’t have time to pick a wall to plant on, just lob it and run, BANG!</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Sage J. Fox">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Sage J. Fox:</div>
<blockquote>
<ul>
<li>Because PEDA wouldn’t be all over Snarks as is, you want us to chuck them against the wall?</li>
</ul>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>You sure PEDA’s guidelines cover foreign lifeforms? If anything they’d be for it to protect the creatures living on earth, splatter away.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/ac3ds-weapon-feedback/14327/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/ac3ds-weapon-feedback/14327/3</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 25 Jul 2015 08:22:07 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14327-3</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/ac3ds-weapon-feedback/14327.rss">ac3d&#39;s Weapon Feedback</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>ac3d&#39;s Weapon Feedback</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Sage_J_Fox]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><span class="bbcode-i">Call of Duty: Black Mesa Ops</span></p>
<p>But more seriously, a lot of these suggestions (beyond stat tweaks) are very… non-Half-Life.</p>
<p>On a few points:</p>
<ul>
<li>
<p>I personally love all the different weapons having different crosshairs, each compliments the weapons function, from the tiny + of the perfectly accurate .357 to the big “eh somewhere in here is good” circle of the shotgun/Gluon.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>They’re redoing the crossbow model, so they aren’t doing anything with the old model regardless. S’why it doesn’t have sprint or fancy pickup animations.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>The Tau cannon <span class="bbcode-i">does</span> gib on the alt charge fire.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Gluon Gun screen has power, temperature, and radiation level readings on it, no idea what you’re going for with a heat signature detector. <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=CqXmXzLfdZ0" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Older versions of it used the screen for the ammo count.</a></p>
</li>
<li>
<p>On that note, not really sure how one would help much on the RPG.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Thought Black Mesa did have rolling grenades when you lob (right click) them on the floor.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Satchel buttons make sense to me, right click for right hand, left click for left hand. Always found having them switch once you’ve thrown one to be more confusing.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Don’t see what use the trip mine would be facing straight up. The enemy would need to walk directly over it.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Because PEDA wouldn’t be all over Snarks as is, you want us to chuck them against the wall?</p>
</li>
</ul>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/ac3ds-weapon-feedback/14327/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/ac3ds-weapon-feedback/14327/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 25 Jul 2015 01:01:58 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14327-2</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/ac3ds-weapon-feedback/14327.rss">ac3d&#39;s Weapon Feedback</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>ac3d&#39;s Weapon Feedback</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[ac3d]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><span class="bbcode-b">Crosshair</span></p>
<p><img src="https://i.imgur.com/i0LQ3v2.jpg" alt="" width="134" height="124"></p>
<ul>
<li>
<p>Make the crosshair grow larger during movement and firing to show reduced accuracy (similar to Counter-Strike)</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Make the normal four dash crosshair the default for all weapons<br>
<span class="bbcode-b">Sprinting</span></p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Remove the sprint activation sound</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Make weapons sway in the direction the player is sprinting (strafing left or right)</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Make the sprinting animation start straight away</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Make the sprinting animations less graceful and more reacting to the player’s steps hitting the ground</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Sync all animations to the player’s footsteps<br>
<span class="bbcode-b">Iron Sights</span></p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Give all appropriate weapons the ability to aim</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Reduce weapon accuracy while moving and aiming</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Make the weapon tilt and sway when moving while aiming<br>
<span class="bbcode-b">Balance</span></p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Reduce the accuracy of all appropriate weapons to make aiming a more viable choice<br>
<span class="bbcode-b">Weapon Models</span></p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Make all night sights on weapons glow in the dark similar to Half-Life 2<br>
<span class="bbcode-b">Weapon Functionality</span></p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Give ability to melee with selected weapon</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Implement a switch fire mode for all appropriate weapons</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Reduce the time from finishing a reload sequence and being able to fire</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Allow all appropriate weapons to keep a round in the chamber when reloading<br>
<span class="bbcode-b">Player Models</span></p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Make a first person view model for Gordon with all the appropriate movement animations</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Make animations for swimming<br>
<span class="bbcode-b">Player Movement</span></p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Give the ability to prone</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Add toggle crouch option</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Add toggle prone option<br>
<span class="bbcode-b">Immersion</span></p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Add option to drop empty clips on the ground when reloading</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Add option to enable realistic reloading, disable magazine pool<br>
<span class="bbcode-b">Gameplay</span></p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Increase the amount of crates that spawn ammo or weapons<br>
<span class="bbcode-b">Crowbar</span></p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Remove the screen tilting when swinging and hitting an object</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Make a charge swing secondary fire mode</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Implement ability to throw the crowbar, similar to SMOD but less comical, this can be used to knock out NPC’s in one hit<br>
<span class="bbcode-b">Glock</span></p>
</li>
</ul>
<p><img src="https://i.imgur.com/QBzKWTA.png" alt="" width="641" height="385"></p>
<ul>
<li>Change the sprinting animation to two hands on the weapon similar to the .357</li>
</ul>
<p><div class="lightbox-wrapper"><a class="lightbox" href="https://i.imgur.com/6dzFCYn.png" title="" rel="nofollow noopener"><img src="https://i.imgur.com/6dzFCYn.png" alt="" width="483" height="500"><div class="meta"><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-far-image svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#far-image"></use></svg><span class="filename"></span><span class="informations">492×509</span><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-discourse-expand svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#discourse-expand"></use></svg></div></a></div></p>
<ul>
<li>
<p>Change the alternate fire button to toggle burst fire mode<br>
<span class="bbcode-b">357</span><br>
<div class="lightbox-wrapper"><a class="lightbox" href="https://i.imgur.com/4JgNNTM.jpg" title="" rel="nofollow noopener"><img src="https://i.imgur.com/4JgNNTM.jpg" alt="" width="601" height="500"><div class="meta"><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-far-image svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#far-image"></use></svg><span class="filename"></span><span class="informations">855×711</span><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-discourse-expand svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#discourse-expand"></use></svg></div></a></div></p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Center the iron sights position</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Zoom in the weapon while aiming down sights more</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Make the sprinting animations clumsy and more uniform</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Reduce the time to zoom in the fov</p>
</li>
</ul>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">MP5</span></p>
<ul>
<li>
<p>Increase fire rate</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Increase short reload time<br>
<span class="bbcode-b">Shotgun</span></p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Reduce reload time</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Increase time between firing and pumping</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Reduce time between double firing and pumping<br>
<span class="bbcode-b">Crossbow</span></p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Reduce reload time</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Implement a quick animation for pulling back the string for the next arrow<br>
<span class="bbcode-b">RPG</span></p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Make the rocket fire instantly</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Reduce/improve the quality of the muzzle flash effect</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Give players the ability to use the scope</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Give the led screen a function e.g. Sensing heat signatures<br>
<span class="bbcode-b">Tau Cannon</span></p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Reduce the time between firing shots</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Give the ability to gib NPC’s<br>
<span class="bbcode-b">Gluon Gun</span></p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Give the alternate fire a function e.g. Charge</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Give the ability to gib NPC’s instead of the disintegrating effect</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Give the led screen a function e.g. Sensing heat signatures<br>
<span class="bbcode-b">Hive Hand</span></p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Reduce the ammo recharge time</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Increase the effectiveness of tracking enemies around corners<br>
<span class="bbcode-b">Grenade</span></p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Center the positon of the grenade being thrown more to reduce hitting walls by accident</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Add Half-Life 2’s crouch and roll ability<br>
<span class="bbcode-b">C4</span></p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Swap the buttons around for throwing the C4 and detonating</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Increase the delay between detonating and explosion<br>
<span class="bbcode-b">Trip mine</span></p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Implement an alternate fire ability to throw the mine in front of the player similar to the grenade, when the mine stops rolling it always activates facing straight up</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Reduce the time from planting and activation<br>
<span class="bbcode-b">Snark</span></p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Implement a charge alternate fire, charging increases the throw speed, the snark explodes on impact creating a puff of spore particles which stuns human enemies, similar to Half-Life 2’s Bug bait</p>
</li>
</ul>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/ac3ds-weapon-feedback/14327/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/ac3ds-weapon-feedback/14327/1</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jul 2015 07:02:02 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14327-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/ac3ds-weapon-feedback/14327.rss">ac3d&#39;s Weapon Feedback</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
