<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Consoles vs Computers</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/consoles-vs-computers/2247</link>
    <description>This topic desperately needs a new thread.

I&#39;m quite biased because I think consoles are for fags but here we go, some PROs and CONs.

CONSOLES CAN: 
-Never have to worry about &quot;omg will this game run on my system plzzzzz answr!!1&quot; 
-Good for actual human interaction via playing with 4 or whatever people who actually exist in the same room at the same time.
-Quite a large development industry ensuring lots of new game releases. Hell they&#39;re still making games for the PS2 ffs. When was the last time you heard of a reputable PC game developer making a game that could run on a Pentium III with 64mb of RAM?
-Geared for fast-paced arcade games.
-Are cheap as shit compared to good gaming PCs.
-Are somewhat mobile as you can bring your little console to other peoples&#39; houses and plug it into any TV and play from there.
-Console games SOMETIMES provide for quite indepth singleplayer games moreso than PCs because even today multiplayer aspects of consoles are quite limited. This is unlike PC games where development focus is overwhelmingly steering towards multiplayer because of the idea that the masses want multiplayer and also because its easier to produce a multiplayer game with absolutely no story, AI mechanic or event scripting and the like where you don&#39;t have to worry about making a &quot;deep&quot; story-driven game, because all anyone cares about is teabagging other human players.
-No WoW.

COMPUTERS CAN:
-Be upgraded. This means that PC game developers are constantly working to improve games in all areas whereas console games are generally confined to making games that can run optimized on specific consoles and will never be able to break that threshold.
-More detailed games with more detailed controls. 112 possible buttons on the keyboard (not even counting combinations) allow for much more detailed gaming environments and controls. 
-These days most games can be modded to hell and back which has spawned an entire population of amateur game developers who will become the next generation of commercial game developers. Moddability can also greatly increase a game&#39;s replayability. Many mods are also of such a quality that rivals commercial titles and are available for free. Free console games are limited to fucking tetris remakes and Bubble Bobble.
-Non-game related, computers are useful for a wide variety of different activities, from being /b/fags to downloading terrabytes of porn to &quot;making spreadsheets&quot; and what the shit ever. 
-PCs allow developers much more freedom to develop content, although they are still somewhat limited by the need for publisher approval and compatibility with Windows and/or Mac. However this is far better than the state of console development; development on consoles is strictly regulated by Sony/Nintendo/et al who impose draconian rules on every-fucking-thing. I used to be a Certification Standards Compliance blah blah for Nintendo and Sony and Microsoft, it was basically my job to make sure every game that came across my desk complied with literally [b]thousands[/b] of individual criteria, the failure of ANY of them would result in a complete shutdown of development until that issue was fixed. And I&#39;m talking about sometimes stupid shit like &quot;EVERY INSTANCE OF INGAME REFERENCE TO CONTROLS MUST BE EXACTLY COMPLIANT TO OUR RULES, ie Xbox controls [i]always[/i] had to be referred to as &quot;A Button&quot; and &quot;B Button&quot; etc, if you missed even a single capitalization, comma, dash or period Microsoft would visit you and rape you in the night.


In the end the console is in my opinion horrifically inferior because it is a controlled, limited technology that impedes technological advancement and confines all games developed for it to strict archaic principles and regulations, and offers only the most shallow of button-mashing arcade gameplay. I still do appreciate older console titles from the NES and that era as while they were graphically limited they often had really cool and addictive gameplay, good stories and blah blah while today it&#39;s all about pizzaz and shiny graphics and millions upon millions of Halo players fagging up the planet. However in console&#39;s defense, World of Warcraft is a PC game and it has eclipsed all other games in terms of the rotten plague festering at the heart of humanity consuming everything great and good in the world that it has created. 

That said, I&#39;d like to see a lot of flaming and irrational anger here and hopefully start what history will write down as the &quot;Great Gaming Civil War&quot; in which PC and Console gamers devastate the internet world.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 02 Jan 2010 19:21:14 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Technology and Gaming</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/consoles-vs-computers/2247.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Consoles vs Computers</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Someonerandm]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Jingles">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/j/46a35a/40.png" class="avatar"> Jingles:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I much prefer to use a controller to a keyboard anyday, just my xbox controllers aren’t wired.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Then you are in a strange, strange world, not to mention a massively small minority.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/consoles-vs-computers/2247/172">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/consoles-vs-computers/2247/172</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 02 Jan 2010 19:21:14 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2247-172</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/consoles-vs-computers/2247.rss">Consoles vs Computers</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Consoles vs Computers</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[LimitBreak]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Jingles">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/j/46a35a/40.png" class="avatar"> Jingles:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I much prefer to use a controller to a keyboard anyday, just my xbox controllers aren’t wired.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>For me, a mouse and keyboard offers much more free range of motion in games.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/consoles-vs-computers/2247/171">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/consoles-vs-computers/2247/171</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 02 Jan 2010 16:59:32 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2247-171</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/consoles-vs-computers/2247.rss">Consoles vs Computers</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Consoles vs Computers</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Jingles]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="garthbartin">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 garthbartin:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I don’t know the answer to your question, but allowing you to make entirely customized controls would help, but it wouldn’t solve the controller problem. The main thing I have against controllers is, on an x-box, it is very hard to move the right analog stick and press B A X or y at the same time. And it’s very hard to use the d-pad while using the left analog stick.</p>
<p>On a keyboard you can and sometimes will use 3 or even 4 buttons almost simultaneously.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I much prefer to use a controller to a keyboard anyday, just my xbox controllers aren’t wired.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/consoles-vs-computers/2247/170">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/consoles-vs-computers/2247/170</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 02 Jan 2010 16:52:57 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2247-170</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/consoles-vs-computers/2247.rss">Consoles vs Computers</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Consoles vs Computers</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Deutscher_Scharfschu]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Lolipopman">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/l/f475e1/40.png" class="avatar"> Lolipopman:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>but Isn’t Finland to the east of europe? I consider it that way, and I live next to it…</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p><a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Winter_War" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Winter_War</a></p>
<p><a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Battle_of_Raate_road" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Battle_of_Raate_road</a></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/consoles-vs-computers/2247/169">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/consoles-vs-computers/2247/169</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jan 2010 23:32:42 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2247-169</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/consoles-vs-computers/2247.rss">Consoles vs Computers</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Consoles vs Computers</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Medevilae]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="MaxTheLimit">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/m/0ea827/40.png" class="avatar"> MaxTheLimit:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I’ve kinda avoided voicing my own opinion in here. So far I’ve just been refuting what seemed to be ill conceived points.<br>
I think the power of arguments on this subject varies depending on the point in each cycle. RIGHT NOW I think that, with all aspect being considered, PC gaming is a more preferential avenue. PC hardware is so cheap right now. Options are so open, and functionally things are pretty good for games. Steam has done a lot for casual gaming fans. It’s implemented a simple functional way for people to get games that stay up to date, and work in an easy layout. I think one of the biggest things against consoles right now it the way the cycle is working for them. All of the big three are close to the same point in their cycle, which is now rather deep. While right now consoles are becoming a bit dated in capabilities ( and they are not looking to update anytime soon ) , it’s interesting to note that when the n ext gen consoles DO come they will likely be VERY powerful and FAR cheaper than comparative PC hardware. All of the big 3 will likely release a next gen console around the same period. This could be a period where the arguments for PC gaming become less valid. Comparative hardware will be more expensive. New gaming features and gaming abilities on the console will make consoles look good for over a year.<br>
I’m just saying that both sides have merit. Right now isn’t a good time for consoles, but with consoles looking decent even in these deep cycle years, PC gaming better hope to make the most of it’s sunny days.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Good points. However, the PC’s capabilities right now are so far above that of a console… The difference is astronomical. Even if consoles do, after a very long ammount of time, “catch up” to the PC’s abilities, the PC will just take a flying leap ahead again in some way…</p>
<p>It’s comparable to a race- the one who starts out ahead can take a break once their ahead, and as soon as the laggard catches up, and is in need of a rest, the one who had already started can just start running again, once again leaving the other behind.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/consoles-vs-computers/2247/168">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/consoles-vs-computers/2247/168</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jan 2010 23:29:29 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2247-168</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/consoles-vs-computers/2247.rss">Consoles vs Computers</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Consoles vs Computers</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Someonerandm]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Russians would have seen to it that their national language was forced upon the people, just like their ideology, so as to make them seem more unified.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/consoles-vs-computers/2247/167">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/consoles-vs-computers/2247/167</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jan 2010 23:14:04 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2247-167</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/consoles-vs-computers/2247.rss">Consoles vs Computers</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Consoles vs Computers</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Lolipopman]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>The brits would probably have done fine if they had just done that assasination on Hitler that they planned. And, correct me if I’m wrong, but Isn’t Finland to the east of europe? I consider it that way, and I live next to it… And why would we be speaking russian? We could still speak our native language, that’s what Skåne did when we stole it from Denmark. They still sound Danish, ans that was 400 years ago…</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/consoles-vs-computers/2247/166">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/consoles-vs-computers/2247/166</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jan 2010 22:52:57 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2247-166</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/consoles-vs-computers/2247.rss">Consoles vs Computers</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Consoles vs Computers</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Deutscher_Scharfschu]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Codgin">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/c/ba8739/40.png" class="avatar"> Codgin:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>sorry if this is way off topic lol, but america saving who’s ass? This is part of why the world not hates but gets annoyed by the American attitude. It was the British who won the big war, ok America did help us and theirs no denying their bravey, but they got involved cause someone took the stick to the dog, britain however saw what Germany was doing and said no, we a small seemingly insiginifcant island took the stand against the biggest threat this world has ever known and won, not because they invaded us but because we believed what they was doing was wrong, we led the way for others to follow. And the SAS? Simply put the best fighting force in the world, just wanted that to be known. Alot of the reasons the rest of the world hates America and England dates way back to the Slave Trade and England conquering most of the known world, that ressciment will never go away, I’m sure their are many other reasons that we conventitly “forget”, who can blame 'em though? Our ancestors did some terrible things. So when someone says your country is stupid, as long as they aren’t french, we (And I mean England, alot of Europe and America) probably deserved it lol</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>where did the British get their guns, vehicles and money from when they were still bankrupt from WWI? wait for it… wait for it… AMERICA! who fought a war on multiple fronts and won? America! who commenced the largest amphibious assault in history? america.</p>
<p>who paid to rebuild western Europe after the war? America.</p>
<p>Face it, if the united states did not get involved in world war two, Germany would have been wiped out by Russia, and western Europe would be speaking Russian right now, including Britain. (probably not the Finns, because they are bad ass) through simple, yet difficult demonstrations of power, the united states kept eager soviet minds at bay for 60 years. (well not really, it all cooled down after johnson’s administration)</p>
<p>god, its people like you who make me think that the majority of the worlds population, not just america, is retarded.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>And the SAS? Simply put the best fighting force in the world, just wanted that to be known</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I’m not even going to begin to argue with you there, there is no such thing as the best fighting force in the world, when your military is big enough, you can have as many special operation units trained to be the best in various fields. the SAS simply cannot be the best at everything they do.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/consoles-vs-computers/2247/165">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/consoles-vs-computers/2247/165</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jan 2010 22:42:27 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2247-165</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/consoles-vs-computers/2247.rss">Consoles vs Computers</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Consoles vs Computers</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Lord_Grievous]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>P to the mothafuckin’ C</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/consoles-vs-computers/2247/164">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/consoles-vs-computers/2247/164</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jan 2010 22:33:48 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2247-164</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/consoles-vs-computers/2247.rss">Consoles vs Computers</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Consoles vs Computers</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[dky.tehkingd.u]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Another thing: You don’t need to install games on a console. Again, consoles are more accessible to those who don’t want to use/don’t have any brainpower.</p>
<p>I prefer PCs actually. Especially for FPS games, they’re much better and more fun. PCs generally work for more games types of games… notice how RTS fails on console due to the messed up controls.</p>
<p>Though games like Ninja Gaiden for example wouldn’t work so well with a PC due to the control scheme… But in that case I guess plugging in a gamepad could solve that issue.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/consoles-vs-computers/2247/163">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/consoles-vs-computers/2247/163</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jan 2010 22:15:11 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2247-163</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/consoles-vs-computers/2247.rss">Consoles vs Computers</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Consoles vs Computers</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[xalener]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Acristoff">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/a/ea666f/40.png" class="avatar"> Acristoff:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>And which one are you. :retard:</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Both.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/consoles-vs-computers/2247/162">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/consoles-vs-computers/2247/162</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jan 2010 22:08:14 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2247-162</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/consoles-vs-computers/2247.rss">Consoles vs Computers</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Consoles vs Computers</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Acristoff]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Kairouseki">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/k/57b2e6/40.png" class="avatar"> Kairouseki:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>PCs’ vast amount of buttons are a plus but consoles don’t require as much maintenance as PCs do.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Thing is though, people will still have to go through similar amounts of maintenance with just having a PC (not for gaming).</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/consoles-vs-computers/2247/161">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/consoles-vs-computers/2247/161</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Dec 2009 05:25:28 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2247-161</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/consoles-vs-computers/2247.rss">Consoles vs Computers</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Consoles vs Computers</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Kairouseki]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I just got into PC gaming during the last year or so and I agree that the PC is the best when it comes to shooters and strategy games. I still for the most part use consoles however. PCs’ vast amount of buttons are a plus but consoles don’t require as much maintenance as PCs do.</p>
<p>PCs have been around for far longer though and are capable of much better graphics and performance. They both have some pros and cons.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/consoles-vs-computers/2247/160">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/consoles-vs-computers/2247/160</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Dec 2009 05:11:35 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2247-160</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/consoles-vs-computers/2247.rss">Consoles vs Computers</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Consoles vs Computers</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[MaxTheLimit]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I’ve kinda avoided voicing my own opinion in here. So far I’ve just been refuting what seemed to be ill conceived points.<br>
I think the power of arguments on this subject varies depending on the point in each cycle. RIGHT NOW I think that, with all aspect being considered, PC gaming is a more preferential avenue. PC hardware is so cheap right now. Options are so open, and functionally things are pretty good for games. Steam has done a lot for casual gaming fans. It’s implemented a simple functional way for people to get games that stay up to date, and work in an easy layout. I think one of the biggest things against consoles right now it the way the cycle is working for them. All of the big three are close to the same point in their cycle, which is now rather deep. While right now consoles are becoming a bit dated in capabilities ( and they are not looking to update anytime soon ) , it’s interesting to note that when the n ext gen consoles DO come they will likely be VERY powerful and FAR cheaper than comparative PC hardware. All of the big 3 will likely release a next gen console around the same period. This could be a period where the arguments for PC gaming become less valid. Comparative hardware will be more expensive. New gaming features and gaming abilities on the console will make consoles look good for over a year.<br>
I’m just saying that both sides have merit. Right now isn’t a good time for consoles, but with consoles looking decent even in these deep cycle years, PC gaming better hope to make the most of it’s sunny days.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/consoles-vs-computers/2247/159">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/consoles-vs-computers/2247/159</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Dec 2009 05:03:15 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2247-159</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/consoles-vs-computers/2247.rss">Consoles vs Computers</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Consoles vs Computers</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Acristoff]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="xalener">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/x/cc9497/40.png" class="avatar"> xalener:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>PCs are for snobbish fuckwads who jizz their pants over a game and then complain about it when it comes out, so they try to change everything about it.</p>
<p>Consoles are for poor homophobic retards.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>And which one are you. :retard:</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/consoles-vs-computers/2247/158">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/consoles-vs-computers/2247/158</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Dec 2009 03:34:30 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2247-158</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/consoles-vs-computers/2247.rss">Consoles vs Computers</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Consoles vs Computers</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Deathmonkey7]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Soooo… gaming sucks?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/consoles-vs-computers/2247/157">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/consoles-vs-computers/2247/157</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Dec 2009 03:23:02 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2247-157</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/consoles-vs-computers/2247.rss">Consoles vs Computers</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Consoles vs Computers</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[xalener]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>PCs are for snobbish fuckwads who jizz their pants over a game and then complain about it when it comes out, so they try to change everything about it.</p>
<p>Consoles are for poor homophobic retards.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/consoles-vs-computers/2247/156">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/consoles-vs-computers/2247/156</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Dec 2009 03:20:28 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2247-156</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/consoles-vs-computers/2247.rss">Consoles vs Computers</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Consoles vs Computers</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Someonerandm]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>But of course. Anyways, I do believe this little tangent has run its course. Onward with the PC/Console flaming!</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/consoles-vs-computers/2247/155">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/consoles-vs-computers/2247/155</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Dec 2009 02:57:11 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2247-155</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/consoles-vs-computers/2247.rss">Consoles vs Computers</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Consoles vs Computers</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[bur]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Someonerandm">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/s/d78d45/40.png" class="avatar"> Someonerandm:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>It fun, though, since people get annoyed about it, which makes me happy when they were being annoying about America.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>In that case, carry on.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/consoles-vs-computers/2247/154">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/consoles-vs-computers/2247/154</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Dec 2009 02:04:20 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2247-154</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/consoles-vs-computers/2247.rss">Consoles vs Computers</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Consoles vs Computers</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Someonerandm]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Like it or not, a country’s history is closely related to its image, I don’t know why. I’m not saying that that view point makes sense, I’m saying that it pisses people off, and so I use it when I want to piss people off. I agree that you should be thankful to the people who fought the war, not their kids.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/consoles-vs-computers/2247/153">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/consoles-vs-computers/2247/153</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Dec 2009 01:35:09 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2247-153</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/consoles-vs-computers/2247.rss">Consoles vs Computers</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Consoles vs Computers</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Acristoff]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Except you didn’t do anything in those wars, you had no effect on it whatsoever. Sorry but if I’m going to feel thankful for people who fought in the war, <span class="bbcode-i">I’m going to be thankful to the people who fought in the war</span>, not those people’s children.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/consoles-vs-computers/2247/152">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/consoles-vs-computers/2247/152</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Dec 2009 01:27:37 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2247-152</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/consoles-vs-computers/2247.rss">Consoles vs Computers</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Consoles vs Computers</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Someonerandm]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>They get annoyed. Notice the above posts. If anything, they are annoyed at you looking like you are taking credit for things we had no part in. Not to mention the whole fact that we did have a part in it.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/consoles-vs-computers/2247/151">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/consoles-vs-computers/2247/151</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Dec 2009 01:12:42 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2247-151</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/consoles-vs-computers/2247.rss">Consoles vs Computers</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Consoles vs Computers</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Acristoff]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>It’s not annoying it makes it look like you’re trying to take credit for things you had no part in.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/consoles-vs-computers/2247/150">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/consoles-vs-computers/2247/150</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 24 Dec 2009 23:54:30 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2247-150</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/consoles-vs-computers/2247.rss">Consoles vs Computers</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Consoles vs Computers</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Someonerandm]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Burbinator">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Burbinator:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Besides, it’s been 60 years. Using the US’s effort in WW2 as an excuse for anything is just stupid.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>It fun, though, since people get annoyed about it, which makes me happy when they were being annoying about America.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/consoles-vs-computers/2247/149">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/consoles-vs-computers/2247/149</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 24 Dec 2009 23:49:11 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2247-149</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/consoles-vs-computers/2247.rss">Consoles vs Computers</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Consoles vs Computers</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Grey_Acumen]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Well, I said I’d inject some intelligence into the thread, I never said it’d stick.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/consoles-vs-computers/2247/148">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/consoles-vs-computers/2247/148</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 24 Dec 2009 23:30:58 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2247-148</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/consoles-vs-computers/2247.rss">Consoles vs Computers</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
