<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Patch Suggestions</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/patch-suggestions/10979</link>
    <description>Tl; dr
Black Mesa should play and feel like Half-Life 2 as much as possible, those who have played the sequel but not the original will find it easier to adapt to its familiar play style.

Jumping
[COLOR=&#39;Red&#39;]-Make it easier to jump up onto ledges the same height or lower than the player, as in HL2
-auto boost when jumping out of water onto ledges in Quake and HL1 needs to return
-height and speed should be the same as HL2

Ladders
[COLOR=&#39;Red&#39;]-all mechanics should work the same as HL1 and HL: S, free movement, auto mount, etc.

Grenade
[COLOR=&#39;Red&#39;]-needs to be thrown more centred to the screen like HL2, currently it is thrown too far right and is easily obstructed by walls

Houndeye
[COLOR=&#39;Red&#39;]-sonic effect intensity (optional)

Crossbow
-BM and HL2 style zoom (optional)

Soldiers 
-reaction time is fine, but their accuracy should be lower on easier difficulties

MP5
-burst and auto firing rates (optional)

Crowbar
-view bob when swinging (optional)
-swing speed should be the same as in HL2

Player
-strength for throwing objects should be lower
-BM and HL2 style death animations (optional)
-BM and HL2 weapon sprint animation styles (optional)
-BM and HL2 style weapon sway (optional)
-HL1 style screen glitch indicating crouch jump has been activated (optional)

HUD
-remember last weapon used in sub-category (optional)
-on-screen display for using trams, currently it is difficult to tell if tram has been engaged or not
-counters turn red when supply is low (optional)
-damage indicators show when taking fall damage (optional)
-HL2 style crosshair for HUD zoom
-fire immediately after using HUD zoom as in HL2

Bugs
[COLOR=&#39;Red&#39;]-View roll selection does not save after quitting
-Cannot turn off radioactive screen noise
-Auto aim always appears enabled
-c2a2c, door near the rocket control room leads outside the map, glass shouldn’t be breakable
-Strange line appears on the shotgun when using flashlight</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2013 04:25:48 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>The Cafeteria</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/patch-suggestions/10979.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Patch Suggestions</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[ysrael214]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Tau cannon doesn’t have magazines and it must stay that way like Half-Life. Tau Cannon also damages 20 in Half-Life, not just Black Mesa.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/patch-suggestions/10979/29">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/patch-suggestions/10979/29</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2013 04:25:48 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-10979-29</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/patch-suggestions/10979.rss">Patch Suggestions</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Patch Suggestions</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Open_Source_Forever]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I think the Tau Cannon &amp; the Gluon Gun should have separate reserve pools. As you guys may remember, in <span class="bbcode-i">Half-Life 1</span>, they both use “Depleted Uranium-235” as ammunition. However, in <span class="bbcode-i">Black Mesa: Source</span>, that was just changed to “Depleted Uranium”, in the name of realism. I think they should still keep the Depleted Uranium as the ammunition for the Tau Cannon, &amp; the Gluon Gun should use “Uranium-235” as ammunition, out of homage to the original. Additionally, the Tau Cannon’s secondary fire should go back to being able to do 25 hit points per Depleted Uranium Unit, &amp; using 13 Depleted Uranium Units on a full charge. Going on that last thing, the Tau Cannon’s magazine should be increased to 156 Depleted Uranium Units (13-1=12, &amp; 12*13=156), with the secondary fire only allowing a full charge if the amount of ammunition currently in the player’s Tau Cannon magazine is currently in a multiple of 13. If the amount isn’t in a multiple of 13, the secondary fire stops charging upon the amount in the magazine going down to a multiple of 13. On a note relating to other stuff, the Rocket Propelled Grenade Launcher should have separate “ammunition in magazine/ammunition in reserve pool” numbers in its HUD ammunition tracker.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/patch-suggestions/10979/28">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/patch-suggestions/10979/28</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2013 03:08:33 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-10979-28</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/patch-suggestions/10979.rss">Patch Suggestions</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Patch Suggestions</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[ojcoolj]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Alright, time to input my suggestions</p>
<ul>
<li>Vortigaunts should be a bit more active in their movements, instead of standing still</li>
<li>Drastically increase Vortigaunt charge time on easy and normal</li>
<li>Add leeches as particle effects like the roaches or as simple props</li>
<li>Add Hazard Course, Uplink, and Surface Tension Uncut as bonus levels of sorts</li>
<li>Prevent achievements from being able to be gained while using cheats</li>
<li>As mentioned earlier, need a bit more reward for actually finding scientists and stuff. Probably let them deploy healthpacks</li>
<li>Add the trip to Xen from the start after the Xen levels are actually done</li>
<li>Response Rules for the HECU should be changed to reduce frequency of lines. Also, stop them shouting “WE’RE TAKING HEAVY FIRE” when you walk directly into their bullets with godmode. You are not taking heavy fire, you lunatic!</li>
<li>Find a place to use unused soundtracks, possibly replacing the infamous Blast Pit end song</li>
<li>Buff the Ichy</li>
<li>Give an option to make the MP5 non-burst fire</li>
<li>Possibly add in a reference or two to the expansion packs, like when one of the scientists has a fantasy about Dr. Cross</li>
<li>The Famous HECU Robot most appear in some way. Maybe a corpse?</li>
<li>It’d be fun if you could actually fight the Alien Grunt from the start of Questionable Ethics, even if he’d be armorless and easier to defeat, it’d be a way to introduce him to the players</li>
<li>Maybe they could alter the Vort’s texture, they look like slimey toads</li>
<li>Vorts also look too bipedal. Back in HL1 they were basically hunchbacked</li>
<li>Barnacle’s should die in 1 Crowbar hit, it only makes sense</li>
</ul>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/patch-suggestions/10979/27">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/patch-suggestions/10979/27</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 13 Dec 2012 16:18:01 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-10979-27</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/patch-suggestions/10979.rss">Patch Suggestions</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Patch Suggestions</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Wangman]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>You want patch suggestions? Here’s patch suggestions…</p>
<p>General/Miscellaneous issues</p>
<ol>
<li>
<p>Splatter effects-Some of the effects on Gordon’s arms disappear instantly when weapon swapping with certain combinations while they seem to remain with other combinations.  Ideally, this persistence problem could be fixed as the effects look great.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Crouch jumping-Numerous players have complained about the amount of crouch jumping that is needed in game. The jump height should be increased such that it still appears realistic but would reduce (but not eliminate) the use of this technique.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Ladder mechanics-Another huge complaint from the community.  The ladder should have the same mechanics as in HL2 with regards to “stickyness.”  Currently, it’s too easy to fall off the ladder and latching on can be problematic, leading to unnecessary player death.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Scientist medical assistance-In the original HL, some of the scientists used to give a single med-pack or syringe when the player was extremely low on health.  Perhaps this feature could be implemented in game as it would help prevent excessive player death and unnecessary reloads.  This would also make the players grateful to see Black Mesa staff.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Battery life for the flashlight-As it stands now, the player can keep their flashlight on from Anomalous Materials all the way to Lambda Core, which doesn’t seem realistic.  The addition of a timer would add an extra element of resource budgeting in game and would be consistent with HL2.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Save game menu-Instead of having the quicksaves/autosaves display the map region (e.g. C2A5F), the actual level name (e.g. Apprehension) should be displayed like in HL2 and beyond in order to minimize confusion.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Integration of community assets-Some players have done excellent work in the community projects section so I am wondering if there are any plans to integrate this into the official steam release?  For instance, Larsa’s “Alone” piece would be absolutely perfect to add to the Xen teleporter puzzle (the three golden leaves). There’s also some good work being done on the particle effects of the weapon blasts and the restoration of the Hazard Course and Surface Tension (see below). Will the development team pick and choose which projects to integrate or simply ignore them all together (which I personally think would be a mistake)?</p>
</li>
</ol>
<p>Balance</p>
<ol>
<li>
<p>Crowbar–Should kill a barnacle on hard mode in no more than 2 hits. This is the traditional barnacle killing weapon in all half life games so players should not have to take damage while using it.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>MP5-Needs a slight damage boost as it is not particularly effective for engaging the tougher enemies in game (e.g. HECU). This would help decrease reliance on the magnum, adjust for the decreased clip size (30 bullets instead of 50) and increase gameplay options.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Crossbow-Inferior weapon in BMS compared to the magnum because of accuracy issues and collision model problems…the bolts often get stuck on walls or props when you are trying to snipe and this should really be fixed. Also, the crossbow cursor is buggy and will disappear after quicksaves.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>RPG-Needs a damage boost versus vehicles (especially versus Apache) as it is an inferior option to a charged tau shot. Why use this weapon and take more damage from the enemy than necessary when you can kill it with just a couple of tau shots?</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Tau cannon-Consider a diminishing returns model for secondary fire damage (charged shots) to balance it against the RPG.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Gluon gun-As with the original HL, this weapon is essentially useless compared to the Tau cannon because it depletes uranium too rapidly. Consider decreasing rate of ammo depletion by ~25% to make it a more viable option.</p>
</li>
</ol>
<p>AI Scripting</p>
<ol>
<li>
<p>Vortigaunt-Missing a stun animation and needs a slight increase in charge-up time. Both features would help gameplay by making the attacks more avoidable. In HL, vortigaunt attacks could be disrupted with powerful weapons (e.g. shot gun/magnum/energy weapons) forcing it to recharge.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Bullsquid-When capable of getting into melee range, the bullsquid should preferentially use charge rather than acid spit.  Possibly pair this with a health buff (~30-50%).</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Houndeye-Consider decreasing their movement speed by 10% as they take a decent amount of damage on hard mode and exist in larger packs in BMS.  This change also makes sense as the player’s default movement speed is walk instead of run.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>HECU-Needs a slight decrease in reaction time and decrease in accuracy (perhaps 65-70% for generic soldiers, 85% for team leaders). Should use more grenades to flush the player out. These changes would allow for more satisfying encounters by increasing gameplay options/tactical diversity, as the player wouldn’t have to hide in a corner and spam magnum/shotgun in hard mode.  The nerf can be partially offset w/an increase in MP5 damage.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Icthyosaur-Should be more difficult to kill. Perhaps 3 crossbow shots or 1.5-2 glock clips on hard mode.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Alien grunt-Should use the primary fire (homing) mode of the hivehand when the player is out of line of sight, since this was the grunt’s main attack in HL. Secondary fire mode for everything else. Have the grunts throw 2-3 snarks to flush out the player if he’s hiding.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Gargantua-Would be nice if they were killable with explosives/energy weapons as they were in the original game.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Apache-Needs a slight decrease in minigun accuracy and perhaps slightly slower hellfire missile attacks as well as a decrease in health to make the cave engagement in Surface Tension more fun. Should be killed with fewer RPGs on hard mode (~7-10 shots, Apache can go critical w/hellfire missiles earlier).</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Abrahms/LAV-Could both use health boosts, especially versus charged tau shots, since they are static targets and their anti-personnel machine guns are easy to avoid.  Armor-wise, they currently feel much weaker than the Apache, which should not be the case.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Leech-Seems to be completely missing from the game, although there is a Barney that references them in Forget about Freeman.  Consider adding a cameo appearance in Questionable Ethics, either in the biodome (in the pond with headcrabs) or reintroduce a few of them in Forget about Freeman.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Tentacle-Unfortunately, the most problematic AI in BMS because it is missing several scripts from HL. This video highlights some of what’s missing (<a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=PkeKfqRo2Uw" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=PkeKfqRo2Uw</a>). The following should help fix the tentacle and make it behave more realistically:</p>
</li>
</ol>
<p>A.	Needs the idle animations back after it does not hear sound for a prolonged period of time (tentacle sits up and growls or gently taps at the floors).</p>
<p>B.	The two closest tentacles need to focus on the site where an explosive has been detonated; the third tentacle can also attack or idle as seen in the video. This adds far more purpose to their movements compared to them always clacking away 120 degrees from each other.</p>
<p>C.	Greater independence between tentacles until it is stimulated by sound (e.g. one tentacle idles, another clacks away at a lower level).</p>
<p>D.	As in HL, tentacles should retreat into the ground when their base is hit with an explosive or when the neck area is hit with firearms. This is a good emergency tactic when the creature is agitated.</p>
<p>Levels</p>
<ol>
<li>
<p>Hazard Course-Really hope the community creates this level and that it gets integrated into Steam. I think it would be helpful because it visually orients players to the game and can introduce them to unusual mechanics (e.g. crouch jumping, long jump, crouching as a stealth tactic).</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Inbound-<br>
A.	The scene where the scientist is locked out and pounding on the door because of radioactive fluid leak, while funny, is inappropriate. Both he and the other scientist should be wearing full HEV suits.</p>
</li>
</ol>
<p>B.	The first Barney you meet after the tram ride uses his fist on the keypad to unlock the door to the facility. Could this be changed to him actually pushing the keypad with a finger?</p>
<ol start="3">
<li>Anomalous Materials-<br>
A.	One of the scientists has a typing animation that is completely off. He is not even close to hitting any of the buttons on the key pad.</li>
</ol>
<p>B.	Another scientist has a typing animation even though he’s crouching over some metal pipes. He should be removed from the game or have his animation changed.</p>
<p>C.	The second Xen landscape needs to be added back to the resonance cascade sequence. This is critical because it’s the only way to visually orient the player to the end game (a la HL2). Here’s hoping it will be added once the Xen levels are done.</p>
<p>D.	Would love to see Eli’s voice redone if possible as he sounds nothing like himself in HL2.</p>
<ol start="4">
<li>
<p>We’ve Got Hostiles and onward-Would like to hear more of the male VOX announcements after the HECU takeover. I heard some of the sound files were missing during compression so hopefully they will be added later.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Blast Pit-<br>
A.	There are some real bullshit enemy spawn positions in this level. For instance, you get cheap-shotted by a bullsquid after dropping out from a tunnel. There is no way to see it coming unless you memorized its location and this negatively impacts immersion. The cautious player should be rewarded for his efforts, not punished.</p>
</li>
</ol>
<p>B.	Some people have reported glitches with the Geiger counter not going off in radiation zones.</p>
<p>C.	In one of the corners at the base of the pit, there is an area with a pair of HEV batteries. Is this area accessible w/o no-clipping or without taking heavy damage? If not, these batteries should be deleted.</p>
<p>D.	The tentacle AI needs some repairs (see above).</p>
<p>E.	It should be possible to deactivate the giant fan. First-time players may not realize that they need to quickly get back on the ladder and they will be stuck below the fan permanently, forcing game reloads. It may also be helpful to increase the fan activation time to address this issue.</p>
<p>F.	I got a game crash when I jumped on the fan before it fully activated and lifted me.</p>
<ol start="6">
<li>Power Up-<br>
A.	There is an iconic music piece introducing the player to this level in the original HL but it’s missing in BMS. Perhaps Joel can compose something for the gargantua/HECU battle?</li>
</ol>
<p>B.	Two marines will come down from the elevator once the power is on. A script should be in place which would have another pair of marines on the upper level come down if the two marines are killed and the elevators are raised. This makes sense as a raised elevator with two dead marines should raise suspicion and would allow the player an opportunity to use trapping techniques (e.g. trip mines, satchel).  Alternatively, there needs to be more cover for the player when he gets back up, as there is none currently.</p>
<ol start="7">
<li>Apprehension-<br>
A.	Ichthyosaur needs a health buff and there are some major problems with crossbow accuracy (see above).</li>
</ol>
<p>B.	The world map just before the cold room is inverted.</p>
<ol start="8">
<li>Questionable Ethics-<br>
A.	There are some serious design and grammatical issues on several of the billboards, posters and signs that stand out like a sore thumb compared to the consistency and professional appearance of the chapters before it. Here are some examples and suggested changes:</li>
</ol>
<p>i.	Lab A sign says audio -&gt; spacial (misspelled), bio chem, bio-&gt; electrics. Suggested change: acoustic analysis -&gt; or audio-spatial-&gt; (all on one line), biochemistry or biochem-&gt; (one word), bioelectrics -&gt; (one word). All of the signs look more professional and realistic when the words are kept on one line. In general, when using “bio” as a prefix, it can be glued directly onto the word w/o using a space or hyphen.</p>
<p>ii.	Similar changes: micro -&gt; optronic necropsy to micro-optronic necropsy -&gt;, optronics -&gt; labs to optronics labs -&gt;, primary -&gt; laser to primary laser -&gt;, &lt;- Lab D (new line) [access] to &lt;-Lab D [access], conference [new line] room to conference room.  There are so many of these mistakes that it’s hard to keep track of them all.  You’ll have to look at each sign carefully.</p>
<p>iii.	The “A03-canteen” sign should be changed to “A03-cafeteria.”  No one uses the word canteen to describe a cafeteria in the U.S.</p>
<p>iv.	The “B07-special treatment” room with the vortigaunt should be renamed.  “Special treatment” is not realistic.  Are they getting special treatment w/cotton candy?  Be specific.</p>
<p>v.	The Biodome Lab Announcements are full of grammatical errors, including inappropriate capitalization (e.g. Pizza, Labs) and inconsistent use of periods.  Change “Doctors, Foreman, Junek” to “Doctors Foreman, Junek” (remove comma).  Change availeable to available. Change todays to today’s.</p>
<p>vi.	“Exoskeletal osteopathics” is nonsense…these scientists are not chiropractors that massage alien backs. Suggest change: exoskeleton analysis.</p>
<p>vii.	“Xeno flora” should be xenoflora (one word) on all of the signs.</p>
<p>viii.	“Minor xenos” is nonsense as xenos is not a real word. Suggested change: xenofauna or minor xenofauna, since this sign is placed over the snark cannon room.</p>
<p>ix.	There is an extra space on the Biodome Facility Floor 1 poster before the word “Decomtamination” that should be deleted. There is an extra space before the word “Disposal” that should be deleted.  The aforementioned grammatical changes should also be incorporated in this poster as well.</p>
<p>x.	There is an extra space on the Biodome Facility Floor 2 poster after “Decon” that should be deleted.  Perhaps change this word to “Decontamination” to reflect the floor 1 poster.</p>
<p>xi.	Outside of the QE building there are signs that read “hydro electric facility.”  Change to “hydroelectric dam” or “hydroelectric facility.”</p>
<p>B.	Would be nice to have leeches make a cameo appearance in the biodome observatory (pond area with headrabs), since they are missing from the game. By keeping the leeches here, the player doesn’t have to interact with them. This also makes the in-game comment regarding leeches in the water legit.</p>
<p>C.	There is a Barney standing outside of the dissection unit room who doesn’t interact with you until after you’ve freed the scientists.  He should say something about rescuing them to cue the players to their objective.</p>
<p>D.	The hole in the wall that is created after activating the laser should cause heat damage on the player HUD if they try to enter it immediately. Adding a cooldown period to the wall would make it more realistic.</p>
<p>E.	The final HECU battle is ridiculous on hard mode given the current level of balance and has been the subject of numerous complaints. The only way to beat it is to hunker in a corner and use magnum/shotgun or memorize the spawns of all of the soldiers. This kills immersion not to mention it defeats the purpose of having all of the defensive locations, since they don’t even get used. My aforementioned balance changes might help fix this (see above).</p>
<ol start="9">
<li>Surface Tension-<br>
A.	Would be nice to have the Apache continue to harass the player up to the cave battle if it hasn’t been damaged in the first confrontation. This is what happened in HL and made it more satisfying to kill it. If this is implemented, the Apache will likely need an accuracy nerf for its minigun.</li>
</ol>
<p>B.	Apache should get a health nerf and be balanced against RPG attacks/charged tau shots (see above). It currently takes too many RPGs and too few charged tau shots to kill it on hard mode.</p>
<p>C.	Some players have reported glitches in the cave battle with respect to the Apache’s pathing and positioning.</p>
<p>D.	The missing tentacle scene is a pretty iconic one and should be included in the level, either in its original incarnation or modified. Perhaps a cinematic sequence where it kills itself on some mines would be interesting…</p>
<p>E.	As many players have complained, the cuts to this level are really sorely felt as many iconic scenes are missing. While the revisions to On A Rail are reasonable, getting rid of C2A5F and C2A5G on Surface Tension significantly diminishes the storytelling aspect of HL. TextFAMGUY1 has been doing phenomenal job restoring these areas (<a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=I8HKlBxJ1NM" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=I8HKlBxJ1NM</a>, <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=7XhMNTDfCTs&amp;feature=BFa&amp;list=ULVmj0mnkwxN8" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=7XhMNTDfCTs&amp;feature=BFa&amp;list=ULVmj0mnkwxN8</a>) and the community really wants to see them integrated with BMS on Steam. Perhaps Joel could add a track or two to the new areas and the voice actors could chip in as well.</p>
<p>F.	The sniper bullet should look more like an actual rifle round.  It clearly looks like something from a Combine energy weapon in its current incarnation.</p>
<p>G.	The alien cannon should make an appearance somewhere in the game even though it’s been replaced by the Abrams. It’s such an unusual set piece and could be used to get rid of the HECU armored units in a scripted sequence (e.g. pair of alien grunts bring out an assembled cannon and use it to kill the Abrams).</p>
<p>H.	 At the end of surface tension, the Garguantua should be scripted to follow the player and only attack the tower once the player is on it. TextFAMGUY1 may be fixing this in his version of C2A5F.</p>
<p>I.	The mortar screen is incredibly glitchy with the mouse cursor sporadically flashing in place of the red dot. It is almost unusable, especially with the Garg shaking the tower.</p>
<p>J.	Post Xen-release touch-ups to Surface Tension and Forget about Freeman would be nice. In HL, you could see the invasion of Xen flora in various parts of the chapter. Perhaps they can be re-added to Black Mesa.</p>
<ol start="10">
<li>Forget about Freeman-<br>
A.	The water areas just prior to the ichthyosaur would be an ideal place to reintroduce leeches.  Just a few are fine.</li>
</ol>
<p>B.	The walkway that the player needs to crawl up after killing the ichthyosaur (just before the sentry turret/marine scene) is illogically designed.  It is completely surrounded by handrails and a ladder is placed inside the walkway rather than outside.  A section of the handrails needs to be removed and a ladder should be placed extending into the water.</p>
<p>C.	The marine that is killed by snarks is buggy.  Sometimes if you don’t look at him, the snarks will explode before he dies, in which case he just stands there with his itchy animation.</p>
<p>D.	During the tank scene, it should be possible for the aliens to kill the Abrahms.  As it stands now, the grunts just get within melee range in the tank’s dead spot and whack away with nothing happening.  Again, using the alien cannon here with a script would work well.  Alternatively, you could give the vortiguants an extreme buff versus mech units such that ~4 shots could destroy them.  Their energy attacks would wreak havoc on electronics so this is a realistic option.  Also, if you kill the tank too quickly, you may trap yourself in the room, which is a serious problem.</p>
<ol start="11">
<li>Lambda Core-<br>
A.	Possibly some pathing problems with the alien AI. The vortigaunts and alien grunts don’t always seem to recognize the player even when they have line of sight.</li>
</ol>
<p>B.	One or two of the alien controllers should be scripted to attack the scientist in the teleporter room if the player is not attacking them. This should force the player to engage rather than running in circles or hiding underneath the teleporter. If more than one controller is scripted, space them out over the course of the teleporter charge up to give the player more time to mop up.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/patch-suggestions/10979/26">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/patch-suggestions/10979/26</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 12 Dec 2012 01:50:08 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-10979-26</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/patch-suggestions/10979.rss">Patch Suggestions</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Patch Suggestions</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Zageron]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Only thing I agree with is HUD suit zoom shoot delay being removed.<br>
Makes working with the magnum a lot more difficult.  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=9" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/patch-suggestions/10979/25">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/patch-suggestions/10979/25</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 11 Dec 2012 07:25:18 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-10979-25</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/patch-suggestions/10979.rss">Patch Suggestions</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Patch Suggestions</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[ac3d]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="elivance">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/e/5f8ce5/40.png" class="avatar"> elivance:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>No…I can’t stand that half-ass zoom of hl2 crossbow.<br>
Finally BM devs made a good overlay fx(scope) and you want back that thing?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Lol I have changed my mind about almost everything on that list since it was posted, but I still stand by the HL2 scope, it’s just quicker, easier and more efficient to use then Black Mesa’s, and I’d take a more efficient scope over a prettier one any day.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/patch-suggestions/10979/24">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/patch-suggestions/10979/24</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 11 Dec 2012 06:41:34 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-10979-24</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/patch-suggestions/10979.rss">Patch Suggestions</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Patch Suggestions</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[All_our_Bass]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I know about editing the cfg file, posting it here means devs can see it.<br>
Also know about the zoom key, I was referring to HL2 where the crossbow zoom is higher than the regular one, and thus better for checking ahead.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/patch-suggestions/10979/23">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/patch-suggestions/10979/23</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 11 Dec 2012 06:04:51 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-10979-23</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/patch-suggestions/10979.rss">Patch Suggestions</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Patch Suggestions</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[ojcoolj]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="All_¥our_Bass">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 All_¥our_Bass:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I too liked the HL2 crossbow zoom, I sometimes would use it as a telescope to look around.</p>
<p>Not a huge deal for me either way personally though.</p>
<p>Weaker zombies or stronger shotgun, I double blasted a zombie at point blank range and it was still standing.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>There is a zoom button.</p>
<p>And you can just alter the .cfg files yourself</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/patch-suggestions/10979/22">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/patch-suggestions/10979/22</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 10 Dec 2012 23:09:02 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-10979-22</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/patch-suggestions/10979.rss">Patch Suggestions</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Patch Suggestions</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[All_our_Bass]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="elivance">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/e/5f8ce5/40.png" class="avatar"> elivance:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>No…I can’t stand that half-ass zoom of hl2 crossbow.<br>
Finally BM devs made a good overlay fx(scope) and you want back that thing?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I too liked the HL2 crossbow zoom, I sometimes would use it as a telescope to look around.</p>
<p>Not a huge deal for me either way personally though.</p>
<p>Weaker zombies or stronger shotgun, I double blasted a zombie at point blank range and it was still standing.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/patch-suggestions/10979/21">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/patch-suggestions/10979/21</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2012 23:23:49 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-10979-21</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/patch-suggestions/10979.rss">Patch Suggestions</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Patch Suggestions</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[ojcoolj]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>Black Mesa should play and feel like Half-Life 2 as much as possible</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>No.</p>
<p>It shouldn’t</p>
<p>Why would it need to?<br>
By that logic, Half Life 2 should play and feel like Half Life 1, which it doesn’t</p>
<p>But I still agree with some points</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/patch-suggestions/10979/20">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/patch-suggestions/10979/20</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2012 23:13:20 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-10979-20</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/patch-suggestions/10979.rss">Patch Suggestions</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Patch Suggestions</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[New_Flyer]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I find it odd that the Tram voice and security requires that you have your Security badge on at ALL TIMES, but not a single employee seems to wear one.</p>
<p>Maybe this should be fixed?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/patch-suggestions/10979/19">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/patch-suggestions/10979/19</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2012 19:01:17 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-10979-19</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/patch-suggestions/10979.rss">Patch Suggestions</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Patch Suggestions</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[elivance]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="ac3d">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/a/22d042/40.png" class="avatar"> ac3d:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Crossbow<br>
-BM and HL2 style zoom (optional)</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>No…I can’t stand that half-ass zoom of hl2 crossbow.<br>
Finally BM devs made a good overlay fx(scope) and you want back that thing?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/patch-suggestions/10979/18">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/patch-suggestions/10979/18</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2012 22:24:36 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-10979-18</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/patch-suggestions/10979.rss">Patch Suggestions</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Patch Suggestions</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[All_our_Bass]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Add in the HEV suit ‘greeting’ you when you first put it on.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/patch-suggestions/10979/17">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/patch-suggestions/10979/17</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2012 22:11:02 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-10979-17</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/patch-suggestions/10979.rss">Patch Suggestions</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Patch Suggestions</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Deathparade]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="ac3d">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/a/22d042/40.png" class="avatar"> ac3d:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Tl; dr<br>
Black Mesa should play and feel like Half-Life 2 as much as possible, [COLOR=‘Blue’]I thought this was a HALF-LIFE 1 remake those who have played the sequel but not the original will find it easier to adapt to its familiar play style.</p>
<p>Jumping<br>
[COLOR=‘Red’]-Make it easier to jump up onto ledges the same height or lower than the player, as in HL2<br>
-auto boost when jumping out of water onto ledges in Quake and HL1 needs to return<br>
-height and speed should be the same as HL2</p>
<p>Ladders<br>
[COLOR=‘Red’]-all mechanics should work the same as HL1 and HL: S, free movement, auto mount, etc.</p>
<p>Grenade<br>
[COLOR=‘Red’]-needs to be thrown more centred to the screen like HL2, currently it is thrown too far right and is easily obstructed by walls</p>
<p>Houndeye<br>
[COLOR=‘Red’]-sonic effect intensity (optional)</p>
<p>Crossbow<br>
-BM and HL2 style zoom (optional)</p>
<p>Soldiers<br>
-reaction time is fine, but their accuracy should be lower on easier difficulties</p>
<p>MP5<br>
-burst and auto firing rates (optional) [COLOR=‘Blue’]Not needed it isn’t Call of Duty you can do burst fire yourself</p>
<p>Crowbar<br>
-view bob when swinging (optional)<br>
-swing speed should be the same as in HL2</p>
<p>Player<br>
-strength for throwing objects should be lower<br>
-BM and HL2 style death animations (optional)<br>
-BM and HL2 weapon sprint animation styles (optional)<br>
-BM and HL2 style weapon sway (optional)<br>
-HL1 style screen glitch indicating crouch jump has been activated (optional)</p>
<p>HUD<br>
-remember last weapon used in sub-category (optional)<br>
-on-screen display for using trams, currently it is difficult to tell if tram has been engaged or not [COLOR=‘Blue’]I see no problem in this? i can see it fine<br>
-counters turn red when supply is low (optional)<br>
-damage indicators show when taking fall damage (optional)<br>
-HL2 style crosshair for HUD zoom<br>
-fire immediately after using HUD zoom as in HL2</p>
<p>Bugs<br>
[COLOR=‘Red’]-View roll selection does not save after quitting<br>
-Cannot turn off radioactive screen noise<br>
-Auto aim always appears enabled<br>
-c2a2c, door near the rocket control room leads outside the map, glass shouldn’t be breakable<br>
-Strange line appears on the shotgun when using flashlight</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>If you feel attacked by me sorry not the best english just that this mod is a Remake of Half-Life 1 and not 2!<br>
And yes i hated the ladders in BM…</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/patch-suggestions/10979/16">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/patch-suggestions/10979/16</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 22 Sep 2012 08:54:21 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-10979-16</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/patch-suggestions/10979.rss">Patch Suggestions</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Patch Suggestions</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[idclip]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Ronster">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/r/5f9b8f/40.png" class="avatar"> Ronster:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I Think that Vorts need to do more damage but slow their charge up time a bit too</p>
<p>HECU could do with being less acurate at distance and do less damage</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>The first for sure, the second maybe.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/patch-suggestions/10979/15">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/patch-suggestions/10979/15</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 22 Sep 2012 08:45:51 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-10979-15</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/patch-suggestions/10979.rss">Patch Suggestions</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Patch Suggestions</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Ronster]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I Think that Vorts need to do more damage but slow their charge up time a bit too</p>
<p>Bullsquids could also do with slight increased health but a slower pause between attacks as default.</p>
<p>HECU could do with being less acurate at distance and do less damage</p>
<p>The Houndeyes are fine and overall improved saying that all the enemies are improved it’s just off balance have not met the controllers as of yet though</p>
<p>Crouch jump should just be a default jump on one key.</p>
<p>The MP5 could do with adding more damage… When you shoot a headcrab with either the MP5 or the Glock it will no longer push a headcrab along the floor this is a sign that this weapon is now much lower than it was and should be put back to HL2 default value.</p>
<p>This may effect the HECU though armed with MP5’s so Hopefully lowering their accuracy will remedy this?</p>
<p>I don’t think the mechanics need a massive overhaul just small tweaks really.</p>
<p>It has been enjoyable and I do not plan to change anything until I play through it as the developers intended I will try some tweaks after completion</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/patch-suggestions/10979/14">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/patch-suggestions/10979/14</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 22 Sep 2012 08:18:38 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-10979-14</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/patch-suggestions/10979.rss">Patch Suggestions</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Patch Suggestions</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[intooblivion]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>All of your suggestions are bad and you should feel bad OP.<br>
Grenades were done WAY better in bm then they were in hl2, the only way I could control grenades to the level I wanted to was to toss them and grab them immediately with the use key. The 357 zoom is already covered by the ironsights, the 357 isn’t meant to be a sniper rifle.</p>
<p>Also, why the fuck would you want the strength of throwing to be lower?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/patch-suggestions/10979/13">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/patch-suggestions/10979/13</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 22 Sep 2012 03:42:32 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-10979-13</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/patch-suggestions/10979.rss">Patch Suggestions</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Patch Suggestions</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[BunnySlippers]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>Originally Posted by TCMOREIRA<br>
I disagree with most of your suggestions.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I also agree with this statement.</p>
<p>This is HL1 not HL2. It should be and play differently. And it does, and I like it a lot.</p>
<p>Part of what made the source engine so popular was the ability to adjust the game through cvars/commands. Many of the complainers need to Google “HL2 commands” learn how to tweak the game to your liking. Personally I love it as is right now. My only complaints are directed to my aging system that make certain areas harder then they really are. I just try a different strategy and keep moving on. I am really just baffled by the complaints about the HERC. I have a 7 year old computer, and really not having too much issue with the AI.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/patch-suggestions/10979/12">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/patch-suggestions/10979/12</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 22 Sep 2012 03:08:39 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-10979-12</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/patch-suggestions/10979.rss">Patch Suggestions</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Patch Suggestions</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[idclip]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="TCMOREIRA">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/t/c2a13f/40.png" class="avatar"> TCMOREIRA:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I disagree with most of your suggestions.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Yep!</p>
<p>I only agree on ladders, and nades.<br>
I could agree on the mp5 but Gordon isn’t a marine, he wasn’t trained to use it so it reasonable that he isn’t able to shot only on bullet. Maybe.<br>
Everything else: heck no! This is the remake of Half Life, if someone who played only HL2 has a problem to play it… well he/she has to deal with it, because Half Life born in this way.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/patch-suggestions/10979/11">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/patch-suggestions/10979/11</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 22 Sep 2012 02:27:18 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-10979-11</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/patch-suggestions/10979.rss">Patch Suggestions</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Patch Suggestions</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[TCMOREIRA]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I disagree with most of your suggestions.<br>
But about the crowbar, I like the idea behind BM’s crowbar, you really feel the weight and impact it has. But the movement it does it’s too repetitive and stiffy (that’s the only problem). Somewhy it feels unnatural until you get used to it.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/patch-suggestions/10979/10">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/patch-suggestions/10979/10</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 22 Sep 2012 01:52:49 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-10979-10</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/patch-suggestions/10979.rss">Patch Suggestions</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Patch Suggestions</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[bur]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>These are, in my opinion, the only changes that are needed:</p>
<p>//JUMP<br>
bms_normal_jump_vertical_speed				“190” //default 160<br>
bms_normal_jump_crouch_vertical_speed		“190” //default 160<br>
bms_double_jump_vertical_speed				“210” //default 180<br>
bms_airboost_jump_vertical_speed			“100” //default 70<br>
bms_long_jump_vertical_speed				“180” //default 150</p>
<p>//WEAPONS<br>
sk_plr_dmg_357						“40” //default 50<br>
sk_npc_dmg_357						“30” //default 15<br>
sk_max_357							“12” //default 18</p>
<p>//ENEMIES<br>
sk_npc_head							“3”</p>
<pre><code>sk_zombie_scientist_health				"50" //default 40
sk_zombie_security_health				"60" //default 50
sk_zombie_dmg_one_slash					"10" //default 15
sk_zombie_dmg_both_slash				"25" //default 30

sk_alien_slave_health					"100" //Default 38
sk_alien_slave_dmg_zap					"50" //default 10

sk_ichthyosaur_health				"200" //default 100
sk_ichthyosaur_melee_dmg			"8" //Default 15
</code></pre>
<p>All those values are from HL2, except the jump speeds. I just changed normal jump speed to HL2’s normal run speed, and changed the rest accordingly.<br>
Other things that are shared like the headcrab or the crowbar are already the same as in HL2.</p>
<p>Other than that, there’s only bug fixing and balancing, but I’d like to see a patch update HL2/eps with BM’s new assets, features and effects.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/patch-suggestions/10979/9">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/patch-suggestions/10979/9</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 22 Sep 2012 01:35:27 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-10979-9</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/patch-suggestions/10979.rss">Patch Suggestions</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Patch Suggestions</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[maxximo]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Hey guys, first we can fix, (or wait to the development updates) all the bugs and glitchs in BM like the collision props, and some animations, and THEN, we can talk about fix the difficult and other issues.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/patch-suggestions/10979/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/patch-suggestions/10979/8</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 21 Sep 2012 17:07:19 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-10979-8</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/patch-suggestions/10979.rss">Patch Suggestions</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Patch Suggestions</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[ShadowNate]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>The only bugs that I mind in BM are collision related.</p>
<p>There have been times that I couldn’t stack boxes on top of each other; they ended up overlapping. And I could go through one ladder, and few boxes/crates.</p>
<p>Otherwise I would like to experiment with some enemies rebalancing, but I’d prefer to test different settings myself and settle with one that is most to my liking.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/patch-suggestions/10979/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/patch-suggestions/10979/7</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 21 Sep 2012 16:59:49 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-10979-7</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/patch-suggestions/10979.rss">Patch Suggestions</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Patch Suggestions</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Dotard]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Honestly, this mod needs a lot of minor fixed and balance adjustments “_”</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/patch-suggestions/10979/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/patch-suggestions/10979/6</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 21 Sep 2012 16:37:04 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-10979-6</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/patch-suggestions/10979.rss">Patch Suggestions</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Patch Suggestions</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Bloodshot]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>You forgot to put “Buff Ichthyosaur” since they suck right now without skill.cfg changes</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/patch-suggestions/10979/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/patch-suggestions/10979/5</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 21 Sep 2012 15:28:22 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-10979-5</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/patch-suggestions/10979.rss">Patch Suggestions</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
