<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Persona 4 Endurance Run</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/persona-4-endurance-run/847</link>
    <description>It&#39;s quite possible that I&#39;m the only one who does, but does anyone else happen to follow the Endurance Run on Giant Bomb? [url=https://www.giantbomb.com/videos/]Click the Endurance Run thing at the top.[/url]

I don&#39;t know how to say it in an inviting way, so I&#39;ll just say this: It is two dudes playing some batshit insane JRPG and talking over it. And it is hilarious. It&#39;s probably the only instance I can imagine where watching someone play a game is more fun than playing it yourself.

There&#39;s a hella lot of videos, but it&#39;s good if you have a summer to waste. Like myself.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 15 Jul 2009 06:32:07 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Technology and Gaming</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/persona-4-endurance-run/847.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Persona 4 Endurance Run</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Nuclear_Spoon]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>It’s quite possible that I’m the only one who does, but does anyone else happen to follow the Endurance Run on Giant Bomb? <a href="https://www.giantbomb.com/videos/" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Click the Endurance Run thing at the top.</a></p>
<p>I don’t know how to say it in an inviting way, so I’ll just say this: It is two dudes playing some batshit insane JRPG and talking over it. And it is hilarious. It’s probably the only instance I can imagine where watching someone play a game is more fun than playing it yourself.</p>
<p>There’s a hella lot of videos, but it’s good if you have a summer to waste. Like myself.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/persona-4-endurance-run/847/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/persona-4-endurance-run/847/1</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jul 2009 06:32:07 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-847-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/persona-4-endurance-run/847.rss">Persona 4 Endurance Run</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
