<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Did you find Surface Tension lacking? The answer: Surface Tension Uncut</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/did-you-find-surface-tension-lacking-the-answer-surface-tension-uncut/11956</link>
    <description>@Mods: Be kind please, I&#39;m trying to spread the word. Leak-free is a ghost town.


[b][u]Introduction[/u][/b][/SIZE]

I&#39;m sure many people, myself included, found the final section of Surface Tension in Black Mesa lacking in some respects. Rightly so, the Black Mesa devs cut out an entire map from HL1&#39;s version and the scene with the Gargantua was hastily pasted onto the end of Black Mesa&#39;s Surface Tension. Lots of rumours fly around that the reason the ending of Surface Tension was so rushed is because the developer left halfway through, and the evidence in the mapping certainly supports this, but I have no conclusive proof. It&#39;s a shame because the rest of Surface Tension was brilliant in almost every single way, it felt wrong for there not to be this fitting, grand conclusion to what basically amounts to the climax of the entire game. 

No more. After the initial disappointment of the ending of Surface Tension, I took it upon myself to personally rectify this. This thread is to advertise my mod, Surface Tension Uncut, which adds back to the chapter what the Black Mesa devs left out.

I strongly felt that the omission of the cut map really harmed the storytelling element of the game, and lessened the impact of Forget About Freeman, as well as removing some iconic scenes from the first game. Seeing all the battles between the aliens and the HECU in Half-Life was one of the most awesome features of Surface Tension, and was definitely missing from Black Mesa. It also tied the story together - it simply [b]made sense[/b] in Half-Life&#39;s Forget About Freeman when the military decided to pull out, but it didn&#39;t really have the same effect in Black Mesa due to the lack of fighting between the military and aliens as observed by the player.


[i]You can find the leak-free thread for this mod [url=&#39;https://forums.blackmesasource.com/showthread.php?t=15065&#39;]here[/url] (by far the most viewed thread on that subforum, 114 pages of discussion and counting!)
You can find my [url=&#39;https://www.moddb.com/mods/black-mesa-surface-tension-uncut&#39;]ModDB page here[/url].[/i]

[b][u]About Surface Tension Uncut[/u][/b][/SIZE]

This project has been in development for 3 months now, and it&#39;s finally complete. Having finished developing this mod, I now feel comfortable releasing it to the general public. It&#39;s been EXTENSIVELY tested with an exhaustive dialogue with the community on leak-free - there have actually been 9 community beta versions already. We&#39;ve all worked hard to absolutely bring these maps up to standard, and I personally strongly feel they are every bit as good as anything Black Mesa has delivered.

This mod is an add-on to Black Mesa. When you install it, it adds 3 maps to Black Mesa&#39;s Surface Tension chapter, which slot in naturally with the rest of the campaign. It must be added to an existing installation of Black Mesa, and as such requires Black Mesa to work. The maps link seamlessly into Black Mesa&#39;s campaign and restore Surface Tension to its former Half-Life 1 glory, possibly even beyond it. I&#39;ve worked hard to dramatically expand the scope and vision of the map, and deliver the grand climax which Surface Tension deserves.

Here&#39;s a brief description of the way in which my mod works:
[quote]
* Black Mesa&#39;s Surface Tension comprises of the maps C2A5A --&gt; C2A5G
* C2A5G is the final map of ST in Black Mesa, which is where the chapter was heavily cut from its Half-Life 1 version. The Gargantua chase was merged with the &quot;vent drop&quot; scene, and all of C2A5F from Half-Life 1 was cut here. They cut C2A5F out and merged the map with the Garg chase.



[list]
[*]My maps range from C2A5G --&gt; C2A5I.
* This expands ST by 3 maps.
* My 3 maps are basically a re-make of Half-Life&#39;s C2A5F, but dramatically expanded, changed, and hopefully, improved.
* C2A5I is Black Mesa&#39;s Gargantua Chase, but re-imagined and &quot;fixed&quot;. The Gargantua no longer humps the tower all day.
* My maps flow seamlessly into one another and connect seamlessly with the main campaign.
[/*:m][/list:u]
[/quote]
[b][u]Downloading and playing[/u][/b][/SIZE]

[u][b][i][url=&#39;https://www.mediafire.com/?45gvj44576y6qcj&#39;]Latest Version: 1.11 (Hotfixed) - Final Release. Download here.[/url][/i][/b][/u][/SIZE]
[COLOR=&#39;Red&#39;]I URGE YOU TO READ THE README AND THE INSTALLATION INSTRUCTIONS BEFORE USING MY MAPS. I WILL NOT BE HELD RESPONSIBLE FOR ANY PROBLEMS WHICH COULD HAVE BEEN SOLVED BY READING THE README.

Bear in mind that my maps replace some stock Black Mesa content, so back up stuff you&#39;re not prepared to lose.

Read the readme for detailed installation instructions, but otherwise, simply extract the contents of the zip to your BMS folder and play Surface Tension. Everything else works perfectly on its own.

[b][u]Media (Screenshots/Videos)[/u][/SIZE][/b]

[url=&#39;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=2nJCg9n5ueI&amp;lc=E-bqejSalGHxzfrb5KZgfenNuDlsT8jB9Jg8VRxN6ZQ&#39;]Click here for a walkthrough of all 3 maps[/url] with a developer commentary from me. I strongly recommend that you watch this, to gain insight into my reasoning for changes and certain bugs. This video is a little outdated (1 or 2 versions old), but the basic design of the mod hasn&#39;t changed much since then.

![](upload://fQkuRDcR50btM3BgDXXDw94DLM2.jpeg)
The first major part of my mod. Dramatically expanded and darkened from HL1&#39;s version, as well as given a proper theme. This large multi-story carpark sets the scene for large scale battles you will be seeing throughout ST Uncut.

![](upload://mufEsSflB7LEIxahAya4jbaXBHl.jpeg)
Top floor of the parking lot. The combat encounter which takes place here is especially fun, and is an entirely new encounter not seen in the original.

![](upload://w8TXqj0q0myg2MlLQcpDgd3pAU7.jpeg)
The &quot;street battle&quot;. The player gets a top down view of a deadly battle between the HECU and Aliens. The vent on the left hand side of the picture is where the player will encounter Snarks, and also the revised &quot;vent drop&quot; scene.

![](upload://exff700pfxRR25NNS9OeTKVJiWf.jpeg)
The Garage after the vent drop. Fairly significantly changed from its HL1 counterpart, but visually consistent with the other garages seen throughout Black Mesa&#39;s Surface Tension. Also home to a reimagined &quot;ambush&quot; involving explosives.

![](upload://oH4BWEhljIkblLZ4etYA8wIEifj.jpeg)
COMPLETELY re-imagined TOW courtyard. The original&#39;s design was very bland and generic, and I&#39;ve given it a serious overhaul. Also take note of the expansive 3d skybox, which really helps to provide a sense of scale.

![](upload://3tycsB77TAjRzEvoSFjv33Z0YOa.jpeg)
Alternate view of the TOW courtyard.

![](upload://l5mO8a4WHYYoUob3x2Nir4BtePf.jpeg)
The warehouse in Half-Life 1 was home to a large scale battle between the HECU and the Aliens. It&#39;s been re-imagined into an outdoor battle to allow for some impressive aerial set pieces. This battle is the highlight and climax of the first map.

![](upload://vfKjQu7cbRnHimqlMkF5hjAswVX.jpeg)
The &quot;Abrams Battle,&quot; which in HL1 was a very nicely scripted outdoor battle which the player is privy to. In my mod it&#39;s the setting for an extremely large scale battle involving multiple aerial elements, ~25 ground units (in waves), and a tank. An awesome battle made even more epic by use of Joel Nielsen&#39;s unused On A Rail track.

![](upload://iCai6LX1SRYcjUIsVQzSUJeqPuw.jpeg)
Alternate shot of the same area, later on during the fight.

![](upload://6T4Hya0xwC1J846FcGtfcvU2s2m.jpeg)
The rooftops the player must climb onto after the battle is one. This area is home to a new Sniper encounter at long range and provides another great sense of scale.

![](upload://f3GeeCJrMjVoMkLKwZuVJSzMQUl.jpeg)
![](upload://ftzfToTOBrxMr2gR1q2C1kuvIC7.jpeg)
2 shots of the re-imagined &quot;Furnace Room,&quot; now home to a new puzzle.

[b][u]What&#39;s next?[/u][/SIZE][/b]

Now that Surface Tension Uncut is done and dusted, I&#39;ve moved my focus to the other extremely cut chapter in Black Mesa - &quot;On a Rail&quot;. I&#39;ve just today started work on OaR Uncut and expect to have it completed within roughly the same timeframe. It aims to restore OaR to its former length/glory whilst also maintaining the same redesigning principles which Black Mesa gave it. I may or may not combine ST Uncut with OaR Uncut to create &quot;Black Mesa Uncut,&quot; which will be an unofficial expansion to the game.

[b][u]Frequently Asked Questions (FAQ)[/u][/SIZE][/b]

[b]Q: How does this affect my Black Mesa campaign, or more specifically, Surface Tension?[/b]
A: My map expands gameplay in Surface Tension by 30 - 45 minutes. It ADDS to what&#39;s already there. None of Surface Tension is affected aside from C2A5G, which in Black Mesa&#39;s version of Surface Tension, is the very last map.

[b]Q: I see you&#39;ve included the first map of Forget About Freeman in your release. Why? Do I have to install it?[/b]
A: If you want the maps to link up with the rest of the campaign, then yes. It&#39;s to do with the way Source handles level changing. Linked maps must contain references to one another. Forget About Freeman&#39;s first map (C3A1A) originally had links to C2A5G (the last map of ST under the BM Dev Team&#39;s version). With my extensions, Forget About Freeman is now linked to C2A5I (which under MY version is the last map of Surface Tension). I didn&#39;t change anything else on Forget About Freeman aside from the map linkage. You don&#39;t HAVE to install it, but C2A5I will crash once you complete it if you don&#39;t.
[b]
Q: Will this be integrated into Black Mesa properly, or remain a fan project?[/b]
A: I don&#39;t know! If the devs approach me asking if they can use my stuff, I&#39;m sure as heck going to say yes! I&#39;d be very proud if something like that were to happen. But I have no plans to approach them.

[b]Q: Why was Surface Tension cut so badly?[/b]
A: The mapper left halfway through the project, and there are probably other reasons too. Either way, I don&#39;t blame the team. The rest of Surface Tension was actually brilliant, the biggest problem was it didn&#39;t have a fitting end like it did in Half-Life 1.

[b]Q: How do I install this?[/b]
A: Read the readme.

[b][u]Credits[/u][/SIZE][/b]

-The Black Mesa dev team for creating such an astonishing game with fantastic maps, especially their Surface Tension chapters!
-Valve for creating the amazing Half-Life universe in the first place, and their groundbreaking series.
-Me (Text FAMGUY1) for all the mapping and design, I did this pretty much all singlehandedly.
-One Free Man (from Facepunch) for fixing the UV mapping bug on one of the stock Black Mesa models for me.
-Mbit, for figuring out the solution to the Osprey pieces doing damage, and proposing a few architectural changes.
-Ronster for helping me get the satchel pipe scene to work properly.
-Conti, for his amazing photoshop mockups and effort on my behalf.
-CFoust for creating Propper, a very useful tool which I&#39;ve made good use of. If you&#39;re a mapper, check it out!
-Joel Nielsen for his awesome music, one old song of which I used in this map set.
-The community at large (particularly Tian Wang (Wangman), Ronster, Dadster, and JessieStorm) for providing me with tonnes of feedback and giving me tips and tricks on how to make things work and how to design areas.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 15 May 2013 20:39:19 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Show Off</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/did-you-find-surface-tension-lacking-the-answer-surface-tension-uncut/11956.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Did you find Surface Tension lacking? The answer: Surface Tension Uncut</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[The_Scientist]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Great mod of a mod.<br>
Not so easy in places  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=9" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/did-you-find-surface-tension-lacking-the-answer-surface-tension-uncut/11956/49">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/did-you-find-surface-tension-lacking-the-answer-surface-tension-uncut/11956/49</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2013 20:39:19 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11956-49</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/did-you-find-surface-tension-lacking-the-answer-surface-tension-uncut/11956.rss">Did you find Surface Tension lacking? The answer: Surface Tension Uncut</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Did you find Surface Tension lacking? The answer: Surface Tension Uncut</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[sm00t]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I was AGREEING with what his post had to say, not thanking…</p>
<p>And the last time I was a “FAN” “of anything” was watching my grandsons baseball team…</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/did-you-find-surface-tension-lacking-the-answer-surface-tension-uncut/11956/48">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/did-you-find-surface-tension-lacking-the-answer-surface-tension-uncut/11956/48</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jan 2013 17:11:38 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11956-48</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/did-you-find-surface-tension-lacking-the-answer-surface-tension-uncut/11956.rss">Did you find Surface Tension lacking? The answer: Surface Tension Uncut</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Did you find Surface Tension lacking? The answer: Surface Tension Uncut</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[bur]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>well, whatever, doesn’t bother me anyway</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/did-you-find-surface-tension-lacking-the-answer-surface-tension-uncut/11956/47">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/did-you-find-surface-tension-lacking-the-answer-surface-tension-uncut/11956/47</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jan 2013 15:14:53 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11956-47</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/did-you-find-surface-tension-lacking-the-answer-surface-tension-uncut/11956.rss">Did you find Surface Tension lacking? The answer: Surface Tension Uncut</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Did you find Surface Tension lacking? The answer: Surface Tension Uncut</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Wangman]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><a class="mention" href="/u/bur">@bur</a><br>
“@ fans” or some bs like that…bout as useful as thanking your mother in a video game.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/did-you-find-surface-tension-lacking-the-answer-surface-tension-uncut/11956/46">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/did-you-find-surface-tension-lacking-the-answer-surface-tension-uncut/11956/46</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jan 2013 04:24:55 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11956-46</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/did-you-find-surface-tension-lacking-the-answer-surface-tension-uncut/11956.rss">Did you find Surface Tension lacking? The answer: Surface Tension Uncut</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Did you find Surface Tension lacking? The answer: Surface Tension Uncut</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[bur]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Crypt19">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Crypt19:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>That’s <span class="bbcode-i">my</span> point.</p>
<p>No one likes the silence, but they have good reason.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>However, this:</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="cman2k">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/c/4bbf92/40.png" class="avatar"> cman2k:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>At this time, no exceptions. We reserve the right to change our minds later.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>And the quality of these maps is something they’d change their minds over, I imagine.</p>
<p>Also, Wangman, maybe I’m remembering incorrectly, but I think there is a thank you to the community in the credits. Not the forums specifically, but it’s basically the same thing.</p>
<p>As for the devs’ silence, the non-disclosure agreement from Greenlight seems like a good reason to me.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/did-you-find-surface-tension-lacking-the-answer-surface-tension-uncut/11956/45">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/did-you-find-surface-tension-lacking-the-answer-surface-tension-uncut/11956/45</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jan 2013 23:25:11 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11956-45</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/did-you-find-surface-tension-lacking-the-answer-surface-tension-uncut/11956.rss">Did you find Surface Tension lacking? The answer: Surface Tension Uncut</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Did you find Surface Tension lacking? The answer: Surface Tension Uncut</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[sm00t]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>What Bur said +1</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/did-you-find-surface-tension-lacking-the-answer-surface-tension-uncut/11956/44">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/did-you-find-surface-tension-lacking-the-answer-surface-tension-uncut/11956/44</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jan 2013 17:06:41 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11956-44</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/did-you-find-surface-tension-lacking-the-answer-surface-tension-uncut/11956.rss">Did you find Surface Tension lacking? The answer: Surface Tension Uncut</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Did you find Surface Tension lacking? The answer: Surface Tension Uncut</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Dotard]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I guess those community works were simply to kill time, nothing to be used.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/did-you-find-surface-tension-lacking-the-answer-surface-tension-uncut/11956/43">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/did-you-find-surface-tension-lacking-the-answer-surface-tension-uncut/11956/43</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jan 2013 10:11:42 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11956-43</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/did-you-find-surface-tension-lacking-the-answer-surface-tension-uncut/11956.rss">Did you find Surface Tension lacking? The answer: Surface Tension Uncut</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Did you find Surface Tension lacking? The answer: Surface Tension Uncut</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Wangman]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Dotard">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/d/d26b3c/40.png" class="avatar"> Dotard:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Ur right, even the Greenlight might have changed things a bit.<br>
About crediting, there’s also a custom furnace model in your “mini-mod” I doubt they would want to credit 5 or more people that weren’t even official devs. But I don’t know more shit about it than you do. But as you said, if they had any problems with it’s existence, they would have said something long ago… so it’s best either to contact them or to wait till they release an update and then act.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>This is a stupid-ass and selfish way of looking at crediting.  Credit MUST be given where it’s due…it’s only fair, especially when it comes in the form of either physical work or ideas that are ultimately executed.  I was never on this forum until ST uncut but dropped by periodically over the years and there was one poster who consistently wrote up good ideas…I believe he was the one who came up w/the portal storm in FaF.  He really should have been credited for this stuff over the years but I doubt he was.  Hell, there’s not even a fucking thank you to the BMS forums for their contributions either.  There really needs to be one after the Xen patch, at least crediting people who’ve made major contributions to bug testing, balancing etc.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/did-you-find-surface-tension-lacking-the-answer-surface-tension-uncut/11956/42">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/did-you-find-surface-tension-lacking-the-answer-surface-tension-uncut/11956/42</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jan 2013 08:40:09 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11956-42</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/did-you-find-surface-tension-lacking-the-answer-surface-tension-uncut/11956.rss">Did you find Surface Tension lacking? The answer: Surface Tension Uncut</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Did you find Surface Tension lacking? The answer: Surface Tension Uncut</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[TextFAMGUY1]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Crypt19">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Crypt19:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>That’s <span class="bbcode-i">my</span> point.</p>
<p>No one likes the silence, but they have good reason.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>That’s not a “good reason”. That’s a statement with no justification. Them having a “good reason” is just as much speculation as anything else that’s gone on in this thread. But, Bur’s probably right. Doesn’t really need to be discussed further.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/did-you-find-surface-tension-lacking-the-answer-surface-tension-uncut/11956/41">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/did-you-find-surface-tension-lacking-the-answer-surface-tension-uncut/11956/41</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jan 2013 02:44:01 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11956-41</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/did-you-find-surface-tension-lacking-the-answer-surface-tension-uncut/11956.rss">Did you find Surface Tension lacking? The answer: Surface Tension Uncut</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Did you find Surface Tension lacking? The answer: Surface Tension Uncut</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypt]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="bur">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/b/87869e/40.png" class="avatar"> bur:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Honestly, I don’t know what you guys are arguing over. The Test Chamber subforum proves that they wouldn’t discard community work off-hand purely on principle. They have actually <span class="bbcode-i">asked</span> the community to contribute to the mod, as they have done in the past as well.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="cman2k">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/c/4bbf92/40.png" class="avatar"> cman2k:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Not allowed:<br>
–Maps<br>
–Sounds</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>That’s <span class="bbcode-i">my</span> point.</p>
<p>No one likes the silence, but they have good reason.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/did-you-find-surface-tension-lacking-the-answer-surface-tension-uncut/11956/40">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/did-you-find-surface-tension-lacking-the-answer-surface-tension-uncut/11956/40</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jan 2013 02:08:50 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11956-40</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/did-you-find-surface-tension-lacking-the-answer-surface-tension-uncut/11956.rss">Did you find Surface Tension lacking? The answer: Surface Tension Uncut</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Did you find Surface Tension lacking? The answer: Surface Tension Uncut</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Dotard]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Hmm… reminds me of someone ;D</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/did-you-find-surface-tension-lacking-the-answer-surface-tension-uncut/11956/39">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/did-you-find-surface-tension-lacking-the-answer-surface-tension-uncut/11956/39</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jan 2013 23:46:17 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11956-39</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/did-you-find-surface-tension-lacking-the-answer-surface-tension-uncut/11956.rss">Did you find Surface Tension lacking? The answer: Surface Tension Uncut</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Did you find Surface Tension lacking? The answer: Surface Tension Uncut</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[bur]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Honestly, I don’t know what you guys are arguing over. The Test Chamber subforum proves that they wouldn’t discard community work off-hand purely on principle. They have actually <span class="bbcode-i">asked</span> the community to contribute to the mod, as they have done in the past as well.</p>
<p>Also, don’t be discouraged by silence. That’s how it’s always been with the dev team, as far as I’ve heard. Communication is not their greatest skill, it seems  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=9" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/did-you-find-surface-tension-lacking-the-answer-surface-tension-uncut/11956/38">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/did-you-find-surface-tension-lacking-the-answer-surface-tension-uncut/11956/38</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jan 2013 23:39:38 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11956-38</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/did-you-find-surface-tension-lacking-the-answer-surface-tension-uncut/11956.rss">Did you find Surface Tension lacking? The answer: Surface Tension Uncut</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Did you find Surface Tension lacking? The answer: Surface Tension Uncut</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[TextFAMGUY1]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Dotard">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/d/d26b3c/40.png" class="avatar"> Dotard:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Ur right, even the Greenlight might have changed things a bit.<br>
About crediting, there’s also a custom furnace model in your “mini-mod” I doubt they would want to credit 5 or more people that weren’t even official devs. But I don’t know more shit about it than you do. But as you said, if they had any problems with it’s existence, they would have said something long ago… so it’s best either to contact them or to wait till they release an update and then act.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I created the custom furnace model myself. There is ONE SINGLE small piece of work in my mod that was done by someone else, everything else I did myself. One Free Man, from Facepunch, fixed the broken UV mapping on a stock Black Mesa model for me. Thus, we are the only two who would require crediting - and in all honesty the BM Dev team could fix the UV mapping in about 10 seconds themselves if they didn’t want to credit yet another person - so it shouldn’t be a problem, as stated.</p>
<p>We’ll just have to wait and see. And I did already contact them, by applying to join the dev team. I’ve received total silence on that front, so I assume it to be a no.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/did-you-find-surface-tension-lacking-the-answer-surface-tension-uncut/11956/37">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/did-you-find-surface-tension-lacking-the-answer-surface-tension-uncut/11956/37</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jan 2013 19:26:33 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11956-37</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/did-you-find-surface-tension-lacking-the-answer-surface-tension-uncut/11956.rss">Did you find Surface Tension lacking? The answer: Surface Tension Uncut</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Did you find Surface Tension lacking? The answer: Surface Tension Uncut</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Dotard]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Ur right, even the Greenlight might have changed things a bit.<br>
About crediting, there’s also a custom furnace model in your “mini-mod” I doubt they would want to credit 5 or more people that weren’t even official devs. But I don’t know more shit about it than you do. But as you said, if they had any problems with it’s existence, they would have said something long ago… so it’s best either to contact them or to wait till they release an update and then act.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/did-you-find-surface-tension-lacking-the-answer-surface-tension-uncut/11956/36">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/did-you-find-surface-tension-lacking-the-answer-surface-tension-uncut/11956/36</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jan 2013 19:11:38 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11956-36</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/did-you-find-surface-tension-lacking-the-answer-surface-tension-uncut/11956.rss">Did you find Surface Tension lacking? The answer: Surface Tension Uncut</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Did you find Surface Tension lacking? The answer: Surface Tension Uncut</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[TextFAMGUY1]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Dotard">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/d/d26b3c/40.png" class="avatar"> Dotard:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>It would be best to email the project’s leader. Also, the only reason for I see they wouldn’t want to include community work is a possibility of a dispute about license/ownership rights.<br>
Like:<br>
(BM) “we proudly present the finished Black Mesa mod after work has concluded on Xen and DM along with restored ST and OaR”<br>
(x community work creator) “hey, credit me, it’s my work!!!”<br>
(BM) “but our assets!!!”<br>
Get it?</p>
<p>It’s likely to prevent hassles.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>That shouldn’t be an issue. Black Mesa was released under a Noncommercial Creative Commons License, and I made sure to release my final ST version under the same license too. They’re quite free to incorporate my work into their own, even without my consent. The only “legal” requirement, as far as I can understand, is that I’m credited. They’re free to modify and use my work however they wish, as long as I’m credited, from what I understand. And that seriously shouldn’t be an issue either, it literally involves adding my name to the credits, and that’s it, which shouldn’t be objectionable at all. The same would apply to any community made works, assuming they released them “correctly”. But, licensing is a very complicated issue, so maybe I’m wrong, but I don’t think so.</p>
<p>The only potential issue I can see in terms of license/ownership rights could possibly due to their agreement/contract/whatever with Valve, which would happen as a result of them being Greenlit and eventually ending up on Steam. That could possibly cause issues, but I just don’t know. I’ve seen plenty of Steam games incorporate community content with very little problem, and those were commercial titles, rather than free Source mods.</p>
<p>This is all speculation, in the end. But it’s an interesting debate, I suppose.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/did-you-find-surface-tension-lacking-the-answer-surface-tension-uncut/11956/35">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/did-you-find-surface-tension-lacking-the-answer-surface-tension-uncut/11956/35</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jan 2013 18:58:03 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11956-35</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/did-you-find-surface-tension-lacking-the-answer-surface-tension-uncut/11956.rss">Did you find Surface Tension lacking? The answer: Surface Tension Uncut</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Did you find Surface Tension lacking? The answer: Surface Tension Uncut</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Dotard]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>It would be best to email the project’s leader. Also, the only reason for I see they wouldn’t want to include community work is a possibility of a dispute about license/ownership rights.<br>
Like:<br>
(BM) “we proudly present the finished Black Mesa mod after work has concluded on Xen and DM along with restored ST and OaR”<br>
(x community work creator) “hey, credit me, it’s my work!!!”<br>
(BM) “but our assets!!!”<br>
Get it?</p>
<p>It’s likely to prevent hassles.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/did-you-find-surface-tension-lacking-the-answer-surface-tension-uncut/11956/34">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/did-you-find-surface-tension-lacking-the-answer-surface-tension-uncut/11956/34</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jan 2013 18:19:11 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11956-34</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/did-you-find-surface-tension-lacking-the-answer-surface-tension-uncut/11956.rss">Did you find Surface Tension lacking? The answer: Surface Tension Uncut</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Did you find Surface Tension lacking? The answer: Surface Tension Uncut</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[TextFAMGUY1]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Crypt19">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Crypt19:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Before I go, I wanna say if this starts sounding rude, it’s not intentional.</p>
<p>Anyway, I apologize for putting my opinions the way I did. By “I doubt it,” I was going on the idea that many mods and games that I’ve played tend to focus more on fixing bugs than bits that didn’t feel up to par. And I agree that I should probably have played the latest version before making assumptions, but you don’t have to be so defensive about it. I did specify that only <span class="bbcode-i">a few bits</span> seemed to not be up to par, but considering you’re assuring me that the versions are so far apart than this may not be the case anymore. You’re acting like I said your work was bad altogether. Considering a shit load (thousands? <span class="bbcode-i">millions?</span>) of people think Black Mesa is so amazingly great - including me - you should still feel like your work is good if your only just under that level of quality.</p>
<p>I’m also not trying to project the devs as “magical” or any of that sort. I’m simply saying that not only are they not accepting maps to be implemented, (that should be enough for my point, anyway) but this is such a large portion of the game that <span class="bbcode-i"><span class="bbcode-b">I</span></span> wouldn’t be surprised if they didn’t wish to implement it. Not everyone wants to take large additions to their game, quality is irrelevant with this point.</p>
<p>It’s not about them being messianic or anything, because they’re not, they’re just people with talent. It’s about Black Mesa being <span class="bbcode-i">their team’s game.</span> Valve may be famous for taking in people’s work because it’s good, but you never hear, “This guy’s good with Cryengine! Crytek should hire him!” But you hear that type of thing everywhere with Valve and it’s modding community. But there’s something about the Black Mesa Team: they’re not Valve. I’ve seen people mentioning the Hazard Course project as hopefully being implemented, which I think is just as unlikely, if not more so. Same with that Blue Shift game. As far as they’re concerned, it could simply be “other people’s mod’s using our assets.”</p>
<p>Which is exactly what they are.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I won’t focus on the question of quality here, because that’s already addressed. If you think parts of the work aren’t up to scratch, that’s cool, I won’t be able to persuade you otherwise. So we can leave that issue behind as it will probably just cause aggravation. I probably shouldn’t have been as defensive as I was, but, hey, it’s my work, I’m allowed to get a bit touchy about it.</p>
<p>Let’s focus on the question of the team implementing not just my work, but works from the community as a whole. Here’s one thing which sets the Hazard Course and ST Uncut very far apart from other works like Uplink/Blue Shift, and any other community mods - we are both recreating things which were ACTUALLY IN HALF-LIFE 1. Black Mesa is supposed to be a remake of Half-Life 1, yet it’s distinctly incomplete in that regard. Xen, is understandable, they’re still working on that - but the omission of Hazard Course, the chapters from OaR and ST, is very puzzling. I understand the team may very well have their reasons - but at least from my perspective it seems fairly perplexing to intentionally leave parts of the original out in what’s supposed to be THE DEFINITIVE remake. I’m not suggesting “Warts and all,” but it seems a tad haphazard to intentionally leave stuff out in a remake. Most HD remakes replicate their original games EXACTLY in this regard, but Black Mesa is supposed to be a step above a typical HD remake, and it certainly is. Which is why I find it bizarre that it falls slightly short on the simplest hurdle of HD remakes several leagues below it.</p>
<p>Again, I just want to make sure everyone knows I’m not crying “Black Mesa needs to implement my work or it’s bad.” Quite the opposite. They can do whatever the hell they like with it, it’s their work, and I never expected anything from the devs anyway in that regard. I’m quite happy to have my little mod sitting where it is right now. But, let’s think about it <span class="bbcode-i">pragmatically for a minute here</span>. There are a few possibilities which exist currently, with regards to Hazard Course/ST Uncut/anything else from the community (such as re-animations/reskins/remodels, etc etc):</p>
<ol>
<li>They implement things like that into Black Mesa, perhaps with a bit of tweaking here and there. The mod now has more quality content with minimal work from the devs. Seems to me like everybody wins here.</li>
<li>They do not implement any community works, and instead do those works themselves. Sure, that’s fine - but it seems like a waste of time FOR EVERYONE when the work has already been done once. In the end I guess there’s still more content in Black Mesa, but their time might have been better spent elsewhere. I personally will be quite angry if their next update includes THEIR OWN take on the cut ST chapters/Hazard Course/whatever. Not because they didn’t choose to include my stuff - but I’ve seen quite a few devs in my forum thread - I would have very much appreciated a heads-up “by the way, we’re already working on this, you might be wasting your time” from them.</li>
<li>They do nothing involving community works. Black Mesa is now intentionally left with less quality content, purely because of principle. It’s still a fantastic game, no doubt, but…doesn’t necessarily live up to what it could be.</li>
</ol>
<p>You see my point?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/did-you-find-surface-tension-lacking-the-answer-surface-tension-uncut/11956/33">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/did-you-find-surface-tension-lacking-the-answer-surface-tension-uncut/11956/33</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jan 2013 17:38:22 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11956-33</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/did-you-find-surface-tension-lacking-the-answer-surface-tension-uncut/11956.rss">Did you find Surface Tension lacking? The answer: Surface Tension Uncut</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Did you find Surface Tension lacking? The answer: Surface Tension Uncut</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypt]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Before I go, I wanna say if this starts sounding rude, it’s not intentional.</p>
<p>Anyway, I apologize for putting my opinions the way I did. By “I doubt it,” I was going on the idea that many mods and games that I’ve played tend to focus more on fixing bugs than bits that didn’t feel up to par. And I agree that I should probably have played the latest version before making assumptions, but you don’t have to be so defensive about it. I did specify that only <span class="bbcode-i">a few bits</span> seemed to not be up to par, but considering you’re assuring me that the versions are so far apart than this may not be the case anymore. You’re acting like I said your work was bad altogether. Considering a shit load (thousands? <span class="bbcode-i">millions?</span>) of people think Black Mesa is so amazingly great - including me - you should still feel like your work is good if your only just under that level of quality.</p>
<p>I’m also not trying to project the devs as “magical” or any of that sort. I’m simply saying that not only are they not accepting maps to be implemented, (that should be enough for my point, anyway) but this is such a large portion of the game that <span class="bbcode-i"><span class="bbcode-b">I</span></span> wouldn’t be surprised if they didn’t wish to implement it. Not everyone wants to take large additions to their game, quality is irrelevant with this point.</p>
<p>It’s not about them being messianic or anything, because they’re not, they’re just people with talent. It’s about Black Mesa being <span class="bbcode-i">their team’s game.</span> Valve may be famous for taking in people’s work because it’s good, but you never hear, “This guy’s good with Cryengine! Crytek should hire him!” But you hear that type of thing everywhere with Valve and it’s modding community. But there’s something about the Black Mesa Team: they’re not Valve. I’ve seen people mentioning the Hazard Course project as hopefully being implemented, which I think is just as unlikely, if not more so. Same with that Blue Shift game. As far as they’re concerned, it could simply be “other people’s mod’s using our assets.”</p>
<p>Which is exactly what they are.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/did-you-find-surface-tension-lacking-the-answer-surface-tension-uncut/11956/32">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/did-you-find-surface-tension-lacking-the-answer-surface-tension-uncut/11956/32</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jan 2013 16:24:36 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11956-32</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/did-you-find-surface-tension-lacking-the-answer-surface-tension-uncut/11956.rss">Did you find Surface Tension lacking? The answer: Surface Tension Uncut</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Did you find Surface Tension lacking? The answer: Surface Tension Uncut</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[TextFAMGUY1]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Flatline">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/f/b9bd4f/40.png" class="avatar"> Flatline:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Has ANYONE officially made any comment to that effect? No, the decision to move the thread was made by a moderator and I have since moved the thread to somewhere more amenable for everyone. This was not based on any directive from a dev and any suggestion that they are ignoring your work is pure guesswork. They are busy getting Xen and the end of the game finished and aren’t even, for the most part, around the forum. I have no doubt that when the time is right they will recognise your work. So EVERYONE, stop this baseless whining, it just makes YOU look bad.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>You’ve misinterpreted what I was saying. Read it again. Though I may not have made it as clear as I should have, I was speaking in hypothetical - it was about IF the devs believed that rather than saying they DO. I don’t think that they DO.</p>
<p>This had absolutely nothing to do with the moderators moving my thread and I never once alluded to that anyway. I already stated above, in an earlier post, that while it was a tad perplexing, it really didn’t bother me a great deal, and I certainly don’t believe it was a big dev conspiracy or any bollocks like that.</p>
<p>I never once stated that the developers made that comment either, specifically about my work not being dev work and hence not being included for that reason. It was Crypt who made that comment and I’ve heard it from several others. This is why I brought it up. I don’t like that viewpoint, so I was countering it. I wasn’t anywhere suggesting that it’s what the BM Devs actually believe.</p>
<p>People have been projecting that “us vs them” viewpoint onto the devs that they would think that ANYTHING the community does, not just this, won’t be incorporated into the game at any point, because it’s not official dev work. I believe that such a viewpoint is narrow and foolish, but perhaps I didn’t put that across correctly. I WAS NOT saying that the devs believe that, nor did I imply that ANYWHERE. I was saying that I think that such a narrow viewpoint on the part of the community is wrong, and that I don’t believe the devs think that - it would be far too narrow minded of them. I was saying (and I did directly state this) that there is almost certainly any number of very valid reasons for them not wanting to include my work - and that’s fine. My implication was that IF THE DEVS WERE TO BELIEVE THAT (and I don’t think that they do, everybody bear that in mind!) it would be foolish and will simply hinder them from creating a better product.</p>
<p>I’m not whining, not in the slightest. As I did say in that post as well, I personally don’t really care if they ignore my work, they owe me nothing and they owe the community nothing either. I was replying in comment to Crypt, I wasn’t addressing the devs.</p>
<p>Maybe this clears things up.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/did-you-find-surface-tension-lacking-the-answer-surface-tension-uncut/11956/31">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/did-you-find-surface-tension-lacking-the-answer-surface-tension-uncut/11956/31</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jan 2013 15:12:44 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11956-31</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/did-you-find-surface-tension-lacking-the-answer-surface-tension-uncut/11956.rss">Did you find Surface Tension lacking? The answer: Surface Tension Uncut</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Did you find Surface Tension lacking? The answer: Surface Tension Uncut</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Flatline]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote group-black-mesa-devs" data-username="TextFAMGUY1">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/user_avatar/leakfree.org/textfamguy1/40/4294_2.png" class="avatar"> TextFAMGUY1:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>As for the whole official dev vs unofficial dev thing, I find that distinction, as Maxwell does, to be wholly irrelevant and quite frankly, stupid. What’s the point of having cut content in a supposed “remake” of Half-Life 1, solely on a principle which has no grounding in reality anyway? There’s no “us and them,” we’re all just modders, making stuff for the community, for free. It seems arrogant to the point of stupidity for them to ignore my work <span class="bbcode-b"><span class="bbcode-i">solely</span></span> on that basis. Don’t get me wrong, there could be any number of valid reasons why they don’t want my work, but if the reason is ONLY because I’m not an official dev, then frankly, it’s moronic. Of course I don’t hold anything against the BM Devs. It’s their work, they can do with it as they please. I never expected anything I did to ever get implemented anyway. But as a pragmatist myself, if someone did my work for me, I’d take it! This ain’t a business endeavor, there’s no shame in it whatsoever.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Has ANYONE officially made any comment to that effect? No, the decision to move the thread was made by a moderator and I have since moved the thread to somewhere more amenable for everyone. This was not based on any directive from a dev and any suggestion that they are ignoring your work is pure guesswork. They are busy getting Xen and the end of the game finished and aren’t even, for the most part, around the forum. I have no doubt that when the time is right they will recognise your work. So EVERYONE, stop this baseless whining, it just makes YOU look bad.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/did-you-find-surface-tension-lacking-the-answer-surface-tension-uncut/11956/30">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/did-you-find-surface-tension-lacking-the-answer-surface-tension-uncut/11956/30</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jan 2013 09:54:37 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11956-30</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/did-you-find-surface-tension-lacking-the-answer-surface-tension-uncut/11956.rss">Did you find Surface Tension lacking? The answer: Surface Tension Uncut</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Did you find Surface Tension lacking? The answer: Surface Tension Uncut</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[TextFAMGUY1]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Crypt19">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Crypt19:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>A few bits seem a bit under Black Mesa’s level of quality. They <span class="bbcode-i">may</span> have been modified (I only played the first release) but I doubt it. Also the Xen fauna littered around conflicts with Black Mesa. Those are from what a dev said was simply scientist reproductions as apposed to actual Xen fauna. I wouldn’t mind seeing the addition to Black Mesa, but I wouldn’t hold it against then if they don’t include it, which is the most likely scenario. It is unofficial work, after all, and they might want to keep mapping and level design to be dev work only.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>First release? Which first release? Public release 0.8, official release 1.0, or final release 1.11? Saying “they may have been modified, but I doubt it” seems a tad rude. The mod’s been modified MASSIVELY from each version so it’s important you’re clear which version you’re talking about here, otherwise your criticism is completely baseless.</p>
<p>To put it into clearer perspective, there were 5 releases in between 0.8 and 1.0.</p>
<p>There were 4 releases in between 1.0 and 1.11, the current final version.</p>
<p>Thus, unless you are talking about the final, current version, your point has no basis, as even 1.0 and 1.11 are worlds apart, and any of my testers will also verify that.</p>
<p>Of course I’m not saying that your opinion is wrong and that it’s wrong to say that you think my work isn’t up to scratch. But it’s a bit ignorant to base criticisms on what you’ve seen in an older version, should that be the case. Though I am very biased and it is just my personal opinion, I believe that my work is at least at Black Mesa standard - not because “I’m a fantastic mapper” or any other arrogance which people choose to project on me, but because of the fantastic rapport I’ve had with this insanely critical and wonderful community. No other maps on Black Mesa, even official work, have received the same level of community feedback and scrutiny, and that’s what makes me feel my work is at the very least, up to scratch. Not through my work. But everyone elses’.</p>
<p>As for the whole official dev vs unofficial dev thing, I find that distinction, as Maxwell does, to be wholly irrelevant and quite frankly, stupid. What’s the point of having cut content in a supposed “remake” of Half-Life 1, solely on a principle which has no grounding in reality anyway? There’s no “us and them,” we’re all just modders, making stuff for the community, for free. It seems arrogant to the point of stupidity for them to ignore my work <span class="bbcode-b"><span class="bbcode-i">solely</span></span> on that basis. Don’t get me wrong, there could be any number of valid reasons why they don’t want my work, but if the reason is ONLY because I’m not an official dev, then frankly, it’s moronic. Of course I don’t hold anything against the BM Devs. It’s their work, they can do with it as they please. I never expected anything I did to ever get implemented anyway. But as a pragmatist myself, if someone did my work for me, I’d take it! This ain’t a business endeavor, there’s no shame in it whatsoever.</p>
<p>As for the whole Xen Flora thing, whatever. The Xen Moss which I use can be seen on Forget About Freeman too, so it hardly conflicts with the rest of Black Mesa. And while it may otherwise “conflict with Black Mesa,” it AGREES WITH HALF-LIFE, which is the game Black Mesa is supposed to be remaking. In HL1 the Xen Flora appears sporadically throughout Surface Tension and FaF, normally accompanying a jump-pad but not always. Thus, I don’t really see how that can be a serious problem either.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/did-you-find-surface-tension-lacking-the-answer-surface-tension-uncut/11956/29">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/did-you-find-surface-tension-lacking-the-answer-surface-tension-uncut/11956/29</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jan 2013 05:45:08 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11956-29</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/did-you-find-surface-tension-lacking-the-answer-surface-tension-uncut/11956.rss">Did you find Surface Tension lacking? The answer: Surface Tension Uncut</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Did you find Surface Tension lacking? The answer: Surface Tension Uncut</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Bloodshot]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>ok</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/did-you-find-surface-tension-lacking-the-answer-surface-tension-uncut/11956/28">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/did-you-find-surface-tension-lacking-the-answer-surface-tension-uncut/11956/28</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 19 Jan 2013 08:32:57 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11956-28</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/did-you-find-surface-tension-lacking-the-answer-surface-tension-uncut/11956.rss">Did you find Surface Tension lacking? The answer: Surface Tension Uncut</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Did you find Surface Tension lacking? The answer: Surface Tension Uncut</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Dr_Maxwell]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>ST Uncut is easily BM-quality; when I replayed the game with Text’s maps installed, they stood out as one of my favorite segments of the game.  As for the inconsistencies with Xen fauna that will be introduced when Xen comes out, I’m sure the BM devs can work with Text when Xen releases.  And it’s completely retarded how you say “dev work only”.  You’re treating the devs like they’re some magical fantasy race that’s superior to mere humans like me, you, and Text.  Hell, Text has outclassed the “official” Black Mesa devs here.  I might have some more comprehension of your point if Black Mesa were an official Valve game, but we’re not talking “corporate programmers and modders” here.  We’re talking “modders and other modders”.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/did-you-find-surface-tension-lacking-the-answer-surface-tension-uncut/11956/27">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/did-you-find-surface-tension-lacking-the-answer-surface-tension-uncut/11956/27</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 19 Jan 2013 04:38:03 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11956-27</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/did-you-find-surface-tension-lacking-the-answer-surface-tension-uncut/11956.rss">Did you find Surface Tension lacking? The answer: Surface Tension Uncut</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Did you find Surface Tension lacking? The answer: Surface Tension Uncut</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypt]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>A few bits seem a bit under Black Mesa’s level of quality. They <span class="bbcode-i">may</span> have been modified (I only played the first release) but I doubt it. Also the Xen fauna littered around conflicts with Black Mesa. Those are from what a dev said was simply scientist reproductions as apposed to actual Xen fauna. I wouldn’t mind seeing the addition to Black Mesa, but I wouldn’t hold it against then if they don’t include it, which is the most likely scenario. It is unofficial work, after all, and they might want to keep mapping and level design to be dev work only.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/did-you-find-surface-tension-lacking-the-answer-surface-tension-uncut/11956/26">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/did-you-find-surface-tension-lacking-the-answer-surface-tension-uncut/11956/26</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 19 Jan 2013 04:29:13 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11956-26</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/did-you-find-surface-tension-lacking-the-answer-surface-tension-uncut/11956.rss">Did you find Surface Tension lacking? The answer: Surface Tension Uncut</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Did you find Surface Tension lacking? The answer: Surface Tension Uncut</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Dr_Maxwell]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>While I find it unlikely that OAR Uncut will be included in the official release of BM by the devs, as long as the devs aren’t stupid or prideful to a fault, I think Surface Tension Uncut will be added to the official mod with Text’s permission.  After all, they’ve admitted that the omission of those areas of Surface Tension wasn’t an intentional choice; it was the result of intervening circumstances.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/did-you-find-surface-tension-lacking-the-answer-surface-tension-uncut/11956/25">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/did-you-find-surface-tension-lacking-the-answer-surface-tension-uncut/11956/25</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 19 Jan 2013 03:23:22 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11956-25</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/did-you-find-surface-tension-lacking-the-answer-surface-tension-uncut/11956.rss">Did you find Surface Tension lacking? The answer: Surface Tension Uncut</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
