<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Need Help With HL2 Skins</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/need-help-with-hl2-skins/13426</link>
    <description>Well, I realize this issue might be a little too off-topic for the BM forums, but I&#39;m sure the people on here will be able to help me out with this issue.

Sorry for my lack of knowledge but, basically, I just want to know how to modify skins for Half-Life 2 and its episodes. More specifically, change the animations set on a model. Here&#39;s why:

Recently, I found this &quot;reanimation project&quot; that has been sort of abandoned for a while now, but I really liked most of the animations on there. 
Here is the link to download it: [url]https://www.mediafire.com/download/ddbow4d4xcmcfqi/HL2+Reanimation+update+3.4.zip[/url]

And a preview: [url]https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=pk3bsfQVPxA[/url] (Don&#39;t download it via the link in the description, it&#39;s down.) 


Now, the animations are, of course, set to the default Half-Life 2 models. I have 2 skins that use models that don&#39;t stray away too far from the defaults, and use the default animations. These are the skins:

[url]https://hl2.gamebanana.com/skins/34127[/url]

[url]https://hl2.gamebanana.com/skins/38758[/url] (I don&#39;t use any of the tacticool add-ons, just the required files for the m203.)

Since the &quot;reanimation project&quot; was made with the default models, I assume it should be rather easy to implement the animations from that pack on the skins I&#39;m currently using? The thing is, I can&#39;t find a guide on how to do so. I don&#39;t have any modding experience, either. However, one thing to note is that, the re-animation pack I linked to earlier has a folder for &quot;SMD&quot; and &quot;QD&quot; files, which, from my understanding, are the actual animations themselves, since the files are named stuff like &quot;reload&quot; and &quot;idle&quot;. This should make things easier, right?

Is there a way I can easily change the animations here? Oh, and since I&#39;m incredibly lazy, I would appreciate it if someone somehow bothered to do this for me. I&#39;m sorry for the long post and the rather odd request.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2014 20:45:08 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Help!</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/need-help-with-hl2-skins/13426.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Need Help With HL2 Skins</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[SaintGaggo]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Well, I realize this issue might be a little too off-topic for the BM forums, but I’m sure the people on here will be able to help me out with this issue.</p>
<p>Sorry for my lack of knowledge but, basically, I just want to know how to modify skins for Half-Life 2 and its episodes. More specifically, change the animations set on a model. Here’s why:</p>
<p>Recently, I found this “reanimation project” that has been sort of abandoned for a while now, but I really liked most of the animations on there.<br>
Here is the link to download it: <a href="https://www.mediafire.com/download/ddbow4d4xcmcfqi/HL2+Reanimation+update+3.4.zip" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://www.mediafire.com/download/ddbow4d4xcmcfqi/HL2+Reanimation+update+3.4.zip</a></p>
<p>And a preview: <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=pk3bsfQVPxA" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=pk3bsfQVPxA</a> (Don’t download it via the link in the description, it’s down.)</p>
<p>Now, the animations are, of course, set to the default Half-Life 2 models. I have 2 skins that use models that don’t stray away too far from the defaults, and use the default animations. These are the skins:</p>
<p><a href="https://hl2.gamebanana.com/skins/34127" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://hl2.gamebanana.com/skins/34127</a></p>
<p><a href="https://hl2.gamebanana.com/skins/38758" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://hl2.gamebanana.com/skins/38758</a> (I don’t use any of the tacticool add-ons, just the required files for the m203.)</p>
<p>Since the “reanimation project” was made with the default models, I assume it should be rather easy to implement the animations from that pack on the skins I’m currently using? The thing is, I can’t find a guide on how to do so. I don’t have any modding experience, either. However, one thing to note is that, the re-animation pack I linked to earlier has a folder for “SMD” and “QD” files, which, from my understanding, are the actual animations themselves, since the files are named stuff like “reload” and “idle”. This should make things easier, right?</p>
<p>Is there a way I can easily change the animations here? Oh, and since I’m incredibly lazy, I would appreciate it if someone somehow bothered to do this for me. I’m sorry for the long post and the rather odd request.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/need-help-with-hl2-skins/13426/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/need-help-with-hl2-skins/13426/1</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2014 20:45:08 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13426-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/need-help-with-hl2-skins/13426.rss">Need Help With HL2 Skins</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
