<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Wireless headset interfering with Wifi?</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/wireless-headset-interfering-with-wifi/13538</link>
    <description>I recently bought this PS4 &quot;gold wireless stereo headset&quot; (that&#39;s gold the name, not the color or material) based on a recommendation from the guy who worked at the store I bought it at. I&#39;ve been using it on my PC on account of I don&#39;t have a PS4 but I wanted a good wireless headset. It&#39;s just a USB plug since my PC has no default bluetooth options and I didn&#39;t want to buy a dongle, but whenever I have it turned on, my wifi randomly disconnects. It&#39;s random but frequent. It just disconnects and interrupts whatever I&#39;m doing. I can really easily and quickly reconnect, but it&#39;s extremely irritating, especially when I&#39;m watching a video, since I have to reload it. This only happens when I have the thing turned on. I&#39;ve had it for less than a week. I&#39;ve kept it turned off for about the last hour, but a few minutes ago I turned it back on and within 2 minutes my Wifi disconnected. I reconnected and reloaded. A few minutes later, it happened again. Rinse and repeat ad infinitum. I can only guess that something about the headset&#39;s wireless USB connection is interfering with my Wifi. Has anyone else had this problem, and do we have a fix?</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 02 Nov 2014 03:14:26 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Help and Support</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/wireless-headset-interfering-with-wifi/13538.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Wireless headset interfering with Wifi?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Kairouseki]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I had this same issue with a headset I used for MGO when I played it. You could try changing the channel on your router. If both the router and the headset are using the same channel it could be causing this issue. Not sure what else you could do if that does work. I returned the headset that was causing the problem for me and got a new one and that fixed it when it was happening for me.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/wireless-headset-interfering-with-wifi/13538/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/wireless-headset-interfering-with-wifi/13538/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 02 Nov 2014 03:14:26 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13538-2</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/wireless-headset-interfering-with-wifi/13538.rss">Wireless headset interfering with Wifi?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Wireless headset interfering with Wifi?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Shaddy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I recently bought this PS4 “gold wireless stereo headset” (that’s gold the name, not the color or material) based on a recommendation from the guy who worked at the store I bought it at. I’ve been using it on my PC on account of I don’t have a PS4 but I wanted a good wireless headset. It’s just a USB plug since my PC has no default bluetooth options and I didn’t want to buy a dongle, but whenever I have it turned on, my wifi randomly disconnects. It’s random but frequent. It just disconnects and interrupts whatever I’m doing. I can really easily and quickly reconnect, but it’s extremely irritating, especially when I’m watching a video, since I have to reload it. This only happens when I have the thing turned on. I’ve had it for less than a week. I’ve kept it turned off for about the last hour, but a few minutes ago I turned it back on and within 2 minutes my Wifi disconnected. I reconnected and reloaded. A few minutes later, it happened again. Rinse and repeat ad infinitum. I can only guess that something about the headset’s wireless USB connection is interfering with my Wifi. Has anyone else had this problem, and do we have a fix?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/wireless-headset-interfering-with-wifi/13538/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/wireless-headset-interfering-with-wifi/13538/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 01 Nov 2014 22:59:44 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13538-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/wireless-headset-interfering-with-wifi/13538.rss">Wireless headset interfering with Wifi?</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
