<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Ask a humanist</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/ask-a-humanist/6936</link>
    <description>Keeping up the trend of various &quot;Ask a *philisophical view*&quot; I bring &#39;Ask a Humanist&#39;.

I bring this thread up as I have seen in other thread on this board severe cases of nihilism and hatred based upon someone&#39;s own belief. So here goes:

Humanism is more a philosophy than a theistic religion, humanist don&#39;t beleive in a God or an pantheon of Gods, we encompass atheism and agnosticism in arguements against theism. 

The core of the philosophy is that life and existence itself should be approached with humanity and reason, not a set of pre-defined principles set out by an organised religion. Any issues would be approached by looking at the available evidence rather than relying on a thousand-year-old dogma or holy book.

We hold an individuals rights and freedoms as central to our philosophy, as well as social cooperation and individual and corporate responsibility.

Feel free to ask questions.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2011 03:59:16 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Off Topic</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/ask-a-humanist/6936.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Ask a humanist</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Zen609]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>A.C. Grayling is the guest on Colbert tonight.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/ask-a-humanist/6936/90">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/ask-a-humanist/6936/90</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2011 03:59:16 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-6936-90</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/ask-a-humanist/6936.rss">Ask a humanist</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Ask a humanist</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[gugamilare]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I think people associate nihilism with living without morals and not having a life purpose.<br>
I’m not saying that this association is necessarily true.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/ask-a-humanist/6936/89">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/ask-a-humanist/6936/89</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 24 Apr 2011 13:45:04 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-6936-89</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/ask-a-humanist/6936.rss">Ask a humanist</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Ask a humanist</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Cat_Fuzz]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Oh I agree, I’m just curious to hear what is wrong with it is all.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/ask-a-humanist/6936/88">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/ask-a-humanist/6936/88</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 24 Apr 2011 03:32:24 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-6936-88</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/ask-a-humanist/6936.rss">Ask a humanist</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Ask a humanist</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[danielsangeo]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Nihilism (like anarchy, though I know they’re not the same thing) has to ignore some basic aspects of the human animal to survive.  Like the fact that we are a sociable species and we interact with others.  These interactions lead to, well, morals, because these morals describe how to interact with one another.</p>
<p>If we were solitary animals, morals generally would not exist for us and then it would be “every man for himself”.  But that just doesn’t work in a species such as ours.</p>
<p>You are welcome to your nihilistic viewpoint but you have to remember that others aren’t nihilists themselves.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/ask-a-humanist/6936/87">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/ask-a-humanist/6936/87</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 24 Apr 2011 02:30:25 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-6936-87</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/ask-a-humanist/6936.rss">Ask a humanist</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Ask a humanist</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Cat_Fuzz]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>As a nihilist, I ask what is so wrong with Nihilism? Admittedly, I don’t fully ascribe myself to nihilism completely, but I’d like to know why that’s frowned upon from a humanistic viewpoint.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/ask-a-humanist/6936/86">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/ask-a-humanist/6936/86</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 24 Apr 2011 02:16:21 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-6936-86</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/ask-a-humanist/6936.rss">Ask a humanist</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Ask a humanist</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[gugamilare]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="X_Mastershot_X">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/x/c5a1d2/40.png" class="avatar"> X_Mastershot_X:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>It is beautiful that people from different countries like you and me can think alike. I exactly know what you are trying to say. Although I have never considered myself as a humanist before, I will read about it.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p><img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=9" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji only-emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Haze">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/h/3ab097/40.png" class="avatar"> Haze:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Well I’d consider myself a humanist as opposed to a follower of other ideologies as I approve of the different teachings of love and respect, but am not swayed by their theories of creation. It’s because of those teachings that I’d consider myself humanist, not just an atheist.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>When I saw a documentary about Buddha’s life, I felt like all supernatural stuff were just a dramatization to make the story prettier and easier to understand. And it worked  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=9" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:">  It was kind of funny, I had the impression that whoever told that story originally did not really mean that literally, although I’m probably wrong.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/ask-a-humanist/6936/85">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/ask-a-humanist/6936/85</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Apr 2011 12:29:41 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-6936-85</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/ask-a-humanist/6936.rss">Ask a humanist</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Ask a humanist</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[danielsangeo]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Zen609">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/z/71e660/40.png" class="avatar"> Zen609:</div>
<blockquote>
<p><span class="mention">@Humanists</span></p>
<p>Do you think atheism or agnosticism is a necessary component of humanism?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I don’t really think that atheism or agnosticism are a necessary component of humanism.  I think you can be theistic humanist or a gnostic humanist.  I feel this question is the same as whether you can “believe in evolution” and “believe in God” at the same time.  I don’t think they’re necessarily exclusive.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/ask-a-humanist/6936/84">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/ask-a-humanist/6936/84</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2011 23:37:49 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-6936-84</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/ask-a-humanist/6936.rss">Ask a humanist</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Ask a humanist</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Haze]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>To a certain degree, yes. Humanism is about approaching life and it’s various problems from a standpoint of humanity and reason, from their own subjective viewpoint, examining the evidence at hand. Religious dogma would often require one to adhere to it’s own practices which not only contradicts the humanist core principle of individual rights in some cases (See religion versus homosexuality) but would also prevent said person from approaching problems subjectively.</p>
<p>I suppose it would be possible to combine humanism and religions in theory; if one was to take both approaches (humanist and religious) and find they come to the same answer for example. But if the answers differ they would need to take the humanist option, obviously else they would not be a humanist.</p>
<p>However, humanism as a core ideal takes evolution and the big bang theory over creationism, therefore it is arguable that yes, atheism and/or agnoticism is a core component of humanism.</p>
<p>Personally I am an atheist.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/ask-a-humanist/6936/83">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/ask-a-humanist/6936/83</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2011 18:47:47 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-6936-83</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/ask-a-humanist/6936.rss">Ask a humanist</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Ask a humanist</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Zen609]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><span class="mention">@Humanists</span></p>
<p>Do you think atheism or agnosticism is a necessary component of humanism?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/ask-a-humanist/6936/82">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/ask-a-humanist/6936/82</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2011 16:39:03 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-6936-82</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/ask-a-humanist/6936.rss">Ask a humanist</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Ask a humanist</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Haze]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>Why humanism and not some other ideology?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Well I’d consider myself a humanist as opposed to a follower of other ideologies as I approve of the different teachings of love and respect, but am not swayed by their theories of creation. It’s because of those teachings that I’d consider myself humanist, not just an atheist.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/ask-a-humanist/6936/81">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/ask-a-humanist/6936/81</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2011 14:52:16 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-6936-81</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/ask-a-humanist/6936.rss">Ask a humanist</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Ask a humanist</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[X_Mastershot_X]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="gugamilare">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/g/f04885/40.png" class="avatar"> gugamilare:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Are all ideologies mutually exclusive? I don’t think so. For instance, I admire Christ, Buddha and Gandhi and I try to learn and imitate their lessons of life, and I consider myself a humanist as well, those philosophies are not exclusive, they actually get along very well, and one helps you understand the other better. I still need to learn about all those things and that is why I’m here asking questions. So, I disagree with the idea that you choose humanism “over” other ideologies. I even disagree with the idea of following one particular religion, shouldn’t we be trying to learn from all of them?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>It is beautiful that people from different countries like you and me can think alike. I exactly know what you are trying to say. Although I have never considered myself as a humanist before, I will read about it.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/ask-a-humanist/6936/80">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/ask-a-humanist/6936/80</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2011 13:46:33 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-6936-80</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/ask-a-humanist/6936.rss">Ask a humanist</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Ask a humanist</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Assassin]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>fuck I care, you “responses” were not the most correct ones.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/ask-a-humanist/6936/79">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/ask-a-humanist/6936/79</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2011 10:12:25 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-6936-79</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/ask-a-humanist/6936.rss">Ask a humanist</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Ask a humanist</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Zen609]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I’m no longer interested in reading your comments or responses. Perhaps other people are, but I’m not. So, don’t expect any further conversation with me.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/ask-a-humanist/6936/78">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/ask-a-humanist/6936/78</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2011 07:46:21 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-6936-78</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/ask-a-humanist/6936.rss">Ask a humanist</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Ask a humanist</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Assassin]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>Dudes give up. Every country is shit on the internet and every country will be defended on the internet. Internet will always find a way to show why your country sucks. Let’s continue the subject on humanism and not just Georgia.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I wouldn’t defend if he didn’t wrote lies about my country. I don’t say that I live in the best country in the world but my country isn’t that shit he is describing.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>Your ignorance of this isn’t my problem. These organizations have documented and recognized human rights violations by Ethnic Georgians.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>you see some crappy documents and I see what is going on here so STOP SUCKING SHIT.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>The scale of the total population might be subjective, but that a minority of 10% is not subjective - it’s 10%, that’s a vast minority. But I guess it’s still too many if you’re Georgian.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>4.6m/100X10=460k is this not lot? 460thousand people are lot enough for 4.6M population country.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>Muslims are NOT Ethnic Georgians. The Georgian culture is defined by their religion. This is what it is to be ‘Georgian’. You yourself have alluded to this in other posts when you mentioned that Georgians have survived as a people through numerous occupations in their history and the religion was the reason.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>there are Muslim georgians and I told you this several times but you still keep sucking shit. and being Georgian doesn’t mean being christian.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>Right, I see you have nothing better to say about this either.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>what shell I say? translate to you georgian history from 20th century and get some shitty response that you have read some shit in some documents? no thnx.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>What you know and think about it is what you were told to know and think about it. You’re in Georgia. I’m not - my understanding of it isn’t through the same propaganda.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>yes propaganda. the helicopters thet flew over my house was propaganda the Russians stealing TOILETS was propaganda the KILLED CITIZENS was propaganda. my closest friend was figting there and many my relatives were there as well and I know it better than you. so sut UP!</p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>And seriously, dude, if you don’t understand that you live in fucking Georgia and everything you’ve EVER been taught about history is propaganda, then you need to pull your head out of your ass and look at where you are. I wouldn’t say that the USSR was artful with propaganda, but they were proficient and thorough.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>so you think that my history is propaganda? go suck shit.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>Georgia didn’t win that war, you batshit crazy, delusional mutherfucker.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>that was another war you retard.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>Russia invaded, occupied, and forced a ceasefire agreement in which Georgia lost 2 partitions of it’s country to independent rule, and they did it in a few days.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>they were lost to russians a long before and it was allways russias plan. everything was going well and “South Osetia” was ready  to join georgia again but then russians started “working” on that “Problem” and now as you see everything is “Fixed”.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>Medvedev announced an end to military occupation of Georgia, and the Russians withdrew as per the agreement. This isn’t retreat.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>oh belive me that was a BIG retreat. there are facts that you don’t know.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>And Sarkozy FORCED Georgia into agreeing to the ceasefire? Right, Georgia didn’t lose the war, Sarkozy ‘forced’ them into a ceasefire agreement.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>sarkozy forced to russia because they weren’t going to retreat when Casefire was announced from both sides.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>One particular aspect of Santa Claus that I find completely bad is the idea that sometimes children are taught that he only gives gifts to Christian children. I mean, is this﻿ really the kind of thing that you should teach your children?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Santa Claus is same Saint Nicolaus and that is the reason.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/ask-a-humanist/6936/77">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/ask-a-humanist/6936/77</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2011 07:29:42 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-6936-77</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/ask-a-humanist/6936.rss">Ask a humanist</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Ask a humanist</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[gugamilare]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="X_Mastershot_X">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/x/c5a1d2/40.png" class="avatar"> X_Mastershot_X:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>My question: Why humanism and not some other ideology?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Are all ideologies mutually exclusive? I don’t think so. For instance, I admire Christ, Buddha and Gandhi and I try to learn and imitate their lessons of life, and I consider myself a humanist as well, those philosophies are not exclusive, they actually get along very well, and one helps you understand the other better. I still need to learn about all those things and that is why I’m here asking questions. So, I disagree with the idea that you choose humanism “over” other ideologies. I even disagree with the idea of following one particular religion, shouldn’t we be trying to learn from all of them?</p>
<p>I was just talking about Santa Claus on commentaries on a Youtube video:</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="me">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 me:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>One particular aspect of Santa Claus that I find completely bad is the idea that sometimes children are taught that he only gives gifts to Christian children. I mean, is this﻿ really the kind of thing that you should teach your children?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Does anyone have more examples of traditions that disseminate discrimination?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/ask-a-humanist/6936/76">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/ask-a-humanist/6936/76</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2011 03:53:55 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-6936-76</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/ask-a-humanist/6936.rss">Ask a humanist</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Ask a humanist</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Zen609]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="danielsangeo">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/user_avatar/leakfree.org/danielsangeo/40/4347_2.png" class="avatar"> danielsangeo:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Oh, for crying out…  This isn’t “Ask a Georgian” or “Georgian History Month”.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Yes, sorry, I didn’t mean to get caught up in a debate about that war. I don’t take sides in that war, and I certainly don’t support Russia’s actions as they are clearly a violation of international law.</p>
<p>None of that has anything to do with Secular Humanism really, except the cause of that war - the ethnic hatred among these Central Asian Ethno-religious groups which has gone on for 20 years all over Central Asia and the Balkans.</p>
<p>But then I got taken for a ride by the Georgia Pride Parade.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/ask-a-humanist/6936/75">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/ask-a-humanist/6936/75</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2011 01:02:45 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-6936-75</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/ask-a-humanist/6936.rss">Ask a humanist</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Ask a humanist</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[danielsangeo]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Oh, for crying out…  This isn’t “Ask a Georgian” or “Georgian History Month”.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/ask-a-humanist/6936/74">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/ask-a-humanist/6936/74</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 19 Apr 2011 22:36:46 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-6936-74</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/ask-a-humanist/6936.rss">Ask a humanist</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Ask a humanist</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Zen609]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Zen609">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/z/71e660/40.png" class="avatar"> Zen609:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>No, they’re not. And this is documented and agreed upon by the minorities, the UN, Amnesty International, and the US State Dept.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Assassin">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/a/ccd318/40.png" class="avatar"> Assassin:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>another one from another dimension?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Your ignorance of this isn’t my problem. These organizations have documented and recognized human rights violations by Ethnic Georgians.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Assassin">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/a/ccd318/40.png" class="avatar"> Assassin:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>exactly. TO YOU!</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>The scale of the total population might be subjective, but that a minority of 10% is not subjective - it’s 10%, that’s a vast minority. But I guess it’s still too many if you’re Georgian.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Zen609">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/z/71e660/40.png" class="avatar"> Zen609:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>No, they’re considered Muslims. ‘Georgians’ are an ethnic group defined by their religion.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Assassin">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/a/ccd318/40.png" class="avatar"> Assassin:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>and again you are retard.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Muslims are NOT Ethnic Georgians. The Georgian culture is defined by their religion. This is what it is to be ‘Georgian’. You yourself have alluded to this in other posts when you mentioned that Georgians have survived as a people through numerous occupations in their history and the religion was the reason.</p>
<p>Nice comment, BTW. Didn’t have anything else to say about it, eh?</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Assassin">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/a/ccd318/40.png" class="avatar"> Assassin:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>duuuuuuuuuuuuude you should stop writting I see that your brains starts malfunctioning</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Right, I see you have nothing better to say about this either.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Assassin">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/a/ccd318/40.png" class="avatar"> Assassin:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>you were observing in real time and I was observing with my real EYE so shut the fuck up please. you know not my history not my country and still you continiue to talk bullshit.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>What you know and think about it is what you were told to know and think about it. You’re in Georgia. I’m not - my understanding of it isn’t through the same propaganda.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Assassin">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/a/ccd318/40.png" class="avatar"> Assassin:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>what has pride to do with that? you say bullshit about history which you don’t understand and will never understand.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>You said it as if you had some pride that Stalin was Georgian.</p>
<p>And seriously, dude, if you don’t understand that you live in fucking Georgia and everything you’ve EVER been taught about history is propaganda, then you need to pull your head out of your ass and look at where you are. I wouldn’t say that the USSR was artful with propaganda, but they were proficient and thorough.</p>
<p>If you take that to mean that I think that you’ve been miseducated - you are correct.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Assassin">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/a/ccd318/40.png" class="avatar"> Assassin:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>georgians won war 30k vs 300k</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Georgia didn’t win that war, you batshit crazy, delusional mutherfucker.</p>
<p>You said so yourself in the last comment you made.</p>
<p>SEE:</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Assassin">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/a/ccd318/40.png" class="avatar"> Assassin:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>lol. yes reason is gorbachev wait did you know that Beria and Stalin were georgians? no of course. and yes there is Lot georgians can do agains russia and the fact that we lost that war doesnt changes the fact that russian army which is serveral (not 2 or 3) times bigger than georgian nearly lost that war but you dont know what happened and you will newer know.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Assassin">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/a/ccd318/40.png" class="avatar"> Assassin:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>yeeees of course. just stop wanking.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Russia invaded, occupied, and forced a ceasefire agreement in which Georgia lost 2 partitions of it’s country to independent rule, and they did it in a few days.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Assassin">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/a/ccd318/40.png" class="avatar"> Assassin:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>georgians fought 5 days after Russians crossed the border and we made them retreat after that asshole sarkozi forced that treatment we retreated back so stop sucking shit.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Medvedev announced an end to military occupation of Georgia, and the Russians withdrew as per the agreement. This isn’t retreat.</p>
<p>And Sarkozy FORCED Georgia into agreeing to the ceasefire? Right, Georgia didn’t lose the war, Sarkozy ‘forced’ them into a ceasefire agreement.</p>
<p>“We won that war, but that tricky French bastard deceived us into this stupid ceasefire agreement - because he and Medvedev are gay lovers - you know how the French are.”</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/ask-a-humanist/6936/73">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/ask-a-humanist/6936/73</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 19 Apr 2011 21:24:29 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-6936-73</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/ask-a-humanist/6936.rss">Ask a humanist</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Ask a humanist</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[X_Mastershot_X]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Dudes give up. Every country is shit on the internet and every country will be defended on the internet. Internet will always find a way to show why your country sucks. Let’s continue the subject on humanism and not just Georgia.</p>
<p>My question: Why humanism and not some other ideology?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/ask-a-humanist/6936/72">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/ask-a-humanist/6936/72</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 19 Apr 2011 20:32:46 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-6936-72</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/ask-a-humanist/6936.rss">Ask a humanist</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Ask a humanist</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Assassin]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>No, they’re not. And this is documented and agreed upon by the minorities, the UN, Amnesty International, and the US State Dept.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>another one from another dimension?</p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>no, 10% is a vast minority. The total population of your entire country is about 4.6 million. My original city has more twice that population in it’s metropolitan area, and that just one city. Nothing about Georgia seems a ‘lot’ to me.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">to me.</span> - exactly. TO YOU!</p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>No, they’re considered Muslims. ‘Georgians’ are an ethnic group defined by their religion</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>and again you are retard.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>Russia didn’t pressure Georgia’s actions.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>duuuuuuuuuuuuude you should stop writting I see that your brains starts malfunctioning</p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>My understanding of Georgia and it’s recent history is from the extensive coverage of Georgia and it’s conflicts in the news. The US has many 24 hour news networks that need to to fill time, and the conflict with Russia saturated our news. We viewed that war in real time. And the reasons, causes, positions and relevant historical backgrounds were written and analyzed in some depth by every major news publication. And that wasn’t the only major event that the world followed in it’s news. The 2004 Revolution, and various incidents of human rights abuses were covered. These things are not secret or unknown.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>you were observing in real time and I was observing with my real EYE so shut the fuck up please. you know not my history not my country and still you continiue to talk bullshit.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>Ah, I see, so Western Democracies are stable and successful, but they’re still shit because democracy is shit? Although it’s stable and successful?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I am not going to argue about this with you.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>And this is a point of pride for you?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>what has pride to do with that? you say bullshit about history which you don’t understand and will never understand.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>no, there’s not.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>georgians won war 30k vs 300k so I doubt half drunk junkie russian soliders can do lot here.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>Russia didn’t even come remotely close to losing that ‘war’.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>yeeees of course. just stop wanking.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>The Georgian military retreated to Tblisi immediately upon the Russians crossing the border into Georgia. The Russians invaded and occupied Georgia effortlessly, then they got the ceasefire agreement that they wanted. Then they left. Georgia is now geographically and numerically smaller. And it only took a few days.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>georgians fought 5 days after Russians crossed the border and we made them retreat after that asshole sarkozi forced that treatment we retreated back so stop sucking shit.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/ask-a-humanist/6936/71">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/ask-a-humanist/6936/71</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 19 Apr 2011 20:13:46 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-6936-71</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/ask-a-humanist/6936.rss">Ask a humanist</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Ask a humanist</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Zen609]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Assassin">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/a/ccd318/40.png" class="avatar"> Assassin:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>yes they are.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>No, they’re not. And this is documented and agreed upon by the minorities, the UN, Amnesty International, and the US State Dept.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Assassin">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/a/ccd318/40.png" class="avatar"> Assassin:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>10% of 5M is not lot?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>no, 10% is a vast minority. The total population of your entire country is about 4.6 million. My original city has more twice that population in it’s metropolitan area, and that just one city. Nothing about Georgia seems a ‘lot’ to me.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Assassin">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/a/ccd318/40.png" class="avatar"> Assassin:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>you are retard man. also we have “few” reasons to hate Musilims</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>EXACTLY.</p>
<p>And by ‘we’, you mean ‘Georgians’</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Assassin">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/a/ccd318/40.png" class="avatar"> Assassin:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>and NO they are considered as georgians.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>No, they’re considered Muslims. ‘Georgians’ are an ethnic group defined by their religion.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Assassin">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/a/ccd318/40.png" class="avatar"> Assassin:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>you dont know how it is to live under pressure of russia…</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Russia didn’t pressure Georgia’s actions.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Assassin">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/a/ccd318/40.png" class="avatar"> Assassin:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>it is easy for you to read wikipedia.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>My understanding of Georgia and it’s recent history is from the extensive coverage of Georgia and it’s conflicts in the news. The US has many 24 hour news networks that need to to fill time, and the conflict with Russia saturated our news. We viewed that war in real time. And the reasons, causes, positions and relevant historical backgrounds were written and analyzed in some depth by every major news publication. And that wasn’t the only major event that the world followed in it’s news. The 2004 Revolution, and various incidents of human rights abuses were covered. These things are not secret or unknown.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Assassin">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/a/ccd318/40.png" class="avatar"> Assassin:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>an in my opinion WD is shit not because it is unstable or unsucsesfull becouse I dont think the Democracy is the best way to rule the country that out of context here anyway.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Ah, I see, so Western Democracies are stable and successful, but they’re still shit because democracy is shit? Although it’s stable and successful?</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Assassin">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/a/ccd318/40.png" class="avatar"> Assassin:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Beria and Stalin were georgians? no of course.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>And this is a point of pride for you?</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Assassin">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/a/ccd318/40.png" class="avatar"> Assassin:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>and yes there is Lot georgians can do agains russia</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>no, there’s not.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Assassin">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/a/ccd318/40.png" class="avatar"> Assassin:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>and the fact that we lost that war doesnt changes the fact that russian army which is serveral (not 2 or 3) times bigger than georgian nearly lost that war</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>That wasn’t even a small part of the Russian military.</p>
<p>Russia didn’t even come remotely close to losing that ‘war’.</p>
<p>The Georgian military retreated to Tblisi immediately upon the Russians crossing the border into Georgia. The Russians invaded and occupied Georgia effortlessly, then they got the ceasefire agreement that they wanted. Then they left. Georgia is now geographically and numerically smaller. And it only took a few days.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/ask-a-humanist/6936/70">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/ask-a-humanist/6936/70</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 19 Apr 2011 19:23:12 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-6936-70</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/ask-a-humanist/6936.rss">Ask a humanist</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Ask a humanist</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Assassin]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>No, they aren’t</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>yes they are.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>Muslims are less than 10% and have historically been hated and periodically expelled. They and other minorities are not considered ‘Georgian’.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>10% of 5M is not lot? you are retard man. also we have “few” reasons to hate Musilims<br>
that I doubt you will understand and NO they are considered as georgians.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>I don’t see how Russia is responsible for the actions of Ethnic Georgians against minorities.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>and you wont.<em>sigh</em> Abkhasia was inhabited by georgians and there were Apsuas (like osetians) who lived in Mountains. and Russia used his propaganda to make those people rebel 300k GEORGIANS were forced to leave home. that will be short story, and about “Southern Osetia” there is no Southern Osetia there is only samachablo. osetians were allowed to live here during Georgia was in SSSR and after we claimed independence there was same as in osetia. you dont know how it is to live under pressure of russia…</p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>Since Georgia has been independent, it hasn’t been able to produce a successful government - none of the governments have survived more than a few years. It’s only been a country for 20 years and still can’t rule itself successfully. ALL of it’s attempts at creating a stable government have failed so far, and you want to say that the Western Democracies are shit?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>todays government is normal and stable and if you have lived here you would see the difference. it is easy for you to read wikipedia. an in my opinion WD is shit not because it is unstable or unsucsesfull becouse I dont think the Democracy is the best way to rule the country that out of context here anyway.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>Your country has existed since 1991, and the reason is Gorbachev. Georgia’s continued existence is ONLY through the grace of Russia. If Russia ever thought it was in the best interest of Russia to incorporate Georgia, they would do that at will, and there isn’t a God Damn thing Georgians could do about it except complain.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>lol. yes reason is gorbachev wait did you know that Beria and Stalin were georgians? no of course. and yes there is Lot georgians can do agains russia and the fact that we lost that war doesnt changes the fact that russian army which is serveral (not 2 or 3) times bigger than georgian nearly lost that war but you dont know what happened and you will newer know.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>In 2008, the Georgian military retreated to Tblisi simply because the Russians crossed the Georgian border. Then the Russain army walked into Tblisi with no resistance.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>were you interpreting the Biblie in this way? I am not even amazed. and than you call me stupid.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>Russia decides if Georgia exists or not, and what shape it will have. Georgia has independent self-rule, but only because that’s what best serves Russia.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>haha, cool guy! go wank.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/ask-a-humanist/6936/69">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/ask-a-humanist/6936/69</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 19 Apr 2011 18:20:21 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-6936-69</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/ask-a-humanist/6936.rss">Ask a humanist</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Ask a humanist</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Zen609]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Assassin">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/a/ccd318/40.png" class="avatar"> Assassin:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Mkalavrishvili is not whole country. also minorities are treated normaly untill they ask something like: gay marriage.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>No, they aren’t</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Assassin">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/a/ccd318/40.png" class="avatar"> Assassin:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>lot of people are muslims in georgia</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Muslims are less than 10% and have historically been hated and periodically expelled. They and other minorities are not considered ‘Georgian’.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Assassin">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/a/ccd318/40.png" class="avatar"> Assassin:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>also about genocide you must be reffering to Abkhazia and Osetia.  you are forgeting that my country is next  to Russia which changes a lot but thats different theme. and half of caucasian nationalities live in georgia so please shut up and dont talk about my country in that tone.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I don’t see how Russia is responsible for the actions of Ethnic Georgians against minorities.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Assassin">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/a/ccd318/40.png" class="avatar"> Assassin:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>so please shut up and dont talk about my country in that tone.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>You mean:</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Assassin">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/a/ccd318/40.png" class="avatar"> Assassin:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>so please shut up and dont talk about facts</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Right, because it’s not fair present evidence that societies and governments  based on religion commit atrocities and human rights violations against those outside that culture/religion.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Assassin">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/a/ccd318/40.png" class="avatar"> Assassin:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>my country was holding all the invaders .</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>By ‘holding the invanders’, you mean conquered by every invader that ever stepped foot into Georgia, right?</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Assassin">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/a/ccd318/40.png" class="avatar"> Assassin:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>there were no dark ages in my country…</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>ahahahaha</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Assassin">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/a/ccd318/40.png" class="avatar"> Assassin:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I think it is like bunch of monkeys crying  in cage jumping runing  and think that they rule but from the outside children laugh at them.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>ahahahaha Yes, that thread is clear evidence of your intellectual superiority and dominance over the sub-human inferiors.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Assassin">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/a/ccd318/40.png" class="avatar"> Assassin:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>relligion is the only reason my country still exists.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Your country has existed since 1991, and the reason is Gorbachev. Georgia’s continued existence is ONLY through the grace of Russia. If Russia ever thought it was in the best interest of Russia to incorporate Georgia, they would do that at will, and there isn’t a God Damn thing Georgians could do about it except complain.</p>
<p>In 2008, the Georgian military retreated to Tblisi simply because the Russians crossed the Georgian border.</p>
<p>Russia decides if Georgia exists or not, and what shape it will have. Georgia has independent self-rule, but only because that’s what best serves Russia.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Assassin">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/a/ccd318/40.png" class="avatar"> Assassin:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>you wanted to say Shit?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Western Democracy is shit?  OK</p>
<p>Since Georgia has been independent, it hasn’t been able to produce a successful government - none of the governments have survived more than a few years. It’s only been a country for 20 years and still can’t rule itself successfully. ALL of it’s attempts at creating a stable government have failed so far, and you want to say that the Western Democracies are shit?</p>
<p>Creating a stable government is just the starting point of a country, and Georgia can’t even do that.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/ask-a-humanist/6936/68">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/ask-a-humanist/6936/68</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 19 Apr 2011 17:38:59 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-6936-68</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/ask-a-humanist/6936.rss">Ask a humanist</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Ask a humanist</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Assassin]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>Hey, do you want to tell us about your minorities and how they’re treated by true Georgians. Or maybe the death squads? Mkalavishvili?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Mkalavrishvili is not whole country. also minorities are treated normaly untill they ask something like: gay marriage.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>Your own country is a good example of a ‘people’ being defined by a religion and then attempting genocide, subjugation , or expulsion on any that are not the same culture and religion.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>genocide? subjugation? lot of people are muslims in georgia also about genocide you must be reffering to Abkhazia and Osetia.  you are forgeting that my country is next  to Russia which changes a lot but thats different theme. and half of caucasian nationalities live in georgia so please shut up and dont talk about my country in that tone.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>the world thinks your’e a bunch of ignorant, backward, genocidal assholes.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>fuck I care about what europe thinks about my country! we are assholes? Vlad von Drakula has done more for europe than any king living there while my country was holding all the invaders european countries were fighting between each other. you don’t know about my country and you you won’t know.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>My way of thinking saved the West from the Dark Ages, your way of thinking IS the Dark Ages.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>there were no dark ages in my country. if we dont consider that whole history is pretty dark.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>Cultural Learnings of America for Make Benefit Glorious Nation of Georgia</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I just dont understand the meaning of this sentence.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>The ‘Ask a Christian’ thread is, let’s face it, a bunch of non-Christians putting Christians on the spot. And that’s debate.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I think it is like bunch of monkeys crying  in cage jumping runing  and think that they rule but from the outside children laugh at them.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>then again, I just did research and the Georgian Constitution separates church and state as well</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>yes  I know and I said that religious government shouldn’t work but it is impossible not to consider anything from bible.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>They seem to have a struggle between a progressive movement that seeks to modernize Georgia, but struggle against this very powerful culture which is defined by the church.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>struggle? stop. just stop that bullshit. relligion is the only reason my country still exists. Europe and Georgia were allways saparated from each other. every time we asked for help the response is only squeezed shit through history. europe always cared only for itself and it will be allways like that.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>Western Democracy</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>you wanted to say Shit?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/ask-a-humanist/6936/67">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/ask-a-humanist/6936/67</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 19 Apr 2011 16:30:23 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-6936-67</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/ask-a-humanist/6936.rss">Ask a humanist</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Ask a humanist</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Zen609]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="danielsangeo">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/user_avatar/leakfree.org/danielsangeo/40/4347_2.png" class="avatar"> danielsangeo:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>We must, as humanists,.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>For the record, I don’t self-describe as a Secular Humanist or anything else. I don’t know who else in the thread describe themselves with the term, the OP I assume, and you.</p>
<p>I probably should have left the comments to actual Secular Humanists, but I do know what it is and had my opinions about it and expressed those in my comments.</p>
<p>I like to express my little opinions, but I don’t pretend to be a committed or dedicated follower of Secular Humanism or any other social or political philosophy.</p>
<p>I probably should have left the comments to those that actually know what they’re talking about - but I have this compulsion to throw in my 2 cents in reaction to some comment or another. But this shouldn’t be taken by anyone as anything other than the face value of the comments, or taken to mean that I’m actually a Secular Humanist and have anything other than superficial knowledge of it.</p>
<p>But I always liked the idea, support it, and root for it like the fan that I am. Go Secularism!</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/ask-a-humanist/6936/66">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/ask-a-humanist/6936/66</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 19 Apr 2011 02:28:04 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-6936-66</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/ask-a-humanist/6936.rss">Ask a humanist</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
