<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>WGH - Vent Mod</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/wgh-vent-mod/12645</link>
    <description>Current Status: Complete - [url]https://www.dropbox.com/s/7lortflu9g82z4r/VentMod.zip[/url]

ModDB - [url]https://www.moddb.com/mods/black-mesa-weve-got-hostiles-vent-mod[/url]

[u]Introduction[/u]

Hey there everyone!

I have begun work on a small project for Black Mesa called &quot;Vent Mod&quot;. It is a sister project to Loop Mod. What this does is add some vent sections after the surface encounter in We Got Hostiles.

In the original Half-Life, the player ventured back underground after barely escaping the surface bombardment in the latter half of the We Got Hostiles. This manifested in a vent maze that we behind the scenes of already explored areas. However, this was not very well received, (seriously, they [i]suck[/i]) and rightfully so as to navigate a maze with a movement speed of such a slow pace, and added to that the fact that the vents themselves were very boring, this was for the most part left out of Black Mesa. Instead the run from the military was more hallways.

There is also a problem in Black Mesa&#39;s implementation of We Got Hostiles in that, spacially speaking, there is a huge descrepency. Over the course of the chapter, the player travels at least five stories up in altitude, but only comes down one at the end of the chapter, resulting in the same areas being much higher up the second time around. This is actually the bigger reason on why this Mod is being made.

Vent Mod aims to deal with both of these problems in a fun way. It will make both the vents interesting, get rid of the maze nonsense, as well as solve a spacial error.

[u]Implementation[/u]

This mod will add new sections to the maps bm_c1a3a and bm_c1a3c.

Integrated into what was already there, the player will head into the vents. The path immediately afterwards will be changed however. It will recreate a few of the scenes that are missing from the original, such as the dead scientist in the cafeteria pantry and the large room in the vent shaft. No source pictures provided.

[u]Media[/u]
![](upload://tLuPJ4aHprZyYZoiM9s3rj3gnTy.png)
![](upload://r1c12bHBhR1vrxNwEKLqlBkJKvv.png)
![](upload://2aoPmYtNHgfOrsPOFnAQoYzBnev.png)
![](upload://aYYw9SPK47yz8wu0io8GpTF4vkF.png)
![](upload://tpIA7VhoFOLnkZtf3kc9WkFLOy9.png)

[u]Other info[/u]
Everyone probably can guess this, but this is the spiritual successor to OpenSourceForever&#39;s &#39;&quot;We&#39;ve Got Hostiles!&quot; Uncut&#39;. There is a few reasons why I&#39;ve started actually working on this mod.

*I got extremely excited. I was at first okay with simply waiting for it to get done but then I had a sudden influx of ideas. I don&#39;t think I can really let that sit. So apologies in advance to OpenSourceForever, but them map-making itches of mine has gotten the better of me!

*I don&#39;t expect it to take as long as Loop Mod. Loop Mod was slow because I was learning new concepts and having to overhaul how the map was constructed. And after all that was done I got tired of working on it and slowed down even further. I spent much less time creating it as I did fixing it. I don&#39;t foresee any of these problems with constructing a series of vents, and besides that most of the work is already done anyways.

*Work on the Contract has ground to a dead halt. Literally. There haven&#39;t been any significant goings-on in about a month. I do remain hopeful that the project will continue but in leau of that I will do this in the meantime.



I already have a good deal of the layout already done, but any suggestions on stuff that I can add into the vents (such as headcrabs) are very welcome.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2019 22:47:13 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Source 1</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/wgh-vent-mod/12645.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>WGH - Vent Mod</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Ronster]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>In terms of the original Mapping from Half Life vs your Mod I am curious about something…</p>
<p>Perhaps we are not fully understanding how this map fits together?</p>
<p>I know you have made the Black Mesa Maps fit together and good job on that…</p>
<p>In Half Life Source say…</p>
<p>I am curious if you put the Fan Obstacle at the Bottom next to the Vents that connect the first Map at the Bottom for the Vent Maze. Does this Line up?</p>
<p>And then as you Come out the Lift instead of the Warehouse in We Got Hostiles  you Have the Warehouse from Uplink (Can Be rotated) and the Surface… The Gate where the Burning Vort is looks like they would have been the Gate or door…where would that put us vertically in terms of the Vent Shaft below? Or Keep the Warehouse from We’ve got Hostiles Surface and Line the Area up on the Surface with the towers only disregarding the Bunker?</p>
<p>I just wonder if it fits???</p>
<p>Obviously Forget about the Transmission Dome that is another level from the game.</p>
<p>If that fits more or less this could mean Uplink may have been a different iteration of we’ve got hostiles surface area…</p>
<p>Alternatively where exactly using the Towers in the compund area in uplink be would the Bunker be?</p>
<p>Was it a case of having to use the Sewers from uplink to get to the Security office because they might line up?</p>
<p>My theory is is that the Surface part of Uplink with Warehouse puzzle and Part of Half life Chronicles are the missing Parts of We’ve got Hostiles… But you are quite god at lining all these things up so I thought I would ask you.</p>
<p>EDIT</p>
<p>Actually the Burning Vort makes perfect sense if that is the electric fence yes.</p>
<p>So the Actual Gate Door might be missing from  inside uplink Surface area but chronicles probably is the part that takes you to the warehouse the otherside of the electric fence.</p>
<p>That would put the vent shaft much more directly over the area to descend down.</p>
<p>The bit in uplink where you have to use the vents to get into the security office is also we got hostiles… That is where you get the keycard.</p>
<p>The Antenna dome bottom of elevator section with the plot and Datacore and sewers fron uplink are from the level Communications center.</p>
<p>So uplink is both We got hostiles cut part and Communications center part put together.</p>
<p>Chronicles is small cut areas stitched together.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/wgh-vent-mod/12645/281">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/wgh-vent-mod/12645/281</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 24 Mar 2019 13:28:17 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12645-281</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/wgh-vent-mod/12645.rss">WGH - Vent Mod</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>WGH - Vent Mod</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[RK1]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Hey, everyone! Long time, no see.</p>
<p>A long while back, I promised that I would do a little bit of tweaking to Vent Mod. So… I never actually did that. I’m pretty sure that this was two or three years ago that I made this promise. Well, now that the Xen pre-patch has gone through (and, apparently, my mods are becoming increasingly broken), I figured it was time that I revisit things.</p>
<p>And why now? Well, I’m freshly graduated from university (I have my Bachelor’s in physics now, but the ride isn’t over yet; I start grad school in the fall and I hope to get my Ph.D someday in the far future). So for now, I have the summer off. This is great opportunity to work on things.</p>
<p>So I’ve gone in and I’ve made an update to Vent Mod for the xen pre-patch release. Here’s what’s new in this version:</p>
<p>-The air raid sirens have been added! They’ve been present in the stock BM for quite some time and now they are available in Vent Mod.</p>
<p>-Flares have been reintroduced! BM is pretty good with lighting and I feel comfortable putting them back in</p>
<p>-The interrogation scene has been removed. People have had mixed feelings about this scene, saying that it looked unfinished / unpolished in regards to the rest of the game. I don’t have it in me to fully flesh it out so I think, for the sake of consistent quality, I should take it out.</p>
<p>-The A has had its lighting fixed (so the areas are brighter and you can actually see in them now).</p>
<p>Most importantly, since this has been compiled under the latest BM compiler tools and built in the latest engine, it will have the nicest possible coat of paint to it, I think.</p>
<p>There isn’t really anything else that I want to do with this mod. I’ve received requests here and there to expand this mod. To be frank, however, I don’t think that there is anything else to add. I’ve, for a long while, considered Vent Mod to be more-or-less content complete; what’s going on now is mostly fixes. But, certainly, if anyone encounters any bugs or other issues which impenge on gameplay, please let me know immediately so that I can sort them out (that is, unless, it’s that pesky level transition bug that sometimes breaks going from C to A; I don’t think I will ever figure that one out).</p>
<p>There will, if I keep my promise, also be an update to Loop Mod, but that will take significantly longer (for reasons that I will details in its own post).</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/wgh-vent-mod/12645/280">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/wgh-vent-mod/12645/280</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 05 Jun 2018 16:46:45 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12645-280</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/wgh-vent-mod/12645.rss">WGH - Vent Mod</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>WGH - Vent Mod</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Medkit]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Seemingly the Xen prepatch screwed up this mod. The AI is disabled. No graphical errors though.<br>
I hope a fix will come.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/wgh-vent-mod/12645/279">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/wgh-vent-mod/12645/279</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 01 May 2018 09:25:17 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12645-279</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/wgh-vent-mod/12645.rss">WGH - Vent Mod</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>WGH - Vent Mod</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Mr_GameCrazy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>The vent issue is now fixed.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/wgh-vent-mod/12645/278">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/wgh-vent-mod/12645/278</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 25 May 2015 00:26:28 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12645-278</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/wgh-vent-mod/12645.rss">WGH - Vent Mod</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>WGH - Vent Mod</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Mr_GameCrazy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Cool. I’ll test your new version when I get back home tomorrow.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/wgh-vent-mod/12645/277">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/wgh-vent-mod/12645/277</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 23 May 2015 00:01:26 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12645-277</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/wgh-vent-mod/12645.rss">WGH - Vent Mod</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>WGH - Vent Mod</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[RK1]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Well, good news I think!</p>
<p>I haven’t actually tested this out but I don’t see why it wouldn’t work. I do believe I’ve solved the problem with not being able to shoot through vents. I realized today that if I package the old version of the vents that you <span class="bbcode-i">could</span> shoot through with the mod, that’d solve the problem right up! That’s right, I think I unbroke the interrogation scene. And the sentry scene if you like to shoot an sentries.<br>
I don’t know why this didn’t occur to me sooner. I’m stoopid.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Mr. GameCrazy">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Mr. GameCrazy:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>-snip-</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I gave it a lookat but I can’t find what’s wrong yet. hmmmmmmmmmmmm.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/wgh-vent-mod/12645/276">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/wgh-vent-mod/12645/276</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 22 May 2015 21:25:09 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12645-276</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/wgh-vent-mod/12645.rss">WGH - Vent Mod</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>WGH - Vent Mod</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Mr_GameCrazy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Please fix this issue as well.</p>
<p><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=uIZIeJF2eZg" rel="nofollow noopener">youtube.com/watch?v=uIZIeJF2eZg</a></p>
<p>Here’s the Steam version of the stock map for comparison:</p>
<p><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=SVrkWXdcd3Q" rel="nofollow noopener">youtube.com/watch?v=SVrkWXdcd3Q</a></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/wgh-vent-mod/12645/275">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/wgh-vent-mod/12645/275</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 14 May 2015 04:02:28 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12645-275</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/wgh-vent-mod/12645.rss">WGH - Vent Mod</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>WGH - Vent Mod</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[RK1]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Just so ya’ll know I’ll be revisiting the mod and responding to freeback in a few days once I’m off vacation.</p>
<p>Cheifly, I am going to attempt and resolve these apparent crashes people are having and I’ll ser if I can revamp the soldier scene since it got broken by the port (curse you nee vent models!)</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/wgh-vent-mod/12645/274">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/wgh-vent-mod/12645/274</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 13 May 2015 21:40:09 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12645-274</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/wgh-vent-mod/12645.rss">WGH - Vent Mod</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>WGH - Vent Mod</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Medkit]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>The mod is great as always, but the interrogation scene must be revisited a bit. We cant shoot through the vent, and even if we try the marines ignore us complitely.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/wgh-vent-mod/12645/273">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/wgh-vent-mod/12645/273</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 13 May 2015 20:04:57 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12645-273</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/wgh-vent-mod/12645.rss">WGH - Vent Mod</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>WGH - Vent Mod</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Joe_chief]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Just finished the mod, everything is overall good nothing  gamebreaking but I have to ask: I noticed that the lighting on a few parts of map A looked a little darker than usual, similarly to when you released the mod for the first time in the previous version but not as significant as then. I also don’t know if maybe this is black mesa or your mod since I downloaded them together and didn’t experience the vanilla version but when I encountered the scientists where gman is, their ties where moving like crazy and I didn’t experience this before in any other part of the game. Also the blood texture in the vent where the bulletholes are still looks like it has been turned 90 degrees and I’ve mentioned this on the previous version. Lastly the blood in the vent where the security guard was killed is missing, not sure if you removed it completely or if I just have it missing.</p>
<p>I was wandering as well if you where planning on making other changes, maybe since the steam version seems more stable, like: Changing the bulletholes to those of ST, adding flares like you originally wanted, and maybe now doing something more in the interrogation scene like a small discusion.</p>
<p>I enjoyed it and soon I’ll reach OAR to try your loop mod. :thumbup:</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/wgh-vent-mod/12645/272">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/wgh-vent-mod/12645/272</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 May 2015 18:45:39 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12645-272</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/wgh-vent-mod/12645.rss">WGH - Vent Mod</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>WGH - Vent Mod</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Pauolo]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Just posted a short bug/error list on the workshop, though I have a few recommendations if you’re willing to change something on the map.</p>
<p>First, the small room you added to the cafeteria makes it that there are no access to behind the counter, from a realistic point of view. I’d suggest leaving the double doors from the vanilla map and moving the room behind the two trays next to those doors.<br>
Second, do you think you can move the vent to above the blue closet? With that, the way back is to climb on the stoves, then the closet, making it a bit more challenging. Also the vent would look better higher.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/wgh-vent-mod/12645/271">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/wgh-vent-mod/12645/271</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 May 2015 15:32:17 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12645-271</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/wgh-vent-mod/12645.rss">WGH - Vent Mod</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>WGH - Vent Mod</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Nevermore2790]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Oh, it’s back now. Thanks.  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=9" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/wgh-vent-mod/12645/270">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/wgh-vent-mod/12645/270</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 07 May 2015 06:16:04 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12645-270</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/wgh-vent-mod/12645.rss">WGH - Vent Mod</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>WGH - Vent Mod</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[RK1]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Nevermore2790">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/n/fbc32d/40.png" class="avatar"> Nevermore2790:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Did you delete it? Needs reupload.  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=9" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:">  This along with your mods and those uncuts make me feel that instead of playing 85%, I’m playing about 87% of the campaign now.  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=9" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I hid it so that I could quickly fix it.</p>
<p>Although it should be apparent that this point that I <span class="bbcode-i">am </span>and insufferable dingus when it comes to releasing stuff. Somehow, I ain’t even mad.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/wgh-vent-mod/12645/269">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/wgh-vent-mod/12645/269</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 07 May 2015 06:01:08 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12645-269</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/wgh-vent-mod/12645.rss">WGH - Vent Mod</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>WGH - Vent Mod</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Nevermore2790]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Did you delete it? Needs reupload.  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=9" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:">  This along with your mods and those uncuts make me feel that instead of playing 85%, I’m playing about 87% of the campaign now.  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=9" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/wgh-vent-mod/12645/268">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/wgh-vent-mod/12645/268</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 07 May 2015 05:40:17 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12645-268</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/wgh-vent-mod/12645.rss">WGH - Vent Mod</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>WGH - Vent Mod</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[RK1]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Double posting.</p>
<p>The steam version of Vent Mod is now ported. You can find it here: <a href="https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=438635262" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=438635262</a></p>
<p>There are some slight regressions here are there that are outside of my control (I’m chiefly looking at the interrogation scene, since you can’t shoot through grates anymore it seems), but I think the steam version is in really good shape.</p>
<p>As always <span class="bbcode-u">please let me know immediately if there is anything gamebreaking or something of that nature!</span></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/wgh-vent-mod/12645/267">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/wgh-vent-mod/12645/267</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 07 May 2015 05:26:32 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12645-267</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/wgh-vent-mod/12645.rss">WGH - Vent Mod</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>WGH - Vent Mod</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[RK1]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Nevermore2790">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/n/fbc32d/40.png" class="avatar"> Nevermore2790:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I hope you’ll port On a Rail Loop mod as well and it being compatible to the Uncut maps as well.  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=9" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Strider397">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/s/e9c0ed/40.png" class="avatar"> Strider397:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Don’t forget about loop mod!!</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I haven’t! I’ll talk about that separately in the appropriate thread later tonight.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/wgh-vent-mod/12645/266">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/wgh-vent-mod/12645/266</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 07 May 2015 01:15:20 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12645-266</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/wgh-vent-mod/12645.rss">WGH - Vent Mod</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>WGH - Vent Mod</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Pauolo]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>And just when I reached WGH last night. Call that a perfect timing.  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/smiley.png?v=9" title=":smiley:" class="emoji" alt=":smiley:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/wgh-vent-mod/12645/265">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/wgh-vent-mod/12645/265</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 06 May 2015 22:12:55 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12645-265</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/wgh-vent-mod/12645.rss">WGH - Vent Mod</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>WGH - Vent Mod</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Strider397]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Don’t forget about loop mod!!</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/wgh-vent-mod/12645/264">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/wgh-vent-mod/12645/264</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 06 May 2015 18:57:20 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12645-264</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/wgh-vent-mod/12645.rss">WGH - Vent Mod</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>WGH - Vent Mod</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Joe_chief]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Do you plan on adding or redoing some parts of the map (structure or asthetic wise)? Also maybe now your dream of adding the flares may come true  with the new engine, hopefully it also got rid of that anoying texture bug.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/wgh-vent-mod/12645/263">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/wgh-vent-mod/12645/263</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 06 May 2015 15:42:13 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12645-263</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/wgh-vent-mod/12645.rss">WGH - Vent Mod</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>WGH - Vent Mod</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Nevermore2790]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I hope you’ll port On a Rail Loop mod as well and it being compatible to the Uncut maps as well.  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=9" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/wgh-vent-mod/12645/262">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/wgh-vent-mod/12645/262</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 06 May 2015 06:13:55 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12645-262</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/wgh-vent-mod/12645.rss">WGH - Vent Mod</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>WGH - Vent Mod</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[RK1]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Howdy everyone!</p>
<p>I hope all of you have been enjoying the steam release! I for one think that it’s really amazeballs so far.</p>
<p>Just letting all of you know that I am working to port Vent Mod into the newest version’s of Black Mesa’s maps. That way you can enjoy Vent Mod along side all of the new shine that the steam version has to offer! A map is already fairly done, and C map shouldn’t take terribly long. But, obviously, I will be testing both maps to make sure they work correctly before this mod hits the workshop.</p>
<p>Stay tuned!</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/wgh-vent-mod/12645/261">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/wgh-vent-mod/12645/261</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 06 May 2015 05:15:37 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12645-261</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/wgh-vent-mod/12645.rss">WGH - Vent Mod</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>WGH - Vent Mod</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Dadster]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Thanks for the update to the Vent Mod, .RK  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=9" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
<p>I’m curious about what new changes you’re adding to your OaR Loop Mod?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/wgh-vent-mod/12645/260">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/wgh-vent-mod/12645/260</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2014 15:42:50 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12645-260</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/wgh-vent-mod/12645.rss">WGH - Vent Mod</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>WGH - Vent Mod</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[RK1]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>However ill-timed it was, your post is very much appreciated. Thanks for stopping by and sharing your thoughts with us!</p>
<p>We had a fair bit of discussion on that and different ways to approach it. I originally had the idea of having some HECU gunning down some Vorts to strengthen their image for this - their introductory chapter. Some people also through their own takes into the hat.</p>
<p>Ultimately someone made the observation that in the original game the HECU were not seen engaging the aliens until Power Up. That personally sealed the deal and it’s why there’s nothing like this in the final product.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/wgh-vent-mod/12645/259">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/wgh-vent-mod/12645/259</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 03 Aug 2014 05:34:59 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12645-259</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/wgh-vent-mod/12645.rss">WGH - Vent Mod</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>WGH - Vent Mod</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Msteps]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Joe chief">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Joe chief:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>You’re kind of late, mod is done.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Yeah I’m pretty embarressed,  I only noticed the date on the post  today. <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/blush.png?v=9" title=":blush:" class="emoji" alt=":blush:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/wgh-vent-mod/12645/258">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/wgh-vent-mod/12645/258</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2014 19:14:07 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12645-258</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/wgh-vent-mod/12645.rss">WGH - Vent Mod</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>WGH - Vent Mod</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Joe_chief]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Msteps">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/m/8e8cbc/40.png" class="avatar"> Msteps:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Indeed, that would be something worth seeing. And if you want the vorts to win add them like this: 3 scientist, 1 guard(ideal weapon: glock, 4 Hecu (1 red beret, 2 MP5 soldiers, and 1 SPAS 12 Soldier), And 4 Vorts (this may be a 51-52% chance that vorts may win).</p>
<p>Plus you could make the area have some cover like some military crates. And this may add some extra detail to the scene.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>You’re kind of late, mod is done.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/wgh-vent-mod/12645/257">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/wgh-vent-mod/12645/257</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2014 21:34:46 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12645-257</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/wgh-vent-mod/12645.rss">WGH - Vent Mod</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
