<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:discourse="http://www.discourse.org/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Suggestion Box - Leakfree</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/c/black-mesa-archive/suggestion-box/34</link>
    <description>Topics in the &#39;Suggestion Box&#39; category Features, details and ideas you’d like to see in-game.</description>
    
      <lastBuildDate>Tue, 11 Sep 2012 19:27:03 +0000</lastBuildDate>
      <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/c/black-mesa-archive/suggestion-box/34.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
        <item>
          <title>Polish Language (and others...)</title>
          <dc:creator><![CDATA[hajducek]]></dc:creator>
          <category>Suggestion Box</category>
          <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Hi there  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=9" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
<p>I have a question - how many languages would be avaiable in Black Mesa: Source? I mean, i don’t need it but many fans in Poland (and other coutries) are so exicted about this mod, but they didn’t know english so good.</p>
<p>So - will be there any translations? If no - can i help? I translated some games and i know the deal.</p>
            <p><small>2 posts - 2 participants</small></p>
            <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/polish-language-and-others/9383">Read full topic</a></p>
          ]]></description>
          <link>https://leakfree.org/t/polish-language-and-others/9383</link>
          <pubDate>Tue, 11 Sep 2012 19:27:03 +0000</pubDate>
          <discourse:topicPinned>No</discourse:topicPinned>
          <discourse:topicClosed>No</discourse:topicClosed>
          <discourse:topicArchived>No</discourse:topicArchived>
          <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-topic-9383</guid>
          <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/polish-language-and-others/9383.rss">Polish Language (and others...)</source>
        </item>
        <item>
          <title>Reality mod</title>
          <dc:creator><![CDATA[Lynxx]]></dc:creator>
          <category>Suggestion Box</category>
          <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I’d like to suggest something I always wanted to see in a 1st person shooter: common sense and logic. Currently „normal“ game physics suggest the use of ragdoll models, collision detection, etc. However all of them are too arcade almost to the level of „cartoon physics“: «Animation follows the laws of physics — unless it is funnier otherwise». In the game, a lot of things are not fun nor possible. Modern games still rely too much on so called „suspension of disbelief“<br>
(see <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Suspension_of_disbelief#Video_games" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Suspension_of_disbelief#Video_games</a> ), despite having hardware resources to act more realistically. I did a quick search of the forum and haven’t found anyone who suggested those ideas en masse. So here’s my incomplete list (impatient ones may scroll down to point 20 and read important P.S.):</p>
<p>1a. Visuals. When I look down, climb or swim, I should see my body parts. In shiny and glossy surfaces there should be reflections of everything, including me. And there is no crosshair in real life — even if you use HEV suit with HUD (more accurately called HMD — Helmet Mounted Display). Weapon aiming will be better, if it’s equipped with a laser pointer, but only RPG have it.</p>
<p>1b. 20 sec flashlight is stupid. HEV spends megajoules of energy for its armor, but can’t find 1% of that for the light? It should be indefinite, just like HEV CPU, sensors and HUD can work for hours with no armor. And not point-sourced, but projected. BTW, where is a flashlight? Best thing to do is to mount it on a helmet in from of a flat band (temple to temple). You also need a button to operate, unless (since it’s indefinite) there is a light sensor and autoswitch with brightness regulation (modern monitors and smartphones have it).</p>
<p>1c. Environment lights are not logical. Why there are lights in vent pipes? To illuminate the way for bugs and headcrabs? Why there are so little areas with total darkness, assuming massive blackouts after the incident? Why there are so little areas with emergency lights (dim but visible to find a way out)? Why lightly damaged areas have all of their lights on? Some of them must be broken, there aren’t eternal. Judging by the lighting, I wouldn’t say BM just experienced a catastrophe — almost everything is bright lit. Add some chaos! Also, at some places the light seems to come from nowhere. Even in Xen there have to be some sources. Also, let’em be interactive: projectile, heavy object (if hit hard and fast enough) or blast wave should be able to break the light, it may explode with optional sparks and smoke, and illumination will decrease. Good shadows are welcome too, but they are very costly…</p>
<p>1d. Gradually HEV suit should get worn and covered by blood, bullet, bite and hit marks and scratches. Freeman must leave a trail on the sand or — if he’s just out of the water — anywhere.</p>
<p>1e. Gordon should blink and squint — caused by sudden bright light, hit in the head, etc. Bright light should leave a streak of afterglow. Catching a laser beam will cause slowly diminishing temporary blindness on that eye. Getting hit hard or being very weak should result in darkening the view.</p>
<p>1f. Telescopic sight for a crossbow shouldn’t cover all the view, considering helmet’s visor. OTH, HEV might have it’s own camera with a good lenses (on the forehead?) — zoomed view might pop in a corner window or cover-all view.</p>
<p>2a. Every movable object should have weight. And Freeman should have limited stamina. It’s not possible to carry whole arsenal of things and still jump and run. If one could attached somehow 10 weapons and 100 ammo packs, he’d weight over 200 kg! The more you weigh (with items) — the less you can move and the more you’ll use energy of stamina reserve. Faster and/or complex movements need more energy: crowbar brandish, climb, swim… Since Freeman is a scientist, not Olympic athlete, he shouldn’t be able to run full speed even for a minute. And while carrying heavy weight — not at all. More tiredness — less speed. Ideally, muscle stamina should count separately for legs and arms. Tired arms would aim badly, tired legs would stumble.</p>
<p>2b. Being so heavy, how can Freeman stay afloat? With HEV suit even without other items he’ll sink, and with an arsenal he’s a living anchor. He might walk on the bottom more often than swim, and use a ladder to get „ashore“. If there’s no ladder — he’ll have to drop fast some of the heavy things and swim up as hard as he can. HEV should show „water detected“ icon, even if the head stays above. Depth meter will be very useful — HEV needs pressure sensor anyway.</p>
<p>3a. Limits of HEV item holders are questionable: how it is practically possible to carry all the weapons and ammo? Remember how X-COM managed this: there are item holders in the backpack (9), belt (6), legs (2) and shoulders (2). A big weapon like RPG (if not carried in the hand) can only fit in the backpack, which takes more time to reach. Max. number of weapons (not counting explosives) is 7: 2 in arms, 2 small (like pistols) on the belt and up to 3 in the bag, but that leaves little place for explosives and ammo, and turns this solder into a slow poking behemoth.</p>
<p>3b. Reaching fast for desired item is also a problem: how to hold it properly (so you won’t loose it after hours of running, jumping, diving and taking hits) and still be able to unhook it easy and fast by touch alone? And what to do with the previous item held in the hand? How much time it actually takes to swap a weapon (and secure the previous one so you won’t loose it)? Is it possible to do it while walking? Crawling? Climbing? Diving? If yes, how much slower it’ll be than standing action? How many days of tedious training it requires? IMO, if climbing or swimming — you can’t even hold anything.</p>
<p>3c. Luckily, Freeman can use left hand to hold and use second weapon or other object (unless main weapon is bulky and requires both hands to hold). However, he’s not ambidexter, so left hand would aim badly. OTOH, left hand can hold a weapon in the right hand to cope better with recoil. Left hand (if free) can also be used to activate an interactive object.</p>
<ol start="4">
<li>If you want to aim better — stretch your arm forward and align weapon to target direction. If you try to move at that moment — arm will shake. (Theoretically, inertia should work here: assuming you always aim at the center of the view, after turning the arm it will stabilize in same direction after some fading oscillations. For same reason aiming at moving target is always worse vs. stationary. However, mouse moving is also inertial, so adding more inertia in the game will be redundant.) The faster you move — the less you can aim. Running, crawling, climbing or swimming disables shooting at all.</li>
</ol>
<p>5a. There should be visible shooting and reload leftover — dropped shells and empty magazines (incorrectly called clips). Lying empty magazine looks like a full one, until you grab it. NPC’s should have finite inventory. If you’re against a grunt and eventually kill him, he’ll leave you just a few bullets in his magazine.</p>
<p>5b. Semi-empty magazines are a problem. For most weapons you can cross-load: pull the bullets out and push them in another magazine, if there is a place — but it’s long. You can use magazines as is, but you have to carry more weight and rely on unpredictable number of bullets after each reload. In theory, HEV can measure somehow and memorize magazine contents, but you still reach your hand to get one of them by touch, and that may not be the full one. Easy solution is not taking a magazine if at least one bullet is missing, but that’ll make Freeman’s life much harder. Better solution is cross-loading between battles: for each weapon with magazines Freeman carries at most one semi-magazine (except the loaded one), empties gathered semi-magazine and puts its bullets in his semi-magazine, until it’s full. If there are more bullets inside gathered semi-magazine, he takes it. When unloading under-used magazine, he either drops it (loosing bullets but saving time), or cross-load it with kept semi-magazine. Fast cross-loading may be done by shifting the bullet out of donor magazine with one thumb and pushing it in acceptor magazine with another, and repeating it. This still needs both hands to be empty, but doesn’t need hard surface to keep bullets in-between, so it’s possible while standing and slow walking.</p>
<p>6a. Actual HEV suit requires up to half an hour to put on, especially for newbie as Gordon. (You may check the procedure of putting a coverall to get into a clean-room in semiconductor fabs — BTW, there is always a mirror to check yourself afterwards.) Before that he needs to take off almost everything and put it in the closet. It’ll be a long and boring non-interactive script. Gordon may arrive from training with that suit on, so he doesn’t need to visit HEV room, but that’s not canonical. Otherwise, in the room there should be a fully automated dressing robot for fast putting on and taking off a suit, but that still needs Gordon to be almost naked. Maybe that robot can also undress him, but that’ll look like a cut from The Jetsons  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=9" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:">  However, we’ve seen that — in the Star Wars, ep.3: barely survived Anakin handled by robots, gets prosthetic limbs and helmet and becomes Darth Vader. Afterwards Vader makes his first «kshhh-pffff», and Gordon hears «Welcome to the HEV mark IV protective system…»  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=9" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
<p>6b. Helmet. There are 3 options:<br>
—No helmet, as Freeman is always depicted. Then it’s impossible to make a lot of things: survive in space or under water, protect from fog, sparks and hits in the head. And no HUD with visual overlap and sound. Not good.<br>
—Helmet on. Everything is OK, but Freeman’s face is invisible, which isn’t esthetically good.<br>
—Alternative helmet on — with large transparent visor (like space-suits have) and projected HUD. If it involves a mouthpiece (like air filter) — it would explain why Freeman’s always mum  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=9" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:">  Also, helmet will get dirty and wet, so there must be some cleaning. Easy is wiping with a hand. Cool is engaging some ultrasound or electrically catalyzed hydrophobic cleaning layer, which magically stays transparent when not active. I don’t know which one is more plausible  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=9" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
<p>6c. Freeman’s old school glasses are a problem. For some reason he didn’t underwent a laser surgery to fix his myopia. He’s being depicted with them everywhere in HL and HL2, but in real life there’s no way he could survive with them instead of the helmet. They can get dirty, wet and broken (and injure his eyes), slip off a nose and fall down. And no HUD! Even if he can wear them inside the helmet, surely they wouldn’t survive HECU ambush. Ideally, Freeman should replace them with a pair of contact lenses before getting into HEV. But that’d impair his iconic look. I don’t know the solution.</p>
<p>6d. How can HECU knock down Freeman without removing his suit? Even taking off the helmet shouldn’t be easy, because there must be internal lock. But the suit is made elsewhere (not by BM) and it’s very much like HECU’s own, so they must know some weak spot in it — like how to unlock the helmet from outside. After catching Freeman in the dark one of the grunts can say «Press here and turn», Freeman’s helmet with HUD image is ripped off, and he gets beaten in the face. (In HL-BS Barny saw 2 grunts carrying Freeman without helmet.) Then they loosely slap the helmet on his head before throwing in the compactor, because there should be no trace of him, including HEV. Awaking from unconscious, he has no time to put it properly and reengage the HUD — just to adjust it after a fall. After getting out of the drain pipe he falls on the sand, dropping the helmet. He gets it again and cleans, but still no time to put it — a headcrab is approaching. Freeman either kill the crab with the crowbar or run away with the helmet in his head. After putting it on properly the HUD should show and say something disturbing: «Warning! HEV integrity may be compromised. Seek technical support!». Then we’re back in business.</p>
<ol start="7">
<li>In real life when walking you have to check the surface in front so you won’t stumble over an object or stairs. However, if the object next to a foot is light — you’ll kick it away. With medium weight — you’ll move it and stumble. Stumbling should hurt your leg, especially if you run. What you need is a visual confirmation of the surface ahead. However, scene awareness is limited in time and space, so rules should be like this — Freeman won’t stumble, if an object is 1) seen last time no more than T seconds ago, 2) located no more than D meters away and 3) positioned at no more than A degrees away from visual normal (screen center direction). This means Freeman will stumble over anything if strafing or moving backwards, unless he’s looking directly under the boots — just as in real life.</li>
</ol>
<p>8a. Mass distribution, impulse and force are largely omitted. Hit or kick should turn and/or push the target at certain angle, velocity and direction — having speed, contact position and mass data. At times it would also push away or turn the attacker. Recoil is present, but made wrong, because objects are not points. Even if they are one-piece, there is a barycenter (center of mass). If pushing directly at it — the object will move. If pushing at a sharp angle to that vector — it’ll move and turn. If pushing at a right or obtuse angle — it’ll just turn. Surface friction also comes to play. Real recoil will try to topple you on a back. Even more precise is to use N-piece (ragdoll) model with certain masses and movement limits of joints between pieces. Here, recoil will move the arm much more than torso and head, and legs wouldn’t move at all. Aiming will be difficult if shooting in series.</p>
<p>8b. There’s no way to keep vertical position all the time. Body can tilt and even fall down in all directions reacting to various events: crawling, hitting, taking a hit, stumbling, firing with recoil, slipping on some surfaces… Long slipping speed should be limited by some terminal velocity, derived from weight, friction, inclination and gravity.</p>
<p>8c. When falling from height it’s possible to soften vertical speed by rolling over a head right after landing on feet (SWATs and SEALs trained at that). If it doesn’t work, it’ll result in at least one fracture, which takes months to heal, unless — read below about medkits… Same with hitting a wall while running — at least head injury is inevitable. Saving from deep fall (even if air drag limits terminal velocity) is not possible by landing on a ladder! It is possible by diving in a liquid, but only in proper position and with certain minimum depth. Also, after landing there is some damage to object or subject below, which may result in death or crushing. This also means that it’s possible to break a wooden crate without any weapon — just by jumping over while carrying something heavy. Some objects are so weak, they wouldn’t even support Freeman’s weight, if stepped on. After being hit by something or someone (floor, wall or enemy melee attack), Freeman might occasionally loose some of it’s items — dropping from hands or inventory (if loosely held). Same rules apply to HECU and SpecOps — push them down to die from a fall or loose a gun.</p>
<p>8d. There is no move control while subject is on air. If you jumped in some direction, you can change it yourself only by firing a weapon with recoil, positioned at a right angle. Wind and blast wave apply too.</p>
<p>9a. It’s impossible to be healed momentarily. Actual medicines are: 1) specialized (no panacea), 2) start working after some minutes, 3) gradually raise effect for minutes to hours, 4) some of them loosing effect for hours to a day and need to be reapplied, otherwise healing will be lost. Some of the damage cannot be healed by medkits at all (e.g. bone fractures require hospitalization), unless Black Mesa developed some portable and ultrafast medicine, which should be scientifically explainable (like nanoshpere-carried tissue-targeted regeneration with stem-cell pre-programming and enzyme growth acceleration). But even that cure can’t be flash-fast heal-all.</p>
<p>9b. Health should be detailed to every major body part: head, torso, 2 arms and 2 legs. If a bullsquid bite your left leg — its health goes down independently (blood loss will hinder overall health, but the suit will stop it immediately). If any body part reaches 0 — you are either dead or deadly injured (like loosing an arm). Health should effect activity of body parts: leg wounds result to lameness, carrying less weight and jumping to less height (if jumping at all); arm injury result in loss of aiming precision and also carrying less weight; head illness impairs overall body coordination and reaction, distort senses (up to hallucinations) and more. However, after the injury Freeman’s immune system should slowly alleviate the damage partially even without medkits — and the healthy he is, the better it’ll work. Apart from stamina reserve, another health-related parameter is heart rate. Even if you are healthy, high heart rate impairs aiming and adds heavy breathing.</p>
<p>9c. After hours of adventures an average MIT graduate will get hungry, and after sweating a lot (even being a superhero) he certainly will be thirsty. Instead of searching for another vending machine with food and water and taking off the helmet, a parenteral nutrient compound (water, sugars, amino and fatty acids, vitamins, minerals) may be administered intravenously (as healing solutions), but the suit should replenish it from outside. Compound energy capacity is 1500 kcal/litre; adult male energy consumption is ranging from 2 (easy handwork while standing) to 23 (running at 30 km/h) kcal/(hour·kg) — here’s where heart rate and total mass matters too. Low nutrients in the blood (AKA hunger) causes lower stamina reserve.</p>
<p>9d. (No, I won’t speculate on Freeman’s needs to pee and poo… Scratch this.)</p>
<p>[Hit the post size limit here… What do I get for writing a longest non-spam post on this forum? Bounty, ban or both?  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=9" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:">  ]</p>
            <p><small>60 posts - 28 participants</small></p>
            <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/reality-mod/9247">Read full topic</a></p>
          ]]></description>
          <link>https://leakfree.org/t/reality-mod/9247</link>
          <pubDate>Wed, 29 Aug 2012 19:00:06 +0000</pubDate>
          <discourse:topicPinned>No</discourse:topicPinned>
          <discourse:topicClosed>No</discourse:topicClosed>
          <discourse:topicArchived>No</discourse:topicArchived>
          <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-topic-9247</guid>
          <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/reality-mod/9247.rss">Reality mod</source>
        </item>
        <item>
          <title>Further Data Maps</title>
          <dc:creator><![CDATA[Dias]]></dc:creator>
          <category>Suggestion Box</category>
          <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I went back &amp; played Half-life’s demo Half-Life: Uplink not too long ago &amp; as the demo ends the screen fades to black &amp; the words “further data needed” pop up on the screen. Well, I just remembered that valve actually made a free promotional CD called <a href="https://www.halflifeuplink.com/furtherdata/" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Further Data</a> that contains 5 deathmatch maps not included in the retail version of Half-Life:</p>
<ul>
<li>doublecross</li>
<li>rustmill</li>
<li>team9</li>
<li>thehill</li>
<li>xen_dm</li>
</ul>
<p>I’m just curious to see the opinions of the maps by those who hadn’t played them before &amp; who’d be interested in seeing these maps be remade for Black Mesa.</p>
            <p><small>15 posts - 8 participants</small></p>
            <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/further-data-maps/9242">Read full topic</a></p>
          ]]></description>
          <link>https://leakfree.org/t/further-data-maps/9242</link>
          <pubDate>Tue, 28 Aug 2012 10:47:19 +0000</pubDate>
          <discourse:topicPinned>No</discourse:topicPinned>
          <discourse:topicClosed>No</discourse:topicClosed>
          <discourse:topicArchived>No</discourse:topicArchived>
          <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-topic-9242</guid>
          <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/further-data-maps/9242.rss">Further Data Maps</source>
        </item>
        <item>
          <title>Enhancing the Abilities and Intelligence of the Mawmen</title>
          <dc:creator><![CDATA[Boundaryman]]></dc:creator>
          <category>Suggestion Box</category>
          <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Note: Just in case your confused, Mawmen was the other word used to describe the Headcrabbed zombies.</p>
<p>I know that Mawmen are slow and are not supposed to be bright, but they’re not completely stupid either. In the chapter, We Got Hostiles, they were smart enough to sneak through the vents and grab one of the Barnies. In the demo, Uplink, it’s suggested that they were working with the Houndeyes to lure you towards them and to trigger a trap which boxed you in with them.</p>
<p>What if you enhanced the Mawmen’s abilities, such as the ability to pick up wrenches and throwing them at you, the ability to climb a ladder and a rope, and the ability to crouch and climb through vents. Also, why not give them the ability to work with other Xen creatures to improve their efforts in trying to defeat you? They would still be slow and easy to kill, but I think some basic intelligence could be beneficial to the gameplay.</p>
            <p><small>25 posts - 17 participants</small></p>
            <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/enhancing-the-abilities-and-intelligence-of-the-mawmen/9067">Read full topic</a></p>
          ]]></description>
          <link>https://leakfree.org/t/enhancing-the-abilities-and-intelligence-of-the-mawmen/9067</link>
          <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jul 2012 20:13:56 +0000</pubDate>
          <discourse:topicPinned>No</discourse:topicPinned>
          <discourse:topicClosed>No</discourse:topicClosed>
          <discourse:topicArchived>No</discourse:topicArchived>
          <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-topic-9067</guid>
          <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/enhancing-the-abilities-and-intelligence-of-the-mawmen/9067.rss">Enhancing the Abilities and Intelligence of the Mawmen</source>
        </item>
        <item>
          <title>Source Filmmaker in Black Mesa?</title>
          <dc:creator><![CDATA[PJAMA]]></dc:creator>
          <category>Suggestion Box</category>
          <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Following the release of Meet the Pyro, we all know that Source Filmmaker is now released as a beta. I was wondering if the Black Mesa team will be able to implement the replay system into Black Mesa Deathmatch and implement Source Filmmaker into Black Mesa.</p>
<p>I’m not very sure if the SFM team will be releasing the codes for the replay system, but to be sure I sent them an email.</p>
<p>Maybe with SFM, The Devs will be able to make a better intro/teaser for Black Mesa’s release.</p>
            <p><small>33 posts - 24 participants</small></p>
            <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/source-filmmaker-in-black-mesa/8994">Read full topic</a></p>
          ]]></description>
          <link>https://leakfree.org/t/source-filmmaker-in-black-mesa/8994</link>
          <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jul 2012 00:00:23 +0000</pubDate>
          <discourse:topicPinned>No</discourse:topicPinned>
          <discourse:topicClosed>No</discourse:topicClosed>
          <discourse:topicArchived>No</discourse:topicArchived>
          <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-topic-8994</guid>
          <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/source-filmmaker-in-black-mesa/8994.rss">Source Filmmaker in Black Mesa?</source>
        </item>
        <item>
          <title>Certain enemies becoming passive?</title>
          <dc:creator><![CDATA[Eion_Kilant_739]]></dc:creator>
          <category>Suggestion Box</category>
          <description><![CDATA[
            <p>So while playing Half-Life I encoutered two parts where some Vortigaunt(s) did not attack. This was due to a bug, I’m sure, but it gave a false sense of freedom that I really liked. The ability to spare certian hostiles (depending on context) is a wonderful ability in games.</p>
<p>This ability is great and is fun to do when I’m killing a ton of enemies and I start to wonder why they keep trying to kill me. So I disarm one and leave him amongst an area I won’t be returning to, as a sign of peace.</p>
<p>Let me describe how it happened in Half-Life (goldrc): I was in the hallway right before the lift to the first encounter of those Black Spec-Ops Ninjas. I get to the part where I’m being ambushed by two Vortigaunts spawning on both ends of the hallway. I kill the one back where I came, get into cover, shoot the one down the hallway, get into cover, and reload.  I pause, knowing it’s not dead. I go around the corner aiming for the head but I pause again as it hasn’t attacked. No more Vortigaunts are appearing and I decide to go up the lift. The Vortigaunt folows me up the lift and still does not attack. The security guard dies and I decide to sent the Vortigaunt back down the elevator, thus sparing it.</p>
<p>The other instance was much later in the game, durring Xen. There comes a part where you walk into an open-ish area that contains something that somewhat resembles a ski lift. I crouch walk into the area and a Vortigaunt walks right next to me but doesn’t react. I soon discover that as long as I don’t bump into these Vortigaunts they will not do their usual attack routine. I can go about my buisness and watch them make hand gestures as some run around the place.</p>
<p>Both of these experiences greatly added to the feel of the game and both make sense when Half-Life 2 is factored in. These were great parts and were enjoyable.</p>
<p>This sort of thing has been built into other games too! Take Halo 3 for example. On the level Crow’s Nest there is a scene with Thel 'Vadam where he attacks two hostile Drones and yells to them about how their leader (the “prophet” Truth) is lying to them (which he is). Normaly Thel 'Vadam kills the drones, but if the player interferes and stops him from killing the drones it will cause certian drones throughout the level to be friendly.</p>
<p>(I also recall a part in Dues Ex where if you spare some certian random people it causes a truce or something.)</p>
<p>What I’m trying to get across is that this is a great feature that should be possible somewhere in the game. Now I’m not suggesting that more than a handful of NPC’s be capable of this, but when a certian NPC encounters a certian pre-set situation it could cease attacking. The ability to spare the life of someone, wether to be a lone survivor or as a sign of peace, is a great thing to be able to do in a videogame.</p>
<p>(The Marines or non-sentient Xen wildlife should not be considered for this.)</p>
            <p><small>113 posts - 37 participants</small></p>
            <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/certain-enemies-becoming-passive/8984">Read full topic</a></p>
          ]]></description>
          <link>https://leakfree.org/t/certain-enemies-becoming-passive/8984</link>
          <pubDate>Tue, 03 Jul 2012 06:35:09 +0000</pubDate>
          <discourse:topicPinned>No</discourse:topicPinned>
          <discourse:topicClosed>No</discourse:topicClosed>
          <discourse:topicArchived>No</discourse:topicArchived>
          <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-topic-8984</guid>
          <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/certain-enemies-becoming-passive/8984.rss">Certain enemies becoming passive?</source>
        </item>
        <item>
          <title>A few things i would like to see in BMS</title>
          <dc:creator><![CDATA[Iyiyiy9]]></dc:creator>
          <category>Suggestion Box</category>
          <description><![CDATA[
            <p>1.i would like to see more scientist models and more character designs to make the environment feel more realistic.<br>
2.some crowbar texture changing things. ex:when you hit an alien with it green blood is on it when you hit a human red blood (a little darker than the crowbars default color) on it and for the blood to casually wash off while in water.<br>
3.for sounds such as foot steps  to be an option to turn off.This one doesn’t bother me but a few of my friends complained about it.<br>
4.some hidden weapons/rooms that don’t require cheats and a reference to chumtoad.</p>
<p>I hope you took some of my suggestion’s into mind and thank you for reading.</p>
            <p><small>9 posts - 6 participants</small></p>
            <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/a-few-things-i-would-like-to-see-in-bms/8944">Read full topic</a></p>
          ]]></description>
          <link>https://leakfree.org/t/a-few-things-i-would-like-to-see-in-bms/8944</link>
          <pubDate>Mon, 25 Jun 2012 05:44:27 +0000</pubDate>
          <discourse:topicPinned>No</discourse:topicPinned>
          <discourse:topicClosed>No</discourse:topicClosed>
          <discourse:topicArchived>No</discourse:topicArchived>
          <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-topic-8944</guid>
          <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/a-few-things-i-would-like-to-see-in-bms/8944.rss">A few things i would like to see in BMS</source>
        </item>
        <item>
          <title>Kleiner&#39;s appearance</title>
          <dc:creator><![CDATA[garrthbarrttinn]]></dc:creator>
          <category>Suggestion Box</category>
          <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I was reading <a href="https://half-life.wikia.com/wiki/Isaac_Kleiner" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">this</a> wiki article about Kleiner. Included in the article is this picture of Kleiner on a magazine cover taken from in-game HL2.<br>
<img src="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/original/2X/d/df707b425ec7cb53215d3f1087cee7feb233932a.png" alt="" data-base62-sha1="vSDsUJGMJxu7UMENK2FropUWmIq" width="204" height="183"><br>
According to the article, “the picture likely dates from around the Black Mesa Incident”. So if the article’s analysis is correct, Kleiner, during the events of Half-Life 1, should have large amounts of brown hair and sideburns as in the cover of the magazine. If I remember right, the actual blackmesa Kleiner looks more or less the same as HL2 Kleiner just with browner and more hair.</p>
<p>Your thoughts? Is the wiki correct in assuming the picture was taken around the time of HL1? Is it too late to change Kleiner’s appearance to match the magazine photo? Is it even a good idea to change his appearance?</p>
            <p><small>16 posts - 12 participants</small></p>
            <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/kleiners-appearance/8883">Read full topic</a></p>
          ]]></description>
          <link>https://leakfree.org/t/kleiners-appearance/8883</link>
          <pubDate>Sun, 10 Jun 2012 09:48:18 +0000</pubDate>
          <discourse:topicPinned>No</discourse:topicPinned>
          <discourse:topicClosed>No</discourse:topicClosed>
          <discourse:topicArchived>No</discourse:topicArchived>
          <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-topic-8883</guid>
          <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/kleiners-appearance/8883.rss">Kleiner&#39;s appearance</source>
        </item>
        <item>
          <title>Post Release Plugins</title>
          <dc:creator><![CDATA[AliDuh1]]></dc:creator>
          <category>Suggestion Box</category>
          <description><![CDATA[
            <p>After the initial release of the game, maybe the developers can release little optionally downloadable packs of content for the game, and not actually working on them during initial development. I have some ideas for some myself. REMEMBER: I am not demanding that the devs do this, but it is a SUGGESTION.</p>
<p><em><span class="bbcode-b">Sharpshooter pack</span></em><br>
For people who liked the HD weapons for the original Half-Life. It replaces all of the current weapons with the ones in the original HD pack except for the weapons that remain unchanged except for higher poly (if it’s hard to understand, it means like replace the Glock with the Beretta, the SPAS-12 sawed-off with SPAS-12 with the stock folded, the MP5 with the M4, etc.)</p>
<p><em><span class="bbcode-b">Filmmaker kit</span></em><br>
access to the TF2 replay editor, for the people making a Half-Life/ Black Mesa movie. I, for one, am one of those people. It should also add a 3rd person view of Gordon with many realistic 3rd person animations.</p>
<p>*<span class="bbcode-b">Smart Moving Pack</span><br>
should add a whole bunch of first person animations, picking up items similar to in L4D, scripted animations, all inspired by this video: <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=wtIp8jOo8_o&amp;feature=player_embedded" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=wtIp8jOo8_o&amp;feature=player_embedded</a></p>
            <p><small>14 posts - 11 participants</small></p>
            <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/post-release-plugins/8781">Read full topic</a></p>
          ]]></description>
          <link>https://leakfree.org/t/post-release-plugins/8781</link>
          <pubDate>Wed, 23 May 2012 06:14:36 +0000</pubDate>
          <discourse:topicPinned>No</discourse:topicPinned>
          <discourse:topicClosed>No</discourse:topicClosed>
          <discourse:topicArchived>No</discourse:topicArchived>
          <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-topic-8781</guid>
          <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/post-release-plugins/8781.rss">Post Release Plugins</source>
        </item>
        <item>
          <title>screen shake</title>
          <dc:creator><![CDATA[iddqd]]></dc:creator>
          <category>Suggestion Box</category>
          <description><![CDATA[
            <p>dont know if already mentioned. but only a few weeks ago cs:go finally found its roots again and implemented screen shake.</p>
<p>now screenshake is what made CS feel so fantastic.</p>
<p>i honestly cant tell if HL has it, and i am just to lazy to check it out. but what i know: screenshake is a musthave for every shootergame.  it is the one reason why CS felt so much better compared to other shooters.</p>
<p>so will it be in there?  will it be at least optional? or is BM going to have a lot of distance to CS-behavior and recoil ?</p>
            <p><small>38 posts - 25 participants</small></p>
            <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/screen-shake/8733">Read full topic</a></p>
          ]]></description>
          <link>https://leakfree.org/t/screen-shake/8733</link>
          <pubDate>Mon, 07 May 2012 11:28:43 +0000</pubDate>
          <discourse:topicPinned>No</discourse:topicPinned>
          <discourse:topicClosed>No</discourse:topicClosed>
          <discourse:topicArchived>No</discourse:topicArchived>
          <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-topic-8733</guid>
          <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/screen-shake/8733.rss">screen shake</source>
        </item>
        <item>
          <title>Music props</title>
          <dc:creator><![CDATA[Unforeseen_Physics]]></dc:creator>
          <category>Suggestion Box</category>
          <description><![CDATA[
            <p>What I mean, basically, is the following.<br>
In Portal, we have this.</p>
<p><div class="lightbox-wrapper"><a class="lightbox" href="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/original/3X/d/9/d9bb1b291e91945ba203fa0850dc263fe3561880.jpeg" data-download-href="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/d9bb1b291e91945ba203fa0850dc263fe3561880" title=""><img src="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/original/3X/d/9/d9bb1b291e91945ba203fa0850dc263fe3561880.jpeg" alt="" data-base62-sha1="v48u0GB8HZoVVeFyF5WLQcXrgic" width="690" height="429" data-small-upload="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/optimized/3X/d/9/d9bb1b291e91945ba203fa0850dc263fe3561880_2_10x10.png"><div class="meta"><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-far-image svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#far-image"></use></svg><span class="filename"></span><span class="informations">1165×725 55.5 KB</span><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-discourse-expand svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#discourse-expand"></use></svg></div></a></div></p>
<p>It would be nice as a bonus for black mesa to feature some cheesy tunes throughout the game played back by some various situational gadgets.<br>
It’s a nice way to add a human touch to the whole thing.<br>
Those devices could be for instance:</p>
<ul>
<li>Radios lying around on desks</li>
<li>Elevator speakers</li>
<li>PA malfunction</li>
<li>A scientist playing a game on his computer</li>
<li>Car radio left on</li>
<li>Cellphone ringing</li>
</ul>
<p>It’s not a must and probably not worth the time, but I don’t think it would take too long to implement either (provided that you guys haven’t already done it).<br>
As for the music itself, I’m sure there are plenty of people here to help out, including me.</p>
<p>That being said,<br>
<a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?feature=player_detailpage&amp;v=J9C78b_FhKA#t=211s" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">the ultimate inspiration.</a></p>
            <p><small>3 posts - 3 participants</small></p>
            <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/music-props/8667">Read full topic</a></p>
          ]]></description>
          <link>https://leakfree.org/t/music-props/8667</link>
          <pubDate>Fri, 13 Apr 2012 19:43:45 +0000</pubDate>
          <discourse:topicPinned>No</discourse:topicPinned>
          <discourse:topicClosed>No</discourse:topicClosed>
          <discourse:topicArchived>No</discourse:topicArchived>
          <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-topic-8667</guid>
          <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/music-props/8667.rss">Music props</source>
        </item>
        <item>
          <title>Crowbar Aesthetics</title>
          <dc:creator><![CDATA[RadicalEdward2]]></dc:creator>
          <category>Suggestion Box</category>
          <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I haven’t seen any topics about this yet, but maybe as the game progresses the Crowbar could show signs of use or small damage (such as scratchs or very light human or alien blood stains). Basically, nothing too noticeable but perhaps a sign than the crowbar has had it’s fair share of use throughout the game. Also, have the model restored to look new again when Gordon has to find a new one (immediately after Apprehension). Just a little suggest. I just thought about it because there was something similar in Left 4 Dead 2.</p>
            <p><small>65 posts - 36 participants</small></p>
            <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/crowbar-aesthetics/8644">Read full topic</a></p>
          ]]></description>
          <link>https://leakfree.org/t/crowbar-aesthetics/8644</link>
          <pubDate>Fri, 06 Apr 2012 16:42:55 +0000</pubDate>
          <discourse:topicPinned>No</discourse:topicPinned>
          <discourse:topicClosed>No</discourse:topicClosed>
          <discourse:topicArchived>No</discourse:topicArchived>
          <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-topic-8644</guid>
          <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/crowbar-aesthetics/8644.rss">Crowbar Aesthetics</source>
        </item>
        <item>
          <title>Suggestion: Deathmatch Bots.</title>
          <dc:creator><![CDATA[deadlife101]]></dc:creator>
          <category>Suggestion Box</category>
          <description><![CDATA[
            <p>May I suggest the option of bots in servers in Deathmatch? Much like in Counter-Strike: Source.</p>
            <p><small>15 posts - 11 participants</small></p>
            <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/suggestion-deathmatch-bots/8642">Read full topic</a></p>
          ]]></description>
          <link>https://leakfree.org/t/suggestion-deathmatch-bots/8642</link>
          <pubDate>Fri, 06 Apr 2012 05:42:24 +0000</pubDate>
          <discourse:topicPinned>No</discourse:topicPinned>
          <discourse:topicClosed>No</discourse:topicClosed>
          <discourse:topicArchived>No</discourse:topicArchived>
          <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-topic-8642</guid>
          <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/suggestion-deathmatch-bots/8642.rss">Suggestion: Deathmatch Bots.</source>
        </item>
        <item>
          <title>I just suggest someone prove this isn&#39;t vaporeware</title>
          <dc:creator><![CDATA[Gordon_D_Freeman]]></dc:creator>
          <category>Suggestion Box</category>
          <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Because I and 99% of the internet thinks Black Mesa Source is a pipe dream.</p>
<p>What’s it been, over two years since the last update ?</p>
<blockquote>
<p><img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/frowning.png?v=9" title=":frowning:" class="emoji only-emoji" alt=":frowning:"></p>
</blockquote>
            <p><small>1 post - 1 participant</small></p>
            <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/i-just-suggest-someone-prove-this-isnt-vaporeware/8626">Read full topic</a></p>
          ]]></description>
          <link>https://leakfree.org/t/i-just-suggest-someone-prove-this-isnt-vaporeware/8626</link>
          <pubDate>Sun, 01 Apr 2012 18:35:52 +0000</pubDate>
          <discourse:topicPinned>No</discourse:topicPinned>
          <discourse:topicClosed>No</discourse:topicClosed>
          <discourse:topicArchived>No</discourse:topicArchived>
          <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-topic-8626</guid>
          <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/i-just-suggest-someone-prove-this-isnt-vaporeware/8626.rss">I just suggest someone prove this isn&#39;t vaporeware</source>
        </item>
        <item>
          <title>multiplayer/campaign ideas</title>
          <dc:creator><![CDATA[headcrabwarrior]]></dc:creator>
          <category>Suggestion Box</category>
          <description><![CDATA[
            <p>what about after the release <em>whenever that is</em> they work on a multiplayer version? with custom modes, for instance maybe something like gears of war 3’s beast mode, or left 4 deads versus mode? like playing as monsters and fighting humans? or maybe they could make an entirely different campaign where you play as something? And what about just some fun gamemodes? like TF2’s slag server</p>
            <p><small>27 posts - 21 participants</small></p>
            <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/multiplayer-campaign-ideas/8603">Read full topic</a></p>
          ]]></description>
          <link>https://leakfree.org/t/multiplayer-campaign-ideas/8603</link>
          <pubDate>Tue, 27 Mar 2012 00:49:43 +0000</pubDate>
          <discourse:topicPinned>No</discourse:topicPinned>
          <discourse:topicClosed>No</discourse:topicClosed>
          <discourse:topicArchived>No</discourse:topicArchived>
          <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-topic-8603</guid>
          <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/multiplayer-campaign-ideas/8603.rss">multiplayer/campaign ideas</source>
        </item>
        <item>
          <title>More Hard Difficulty &quot;specials&quot;</title>
          <dc:creator><![CDATA[Grey_Acumen]]></dc:creator>
          <category>Suggestion Box</category>
          <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I know suggestions are rarely worth submiting this far in, but I just thought it would be fun if there were more features that only popped up on hard difficulty, like how assassins can turn invisible.<br>
Specifically it would be cool if icthyosaurs could leap from the water and drag you in on hard difficulty. The code for it should already be somewhere in the code, (in some form) since it sort of happens to the scientist in the cutscene for the tranq bow.</p>
            <p><small>20 posts - 12 participants</small></p>
            <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/more-hard-difficulty-specials/8556">Read full topic</a></p>
          ]]></description>
          <link>https://leakfree.org/t/more-hard-difficulty-specials/8556</link>
          <pubDate>Mon, 12 Mar 2012 07:51:50 +0000</pubDate>
          <discourse:topicPinned>No</discourse:topicPinned>
          <discourse:topicClosed>No</discourse:topicClosed>
          <discourse:topicArchived>No</discourse:topicArchived>
          <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-topic-8556</guid>
          <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/more-hard-difficulty-specials/8556.rss">More Hard Difficulty &quot;specials&quot;</source>
        </item>
        <item>
          <title>Including BMS on a Valve Game Package</title>
          <dc:creator><![CDATA[Ringleader]]></dc:creator>
          <category>Suggestion Box</category>
          <description><![CDATA[
            <p>A while ago I suggested that the BMS team try to get Valve to include Black Mesa in one of their game packs. I thought it would be a nifty way to distribute it to a lot of people easily, and maybe even have it ported to consoles.</p>
<p>I just wanted to refresh this idea, given that it’s been a while since it’s been talked about and BMS is closer to completion.</p>
            <p><small>20 posts - 16 participants</small></p>
            <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/including-bms-on-a-valve-game-package/8507">Read full topic</a></p>
          ]]></description>
          <link>https://leakfree.org/t/including-bms-on-a-valve-game-package/8507</link>
          <pubDate>Fri, 24 Feb 2012 00:16:52 +0000</pubDate>
          <discourse:topicPinned>No</discourse:topicPinned>
          <discourse:topicClosed>No</discourse:topicClosed>
          <discourse:topicArchived>No</discourse:topicArchived>
          <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-topic-8507</guid>
          <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/including-bms-on-a-valve-game-package/8507.rss">Including BMS on a Valve Game Package</source>
        </item>
        <item>
          <title>Having hands disappear during certain actions</title>
          <dc:creator><![CDATA[Actioncomedyteen98]]></dc:creator>
          <category>Suggestion Box</category>
          <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I think that in certain actions your hands when holding a weapon should disappear in these situations:</p>
<blockquote>
<p>Collecting ammo<br>
Charging your suit<br>
Climbing a ladder<br>
Pulling a lever<br>
Pressing a button<br>
Opening and Closing a door<br>
etc.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>I hope to see this in the game because it seems a little more realistic that way.</p>
<p>Comment how good or bad this idea is if you’d like.</p>
<p>Update: I thought this idea was pretty stupid also.</p>
            <p><small>59 posts - 31 participants</small></p>
            <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/having-hands-disappear-during-certain-actions/8452">Read full topic</a></p>
          ]]></description>
          <link>https://leakfree.org/t/having-hands-disappear-during-certain-actions/8452</link>
          <pubDate>Sun, 05 Feb 2012 19:32:38 +0000</pubDate>
          <discourse:topicPinned>No</discourse:topicPinned>
          <discourse:topicClosed>No</discourse:topicClosed>
          <discourse:topicArchived>No</discourse:topicArchived>
          <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-topic-8452</guid>
          <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/having-hands-disappear-during-certain-actions/8452.rss">Having hands disappear during certain actions</source>
        </item>
        <item>
          <title>New Trailer before relase BM?</title>
          <dc:creator><![CDATA[czolko]]></dc:creator>
          <category>Suggestion Box</category>
          <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Can we expect new Black Mesa Trailer before official release ??</p>
            <p><small>86 posts - 53 participants</small></p>
            <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/new-trailer-before-relase-bm/8414">Read full topic</a></p>
          ]]></description>
          <link>https://leakfree.org/t/new-trailer-before-relase-bm/8414</link>
          <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2012 22:47:32 +0000</pubDate>
          <discourse:topicPinned>No</discourse:topicPinned>
          <discourse:topicClosed>No</discourse:topicClosed>
          <discourse:topicArchived>No</discourse:topicArchived>
          <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-topic-8414</guid>
          <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/new-trailer-before-relase-bm/8414.rss">New Trailer before relase BM?</source>
        </item>
        <item>
          <title>M1 Firing System</title>
          <dc:creator><![CDATA[Dark_Signal]]></dc:creator>
          <category>Suggestion Box</category>
          <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Hello again Black Mesa,</p>
<p>I return with yet another suggestion to make for the mod while it’s still in development.</p>
<p>Although the developers have not released any updates on this site, it is still fortunate that there are updates produced independently by the developers on other sites, such as this video <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=qSe1NUsvZBY" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">here.</a> I don’t know how old this video is, but after seeing this video, I feel that it is in my best interest to offer the idea of changing the firing mechanism of the tank.</p>
<p>For one, a tank shell travels REALLY fast: about at least over 4000 fps. I done the calculations with Source units, and the shell would have to be traveling well over 78,000 game units in Source. Frankly that’s just too much for the source engine to handle. That’s why source made the func_tankmortar entity that gets the vector of the entity, and creates an explosion at the vector end position. I suggest that the tank’s firing mechanism should follow the same principle, with graphical modifications of course.</p>
<p>Secondly, the explosion magnitude of the resulting shell explosion seems way too small as well. For a heavy battle tank, I’d imagine the explosion size would be much greater, unless if a larger explosion size would hinder engine performance, or it’s supposed to be utilizing a different shell of some sort. Either way, I do feel that to show the true power of the M1, it’s explosion size should be increased; especially since to the best of my knowledge, the player is only going to fight it once.</p>
<p>I don’t have any complaints about how strong the tank is, has you have already stated on the wiki, but I’m not under the impression that the adjustments I have stated above will hinder gameplay in any way, so hopefully these ideas will see their way though.</p>
            <p><small>12 posts - 8 participants</small></p>
            <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/m1-firing-system/8405">Read full topic</a></p>
          ]]></description>
          <link>https://leakfree.org/t/m1-firing-system/8405</link>
          <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2012 20:08:23 +0000</pubDate>
          <discourse:topicPinned>No</discourse:topicPinned>
          <discourse:topicClosed>No</discourse:topicClosed>
          <discourse:topicArchived>No</discourse:topicArchived>
          <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-topic-8405</guid>
          <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/m1-firing-system/8405.rss">M1 Firing System</source>
        </item>
        <item>
          <title>Bhop, strafes as they were (MP and SP)</title>
          <dc:creator><![CDATA[monarch]]></dc:creator>
          <category>Suggestion Box</category>
          <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Or is it gonna be that slow run-on-shift and shoot with smg nub mod like current broken HL2dm atm`?<br>
I dont tell i hate that</p>
<p>Multiplayer will b :fffuuu: w/o bhop and fast movement :zip:</p>
<p>idc about SP , but also want it on as well</p>
            <p><small>115 posts - 32 participants</small></p>
            <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/bhop-strafes-as-they-were-mp-and-sp/8215">Read full topic</a></p>
          ]]></description>
          <link>https://leakfree.org/t/bhop-strafes-as-they-were-mp-and-sp/8215</link>
          <pubDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2011 14:24:17 +0000</pubDate>
          <discourse:topicPinned>No</discourse:topicPinned>
          <discourse:topicClosed>No</discourse:topicClosed>
          <discourse:topicArchived>No</discourse:topicArchived>
          <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-topic-8215</guid>
          <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/bhop-strafes-as-they-were-mp-and-sp/8215.rss">Bhop, strafes as they were (MP and SP)</source>
        </item>
        <item>
          <title>Blood Streams, Ragdoll Features, Office Complex, Objects</title>
          <dc:creator><![CDATA[tomdemko]]></dc:creator>
          <category>Suggestion Box</category>
          <description><![CDATA[
            <p>–Blood Streams–<br>
<a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=E0BiUJrjNtw" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=E0BiUJrjNtw</a><br>
Something similar like this other mod for Half-Life, SMod Tactical.</p>
<p>I have an idea that this could also be used on liquid filled barrels, water pipes, etc. Would be cool headshotting a Grunt/Scientist seeing them with blood streaming out of where you shot them. If possible, I would recommend this probably not occurring all the time when you shoot someone. Perhaps you have to shoot them in a certain spot like the neck.</p>
<p>–Ragdoll Features–<br>
To add onto this subject, you will realise that in the vid I linked above shows that when you kill someone their ragdoll is stiff. Maybe BMS can have that for more realism.</p>
<p>–Office Complex–<br>
The parts where you fall out of the ceiling at the office complex, do you think it would be cool to add some DMM to those? The only problem is that it can kill and be able to float down with if too light.</p>
<p>–Objects–<br>
How will the objects such as boxes be like in BMS? Would you be able to push them around for cover, etc? That’s pretty much what I’m talking about. No more text needed…</p>
            <p><small>63 posts - 21 participants</small></p>
            <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/blood-streams-ragdoll-features-office-complex-objects/7989">Read full topic</a></p>
          ]]></description>
          <link>https://leakfree.org/t/blood-streams-ragdoll-features-office-complex-objects/7989</link>
          <pubDate>Thu, 20 Oct 2011 10:37:59 +0000</pubDate>
          <discourse:topicPinned>No</discourse:topicPinned>
          <discourse:topicClosed>No</discourse:topicClosed>
          <discourse:topicArchived>No</discourse:topicArchived>
          <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-topic-7989</guid>
          <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/blood-streams-ragdoll-features-office-complex-objects/7989.rss">Blood Streams, Ragdoll Features, Office Complex, Objects</source>
        </item>
        <item>
          <title>DM ventrilaquism.</title>
          <dc:creator><![CDATA[xalener]]></dc:creator>
          <category>Suggestion Box</category>
          <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I’m damn sure this has been grazed upon before. There’s no question about this mod that hasn’t been asked yet. The thing is, if it’s been mentioned I haven’t seen it, and I’ve been here a while so…</p>
<p>yeah.</p>
<p>Would it be at all possible to animate the jaw of an MP character’s mouth to open more depending on the volume of the person speaking into their mic?</p>
<p><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?feature=player_detailpage&amp;v=RXMjwvyD9IQ#t=57s" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://www.youtube.com/watch?feature=player_detailpage&amp;v=RXMjwvyD9IQ#t=57s</a> Something like that.</p>
<p>Something simple. No lip movements in this, they look shit anyway (see uncharted 2).</p>
<p>I haven’t the slightest clue if this is something that would have to have been set up for way early on or if it could be added in on a whim or if it could be added on a whim but won’t be (most likely)… but I was more curious as to if it could even work with the current source.</p>
            <p><small>19 posts - 8 participants</small></p>
            <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/dm-ventrilaquism/7954">Read full topic</a></p>
          ]]></description>
          <link>https://leakfree.org/t/dm-ventrilaquism/7954</link>
          <pubDate>Tue, 11 Oct 2011 03:42:31 +0000</pubDate>
          <discourse:topicPinned>No</discourse:topicPinned>
          <discourse:topicClosed>No</discourse:topicClosed>
          <discourse:topicArchived>No</discourse:topicArchived>
          <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-topic-7954</guid>
          <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/dm-ventrilaquism/7954.rss">DM ventrilaquism.</source>
        </item>
        <item>
          <title>HECU Marines</title>
          <dc:creator><![CDATA[Robot_Nixon]]></dc:creator>
          <category>Suggestion Box</category>
          <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Hey guys, long time visitor and fan, finally decided to sign up.  I just have a few minor suggestions for my favorite enemy AI to this day, the HECU Marines.  As a US Marine myself, I’ve always thought they were the most badass, and intelligent AI.  When most other enemies would stay put when you retreated o find health, the Marines would follow you and ruin your day.</p>
<p>But like the original HL, there are some small suggestions for added realism and gameplay.</p>
<p>1: Marines dont wear berets, they wear the 8-point covers (hats).  If there could be a model of those, that would be epic.<br>
2: Adding the weapon of the element of the USMC fireteam i usually fill, the SAW gunner.<br>
3: Marines yelling “Doc!” or “Corpsman!” instead of medic (Marines don’t have medics, they’re Navy Corpsmen)<br>
4: Oakley sunglasses, perfect fit for the desert-bound HECU Marine<br>
5: Keep doing an amazing job  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=9" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
            <p><small>42 posts - 19 participants</small></p>
            <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/hecu-marines/7935">Read full topic</a></p>
          ]]></description>
          <link>https://leakfree.org/t/hecu-marines/7935</link>
          <pubDate>Tue, 04 Oct 2011 20:02:59 +0000</pubDate>
          <discourse:topicPinned>No</discourse:topicPinned>
          <discourse:topicClosed>No</discourse:topicClosed>
          <discourse:topicArchived>No</discourse:topicArchived>
          <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-topic-7935</guid>
          <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/hecu-marines/7935.rss">HECU Marines</source>
        </item>
        <item>
          <title>The Glock 17 for HECU Marines</title>
          <dc:creator><![CDATA[wafflewarrior7]]></dc:creator>
          <category>Suggestion Box</category>
          <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Originally, Hecu marines would fire they’re Mp5’s, or Spas-12’s until they ran out of ammunition, at which point they would drop said weapon, and equip a glock 17. Weather this sidearm had unlimited ammunition is unknown, as it is irrelevant- But according to the WIKI, this was removed because it made grunts much weaker, players would simply take cover until they switched to they’re pea shooters.<br>
I think that the Idea was originally pretty interesting, and though it had flaws, <span class="bbcode-i">it should be revised</span>.<br>
Perhaps Grunts who are killed by a player, have a percentage chance of dropping to the ground in an animation, and whilst down, whip out they’re pistol to make a last-ditch effort to kill Freeman, and in turn, possibly survive.<br>
Not only would such a feature make sense, (they Are wearing ballistic plates, against presumably 9mm rounds, and other weaponry from the late 90’s (not counting nuclear/alien weps))<br>
[COLOR=‘LightBlue’]<span class="bbcode-b">Pros of this feature: </span><br>
adds alot of character to the game- makes player feel ‘my god, I’m killing human beings,’ despite how monstrous they’re actions are. A good sense of inner conflict, as well as pity for the enemy. It allows for headshots to have more relevance, and for the player to think twice before charging into a room, guns blazing, or if anything, double check if they’re really dead or not.<br>
[COLOR=‘Red’]<span class="bbcode-b">Cons of this feature:</span><br>
This will require manpower, and a at least 9-10 hours to code, animate, and get the voice-acting down. It will take at least a week or two to implement into the game, as well as test and rig so that it isn’t so awkward.<br>
[COLOR=‘Orange’]<span class="bbcode-b">What it may mean for black mesa:</span><br>
Not only will this show players that black mesa is a mod with some soul to it, but it will make players go back again and again, having fun that lasts, and enjoying the fantastic voice acting that it would require. “Damn, thats cool!” and “gah, this guy’s shooting me from behind, I thought I killed him!”</p>
<hr>
<p>Thanks for reading, Developer or not, and hopefully this is considered, if not added.  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/smiley.png?v=9" title=":smiley:" class="emoji" alt=":smiley:"></p>
            <p><small>30 posts - 20 participants</small></p>
            <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/the-glock-17-for-hecu-marines/7875">Read full topic</a></p>
          ]]></description>
          <link>https://leakfree.org/t/the-glock-17-for-hecu-marines/7875</link>
          <pubDate>Sat, 24 Sep 2011 21:12:42 +0000</pubDate>
          <discourse:topicPinned>No</discourse:topicPinned>
          <discourse:topicClosed>No</discourse:topicClosed>
          <discourse:topicArchived>No</discourse:topicArchived>
          <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-topic-7875</guid>
          <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/the-glock-17-for-hecu-marines/7875.rss">The Glock 17 for HECU Marines</source>
        </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
