<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Marc Laidlaw&#39;s &#39;Epistle 3&#39;</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/marc-laidlaws-epistle-3/15255</link>
    <description>Marc Laidlaw posted this on his blog tonight, and I think this is the closest we&#39;re going to get to a conclusion to Half-Life.
Some assembly required, as it&#39;s an IP-free bizarro world, but it&#39;s closure.

[url=&#39;https://www.marclaidlaw.com/epistle-3/&#39;]Episle 3[/url]</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 24 Sep 2017 08:30:39 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Half-Life Series</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/marc-laidlaws-epistle-3/15255.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Marc Laidlaw&#39;s &#39;Epistle 3&#39;</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[ESToomere]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="LordDz">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/l/d2c977/40.png" class="avatar"> LordDz:</div>
<blockquote>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="gladoscake122">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/g/f07891/40.png" class="avatar"> gladoscake122:</div>
<blockquote>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="k3nny1550">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/user_avatar/leakfree.org/k3nny1550/40/4952_2.png" class="avatar"> k3nny1550:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>That’s probably another reason the game didn’t get made. Too many loose ends like this.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>so strange and vague, it just <span class="bbcode-b">keeps going on and on</span>. And that’s the point.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Naaaaaaaah… It sorta stopped after Episode two  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/wink.png?v=9" title=":wink:" class="emoji" alt=":wink:"></p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Oh hey LordDz, long time.</p>
<p>It’s great Laidlaw concluded the thing, still a better ending than Lost.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/marc-laidlaws-epistle-3/15255/50">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/marc-laidlaws-epistle-3/15255/50</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 24 Sep 2017 08:30:39 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-15255-50</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/marc-laidlaws-epistle-3/15255.rss">Marc Laidlaw&#39;s &#39;Epistle 3&#39;</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Marc Laidlaw&#39;s &#39;Epistle 3&#39;</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[LordDz]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="gladoscake122">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/g/f07891/40.png" class="avatar"> gladoscake122:</div>
<blockquote>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="k3nny1550">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/user_avatar/leakfree.org/k3nny1550/40/4952_2.png" class="avatar"> k3nny1550:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>That’s probably another reason the game didn’t get made. Too many loose ends like this.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>so strange and vague, it just <span class="bbcode-b">keeps going on and on</span>. And that’s the point.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Naaaaaaaah… It sorta stopped after Episode two  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/wink.png?v=9" title=":wink:" class="emoji" alt=":wink:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/marc-laidlaws-epistle-3/15255/49">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/marc-laidlaws-epistle-3/15255/49</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 23 Sep 2017 23:55:16 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-15255-49</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/marc-laidlaws-epistle-3/15255.rss">Marc Laidlaw&#39;s &#39;Epistle 3&#39;</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Marc Laidlaw&#39;s &#39;Epistle 3&#39;</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[gladoscake122]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="k3nny1550">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/user_avatar/leakfree.org/k3nny1550/40/4952_2.png" class="avatar"> k3nny1550:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>That’s probably another reason the game didn’t get made. Too many loose ends like this.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>The games were always going to end on cliff-hangers though, it wouldn’t be Half-Life if we had 100% exposition and all loose ends tied up, there’d be no remaining speculation, no remaining questions, and i think a big part of Half-Life is centered around not knowing what’s really going on behind the scenes, even the truth is so strange and vague, it just keeps going on and on. And that’s the point.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/marc-laidlaws-epistle-3/15255/48">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/marc-laidlaws-epistle-3/15255/48</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 23 Sep 2017 23:04:04 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-15255-48</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/marc-laidlaws-epistle-3/15255.rss">Marc Laidlaw&#39;s &#39;Epistle 3&#39;</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Marc Laidlaw&#39;s &#39;Epistle 3&#39;</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[k3nny1550]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>That’s probably another reason the game didn’t get made. Too many loose ends like this.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/marc-laidlaws-epistle-3/15255/47">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/marc-laidlaws-epistle-3/15255/47</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Sep 2017 19:10:42 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-15255-47</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/marc-laidlaws-epistle-3/15255.rss">Marc Laidlaw&#39;s &#39;Epistle 3&#39;</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Marc Laidlaw&#39;s &#39;Epistle 3&#39;</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[gladoscake122]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Boundaryman">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/b/ed655f/40.png" class="avatar"> Boundaryman:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I like a lot of ideas Marc Laidlaw laid out in Epistle 3. The Bootstrap Device which propelled the Borealis to the Antarctic reminds me of the noclip-like invisibility cloak device used on the Pegasus in Star Trek: The Next Generation (the ship can fly through solid objects while invisible, and then got stuck inside an asteroid). I figured that some conflict would occur between Alyx and Mossman, though I’m not sure I’d want the conflict to be handled the way it w as. I also expected that Breen to be in an alien host, and I like to choice to let him live or give him a mercy killing. I still would rather have Breen turn into an alien boss fight, but that’s just me.</p>
<p>Having Alyx and Gordon plunge the Borealis into Combine territory as a suicide attack seems stupid, and judging by the conclusion, it didn’t make much of a difference against the Combine.</p>
<p>Anyway, I like the idea of the Bootstrap Device, and it makes sense. I originally expected a device which was an expanded version of Aperture’s portal gun. Something like a big generator which opened seamless portals to any part of the universe or the world. I expected to have Gordon and Alyx teleport back to Xen, then teleport to the Combine’s world, then having to survive in that world and fight the Combine Advisors like Gordon fought the Xen Masters and the Nihilinth back on Xen.</p>
<p>Laidlaw’s Epistle makes no mention of encountered other Combine Advisors in the Borealis. They’ve been built up as these enemies that you were destined to fight in the Episodes, and there’s no mention of fighting them. Judging Episode 2, the Advisors would be the toughest enemies to fight. They are powerful, telekinetic, and can paralyze you any time before they stick their tongues into your head. You need some kind of special weapon, power-up, or tactics to take them on. What possibilities are there? An anti-telekinetic module? An Advisor Buster? Using the environment against the Advisors a la the Tentacles by being stealthy and quick? Using Dog against them? Part of me likes to think that maybe Gordon may find the Portal Gun, and use it to use the environment against the Advisors.</p>
<p>Now that the Epistle is out, how will Mossman will be handled? I mean, her claim that she was helping the resistance all along makes sort of sense, because her reasons for betraying the resistance and Gordon did not. Still, she left Gordon and Alyx behind in Nova Prospekt to fend for themselves after telelporting Eli to the Citadel, and that was a reckless gamble. She only managed to betray Breen because Gordon survived, wrecked Breen’s army, then got caught. If she depended on Gordon and Alyx alive, she could’ve teleported them back to the Citadel with her instead of leaving them to die. I feel that there’s more to Mossman that needs to be explored.</p>
<p>I certainly hope Valve knows what they’re doing. for a new Half-Life.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>To be honest, I always expected that Alyx would be more colder and have unsound judgement after experiencing the events of EP2, without the voice of reason from her father, she’d go ham on anyone who’d dare get in the way of her fulfilling his dying wish.</p>
<p>I think they originally intended to send their huge space-time ‘bomb’ into a structure like the Citadel or take out enemies near by, to send a message like ‘You don’t own us’ to the Union. And their suicide would give the signal to other races to ‘fight back’ and finish what they started. But then they realized what they were up against, Humanity has no hope of taking out the ‘Combine’ completely but they’ve shown that they can do a lot with the right resources in the right place, or rather, the right <em>man</em> in the wrong <em>place</em>… but they managed to block them out of our zone in EP2 and destroyed a piece of technology that would have given them instant teleportation for their larger forces, so the best they can do is to keep closing their portals and taking out their control centers.</p>
<p>I’m sure that this short summary of the main events is missing a lot of battle sequences and fighting, minute details that would have held more meaning in an actual episode, but i do suppose the ‘Combine base’ described as being in the arctic would have played out like Air Exchange and Weather Control, Kraken Base, and the Borealis chapters being a lot like the Citadel in HL2, there would be a lot of potential for exposition, easter eggs, boss fights and puzzle elements in the middle. Breengrub probably was fought before being executed, and the sequence could have been like a nightmarish love-craft equivalent to a caterpillar turning into a butterfly, Breen’s host body cracking open into that flow–y abstract entity from the 2008 concept art. Perhaps fighting his god-like form on the Borealis while going through Xen, all hallucinogenic  and trippy. Or he starts bending our perception of reality, the Arctic environment becoming Xen-ish… something like that.</p>
<p>Regarding Mossman, i have a little headcanon that she was an ex-Aperture employee and joined the company after losing to Gordon in the fight for the position in the Black Mesa test chamber, interestingly, Alyx mentioned how she droned on about how she should have been in the test chamber on the day of the incident, but what could that mean? did she think she could have done what Gordon did? did she know what would happen? i’m not so sure, but it sounds like Aperture is how she knew a great deal of the Borealis and even where it was sent, she even was in possession of ‘resonance keys’ that would allow them to materialize it into their reality, but it’s confusing, her discovery of the ship would have taken place some days before EP1, right? and she went on the trip to find the Combine portal codes, it’s almost as if the Combine were aware of the ship’s location and possibly studying it during HL2, hence Mossman’s attacked by soldiers at a research station. She mentions that she was a double agent, spy, so she had to get on the Combine’s side to get access to the keys and find out where the ship was, but why wasn’t it mentioned by the Resistance before EP2? did she not tell them about it or wasn’t very sure of it? how exactly did the Combine find it but didn’t… use it? and why did the ship only become significant to Gman after HL2? was it always part of his plans for Gordon before the Vortigaunts intervened? did the Borealis only just reappear after HL2? it’s confusing.  And another thing. How exactly was the Borealis docked during the 7 Hour War when it supposedly vanished randomly like a freak accident and there was a crew on board still when they would have left the project once it was discarded and sealed years later like everything in Old Aperture, how did the Combine find the dock, if it was supposedly miles underground? they came in from land, sea and air, so that means they broke in and went to the bowels of the facility, yet left technology like GLaDOS and the Portal Gun behind while looking for this ship? does someone have an explanation for this? it doesn’t work with the timeline at all. Unless it’s because of time travel.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/marc-laidlaws-epistle-3/15255/46">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/marc-laidlaws-epistle-3/15255/46</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Sep 2017 08:55:29 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-15255-46</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/marc-laidlaws-epistle-3/15255.rss">Marc Laidlaw&#39;s &#39;Epistle 3&#39;</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Marc Laidlaw&#39;s &#39;Epistle 3&#39;</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Boundaryman]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I like a lot of ideas Marc Laidlaw laid out in Epistle 3. The Bootstrap Device which propelled the Borealis to the Antarctic reminds me of the noclip-like invisibility cloak device used on the Pegasus in Star Trek: The Next Generation (the ship can fly through solid objects while invisible, and then got stuck inside an asteroid). I figured that some conflict would occur between Alyx and Mossman, though I’m not sure I’d want the conflict to be handled the way it w as. I also expected that Breen to be in an alien host, and I like to choice to let him live or give him a mercy killing. I still would rather have Breen turn into an alien boss fight, but that’s just me.</p>
<p>Having Alyx and Gordon plunge the Borealis into Combine territory as a suicide attack seems stupid, and judging by the conclusion, it didn’t make much of a difference against the Combine.</p>
<p>Anyway, I like the idea of the Bootstrap Device, and it makes sense. I originally expected a device which was an expanded version of Aperture’s portal gun. Something like a big generator which opened seamless portals to any part of the universe or the world. I expected to have Gordon and Alyx teleport back to Xen, then teleport to the Combine’s world, then having to survive in that world and fight the Combine Advisors like Gordon fought the Xen Masters and the Nihilinth back on Xen.</p>
<p>Laidlaw’s Epistle makes no mention of encountered other Combine Advisors in the Borealis. They’ve been built up as these enemies that you were destined to fight in the Episodes, and there’s no mention of fighting them. Judging Episode 2, the Advisors would be the toughest enemies to fight. They are powerful, telekinetic, and can paralyze you any time before they stick their tongues into your head. You need some kind of special weapon, power-up, or tactics to take them on. What possibilities are there? An anti-telekinetic module? An Advisor Buster? Using the environment against the Advisors a la the Tentacles by being stealthy and quick? Using Dog against them? Part of me likes to think that maybe Gordon may find the Portal Gun, and use it to use the environment against the Advisors.</p>
<p>Now that the Epistle is out, how will Mossman will be handled? I mean, her claim that she was helping the resistance all along makes sort of sense, because her reasons for betraying the resistance and Gordon did not. Still, she left Gordon and Alyx behind in Nova Prospekt to fend for themselves after telelporting Eli to the Citadel, and that was a reckless gamble. She only managed to betray Breen because Gordon survived, wrecked Breen’s army, then got caught. If she depended on Gordon and Alyx alive, she could’ve teleported them back to the Citadel with her instead of leaving them to die. I feel that there’s more to Mossman that needs to be explored.</p>
<p>I certainly hope Valve knows what they’re doing. for a new Half-Life.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/marc-laidlaws-epistle-3/15255/45">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/marc-laidlaws-epistle-3/15255/45</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 20 Sep 2017 00:38:07 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-15255-45</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/marc-laidlaws-epistle-3/15255.rss">Marc Laidlaw&#39;s &#39;Epistle 3&#39;</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Marc Laidlaw&#39;s &#39;Epistle 3&#39;</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[geekofalltrades]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Kenley">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/user_avatar/leakfree.org/kenley/40/4737_2.png" class="avatar"> Kenley:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>They would have to know that would come across as foreshadowing of the upcoming game. This suggests at least that the Portal 2 developers thought in 2011 that EP3 was on its way to eventual release.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Or, that Ep3 was still thought to be on its way in 2007, when Portal was released and the devs started thinking about and designing Portal 2 - and, given that 2007 was the release of Ep2, as well, it’s not really surprising that Ep3 was assumed at that point.</p>
<p>Games take a long time to design and make. The story for Portal 2 was certainly nailed down in its final form long before its 2011 release.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/marc-laidlaws-epistle-3/15255/44">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/marc-laidlaws-epistle-3/15255/44</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 31 Aug 2017 04:27:50 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-15255-44</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/marc-laidlaws-epistle-3/15255.rss">Marc Laidlaw&#39;s &#39;Epistle 3&#39;</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Marc Laidlaw&#39;s &#39;Epistle 3&#39;</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Kenley]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="gladoscake122">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/g/f07891/40.png" class="avatar"> gladoscake122:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Is it possible that when EP3 failed as a project, that’s what made them rethink the decision to take Chell out of Portal 2?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>That doesn’t really make sense. Why would they include an easter egg of the Borealis in Portal 2 if EP3 had already been scrapped? They would have to know that would come across as foreshadowing of the upcoming game. This suggests at least that the Portal 2 developers thought in 2011 that EP3 was on its way to eventual release. However, evidently when Laidlaw left Valve in 2016 (or since having left) it seemed to him that HL3/EP3 is not going to be released. At least not in recognizable form. If he thought it was coming out in the foreseeable future, it would have made more sense to just wait and let the game tell its own story. Presumably, things changed between 2011 and 2016, which makes sense.</p>
<p>Now maybe I’m wrong. Maybe:</p>
<ul>
<li>The Borealis in Portal 2 was meant to serve as a call back, rather than foreshadowing (which is possible, but hopefully they’d realize that would backfire)</li>
<li>EP3 is in the same state now (some level of development hell) as it was in 2011, but the perspectives of the Portal 2 devs and Marc Laidlaw are just different, causing them to disagree on whether it’s likely to be released</li>
<li>HL3/EP3/some related IP is in serious development, but it has deviated far from Laidlaw’s original story vision, so that he is offering his own ideal culmination of the arc (as true “fanfiction” which will contradict or otherwise differ in a major way from the eventual canonical continuation of the franchise)</li>
</ul>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/marc-laidlaws-epistle-3/15255/43">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/marc-laidlaws-epistle-3/15255/43</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 31 Aug 2017 03:25:11 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-15255-43</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/marc-laidlaws-epistle-3/15255.rss">Marc Laidlaw&#39;s &#39;Epistle 3&#39;</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Marc Laidlaw&#39;s &#39;Epistle 3&#39;</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[drgibbles]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Personally I believe there has been a lot of work done on the Half-life/Portal games that we don’t know about.  I don’t ever recall any official statement that said things were cancelled.  What I do remember though, is that they were talking about doing something “pretty ambitious”.  I cant help but feel that there is more to it that hasn’t been found.  Like mentioned above the Borealis stuff, the unused photos and textures from the portal game, of the Borealis and scientist from Black Mesa standing in front of it.  The plans of the Borealis that J. Mossman sent, the message that talked about having to send the Borealis off in a hurry by punching something in to the OR BOX.  Just so many options to type the HL-Portal stuff together,  time travel, alternate timelines, even the Minerva stuff, it just seems too good to let it go a full decade without anything being done.  Wishful thinking, sure, but I’d rather believe than not.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/marc-laidlaws-epistle-3/15255/42">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/marc-laidlaws-epistle-3/15255/42</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 31 Aug 2017 01:36:38 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-15255-42</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/marc-laidlaws-epistle-3/15255.rss">Marc Laidlaw&#39;s &#39;Epistle 3&#39;</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Marc Laidlaw&#39;s &#39;Epistle 3&#39;</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[gladoscake122]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Solokiller">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/s/e56c9b/40.png" class="avatar"> Solokiller:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Why would they include references to the Borealis in Portal 2 if they’d already stopped working on Episode 3 by then? They had to have known it would just hype Episode 3 even more.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Is it possible that when EP3 failed as a project, that’s what made them rethink the decision to take Chell out of Portal 2? back in 2007 they originally planned to give her freedom as soon as she was outside, GLaDOS hinted at the possibility that she’d find Black Mesa for help in the credits, and I do recall Valve saying somewhere that they designed Chell for the Half-Life world but they came to find that she fit nicely in Portal, and then they mixed the two worlds together, and apparently she was to have connections with the characters in some way.</p>
<p>I think the EP3 2007-2008 plots involved Chell in some way and thus Portal and Half-Life would have been more connected but when the project didn’t pull through for some reason, they distanced the two worlds and put Chell back in Aperture and also GLaDOS, maybe they planned for her to be in HL3, considering they were supposedly editing prototype EP2 maps and putting in new mechanics as some proof-of-concept kind of thing… since 2012-2013. Maybe Portal 2 was planned to take place post-EP3 and during HL3?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/marc-laidlaws-epistle-3/15255/41">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/marc-laidlaws-epistle-3/15255/41</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 30 Aug 2017 22:28:23 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-15255-41</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/marc-laidlaws-epistle-3/15255.rss">Marc Laidlaw&#39;s &#39;Epistle 3&#39;</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Marc Laidlaw&#39;s &#39;Epistle 3&#39;</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[drgibbles]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="snark567">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/s/bbe5ce/40.png" class="avatar"> snark567:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>It’s not like his story is cannon anyways so whatever. The real continuation of Half Life will include the Strogg from Quake 2/4 which will be part of the combine and you’ll have Doom guy helping you fight them.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I’M IN!</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/marc-laidlaws-epistle-3/15255/40">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/marc-laidlaws-epistle-3/15255/40</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 30 Aug 2017 20:33:02 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-15255-40</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/marc-laidlaws-epistle-3/15255.rss">Marc Laidlaw&#39;s &#39;Epistle 3&#39;</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Marc Laidlaw&#39;s &#39;Epistle 3&#39;</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[snark567]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>It’s not like his story is cannon anyways so whatever. The real continuation of Half Life will include the Strogg from Quake 2/4 which will be part of the combine and you’ll have Doom guy helping you fight them.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/marc-laidlaws-epistle-3/15255/39">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/marc-laidlaws-epistle-3/15255/39</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 30 Aug 2017 13:46:15 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-15255-39</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/marc-laidlaws-epistle-3/15255.rss">Marc Laidlaw&#39;s &#39;Epistle 3&#39;</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Marc Laidlaw&#39;s &#39;Epistle 3&#39;</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Solokiller]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Why would they include references to the Borealis in Portal 2 if they’d already stopped working on Episode 3 by then? They had to have known it would just hype Episode 3 even more.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/marc-laidlaws-epistle-3/15255/38">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/marc-laidlaws-epistle-3/15255/38</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 30 Aug 2017 07:32:45 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-15255-38</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/marc-laidlaws-epistle-3/15255.rss">Marc Laidlaw&#39;s &#39;Epistle 3&#39;</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Marc Laidlaw&#39;s &#39;Epistle 3&#39;</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[drgibbles]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>1.He could have put that out while working there, nda’s don’t expire after 6 months.<br>
2.Doubtful.<br>
3.Exactly.<br>
4.It might.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/marc-laidlaws-epistle-3/15255/37">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/marc-laidlaws-epistle-3/15255/37</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 30 Aug 2017 01:24:23 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-15255-37</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/marc-laidlaws-epistle-3/15255.rss">Marc Laidlaw&#39;s &#39;Epistle 3&#39;</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Marc Laidlaw&#39;s &#39;Epistle 3&#39;</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[RedEye9]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="drgibbles">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/d/74df32/40.png" class="avatar"> drgibbles:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I’m happy to read what Marc put out, but the only question I have, is WHY now, If its been dead this long? Reading this, I cant help but tie it closely to “Minerva” by Adam Foster, turns out what he wanted to do was pretty similar to what Marc just put out.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<ol>
<li>He could not put it out earlier because he was an employee of Valve.</li>
<li>He decided to put it out now because he wanted his website to go down due to the flood of traffic.</li>
<li>If not now, when?</li>
<li>Doe it really matter.</li>
</ol>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/marc-laidlaws-epistle-3/15255/36">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/marc-laidlaws-epistle-3/15255/36</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 29 Aug 2017 22:48:05 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-15255-36</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/marc-laidlaws-epistle-3/15255.rss">Marc Laidlaw&#39;s &#39;Epistle 3&#39;</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Marc Laidlaw&#39;s &#39;Epistle 3&#39;</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[drgibbles]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I’m happy to read what Marc put out, but the only question I have, is WHY now, If its been dead this long? Reading this, I cant help but tie it closely to “Minerva” by Adam Foster, turns out what he wanted to do was pretty similar to what Marc just put out.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/marc-laidlaws-epistle-3/15255/35">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/marc-laidlaws-epistle-3/15255/35</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 29 Aug 2017 22:28:56 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-15255-35</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/marc-laidlaws-epistle-3/15255.rss">Marc Laidlaw&#39;s &#39;Epistle 3&#39;</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Marc Laidlaw&#39;s &#39;Epistle 3&#39;</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Raziel_ZV]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>“What if the final explosion powers a huge timeloop singularity that puts Gertrude back on the Green Valley Science Factory Inbound Train…”</p>
<p>THIS I imagined many times that could be quite suitable and FINAL ending for HL.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/marc-laidlaws-epistle-3/15255/34">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/marc-laidlaws-epistle-3/15255/34</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 29 Aug 2017 18:38:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-15255-34</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/marc-laidlaws-epistle-3/15255.rss">Marc Laidlaw&#39;s &#39;Epistle 3&#39;</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Marc Laidlaw&#39;s &#39;Epistle 3&#39;</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[k3nny1550]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Further data on why he released what he did, when he did.</p>
<p><img src="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/original/2X/d/dec8503fa5a269b3340eb3f3cf963a248fc1b2bb.jpeg" alt="laidlaw.JPG" data-base62-sha1="vMPaq4lTEEEETHOs26XmmiVRPjJ" width="591" height="344"></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/marc-laidlaws-epistle-3/15255/33">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/marc-laidlaws-epistle-3/15255/33</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2017 06:36:33 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-15255-33</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/marc-laidlaws-epistle-3/15255.rss">Marc Laidlaw&#39;s &#39;Epistle 3&#39;</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Marc Laidlaw&#39;s &#39;Epistle 3&#39;</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Flavrans]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Marc Laidlaw shared some more thoughts on the Epistle on his Twitter account:</p>
<p><a href="https://twitter.com/marc_laidlaw/status/901647787854462976" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Epistolary Afterthoughts</a></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/marc-laidlaws-epistle-3/15255/32">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/marc-laidlaws-epistle-3/15255/32</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2017 00:23:09 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-15255-32</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/marc-laidlaws-epistle-3/15255.rss">Marc Laidlaw&#39;s &#39;Epistle 3&#39;</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Marc Laidlaw&#39;s &#39;Epistle 3&#39;</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[k3nny1550]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>As far as I’m aware, the only things that were ironclad canon about the Gearbox expansions were:</p>
<p>A. Black Mesa was nuked by the government</p>
<p>B. The HL2 Barney’s last name is Calhoun.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/marc-laidlaws-epistle-3/15255/31">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/marc-laidlaws-epistle-3/15255/31</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2017 22:33:05 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-15255-31</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/marc-laidlaws-epistle-3/15255.rss">Marc Laidlaw&#39;s &#39;Epistle 3&#39;</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Marc Laidlaw&#39;s &#39;Epistle 3&#39;</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crawfish]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="k3nny1550">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/user_avatar/leakfree.org/k3nny1550/40/4952_2.png" class="avatar"> k3nny1550:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Tbh, including Barney in the plot would have been too fanservicey. He’s a dark comedy character, and the narrative for Ep3 was going in a much more serious direction. Maybe he should have been seen in a call or something, hearing about Eli and reacting, but I personally wouldn’t have put him in the lineup for the actual mission to the Borealis.</p>
<p>As for Shep, he’s Gearbox. Not really that canon imho.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Didn’t Gearbox help with the original Half-Life too?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/marc-laidlaws-epistle-3/15255/30">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/marc-laidlaws-epistle-3/15255/30</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2017 20:54:10 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-15255-30</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/marc-laidlaws-epistle-3/15255.rss">Marc Laidlaw&#39;s &#39;Epistle 3&#39;</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Marc Laidlaw&#39;s &#39;Epistle 3&#39;</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[k3nny1550]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Tbh, including Barney in the plot would have been too fanservicey. He’s a dark comedy character, and the narrative for Ep3 was going in a much more serious direction. Maybe he should have been seen in a call or something, hearing about Eli and reacting, but I personally wouldn’t have put him in the lineup for the actual mission to the Borealis.</p>
<p>As for Shep, he’s Gearbox. Not really that canon imho.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/marc-laidlaws-epistle-3/15255/29">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/marc-laidlaws-epistle-3/15255/29</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2017 20:43:02 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-15255-29</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/marc-laidlaws-epistle-3/15255.rss">Marc Laidlaw&#39;s &#39;Epistle 3&#39;</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Marc Laidlaw&#39;s &#39;Epistle 3&#39;</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[snark567]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Nova Terra">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Nova Terra:</div>
<blockquote>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="yrr">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/y/2bfe46/40.png" class="avatar"> yrr:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>(maybe from Alyx perspective this time ? Or a complete new character and game but still in the same universe like with the Portal series).</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>G-man can still use Shepard if he wants to too.At least we know how the Combine homeword looks like,it’s just a giant metal sphere which is kinda boring in my opinion but I didn’t expect much more from them just by looking on their Citadel and synth design.Also it could be so cool to see “glimpses of other worlds” and sadly there was no place for Barney and Adrian in EP3 plot.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>You can always modify the plot.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/marc-laidlaws-epistle-3/15255/28">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/marc-laidlaws-epistle-3/15255/28</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2017 09:26:36 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-15255-28</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/marc-laidlaws-epistle-3/15255.rss">Marc Laidlaw&#39;s &#39;Epistle 3&#39;</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Marc Laidlaw&#39;s &#39;Epistle 3&#39;</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[gladoscake122]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Let’s be honest, Valve gave us fans a brutal cliffhanger then made us think we’d return to the world of Gordon Freeman very soon, way back in 2007-2008… teasing how innovative and new EP3 would be, a feature even better than the Portal Gun, new visual elements and things that weren’t really in the previous games, which you could tell from the concept art that they really were aiming for something amazing, but then, silence. Well it wasn’t instant but slowly they stopped mentioning EP3’s progress though did confirm it was still happening, then they started to stop talking about it completely, it did not pull through successfully as a project at Valve and we weren’t notified of what went wrong, they started to focus on a MMORPG called Dota 2, they made CSGO and gave it a skin and spray store, back in 2011 they made Portal 2 which was a pretty successful game, let alone sequel to Portal 1 and just demonstrated they are still capable of making wonderful games, as well as continuations of games, but… they got greedy, their business models completely changed, they didn’t think EP2 needed a rightful continuation or so  it seemed, at some point the community began digging up lost code from EP3 and even HL3, they found the so called ‘development team’ for HL3 and discovered a supposed EP3 Movie, at some point Gabe finally addresses the issues and states that they’d need a good reason to go back and do a ‘classic product’ and that it’d be unwise if they ignored what they learned from Portal 2… which apparently was the beginning of the end of the classic Valve we knew and loved, no more story-focused single player titles from them,  they’ve branched out of the HL2 genre in so many ways, they’re even focusing on VR, while I’m excited about and cannot wait to play HL2 on the VR, it doesn’t appear to be the anticipated endeavor the community hoped for, and with all that taken in consideration…</p>
<p>they make a card game… apparently a clone of another card game I hear, they really just don’t care and they’ve grown too big, maybe it’s good for them but not for us, sticking with Valve like it’s the Valve we remembered is just pointless, they’ve changed and they don’t need <em>us</em> anymore. They don’t need Half-Life anymore. I honestly think that an actual HL3 from them in this day and age would be a complete sham and just a cash grab, it’s really for the best that there won’t be another Half-Life in this sense, really.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/marc-laidlaws-epistle-3/15255/27">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/marc-laidlaws-epistle-3/15255/27</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2017 05:27:55 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-15255-27</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/marc-laidlaws-epistle-3/15255.rss">Marc Laidlaw&#39;s &#39;Epistle 3&#39;</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Marc Laidlaw&#39;s &#39;Epistle 3&#39;</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[JohnWorfin]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>This is incredibly sad. Yes technically valve did not owe us another game, but to let their flagship game and one of the greatest videogames of all time  just fall by the wayside? WTF were they thinking?  I guess the gobs of money they make off of steam and micro transactions made them think they didn’t  need to make another single player game</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/marc-laidlaws-epistle-3/15255/26">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/marc-laidlaws-epistle-3/15255/26</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 26 Aug 2017 22:34:26 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-15255-26</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/marc-laidlaws-epistle-3/15255.rss">Marc Laidlaw&#39;s &#39;Epistle 3&#39;</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
