<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Five Guys Burger and Fries</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/five-guys-burger-and-fries/13431</link>
    <description>Welp, doesn&#39;t seem like anyone has started a topic on this one yet.

For those of you who haven&#39;t heard, an indie game dev got into a lot of personal shenanigans with her boyfriend at the time and the now ex boyfriend has gone public and the whole thing has turned into a massive shitstorm. A lot of people are claiming that she was using personal shenanigans, particularly the nature of who she was shenaniganing with, to boost positive press for her game.

In a semi-related story, the same game dev drummed up support for her game by calling attention to some supposed harassment in a couple posts on an obscure imageboard and some calls she claimed the members of the imageboard made to her personal phone.

In yet another semi-related story, the same indie dev killed an indiegogo campaign with bad press because she thought it was offensive (and definitely not because she is working on a semi-competing project) and in response /v/ is saving the campaign with thousands of dollars in donations. In turn (but also as a result of all the other crazy shit), everything turned into a hacking/doxxing battle in which the actual parties committing the doxxing aren&#39;t very clear. A lot of people are claiming it&#39;s a false flag, which seems a little [b]fish[/b]y to me. Looks like a third party/parties just trying to add to the shirtstorm.

Here&#39;s the massive post by the ex:
[url=&#39;https://thezoepost.wordpress.com/&#39;]The Zoe Post[/url]
Here&#39;s the story of the supposed imageboard harassment and phone calls:
[url=&#39;https://imgur.com/a/4VOcx&#39;]Wizardchan collage[/url]</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 22 Apr 2020 23:01:34 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Off Topic</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/five-guys-burger-and-fries/13431.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Five Guys Burger and Fries</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Catsmack]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><span class="mention">@ChickenProtrector</span> … Did you know that the Capybara is a semi-aquatic mammal found in South America?  In fact it is.  It’s a rodent and related to the beaver.  Just saying <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/rat.png?v=9" title=":rat:" class="emoji" alt=":rat:"></p>
<p>It is found all over South America according to Wikipedia<br>
</p><aside class="onebox wikipedia">
  <header class="source">
      <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Capybara" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">en.wikipedia.org</a>
  </header>
  <article class="onebox-body">
    <div class="aspect-image" style="--aspect-ratio:220/147;"><img src="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/original/2X/8/8092b6db6aed2628e331660a7cd664b71fd4c0b8.jpeg" class="thumbnail" width="220" height="147"></div>

<h3><a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Capybara" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Capybara</a></h3>

<p>

 Sus hydrochaeris Linnaeus,&nbsp;1766
 The capybara (Hydrochoerus hydrochaeris) is a giant cavy rodent native to South America. It is the largest living rodent in the world. Also called capivara (in Brazil), chigüire, chigüiro (in Colombia and Venezuela), carpincho (in Argentina, Paraguay and Uruguay) and ronsoco (in Peru), it is a member of the genus Hydrochoerus, of which the only other extant member is the lesser capybara (Hydrochoerus isthmius).  Its close relatives include guinea pigs and rock ...</p>

  </article>
  <div class="onebox-metadata">
    
    
  </div>
  <div style="clear: both"></div>
</aside>

<p>But don’t be fooled … I have seen many swimming in the open grassy creeks surrounding the University of Central Texas near Fort Hood.  They are HUGE!</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/five-guys-burger-and-fries/13431/61">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/five-guys-burger-and-fries/13431/61</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 22 Apr 2020 22:18:12 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13431-61</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/five-guys-burger-and-fries/13431.rss">Five Guys Burger and Fries</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Five Guys Burger and Fries</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Chickenprotector]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Bump/Double post for a new pair of bits of juicy information from the same journalist (Milo) of the articles I’ve posted. The guy’s at least solid in his sources.</p>
<p><a href="https://www.breitbart.com/Breitbart-London/2014/09/22/They-re-on-to-us-gaming-journalists-respond-to-their-critics-in-series-of-new-GameJournoPros-emails" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Article 1</a>: <a href="https://yiannopoulos.net/2014/09/22/new-gamejourno-pro-leak-the-email-summaries/" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">(related to this - too long to post)</a>. I used code tags because it’s a LONG ass article, especially when I’m posting two of these.</p>
<p>[code]<br>
A second tranche of leaked emails from the secret GameJournoPros mailing list, dated September 2014 and published today by Breitbart London, reveals video game journalists insulting popular YouTubers and laughing off the prospect of readers challenging them about ethical violations.</p>
<p>This new leak follows an earlier release of emails dated August, which showed games journalists joking about having sex with public relations executives and game developers.</p>
<p>It was an unfortunate choice of topic given that the video game journalism industry had just been rocked by revelations that developer Zoe Quinn – allegedly according to her ex-boyfriend – had enjoyed five sexual relationships in quick succession with industry figures, including a journalist, while receiving lavish praise for her Depression Quest game and being in receipt of financial support from journalists who reported on her.</p>
<p>In these new emails, from September, discussing journalist Jenn Frank’s good-bye letter to the industry, which was swiftly rescinded last week when she began to once again write for the Guardian newspaper, the denizens of GameJournoPros can be seen alternately considering their position in the industry and dismissing their critics.</p>
<p>Frank announced her departure from games journalism after readers pointed out that an opinion piece of hers, published by that newspaper, originally failed to include a disclaimer that she knew one of the subjects of her piece, Zoe Quinn.</p>
<p>In response to what some readers will consider an appropriate move after the exposure of professional failures, Ben Kuchera, an opinion editor at Vox Media-owned Polygon, defended Frank, writing on 11 September: “If I were freelance these days I’d leave game writing so quickly your head would spin.”</p>
<p>NOTHING TO SEE HERE</p>
<p>James Fudge, managing editor of <a href="http://GamePolitics.com" rel="nofollow noopener">GamePolitics.com</a>, wrote: “[N]one of us have received angry emails from readers about GamerGate. Most people have no idea that it is even happening.”</p>
<p>The <span class="hashtag">#GamerGate</span> hashtag, which has swept social media in recent weeks, has been used by gamers to express their disappointment in widespread ethical failures by video game journalists, who have allowed far-Left feminist campaigners to saturate the news agenda with allegations of “misogyny” and sexism directed not just at games studios but at ordinary gamers themselves.</p>
<p>But it’s not just GamerGaters who are capable of ugly behaviour. Reporters sympathetic to the <span class="hashtag">#GamerGate</span> movement have had their home addresses and phone numbers published online and have been sent toilet rolls and unsheathed syringes containing unknown liquids via ordinary mail.</p>
<p>On the same date in September, senior video game journalists were engaged in a lengthy, sneering thread about popular YouTube personality TotalBiscuit, who reviews games. Some professional bloggers resent the popularity of YouTubers, say insiders, because YouTubers have large, engaged fan bases, whereas journalists are often the subject of ridicule and tough questioning from readers.</p>
<p>But only now can we see how they speak about such reviewers behind closed doors - in a forum that list founder Kyle Orland was proud remained unknown about by the wider public.</p>
<p><img src="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/original/3X/e/9/e98bf5aec135a3f4b324a821c29ea0c8b1762f8d.jpeg" alt="" data-base62-sha1="xk36ZVsXvpaEZLuQU8UyqNLkgUd" width="650" height="356"></p>
<p>PLAYGROUND BULLIES</p>
<p>In a thread sarcastically titled, “The time TotalBiscuit told on me,” Dan Stapleton, reviews editor at IGN, says: “I have some experience picking fights with egotistical YouTube personalities who label themselves as ill-tempered in some fashion. Not something I recommend.”</p>
<p>Susan Arendt, managing editor of Joystiq, adds: “TotalBiscuit has an insanely thin skin. Speaking from personal experience.”</p>
<p>Other journalists can be seen complaining about the “abuse” they receive at the hands of gaming punters. Further reading suggest the definition of “abuse” meant is tweets and Facebook statuses critical of mainstream coverage, rather than actual threats or foul language.</p>
<p>Writer and editor Chris Dahlen calls <span class="hashtag">#GamerGate</span> supporters “knuckleheads,” while Polygon’s Kuchera mocks the <span class="hashtag">#notyourshield</span> hashtag, which was started to draw attention to women and other minorities who do not support the radical feminist agenda of the mainstream gaming publications.</p>
<p>CRYSTAL BALLS</p>
<p>An earlier private email thread, dated 7 September 2014, is entitled, “Putting Gamergate behind us?” In light of the continuing controversy surrounding press ethics in the gaming industry, that subject line will strike many readers as comically hopeful. Some of the following emails come from abridged summaries sent by Google to one member of the list.</p>
<p>But in emails that will infuriate readers, many of whom believe the elite bloggers of publications such as Vox Media-owned Polygon, Gawker-owned Kotaku and Conde Nast-owned Ars Technica are hopelessly out of touch with ordinary gamers, journalists can be seen further insulting and denigrating their own constituencies.</p>
<p>For example, Michael Futter, news editor at Games Informer, describes questioning by gamers as “crackpot,” urging his colleagues to avoid engaging with readers on social media.</p>
<p>There is evidence on the list that some writers, particularly those in more regular contact with games companies and gamers themselves, did foresee the coming drama.</p>
<p>Michael Zenke, a video game content writer who is currently working on Elder Scrolls Online, responds that, “There are people in the industry that care about this. A lot.”</p>
<p>Zenke is backed up by Matt Hawkins, who writes: “I’ll echo Michael’s sentiments, primarily on the indie side of the spectrum.”</p>
<p>That conversation peters out, before being taken to private emails.</p>
<p>What will strike many readers as remarkable is how ill-prepared senior editors on the GameJournoPros list were for the controversy that arrived when questions began to be asked openly about their closeness to their subjects and the general standards of ethics in video game journalism.</p>
<p>For the most part, the latest batch of emails leaked to Breitbart show widespread denial on the part of video games journalists that there is any problem at all. Dahlen is seen at one point to say: “This is a good time to point out that <span class="hashtag">#gamergate</span> was never about ‘corruption’” - something with which many tweeters will not agree.</p>
<p>“This is a big topic and it’s leading to people being hurt. I don’t want to minimize that, concedes Kuchera, before adding: But I don’t think your average reader of online gaming news has been affected much.”</p>
<p>Kuchera, writing on 7 September, could not have been more wrong. Then again, the Polygon editor has a special talent for saying the unsayable: in conversation on 11 September 2014, he wrote: “Jobs writing are so hard to come by that it’s really hard to fault anyone for much these days.”</p>
<p>Unluckily for Kuchera, readers in the weeks since then have made it clear that they expect much, much higher standards.[/code]</p>
<p><a href="https://www.breitbart.com/Breitbart-London/2014/09/21/GameJournoPros-we-reveal-every-journalist-on-the-list" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Article 2</a>:</p>
<p>[code]Last week, Breitbart News revealed a secret video game journalist mailing list used by a clique of influential writers, editors, and bloggers, some of whom attempted to bully their colleagues with it in an attempt to shape the news agenda for political purposes.</p>
<p>We can today reveal the complete list of journalists, some 150 key industry figures, on the list. Outlets with representation span the entire video games journalism universe and include Polygon, Ars Technica, Wired, Eurogamer, Destructoid, Kotaku, Joystiq, TechRadar, and many other well-known brands in games publishing.</p>
<p>But they also include freelancers and staffers for publications as solidly mainstream as the Associated Press, CNBC, and USA Today, together with technology industry stalwarts such as Motherboard, owned by VICE, VentureBeat, and CNet.</p>
<p>Even more disturbingly, Tom Curtis, a marketing executive from game publisher Ubisoft, and Billy Shibley, a community manager for Destiny from Activision, are also present on the list, which begs the question why marketing managers are included on a mailing list for the journalists who are supposed to be writing about their employers.</p>
<p>On Thursday, we shared a series of disturbing messages from the GameJournoPros mailing list which demonstrated widespread ethical failures among some of game journalism’s most senior figures. The emails were evidence, we said, that video game journalism was in need of urgent reform.</p>
<p>This new information shows just how far-reaching the influence of GameJournoPros has been since the list was founded four years ago by Kyle Orland, senior gaming editor at Conde Nast’s Ars Technica. It suggests that readers have been right to worry about ideological co-ordination between journalists across dozens of different publications.</p>
<p>Although not all journalists on the list are implicated in allegations of collusion, and plenty of writers have been seen, in emails leaked to Breitbart, disagreeing with the activist tactics of their colleagues, their continued participation in the list leaves them open to influence by its more vocal, activists members, including Orland and Ben Kuchera, an opinion editor at Vox Media-owned Polygon.</p>
<p>Additionally, one list member, who was not the member who leaked the list to us and spoke on condition of anonymity, said this morning: “I don’t post but I do read it, almost religiously. And yes you do get affected by what Ben [Kuchera] and others are saying. After all they are big names. It makes you reconsider your choice of words and how you say things.”</p>
<p>This member list was supplied by a disaffected member of the group. We contacted Orland for comment, but he had not replied as we went to press. A small number of screen names, which could not be traced to their owners or whose ownership could not be conclusively verified, have been omitted.</p>
<p><em>images of the page itself</em></p>
<p>THE JOURNALISTS</p>
<p>Adam Rosenberg - Digital Trends<br>
Alex Navarro - Giant Bomb<br>
Alex Rubens - IGN, G4TV, PCWorld, Official Xbox Magazine, Polygon, <span class="mention">@Gamer</span> Magazine, Games Radar, Joystiq, Kotaku, Destructoid, Tech Hive, Game Informer<br>
Andrew Fitch - the Geekbox podcast<br>
Andrew Groen - Penny Arcade (ex?), Wired<br>
Andrew Hayward - StuffTV, TechHive, IGN, Macworld,Maclife, Jostiq<br>
Andrew a Cunningham - ArsTechnica<br>
Andy Chalk - PC Gamer<br>
Andy Eddy - author, “Game Over Press Start To Continue”<br>
Annette Cardwell - Yahoo! Shine, Wikia<br>
Anthony John Agnello - Joystiq, The AV Club, Edge, Fast Company<br>
Ben Kuchera - Editor at Polygon<br>
Ben Gilbert - Senior Editor for Engadget<br>
Billy Shibley - Social/Community for <span class="mention">@DestinytheGame</span> (Activision), former Editorial Manager at Machinima<br>
Brad Gallaway - Managing Editor of <a href="http://GameCritics.com" rel="nofollow noopener">GameCritics.com</a><br>
Bradley Shoemaker - Giant Bomb<br>
Brandon Cackowski-Schnell - The Escapist<br>
Brandon Justice - Ex Gamefan, IGN, SEGA, EA &amp; EGM<br>
Brandon Boyer - Chairman, Indie Games Festival<br>
Brian Leahy - Previously Shacknews &amp; G4tv<br>
Britton Peele - Entertainment Editor Dallas Morning News<br>
Casey Johnston - Culture Editor at Ars Technica<br>
Charles Husemann - Development Manager at Recource Gaming Nexus EIC<br>
Chris Dahlen - Game dev and writer<br>
Chris Plante - Senior Editor at The Verge<br>
Christopher Grant - Editor-in-Chief at Polygon<br>
Conrad Zimmerman - Podcaster, freelance writer/critic<br>
Cory Banks - Former Managing Editor at PC Gamer<br>
Dale North - Editor-in-Chief at Destructoid<br>
Dale (Laura Dale) - <a href="http://Indiehaven.com" rel="nofollow noopener">Indiehaven.com</a>, Kotaku UK, Telegraph, Guardian, MYM, MCM<br>
Dalibor Dimovski - Gamedev<br>
Dan (Dan Stapleton) - IGN, PC Gamer<br>
Dan Crabtree - GamerNode<br>
Dana Wollman - Engadget managing editor<br>
Daniel Starkey (Twitter deleted, cached) - Eurogamer, GameSpot, Joystiq, Kotaku<br>
Daniel Feit - Wired<br>
Danielle - Senior Reviewer at Polygon<br>
Davetach - Polygon<br>
David Thomas - Youtuber “Game Dave” (I believe.)<br>
Dead Yet Living - Unsure<br>
Dean Takahashi - Lead Writer for Games Beat at Venture Beat<br>
Dennis Scimeca - The Daily Dot (Formerly ArsTechnica, NPR, GamesBeat, Polygon, Kotaku, The Escapist, Gamasutra<br>
Devin Connors - The Escapist (past Tom’s Guide, GameFrontCom)<br>
Devin Kofsky - Social Media Celebrity Cruise? Freelance I think in the past.<br>
Dtroid Niero - Destructoid<br>
Erick Eckstein - Esquire Network, G4TV,<br>
Erick Frederikesn / piratesyar - Technobuffalo<br>
Garnett Lee - Shout Engine<br>
Garrett Martin - Paste games editor, Boston Herald game critic<br>
George Wiedman - Super Bunnyhop (youtube)<br>
Greg Tito - The Escapist<br>
Gregory Gay - The Escapist<br>
Harold Goldberg - New York Times, NPR, books<br>
Heidi Kemps - Freelance, Joystiq<br>
Issac Ferderspiel - IndieHaven, former Game Informer Intern<br>
Jake Gaskill - G4TV<br>
James Fudge - Editor <a href="http://GamePolitics.com" rel="nofollow noopener">GamePolitics.com</a><br>
Jarred Newman<br>
Jason Fanelli - Arcade Sushi, GamesRadar, PocketGamer, Gamernode<br>
Jason Leyanna (no twitter I found) - Realm of Gaming<br>
Jason Schreier - Kotaku Australia, Wired<br>
Jason Venter - Honest Gamers Editor in Chief, IGN, Gamespot, GamesRadar, Joystiq<br>
Jason Wilson<br>
Jaz Rignall<br>
Jeffery Matulef - US News Editor at Eurogamer (Former AV Club, G4TV, Paste, Joystiq,OXM)<br>
Jeremy Zoss - Zoss Media, Giant Bomb<br>
Joe Osborne - Reviews Editor TechRadar<br>
John Funk - The Escapist<br>
Jonathan Deesing - Joystiq<br>
Jorge Jimenez - Blogger?, Staff Writer Dualshockers<br>
Joseph Leray - TouchArcade, Destructioid<br>
Josh Tolentino - Destructioid, Japanator<br>
Julian Murdoch - Comic Vine?<br>
Justin McElroy - Polygon<br>
Kate Cox - Consumerist, <a href="http://GameCritics.com" rel="nofollow noopener">GameCritics.com</a><br>
Kevin Kelly - Wired<br>
Kyle Orland - Senior Gaming Editor for Ars Technica<br>
Kyle Horner - Developer at WB Games/Turbine, Writer, Editor<br>
Leah B. Jackson - Riot Games eSports web content coordinator (formely IGN/G4)<br>
Logan Westbrook - The Escapist<br>
Lou Kesten - Associated Press<br>
Ludwig Kietzmann - Joystiq Editor-in-chief<br>
Maddy Myers - PasteGames Assitant Editor<br>
Mark Burnham - Online Media Manager QuinStreet (Formerly EIC at Game Front)<br>
Matthew Kumar - Freelance, CEO of MKULTRAgames, publisher of exp.?<br>
Matt Matthews - Gamasutra<br>
Matthew Sakey - Freelance, NYU game center<br>
Meghan - IGN<br>
Michael McWhertor - Deputy News Editor at Polygon<br>
Mike Futter - News Editor at Game Informer<br>
Michael Rougeau - Kotaku, Gamespot, TechRadar, more<br>
Mike Wehner - Daily Dot, USA Today, Yahoo<br>
Mitch Dyer - Editor, IGN<br>
Chris Morris - CNBC, Variety, Coast to Coast Radio<br>
N’Gai Croal - Newsweek (previous)<br>
N. Evan Van Zelfden (no twitter) - Venture Beat, The Escapist, Slate<br>
Nathan Grayson - Kotaku<br>
Nathan Meunier - Freelance, Podcaster<br>
Nick Chester - Harmonix<br>
Phillip Kollar - Polygon, Game Informer<br>
Pikoeri Egm - EGM, ex GameFan, ex Play<br>
Richard Mitchell - Joystiq<br>
Rob Zacny - PCGamesN, The Escapist, Polygon, IGN<br>
Rod “Slasher” Breslau - Past (OnGamers)<br>
Rollin Bishop - Contributing Editor at LaughingSquid, formerly Geeokosystem, The Mary Sue<br>
Ron Whitaker - Managing Editor GameFront<br>
<a href="http://RPad.TV" rel="nofollow noopener">RPad.TV</a> -  <a href="http://Rpad.tv" rel="nofollow noopener">Rpad.tv</a><br>
Ryan Kuo - Kill Screen<br>
Ryan Scott - Editorial Director at Geekbox Media<br>
Ryanflemingpdx - Gamig and Cinema Editor Digital Trends (former)<br>
Sam Machovech - Tech Reporter Ars Technica<br>
Samit Sarkar - Polygon , formerly at Destructoid<br>
Sarah LeBoeuf - The Escapist<br>
Savethekitsune (Cassandra Khaw, I believe.) - Verge<br>
Scott Nichols - Freelance Critic, Digital Spy<br>
Scott Steinberg - Speaker &amp; Futurist, Writes for Inc, Mashable (Past?), Huffpo<br>
Sebastian Haley - Venture Beat<br>
Shoe (Wild Guess - Dan “Shoe” Hsu) - VentureBeat<br>
Simon Ferrari - Adjunct NYU GameCenter, INDIECADE, Different Games, Indie-Fund Dev outreach team<br>
Sinan Kubba - Joystiq<br>
Sincerelysophie (Sophie/Sam Prell) - Joystiq, G4, Destructoid<br>
Steven Kent (Didn’t find Twitter) - Book Writer, freelance lots of places from the past<br>
Steve Haske - Wired, Medium (not a real site, anyone can do that), Complex Mag?<br>
Susan Arendt - Managing Editor at Joystiq<br>
Taylor Cocke - Web content coordinator at Riot Games/Lolesports, but widely written at IGN, Edge, and others.<br>
The Gamegoat - Youtuber<br>
Tim Stevens - Editor at Large, C’net<br>
Timothy J. Seppala - Engadget contributing editor.<br>
Tina Amini - Deputy Editor at Kotaku<br>
Tom Curtis - “Digital Marketing Guy” at Ubisoft, formerly at Gamasutra<br>
Tom Chick - <a href="http://quartertothree.com" rel="nofollow noopener">quartertothree.com</a><br>
Will Tuttle - Sr. Communications Manager for Xbox and Editorial Overseer of Xbox Wire, IGN (past)<br>
William Usher - Assistant Editor Gaming Blend<br>
Max Parker - Columnist for Pittsburgh Post-Gazette<br>
Xav De Matos - Joystiq<br>
Yannick LeJacq -  Motherboard (VICE), Kotaku UK<br>
Zack Stern - PCWorld, Macworld, others[/code]</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/five-guys-burger-and-fries/13431/60">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/five-guys-burger-and-fries/13431/60</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 22 Sep 2014 14:42:47 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13431-60</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/five-guys-burger-and-fries/13431.rss">Five Guys Burger and Fries</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Five Guys Burger and Fries</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Chickenprotector]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>That’s the problem. Believe me, before this entire thing became a shit’acane many of the Pro-GG camp tried to reach out to establish dialogue with the other camp (and actually some continue to do so) so that we as a community could at least understand what their driving force(s) are. They won’t come out of their play pen.</p>
<p>And I do agree, some of this is fucking stupid, but it’s the internet, what the fuck can you do.</p>
<p>… and KYM is actually where I’ve been getting my news updates from… the comment section has shit hourly in most circumstances.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/five-guys-burger-and-fries/13431/59">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/five-guys-burger-and-fries/13431/59</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 21 Sep 2014 04:25:41 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13431-59</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/five-guys-burger-and-fries/13431.rss">Five Guys Burger and Fries</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Five Guys Burger and Fries</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Grach]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>The worst part is that the toxic elements of the movements only fuels their analogue. So sure, anti-GG people point to the doxxing and harassment of Zoe and the pro-GG people point to the harassment and virulent hatred of the neutral side and the more reasonable people. In the end, these people are one and the same: they’re the anarchists that hide behind a flag just to take out their hatred against a group, like fucking cavemen. I’m sure if the people who mean good in both sides probably could have an agreement and build towards something that’s worth working for.</p>
<p>EDIT: Also, I almost forgot: Props to KYM. These guys are like actual journalists, getting in and reporting everything they see and then write it down. It’s literally the most reliable source about this whole flustercuck.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/five-guys-burger-and-fries/13431/58">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/five-guys-burger-and-fries/13431/58</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 21 Sep 2014 04:04:59 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13431-58</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/five-guys-burger-and-fries/13431.rss">Five Guys Burger and Fries</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Five Guys Burger and Fries</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Chickenprotector]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Ignoring the idiots involved, I already stated my opinion on this: I don’t want a cabal of idiots shutting down my dream before it can be put out there. That’s what these people have practically turned into, and that’s one of the primary reasons why as a aspiring indie developer that I want to shut these people down as well.</p>
<p>There could be <span class="bbcode-b">numerous</span> reasons as to why other pro-GG people are fighting them, from ethics to the simple fact that Anita, Quinn and her camp are fucking hypocrites.</p>
<p>In addition to that there <span class="bbcode-i">are</span> female protagonists in many of the mainstream games. Mass Effect had one, Skyrim has one (if the player decides to play a female character), and <a href="https://youtu.be/RXMoLCA3GQ4?t=7s" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">I could list numerous instances</a>. And I don’t disagree about there being a more diverse scene, I wouldn’t mind that at all.</p>
<p>There <span class="bbcode-i">is</span> one thing that bothers me though, and that is many of the “hardcore” games, such as Call of Duty, Team Fortress, Crysis, etc. There’s an overwhelming majority of male players, and that’s something that should change imo, but that’s regarding the community, not the developers or the press. Believe me, I’ve tried to get some of my female friends into the games I play, it isn’t easy.</p>
<p>Oh and as if it couldn’t get any fucking better: These fools decided to try and doxx/DDoS several prominent figures inside of the movement, as much good as it did them earlier today.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/five-guys-burger-and-fries/13431/57">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/five-guys-burger-and-fries/13431/57</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 21 Sep 2014 03:25:41 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13431-57</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/five-guys-burger-and-fries/13431.rss">Five Guys Burger and Fries</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Five Guys Burger and Fries</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Kairouseki]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>The problem also is that people kick and scream saying there need to be more female characters but then the female characters that are made aren’t good enough or somehow offend these people. And you’re right, there’s no reason to have diversity just for the sake of having it. At the same time though I can’t think of much reason to have a female or a black character over a white male in most instances*. The only reason you would would be for the sake of the diversity. This applies to gay characters too. The ones that do exist are generally walking stereotypes because the devs want to make sure you know this character is gay and that becomes their sole character trait.</p>
<p>*Assuming the person making the game is a white male. Which is a pretty good bet I think. People would tend to make character similar to themselves as they know how they work, at least this makes sense to me.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/five-guys-burger-and-fries/13431/56">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/five-guys-burger-and-fries/13431/56</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 21 Sep 2014 01:47:33 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13431-56</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/five-guys-burger-and-fries/13431.rss">Five Guys Burger and Fries</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Five Guys Burger and Fries</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Grach]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Whats more annoying about this bullshit internet conflict is that it has absolutely fuck all to do <span class="bbcode-i">actual games</span>. Yes, the industry needs more female characters, more compelling stories and better representation. The problem with this it also fucking needs actual <span class="bbcode-i">characters</span>. It’s no use screaming like Kratos into the heavens “<span class="bbcode-b">WE NEED BETTER GENDER REPRESENTATION AND POLITICS IN VIDEOGAMES AREEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEES</span>” when lazy videogame makers will only throw a bunch of dices when making a character; one labeled “gender” one  “sexuality” and one with “race”. It’ll eventually fall into the shit abyss that generic videogames fall into all the time, eventually deprecating even the point of having a protagonist that’s <span class="bbcode-i">not</span> a white male bullshit badass soldier (they’ll only change the white male part, so you get a japanese female bullshit badass soldier).</p>
<p>All of this is badly focused is all I’m saying. There’s no point of having a female protagonist for the sake of having a female protagonist. I hope in the end games that have an excuse plot, like Doom or Gears of War should just let you choose your sex in the beginning and never adress it ever again. It will make these dipshit “equality” fuckers shut the fuck up for once, which will make their dipshit enemies shut the fuck up by extension.</p>
<p>Just everyone shut the fuck up your so annoying kidding i lov erryone of ya xoxo</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/five-guys-burger-and-fries/13431/55">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/five-guys-burger-and-fries/13431/55</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 21 Sep 2014 01:41:15 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13431-55</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/five-guys-burger-and-fries/13431.rss">Five Guys Burger and Fries</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Five Guys Burger and Fries</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Chickenprotector]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Well it’s in total chaos. They nuked at least 4 boards I think already from what I’ve heard. Even though I don’t frequent the site, I don’t blame Moot for wanting to cover his ass. It was POORLY handled though. Best to live and let live, find another place to discuss things (pirmarily 8chan).</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/five-guys-burger-and-fries/13431/54">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/five-guys-burger-and-fries/13431/54</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 20 Sep 2014 00:39:12 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13431-54</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/five-guys-burger-and-fries/13431.rss">Five Guys Burger and Fries</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Five Guys Burger and Fries</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[DeleteThis]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Even 4chan is being censored by this jeez</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/five-guys-burger-and-fries/13431/53">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/five-guys-burger-and-fries/13431/53</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 20 Sep 2014 00:22:31 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13431-53</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/five-guys-burger-and-fries/13431.rss">Five Guys Burger and Fries</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Five Guys Burger and Fries</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Chickenprotector]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><a href="https://yiannopoulos.net/2014/09/19/gamejournopros-zoe-quinn-email-dump/" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Speaking of information dumps… Milo released the e-mail thread in its entirety.</a></p>
<p>It’s WAY too long to post in the forum… if you want to read it, click the link, the last article I posted has a few of the contained e-mail.</p>
<p>Edit: <a href="https://medium.com/@upstreamism/to-fair-minded-proponents-of-gamergate-7f3ce77301bb" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">I found a wonderfully unbiased article on KYM.</a> It does bring to light some of the hypocrisy on the pro-side. To be honest the reason I’m tracking this so closely (and support the pro-side) is I want to get into the gaming industry and I don’t want some cabal of idiots telling me how I should direct my game creatively without my asking them and if I don’t conform to their ideology to shut me down. I don’t want that at all.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>To fair-minded proponents of <span class="hashtag">#GamerGate:</span></p>
<p>A few nights ago, I spent several hours on Twitter asking questions and patiently reading the answers from a dozen or so of your fellow gamers. I had already read a fair amount about <span class="hashtag">#GamerGate</span> and the events surrounding it, but I wanted to get a clearer sense of what it means to the people who were promoting the tag. I endeavored to be as fair-minded about it as I knew how. Now that I’m determined to respond (after a day of debating with myself whether or not it was worth doing so), I hope you’ll give the same consideration to what I have to say.</p>
<p>To whom am I speaking? I should specify, shouldn’t I? After all, as the gamers I talked to on Tuesday made it clear, there are a great many people involved, and not all of them see entirely eye-to-eye. In general, though, those of you who were patient enough to answer my questions seemed to agree on three broad points:</p>
<ol>
<li>That you see the word gamer as a valuable way to identify yourself;</li>
<li>That you are dismayed with what you see as corruption in the gaming press; and</li>
<li>That you are opposed to exclusion — and, therefore, to harassment.</li>
</ol>
<p>That last item is an important distinction. While nearly everyone I spoke to last night insisted on that point, not everyone has taken the same approach. Others have struck upon harassment as a handy tool for achieving their goals. We’ll get back to them in a moment, but for now I want to specifically address those who sincerely want <span class="hashtag">#GamerGate</span> to be about inclusion, not exclusion.</p>
<p>With nearly every gamer I spoke to, I started out by asking, “What do you see as the overarching goal of <span class="hashtag">#GamerGate</span>?” When, as was often the case, you answered “corruption,” I made a point of following up by asking what practices you had in mind. And it’s there, in your answers to that question, that I could see the goals and imperatives of your activism begin to diverge. Some asked only for more prominent disclaimers whenever a writer had a potential conflict of interest. Others argued that disclaimers weren’t enough, and that writers ought to be recused whenever a relationship might be thought to go beyond the bounds of the professional. Still others felt that developers were capable of exerting too much financial pressure over the gaming press. Even while arguing that <span class="hashtag">#GamerGate</span> was not primarily about the accusations of a certain ex-boyfriend, yet others seemed primarily concerned that sexual relationships with developers had a rampant and undue influence on how writers report on games.</p>
<p>Regardless of which of those concerns you raised, many of you made the point that the gaming press generally does not adhere to traditional journalistic standards. You have a point. “The standard should be higher,” you told me. I’m inclined to agree.</p>
<p>There are, however, significant distinctions that need to be made, and virtually no one I spoke to made them. More than once, I was pointed to the Society of Professional Journalists Code of Ethics or the “10 Absolutes of Reuters Journalism” as a baseline for reform. Some of the standards we find in those are applicable across the board — bans on plagiarism, for example. Others are not.</p>
<p>To understand why, it’s necessary to acknowledge another distinction. Those codes were written primarily to uphold the reliability of news reportage, but not everything published in the gaming press is news reportage. Even stories that look like news aren’t always news. That’s because, historically, games journalism grew out of what’s called the enthusiast press — meaning that it was (and still is) written primarily by gaming enthusiasts, for other gaming enthusiasts.</p>
<p>It’s possible to see that distinction a bit more clearly if you compare the way games have traditionally been written about in a venue like, say, the New York Times, versus the way they usually covered in gaming magazines. Even when they weren’t being downright skeptical, non-enthusiast publishers tended to be at least agnostic about the value of games in general. When you write for an enthusiast press, though, you’ve already thrown out some measure of objectivity, since it’s assumed that you and your reader already agree that games are worth your time, money and interest.</p>
<p>Its origins as an enthusiast press have left a deep impress on the industry. A current events reporter for Reuters may sneak into a war zone to get the unvarnished truth, but that isn’t how enthusiast presses work. They rely for most of their information on the companies whose products they cover. Most of the news stories you read on your favorite gaming site are based on press releases. The interviews wouldn’t be possible if the site hadn’t maintained an amicable relationship with the publisher. The juicy tidbits that weren’t meant to be revealed so early are typically the result of writers and developers chumming it up at expos and conferences.</p>
<p>“Corruption” probably isn’t the right word for all of that. It isn’t like gaming magazines and sites started out with the standards endorsed by the SPJ and Reuters, but lost sight of their values over time. All along, chumminess with the makers of video games has been the cost of access to the information you’ve demanded as a gamer. That isn’t a recent development, and if you’ve been supporting the gaming press up until now, then you’ve been complicit in supporting those relationship, whether you realized it or not.</p>
<p>And if you really think it through, you probably don’t want that to change entirely. After all, as gamers — which is to say, as enthusiasts — most of us enjoy the anticipation that’s created when a gaming site reports what they’ve learned about an upcoming release, even when that report is based on a press release. You cannot avoid or dissolve the relationships that make those reports possible, save at the cost of losing that coverage.</p>
<p>All the same, some gaming publications have, over the last several years, made a concerted effort to include more investigative journalism. You can usually distinguish it from news based on press releases by the fact that investigative journalism usually makes someone look bad. Which is how we should want it — that freedom to make someone look bad when they’ve done bad is what the codes and standards you pointed me to were written to protect. If you want that sort of coverage (and ask youself, do I want it? — maybe you don’t) then it makes sense to insist on more traditional journalistic standards. But because this is still a relatively new approach for the gaming press, doing so is less about decrying corruption than it is about encouraging the industry to grow.</p>
<p>Growth will mean insisting upon the distinction between serious investigative journalism and the sort of enthusiast reporting that has traditionally passed for gaming news. If you’re promoting <span class="hashtag">#GamerGate</span> because you like the way the gaming press covered games before writers starting investigating topics like labor exploitation and the gender divide, then you may want to stop insisting on higher journalistic standards. If those standards are important to you, then you’ll have to tolerate those sorts of articles, even when you don’t like the light they cast on gaming. As William Randolph Hearst famously said, “News is something somebody doesn’t want printed; all else is advertising.”</p>
<p>The same goes for the third tier (after enthusiast and investigative reporting) of the gaming press: criticism. As much as, or maybe even more than, reporting, many of you told me that you wanted to ensure that game reviews remain objective. Depending on what you mean by “objective,” that may not be possible, but I think we can all agree that, at the very least, reviews should be relatively unbiased by the author’s relationship to the people or companies whose games they review.</p>
<p>At the same time, many of you told me that you wanted to see less social criticism in those reviews. If you really think that through, you’ll see that you can’t have it both ways. There’s a deep contradiction imbedded in the notion that, on the one hand, writers shouldn’t be beholden to developers when they review a game, and that, on the other hand, they should avoid criticisms they feel are relevant. Most game publishers don’t want to be criticized for the social prejudices they may have worked into their games. As such, the simple fact that a writer or editor would be willing to publish a social criticism ought to be treated as evidence that the venue is maintaining some independence from the industry on which it reports. Even when it doesn’t interest you, even when you disagree with what’s been said— even if, as some of you expressed, you feel personally affronted on the game’s behalf — you ought to welcome such criticism as a check on the sort of cozy developer/press relationship you’ve called corrupt.</p>
<p>Which is just as well, since those of you who answered my questions on Twitter couldn’t point me to a really viable plan for effecting change. After “what do you hope to achieve,” the question I asked most was, “How do you intend to achieve it?” Some of you seemed to think that the social media campaign would be enough to shame publishers into adopting your standards. It’s possible that, at least for the time being, we’ll see more disclaimers pointing out potential conflicts of interest, but beyond that, I wouldn’t expect much voluntary action on the part of publishers. They themselves may want to see more serious journalism, but their bread and butter is still the enthusiast tier of the industry. They mostly cannot afford to cut ties with the companies on which they report.</p>
<p>“So we’ll force their hands,” some of you told me. You suggested boycotting outlets that didn’t adopt your standards. But there’s a serious chicken-and-egg problem with that plan. After all, the point is to increase transparency, but how can you know which outlets to boycott unless they’re already being transparent about those relationships? Some suggested an independent review board tasked with ensuring transparency, without any real plan for funding it or making its pronouncements enforceable. Without some means of forcing recalcitrant outlets to make their relationships more transparent, the only viable way to decide who gets boycotted is the shotgun approach. But to send an effective message, a boycott must be narrowly targeted. The nature of your complaint makes that practically impossible.</p>
<p>Beyond which, the probability is that all of your favored outlets have those relationships. Even gaming news sites that don’t have direct relationships are indirectly dependent on them, since their coverage is largely aggregated from the sites that do. And, anyway, as I noted earlier, <span class="hashtag">#GamerGate</span> proponents have diverse ideas as to what’s inappropriate.</p>
<p>The best suggestion I’ve seen so far, in fact, is simply, “If you can’t beat ‘em, join ‘em.” Some gamers are looking at the possibility of starting their own news and review site. Insofar as that gives you the opportunity to put your standards into practice, that’s a project you should actively support. For reasons that I’ve spelled out in detail above, it will likely be much more difficult than you expect, but it is, right now, your best hope of achieving something with the momentum you’ve amassed.</p>
<p>There is, as it happens, one group using the <span class="hashtag">#GamerGate</span> hashtag that has figured out an effective plan for changing the gaming press. Their method is continual harassment. They hurl invective, issue threats, expose sensitive information (like bank account numbers) and generally work to intimidate writers out of the business of printing something somebody doesn’t like. Typically, they target individuals rather than institutions, especially those with relatively small support systems, like financially vulnerable freelancers and independent developers, or non-commercial blogs sustained by reader donations rather than ad revenue.</p>
<p>That isn’t news to you, of course. You were quick to disavow that sort of exclusion. <span class="hashtag">#GamerGate</span>, you told me, is about inclusion. That’s part of why you placed so much value on the term gamer, and why you were so frustrated at the recent spate of articles suggesting that the gamer identity is dead or dying. Gaming had connected you with a community where you felt accepted, and to have that repudiated felt like another form of exclusion.</p>
<p>If the sheer fact that they’re using your name to harass other gamers isn’t enough to motivate you, then maybe recognizing how they’ve worked to undermine your goals will. The fact of the matter is that some of the people they’ve driven away are people who have spent years working to transform the gaming press from an enthusiast press to a more properly journalistic industry. They’ve done so by daring to say and print things that games developers don’t necessarily want them to say. They’ve fought to make gaming more inclusive for people who have generally felt excluded. They are, in other words, deeply allied to the causes you’ve espoused, and they’re being targeted because, against all odds, they’ve managed to gain ground. You can’t afford not to rally to their defense because you can’t afford to see them give up.</p>
<p>It is, at any rate, imperative that you recognize not only that others are using <span class="hashtag">#GamerGate</span> to do exactly the things you claim to revile, but also that they’ve been more effective at achieving their goals than you’ve been at achieving yours. That, in no small part, is why you’re all being lumped together. You may think that you represent <span class="hashtag">#GamerGate</span> more truly than the harassers, but the public can’t help but see successful attacks as a kind of ownership. That may be unfair, but you’d be foolish to ignore it. At this point, the harassers have done so much damage that your best recourse may be to simply abandon the <span class="hashtag">#GamerGate</span> umbrella altogether, in favor of a rallying call that’s harder to co-opt. Every time they successfully run someone out of their home or damage the reputation of a potential ally, they take a stronger hold on the names under which you’ve rallied, and you lose a little bit more.</p>
<p>You lose because it gets harder to espouse your cause when people associate it with harassment and misogyny. You lose because the number of people actively working to make the press more reliable and gaming more inclusive dwindles a little more. You lose because more people feel excluded from gaming. You lose, most of all, because hate takes a greater share of the world.</p>
<p>I sincerely hope you get it figured out.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/five-guys-burger-and-fries/13431/52">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/five-guys-burger-and-fries/13431/52</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2014 12:25:21 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13431-52</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/five-guys-burger-and-fries/13431.rss">Five Guys Burger and Fries</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Five Guys Burger and Fries</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[garrthbarrttinn]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><a class="mention" href="/u/chickenprotector">@chickenprotector</a> damn nice information drop. That’s so pretty solid information that can’t just be brushed aside as drama or personal life.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="JeffMOD">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/user_avatar/leakfree.org/jeffmod/40/4333_2.png" class="avatar"> JeffMOD:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Yeah, even if the allegations are true, it doesn’t justify <span class="bbcode-i">any</span> of what’s happened.<br>
Also, pretty sure <span class="bbcode-b">none</span> of the gaming journalists involved are getting even a fraction of the harassment Zoe Quinn is, even though the issue is supposedly over gaming journalism being corrupt.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>It’s in my opinion one huge scam. Go on the internet and say something unpopular with any significant voice, hell, even without a significant voice or even with a relatively popular opinion, and you WILL get harassed. It’s just statistics. If you take a MASSIVE audience that can largely say whatever they want without consequences, no matter how high a standard that community meets and no matter how small a percentage is prone to harass, the audience will be large enough that at certain amount of people will target you.</p>
<p>Now this has always happened to people on the internet with significant followings, and they just ignored it. Which is, honestly, the only reasonable response. Along come feminists who gain an audience and then say unpopular things and when the inevitable minority which is prone to harassment harasses them they seize the harassment and market it. And market it damn well. It’s how they make money. They call it misogyny and ask for donations and laugh all the way to the bank. Or hell, maybe they even believe in their gold bricks. Still doesn’t mean they’re not just red ones painted over.</p>
<p>Of course I’d consider actions with more real world consequences such as doxing to be more serious and something that doesn’t necessarily happen to everyone. But then again, given that Zoe Quinn’s supposed dox revealed absolutely nothing significantly personal, whether or not it was a legitimate attempt to harm her or a false flag is up for discussion and even if it wasn’t it’s still not a big deal given the things like phone numbers had nothing even to do with her.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/five-guys-burger-and-fries/13431/51">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/five-guys-burger-and-fries/13431/51</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2014 06:35:22 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13431-51</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/five-guys-burger-and-fries/13431.rss">Five Guys Burger and Fries</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Five Guys Burger and Fries</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Chickenprotector]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>That’s over a week old. <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Tkto-HtXqg8" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Steve came out of his box.</a> He’s lost everything in the last month despite at least trying to be the voice of reason and being objective, but got shot in the foot instead. I feel bad for the guy, shouldn’t’ve had to resign from his job to retain his own integrity, but at the very least I’m glad he can feel validated about his concerns now.</p>
<p>I watched a <a href="https://www.hitbox.tv/kingofpol" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">live stream (will be up again sometime tomorrow)</a> - <a href="https://twitter.com/kingofpol/" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">(his twitter if you want to watch the next one - he was forced to sign up for one to communicate with people, he doesn’t like social media)</a> earlier today with Adam Baldwin and Milo (the author of the article I posted previously) - apparently Milo is about to drop another nuke on the anti-gg camp some time today or tomorrow, depending on your timezone.</p>
<p>On another note, it’s hilarious that none of the anti-gg people won’t come out of their playground to attempt to act like adults and tell their side of the story. There was one on the live stream I watched (well listened to) but I never heard of her prior to that and she wasn’t fast enough with the moderator (pol) as he needed to cut it and get some sleep as he had work later in the day. I understand their fear of the backlash they’ll suffer, but come on, if you’re so adamant about it, get off your high horse.</p>
<p>Edit: Obviously I’m pro-gg…</p>
<p>Edit <span class="hashtag">#2:</span> I’m glad this has been going on for a month now… it gives me something to read/watch when I’m bored out of my mind with repetitive topics.</p>
<p>Edit <span class="hashtag">#3:</span> <a href="https://www.breitbart.com/Breitbart-London/2014/09/18/The-emails-that-prove-video-games-journalism-must-be-reformed" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">New nuke!</a></p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>In light of our revelations about the secret gaming journalism mailing list GameJournoPros, few can doubt that damaging groupthink has taken hold of the video games journalism establishment.</p>
<p>But quite how absurdly close to their subjects some gaming journalists are has been laid bare in black and white thanks to the leak of hundreds of emails from this private mailing list, which has been used by some games industry journalists to aggressively influence the opinions, policies and reporting priorities of other publications.</p>
<p>The emails below, copied verbatim from a chain about games developer Zoe Quinn and shared with Breitbart by a sympathetic source in the games industry, spell out in disturbing detail how gaming journalists threw objectivity out of the window and became cheerleaders for Quinn after it was revealed that she had started a sexual relationship with a journalist just days after she appeared in his reporting.</p>
<p>Not only did at least one of their number have sex with Quinn, but, in an astonishing breach of critical distance, games journalists can be seen in the leaked emails proposing that members of the list together to purchase her a “feel better” gift, and even a “signed letter of support.” They call her ex-boyfriend, on whom Quinn cheated with five other men in the games industry, a “psychopath,” asking why a VICE interview with him wasn’t more hostile.</p>
<p>In a long apology published today on Ars Technica, senior gaming editor Kyle Orland, who founded GameJournoPros four years ago, admitted that comments we drew attention to yesterday had been “an error in judgment.” Orland was anxious to stress, contrary to our observations, that GameJournoPros is merely a discussion forum, and its existence does not indicate collusion.</p>
<p>But what emerges from closer inspection of the leaked emails is, if anything, more damning than allegations that journalists used it to reach consensus about breaking news. Dozens of prominent journalists in the gaming world are seemingly unaware of basic journalistic obligations and appear incompetent, unethical and confused.</p>
<p>“There is an ocean of distance between ‘hi we’re strangers and we’re aware of your dirty laundry’ and ‘Hi, we’re your colleagues, and we appreciate the work you do for our community. Illegitimi non carborundum’,” writes Andrew Groen, a contributor to WIRED, seemingly unaware that Quinn is not a “colleague,” but the subject of reporting. Describing Quinn as a colleague shows how paper-thin the barrier between reporter and reported has become.</p>
<p>The emails also show journalists reluctant to engage with questions of propriety. “As sympathetic as I am to the horrible harassment Zoe faced,” writes Kotaku reporter Jason Schreier, “I think this incident has raised enough questions about the incestuous relationship between press and developers already.”</p>
<p>Attempts to shut down enquiries in this way will strike most professional journalists, not to mention readers, as shocking. They demonstrate that the elite club of games bloggers and editors did not want to engage with allegations made by readers about their handling of the Zoe Quinn affair, perhaps for fear of what might surface.</p>
<p>Even after being exposed as conflicted, games journalists are still being less than straightforward about the extent of their collusion. In his apology today, Kyle Orland said, “No one else in the group took [my suggestions] seriously.” That is not what the leaked emails show.</p>
<p>Breitbart is today releasing a selection of emails further to the messages published yesterday that demonstrate how urgently reform is needed among journalists who cover an industry worth over $80 billion. The emails cover journalists whose writing appears in almost every major gaming outlet and many technology publications, including Polygon, Eurogamer, GameSpot, Joystiq, Kotaku and WIRED.</p>
<p>Readers will be left asking whether these writers and editors have any idea what journalists are for, what their obligations and responsibilities are, and why evidence of conflict of interest and collusion are so troubling to their audience.<br>
The emails</p>
<p>I had a thought. Maybe a bad one. You tell me: I remember a few years back when Patrick Klepek hit on some tough circumstances we all pitched in to get him a “feel better” gift. Anybody think something like that could be appropriate to address the circumstances that have been forced upon Zoe? Even if it’s not monetary. Maybe a signed, joint letter of support from the Game Journo Pros. I know she’s not a member of the group like Patrick was, but I do know that this is part of a broader theme of the industry losing talent to the toxic culture. And that’s our business. In my mind, it’s a joint show of solidarity to match the trolls’ joint show of force … The last thing I think we want is Zoe thinking she’s under attack <em>alone.</em> The brain has a way of convincing you that silent people are against you.<br>
— Andrew Groen, WIRED contributor</p>
<p>As the person I’m going to assume is the most irrationally optimistic person here, I like this idea. Small bits of kindness can do a lot, even when found in oceans of shit.<br>
— Dan Starkey, Eurogamer, GameSpot, Joystiq, Kotaku</p>
<p>This is barely a game-industry story, no matter how some people want to frame it. This is a story about a person who happens to be in the game industry and their personal relationships (no matter how it may weave back into “the industry” and however poor the person’s judgments may have been) and public expose of private materials by that person’s partner as revenge, so I don’t think we, as games press, should support furthering the story by commenting, editorializing or even allowing others to ruminate on it.<br>
— Andy Eddy</p>
<p>Who here hasn’t slept with a PR person or game developer? <span class="hashtag">#AMIRITE</span><br>
— William O’Neal, editor-in-chief, <a href="http://TechRadar.com" rel="nofollow noopener">TechRadar.com</a></p>
<p>I like the signed letter of support idea. Even better if we can get some developers in on that. Anyone want to volunteer to draft something?<br>
— Kyle Orland, Ars Technica</p>
<p>I’d also suggest that - if others think the letter is a good idea - we should do this entirely under the radar, organizing it through word-of-mouth and email rather than Twitter. I made the mistake earlier of publicly voicing support and in doing so drawing more attention to the issue. I’d rather not make that mistake again.<br>
— Andrew Groen, WIRED contributor</p>
<p>As sympathetic as I am to the horrible harassment Zoe faced, I think this incident has raised enough questions about the incestuous relationship between press and developers already.<br>
— Jason Schreier, Kotaku</p>
<p>Silver lining: Quinn is getting a bunch of new Patreon patrons today, apparently.<br>
— Kyle Orland, Ars Technica</p>
<p>I would prefer not to be associated with this. It feels wrong to me. I think it feels very off to reach across the fence from journalist to subject in this way. I prefer professional distance, especially given the accusations being levied at us from outside.<br>
— Mike Futter, Game Informer</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/five-guys-burger-and-fries/13431/50">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/five-guys-burger-and-fries/13431/50</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2014 22:44:19 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13431-50</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/five-guys-burger-and-fries/13431.rss">Five Guys Burger and Fries</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Five Guys Burger and Fries</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[k3nny1550]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=e78JRIHRjC0" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Love this take.</a> TotalBiscuit is always quite an articulate speaker.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/five-guys-burger-and-fries/13431/49">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/five-guys-burger-and-fries/13431/49</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2014 22:31:37 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13431-49</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/five-guys-burger-and-fries/13431.rss">Five Guys Burger and Fries</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Five Guys Burger and Fries</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[DeleteThis]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><img src="https://pbs.twimg.com/media/BxbS7SsCcAAStzP.jpg:large" alt="" width="598" height="238"></p>
<p><a href="https://twitter.com/OriginalSprax/status/511085307199254528/photo/1" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://twitter.com/OriginalSprax/status/511085307199254528/photo/1</a><br>
<a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/gamergate" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://twitter.com/hashtag/gamergate</a><br>
<a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/NotYourShield?src=hash" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://twitter.com/hashtag/NotYourShield?src=hash</a><br>
<div class="lightbox-wrapper"><a class="lightbox" href="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/original/2X/2/22d4918a64696f047a8036eb6a47fa909b9bff00.jpeg" data-download-href="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/22d4918a64696f047a8036eb6a47fa909b9bff00" title="Bxe9YGlIgAAxnOD.jpg"><img src="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/original/2X/2/22d4918a64696f047a8036eb6a47fa909b9bff00.jpeg" alt="Bxe9YGlIgAAxnOD.jpg" data-base62-sha1="4Y7EUPgHbnsfat4ss5yHHjL5z3i" width="690" height="500" data-small-upload="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/optimized/2X/2/22d4918a64696f047a8036eb6a47fa909b9bff00_2_10x10.png"><div class="meta"><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-far-image svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#far-image"></use></svg><span class="filename">Bxe9YGlIgAAxnOD.jpg</span><span class="informations">1024×667 56 KB</span><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-discourse-expand svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#discourse-expand"></use></svg></div></a></div></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/five-guys-burger-and-fries/13431/48">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/five-guys-burger-and-fries/13431/48</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2014 18:57:51 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13431-48</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/five-guys-burger-and-fries/13431.rss">Five Guys Burger and Fries</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Five Guys Burger and Fries</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Chickenprotector]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Don’t get me wrong. I don’t condone harassment, but what’s to say she’s not lying about how much harassment she’s getting? I know that she’s <span class="bbcode-b">at least</span> receiving some flak for her own stupidity, but she’s been proven to be a pathological liar.</p>
<p>That said, I reiterate, I don’t condone harassment and death threats. Imo people need to take a step back and breathe. If the idiots in the Quinn camp didn’t overreact, this shit wouldn’t be happening. They continue to overreact and this shit <span class="bbcode-i">still</span> continues because of it.</p>
<p>On the plus side if she’s tired of the harassment <span class="bbcode-i">why doesn’t she pull out like a normal person would?!</span> Just shut the fuck up and not talk for a while till the heat dies down. Don’t get on twitter, etc. It boggles my mind, I know these people aren’t logical, but if you’re smart, you’d have pulled by now if you’re as tired of the harassment as you think they would be by this point.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/five-guys-burger-and-fries/13431/47">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/five-guys-burger-and-fries/13431/47</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2014 11:50:11 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13431-47</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/five-guys-burger-and-fries/13431.rss">Five Guys Burger and Fries</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Five Guys Burger and Fries</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[JeffMOD]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Yeah, even if the allegations are true, it doesn’t justify <span class="bbcode-i">any</span> of what’s happened.<br>
Also, pretty sure <span class="bbcode-b">none</span> of the gaming journalists involved are getting even a fraction of the harassment Zoe Quinn is, even though the issue is supposedly over gaming journalism being corrupt.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/five-guys-burger-and-fries/13431/46">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/five-guys-burger-and-fries/13431/46</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2014 11:20:36 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13431-46</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/five-guys-burger-and-fries/13431.rss">Five Guys Burger and Fries</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Five Guys Burger and Fries</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Orpheon]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><a href="https://www.cracked.com/blog/5-things-i-learned-as-internets-most-hated-person/" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Here’s an interview with Zoe Quinn.</a> Obviously not unbiased since it’s her telling it, but shows just how insane this whole thing is.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/five-guys-burger-and-fries/13431/45">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/five-guys-burger-and-fries/13431/45</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2014 05:08:57 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13431-45</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/five-guys-burger-and-fries/13431.rss">Five Guys Burger and Fries</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Five Guys Burger and Fries</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Chickenprotector]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Yeah. There’s some irony in that…</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/five-guys-burger-and-fries/13431/44">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/five-guys-burger-and-fries/13431/44</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2014 04:21:26 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13431-44</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/five-guys-burger-and-fries/13431.rss">Five Guys Burger and Fries</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Five Guys Burger and Fries</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[DeleteThis]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>It’s insane how this is still going on. 5 weeks in internet time is like a century</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/five-guys-burger-and-fries/13431/43">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/five-guys-burger-and-fries/13431/43</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2014 04:16:19 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13431-43</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/five-guys-burger-and-fries/13431.rss">Five Guys Burger and Fries</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Five Guys Burger and Fries</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Chickenprotector]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Thread necro…</p>
<p><a href="https://www.breitbart.com/Breitbart-London/2014/09/17/Exposed-the-secret-mailing-list-of-the-gaming-journalism-elite" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">The shitstorm has become a full blown category 5 shitacane.</a></p>
<p>If you’re not caught up: <a href="https://knowyourmeme.com/memes/events/gamergate" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://knowyourmeme.com/memes/events/gamergate</a> Read through this.</p>
<p>Numerous images. I know it’s a conservative site.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p><a href="https://cdn.breitbart.com/mediaserver/Breitbart/Breitbart-London/2014/09/17/kyle-orland-screenshot.jpg" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://cdn.breitbart.com/mediaserver/Breitbart/Breitbart-London/2014/09/17/kyle-orland-screenshot.jpg</a></p>
<p>Several prominent gaming journalists across America are part of a secret mailing list on which they discuss what to cover, what to ignore, and what approach their coverage should take to breaking news, Breitbart can reveal.</p>
<p>High-profile editors, reporters, and reviewers from heavyweight gaming news sites such as Polygon, Ars Technica, and Kotaku use the private Google Groups mailing list, which is called Gaming Journalism Professionals or GameJournoPros, to shape industry-wide attitudes to events, such as the revelation that developer Zoe Quinn had a sexual relationship with at least one prominent games journalist – a journalist who had mentioned her and her products in his reporting.</p>
<p>Emails seen by Breitbart from August of this year show Kyle Orland, a senior gaming editor at Ars Technica, discussing the Zoe Quinn scandal. He wrote: “I don’t want to in essence reward the jerks doing this by giving their ‘issue’ any attention at all … I’m not even going to give the bullshit ‘journalism ethics’ excuse for these attacks the time of day.”</p>
<p>Orland continued: “I would LOVE to use my platform to reproach this kind of behavior… but that would go against Quinn’s valid and understandable desire not to have this personal matter publicized by the media… Maybe we should just stick to Twitter to boost the signal on this one, rather than our ‘front pages.’”</p>
<p>“Maybe we should get a public letter of support going around decrying these kinds of personal attacks, signed by as many sympathetic journalists/developers as we can,” he wrote. “Maybe we should just use this as an excuse to give more attention to her work… I know I’ve been meaning to review Depression Quest since its Steam release.”</p>
<p><a href="https://www.breitbart.com/mediaserver/26565B83C18A46CFA70C4D0C47322EB6.jpg?h=361&amp;w=640" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://www.breitbart.com/mediaserver/26565B83C18A46CFA70C4D0C47322EB6.jpg?h=361&amp;w=640</a></p>
<p>The sight of journalists not only engaging in activism on behalf of their reporting subjects but also discouraging other reporters and editors from covering stories of interest to their readers will be disturbing to many in the industry, who have long suspected a persistent bias and unusual levels of co-operation and co-ordination from senior journalists.</p>
<p>Polygon editor Ben Kuchera is seen on the list offering support to Quinn and chiding other writers for not actively doing the same.</p>
<p><a href="https://www.breitbart.com/mediaserver/E9D0BF53BE8746319179C28F701684A8.jpg" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://www.breitbart.com/mediaserver/E9D0BF53BE8746319179C28F701684A8.jpg</a></p>
<p>The GameJournoPros emails appear to confirm widely-held suspicions that video game journalists operate with one voice and collude on major issues to distort coverage of ethics violations and to support figures to whom they are politically sympathetic.</p>
<p>This revelation echoes the 2010 JournoList scandal, in which liberal reporters were caught colluding and smearing their ideological opponents in a private mailing list set up by Ezra Klein, now the editor-in-chief of <a href="http://Vox.com" rel="nofollow noopener">Vox.com</a>.  The exposure of JournoList cost Washington Post reporter David Weigel his job, after Weigel was seen mocking conservative figures on whom he also reported in the pages of the Post.</p>
<p>Readers with knowledge of the GameJournoPros list and in particular its membership are strongly encouraged to contact us with what they know.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/five-guys-burger-and-fries/13431/42">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/five-guys-burger-and-fries/13431/42</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2014 01:06:30 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13431-42</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/five-guys-burger-and-fries/13431.rss">Five Guys Burger and Fries</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Five Guys Burger and Fries</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[sloshedtrain]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>You guys need to read this article.<br>
<a href="https://apgnation.com/archives/2014/09/09/6977/truth-gaming-interview-fine-young-capitalists" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Fine Young Capitalist Interview.</a></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/five-guys-burger-and-fries/13431/41">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/five-guys-burger-and-fries/13431/41</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2014 07:42:20 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13431-41</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/five-guys-burger-and-fries/13431.rss">Five Guys Burger and Fries</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Five Guys Burger and Fries</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[papernick]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Kairouseki">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/k/57b2e6/40.png" class="avatar"> Kairouseki:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>No, I agree that there are good indie games but a lot of the ones that are big hits shouldn’t be, at least in my opinion. I haven’t played Dear Esther or Stanley Parable but video games need to stop trying to be walking simulators. Gone Home is the best example as it’s literally less than half an hour long of essentially nothing and praised more for its “message” than anything. I don’t think the scene needs any regulation, just that video games should be praised for being video games and games that rely solely on being “progressive” or whatever shouldn’t be getting 10/10 scores. Though I suppose that’s a larger issue with the community than anything to do with the industry and the AAA industry has similar issues. Video games have stopped being required to be video games really and I think that’s an issue.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Just wanted to say that Stanley Parable is an excellent game, and definitely NOT just a walking simulator.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/five-guys-burger-and-fries/13431/40">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/five-guys-burger-and-fries/13431/40</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2014 15:27:55 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13431-40</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/five-guys-burger-and-fries/13431.rss">Five Guys Burger and Fries</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Five Guys Burger and Fries</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[DeleteThis]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Oh jeez it’s just like the postmodern art “movement” all over again<br>
A bunch of colors vomited onto a canvas now counts as art and is therefore worth millions! yay.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/five-guys-burger-and-fries/13431/39">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/five-guys-burger-and-fries/13431/39</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2014 03:50:19 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13431-39</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/five-guys-burger-and-fries/13431.rss">Five Guys Burger and Fries</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Five Guys Burger and Fries</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Chickenprotector]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Define “video games” because it’s technically interactive media imo. Most of them fit the criteria despite being nothing more than a fucking simulator.</p>
<p>But I digress, yeah, there I agree with you. Though hype is part of the problem. <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=cd13fE5WJ3c" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">I’d recommend watching/listening TotalBiscuit’s take on this.</a> It sheds a bit of light on the issue you describe.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/five-guys-burger-and-fries/13431/38">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/five-guys-burger-and-fries/13431/38</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2014 03:32:53 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13431-38</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/five-guys-burger-and-fries/13431.rss">Five Guys Burger and Fries</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Five Guys Burger and Fries</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Kairouseki]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>No, I agree that there are good indie games but a lot of the ones that are big hits shouldn’t be, at least in my opinion. I haven’t played Dear Esther or Stanley Parable but video games need to stop trying to be walking simulators. Gone Home is the best example as it’s literally less than half an hour long of essentially nothing and praised more for its “message” than anything. I don’t think the scene needs any regulation, just that video games should be praised for being video games and games that rely solely on being “progressive” or whatever shouldn’t be getting 10/10 scores. Though I suppose that’s a larger issue with the community than anything to do with the industry and the AAA industry has similar issues. Video games have stopped being required to be video games really and I think that’s an issue.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/five-guys-burger-and-fries/13431/37">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/five-guys-burger-and-fries/13431/37</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2014 03:05:12 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13431-37</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/five-guys-burger-and-fries/13431.rss">Five Guys Burger and Fries</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
