<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Changing the Scientist&#39;s Hiding Spot</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/changing-the-scientists-hiding-spot/11861</link>
    <description>I&#39;ve managed to play Black Mesa: very good so far. A bit crazier in its gameplay, like HL2: E2, but they serve as new challenges for me to adapt to. 

I did notice how the hiding place of one particular scientist, the one on top of that generator right next to the Blast Pit, was altered, and therefore, I think, lost its humor. The original version was hilarious because the scientist&#39;s hiding spot was so ridiculous, and his line &quot;Go away, and don&#39;t tell anybody I&#39;m here!&quot; works so well with the setting. The new hiding place is not as wonderfully ridiculous, and the scientist just comes across as a self-preserving schmuck rather than as someone who would climb to any ludicrous spot just to escape the monsters, even at the cost of being cut off from the others by dangerous rotating mechanisms. The puzzle is easier to climb, but it fails to retain the humor of that particular part of the original. 

However, I did make it funny again by shooting him after he said that he ditched the other scientists because they were dead weight. Then I hit him with a crowbar a few times, with him exclaiming before the final blow: &quot;You were supposed to be our savior!&quot; Also, when I dropped a satchel charge in front of him, he gasped and did nothing. You did a thorough job with the scientists&#39; reactions, BMS team. I do commend you for that.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 17 Dec 2012 16:26:22 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>The Cafeteria</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/changing-the-scientists-hiding-spot/11861.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Changing the Scientist&#39;s Hiding Spot</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[D3lta]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I think they removed the scientist to the controll room to make it more sensible.<br>
I don’t think pussys like the science team would even bother to turn the fan on though.Would be fun to see them fall or something :p.<br>
But I agree with you.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/changing-the-scientists-hiding-spot/11861/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/changing-the-scientists-hiding-spot/11861/3</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 17 Dec 2012 16:26:22 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11861-3</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/changing-the-scientists-hiding-spot/11861.rss">Changing the Scientist&#39;s Hiding Spot</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Changing the Scientist&#39;s Hiding Spot</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Mr_Saurus]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I agree. It’s a very small thing, but that moment was actually pretty funny for me in original half life. They say the secret to humor is surprise, after all.</p>
<p>I also made the black mesa version funny though by gibbing him with a keyboard accidentally.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/changing-the-scientists-hiding-spot/11861/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/changing-the-scientists-hiding-spot/11861/2</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 17 Dec 2012 14:57:49 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11861-2</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/changing-the-scientists-hiding-spot/11861.rss">Changing the Scientist&#39;s Hiding Spot</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Changing the Scientist&#39;s Hiding Spot</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Boundaryman]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I’ve managed to play Black Mesa: very good so far. A bit crazier in its gameplay, like HL2: E2, but they serve as new challenges for me to adapt to.</p>
<p>I did notice how the hiding place of one particular scientist, the one on top of that generator right next to the Blast Pit, was altered, and therefore, I think, lost its humor. The original version was hilarious because the scientist’s hiding spot was so ridiculous, and his line “Go away, and don’t tell anybody I’m here!” works so well with the setting. The new hiding place is not as wonderfully ridiculous, and the scientist just comes across as a self-preserving schmuck rather than as someone who would climb to any ludicrous spot just to escape the monsters, even at the cost of being cut off from the others by dangerous rotating mechanisms. The puzzle is easier to climb, but it fails to retain the humor of that particular part of the original.</p>
<p>However, I did make it funny again by shooting him after he said that he ditched the other scientists because they were dead weight. Then I hit him with a crowbar a few times, with him exclaiming before the final blow: “You were supposed to be our savior!” Also, when I dropped a satchel charge in front of him, he gasped and did nothing. You did a thorough job with the scientists’ reactions, BMS team. I do commend you for that.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/changing-the-scientists-hiding-spot/11861/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/changing-the-scientists-hiding-spot/11861/1</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 17 Dec 2012 03:21:47 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11861-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/changing-the-scientists-hiding-spot/11861.rss">Changing the Scientist&#39;s Hiding Spot</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
