<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Banned from viewing or reporting bug issues</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/banned-from-viewing-or-reporting-bug-issues/12169</link>
    <description>There I was, anonymously submitting BM bug issues to Bitbucket. Watched as some 20 of them were tagged as &quot;resolved&quot;. Everything&#39;s been fine for several weeks. I ramped up my submissions. Earlier today, I could no longer submit or access the issues page. Thinking there was a change in the policy for submissions, I signed up as a member at Bitbucket. Happily, I was once again able to view and submit bug issues, and did so. But within half an hour, I received an email stating &quot;that the bugs I was reporting could not be fixed&quot; and was asked to &quot;stop submitting bugs related to clipping issues&quot;, even though some of my bugs that had been &quot;resolved&quot; were clipping related. Immediately thereafter, I was again blocked from viewing or accessing the issues page, even after repeated attempts.

I&#39;m trying to do my part in giving back and doing the little that I can in improving BM and this is the thanks I get for my efforts. Needless to say, this has left a very bad taste in my mouth.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2013 07:49:57 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>In-game Issues (Mod)</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/banned-from-viewing-or-reporting-bug-issues/12169.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Banned from viewing or reporting bug issues</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Dadster]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Please, never mind my multiple posts (is this an excitable moment for 'ya?)</p>
<p>Forum Dev, please delete this post entry. My apologies. Please amalgamate my recently posted <span class="bbcode-u">RELATED</span> entries in the best way possible. Make me look to appear as an ALPHA dog, please.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/banned-from-viewing-or-reporting-bug-issues/12169/31">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/banned-from-viewing-or-reporting-bug-issues/12169/31</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2013 07:49:57 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12169-31</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/banned-from-viewing-or-reporting-bug-issues/12169.rss">Banned from viewing or reporting bug issues</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Banned from viewing or reporting bug issues</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Dadster]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Please excuse what appears to be multiple posts. This is attributable to me not being able to respond quickly enough to submissions from other forum members. I guess I’m involved in an interesting topic, or a sex scandal of some kind (I wish).</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/banned-from-viewing-or-reporting-bug-issues/12169/30">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/banned-from-viewing-or-reporting-bug-issues/12169/30</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2013 07:30:48 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12169-30</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/banned-from-viewing-or-reporting-bug-issues/12169.rss">Banned from viewing or reporting bug issues</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Banned from viewing or reporting bug issues</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Dadster]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Cpl.1nsane">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/user_avatar/leakfree.org/cpl.1nsane/40/4631_2.png" class="avatar"> Cpl.1nsane:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>If I mark something as resolved that usually means I’ve gone in and corrected the issue, I’d use ‘wont fix’ other wise.</p>
<p>An example might be some of the railings (and chain link fences) you’ve pointed out as clipping into walls and such, this is usually done to try to fit the models into that space (since they’re modular) they don’t always fit perfectly. So it might come down to a case of the prop clipping into the wall slightly VS z-fighting issues or some such.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>That’s very useful to know. Thanks for the feedback. I’ll continue to report them to you, in case they’re fixable. If not, just mark them as “WONTFIX” and I’ll move on to other issues. You really need to inform us as such so that we don’t dwell on additional instances of the same issue. Please, help yourselves by <span class="bbcode-u">EDUCATING</span> bug reporters on this issue.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/banned-from-viewing-or-reporting-bug-issues/12169/29">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/banned-from-viewing-or-reporting-bug-issues/12169/29</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2013 07:12:52 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12169-29</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/banned-from-viewing-or-reporting-bug-issues/12169.rss">Banned from viewing or reporting bug issues</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Banned from viewing or reporting bug issues</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Dadster]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="your-name-here">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/y/e480ec/40.png" class="avatar"> your-name-here:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>From this post, it’s clear that after the walls of text I wrote, you don’t seem to care what we think. You will continue to post bugs we clearly said not to post about. No amount of writing will bring you around to our view. We aren’t call of duty and we don’t give a fuck about realism. I am sorry you feel that way. I wish you luck in your bug hunting endeavors. There may be other mods that could use your clipping expertise.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Wait a minute… hold on there… <span class="bbcode-u">WHERE</span> are you coming from? Talking about taking things going south in a <span class="bbcode-u">HURRY</span>, SHEEESH and holy macklemore!!! Don’t you think that you may be overreacting just a little bit, here? I really do care about everything you think about!!!</p>
<p>I think I’ve understood where “you’re coming from” as is hopefully evidenced in the examples I’ve provided to you in my post <span class="hashtag">#15</span>. I think ALL (at the very least, most) of these issues fall into your acceptable category, as outlined in your post <span class="hashtag">#16</span>. Does that not show a change in attitude, thinking and understanding on my part?</p>
<p>My comments in post <span class="hashtag">#24</span> are <span class="bbcode-u">NOT</span> directed at BM, but from the perspective of a newly started/designed project, and not one that’s already been long in development, like BM is. It was in no way meant to besmirch or belittle BM. Think!!!. Why would I do that to something that I obviously enjoy and admire and have spent hundreds of hours on, in both playing and, more so, finding ways to improve upon it. It doesn’t make any sense for me to do that, does it?</p>
<p>I’m very appreciative for all your time and efforts (I assume you’re a busy man) in showing me the ways to effectively and efficiently submit my bug reports to you, and would very much like to continue to do so. I think my keen eye and detailed scrutiny, can be very beneficial to improving BM. Big picture wise, isn’t that something that we both, and with the help of many, many others from the BM community, want to utilize?</p>
<p>I certainly apologize for anything that may have been misinterpreted or misconstrued, and I hope that we can put this gross misunderstanding behind us.</p>
<p>If you haven’t done so already, please recognize that I’ve gone the extra mile here to get this resolved. I could’ve easily, and in my view would’ve been justified in doing so, taken the low road, but I haven’t out of respect for you, your team and the BM mod, because in the end, it’s unnecessarily stressful, harmful, wasteful and detrimental and serves no beneficial productive purpose.</p>
<p>So, can we shake hands and move on, please? There’s an “olive branch” peace offering dangling in front of your face… Oh, I’m sorry, it’s clipping into your forehead… who said mapping was easy? If I could get access to the bug tracker, I could report this issue. :lol:</p>
<p>Don’t think I’m taking this situation lightly. I’m not. In your view, it’s serious, but not as serious as you may think it should be. Trust me, when it comes to identifying possible bugs in BM, you already know that I’m a very ardent and thorough individual and feel that I can provide you with unique and obscure observations that are important and should be considered for possible correction. When it comes to my bug tracker submissions, whether you “use it” or “lose it”, doesn’t matter to me. For whatever reasons, it’s entirely your call, on what issues should be addressed. After all, it’s your mod and what actions are deemed necessary, from up on high, should be left in your capable hands. My focus, based on your recent guidelines to me, is to bring issues to light and to your attention and then to let you decide on what appropriate actions, if any, should be taken. Just let me/us <span class="bbcode-u">ACCURATELY</span> and <span class="bbcode-u">DEFINITELY</span> know if a reported issue has been <span class="bbcode-u">TRULY</span> “resolved”.</p>
<p>HELLO, someone!!! Can I and others please be given access to the Bitbucket issues page to view your helpful image links and the BM issues page. If not, please give us your approximate timetable/schedule/availability to view the very useful bug reporting pages.</p>
<p>Thank you, in advance, for your valued help and assistance.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/banned-from-viewing-or-reporting-bug-issues/12169/28">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/banned-from-viewing-or-reporting-bug-issues/12169/28</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2013 04:53:25 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12169-28</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/banned-from-viewing-or-reporting-bug-issues/12169.rss">Banned from viewing or reporting bug issues</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Banned from viewing or reporting bug issues</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Dadster]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="ThunderDash">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 ThunderDash:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Obviously I can’t speak for the devs on whether issues like these are ones they’ll pursue, but generally issues with static props clipping through each other are fixable. The only major barricade I can think of would be the scale of the props and the size of the area (for instance, if you have a pipe connected to a wall that’s clipping through another pipe, it might be unfixable because if you move either one of them they’d clip through the walls into the next room).</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Yeah, you’re right. I check that out as much as possible by noclipping through walls to see how much of an object is clipping, and to see what’s on the other side of the wall. There are loads of instances where cleverly clipping objects into walls results in some very acceptable results, if done correctly.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/banned-from-viewing-or-reporting-bug-issues/12169/27">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/banned-from-viewing-or-reporting-bug-issues/12169/27</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2013 03:04:10 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12169-27</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/banned-from-viewing-or-reporting-bug-issues/12169.rss">Banned from viewing or reporting bug issues</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Banned from viewing or reporting bug issues</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Dadster]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="your-name-here">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/y/e480ec/40.png" class="avatar"> your-name-here:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>You are correct, they should have been set to won’t fix. That’s our bad on our part. Though anyone getting messages from a bug tracker should probably have that looked at  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=9" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
<p>It looks like most of these are on the tracker. This is what a bug tracker is for, not a forum. When John and I have spare cycles, we will review them.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Actually, almost all of these are <span class="bbcode-u">NEW</span> ones that I’ve collected since being blocked from posting further new bugs on Bitbucket.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/banned-from-viewing-or-reporting-bug-issues/12169/26">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/banned-from-viewing-or-reporting-bug-issues/12169/26</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2013 03:00:22 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12169-26</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/banned-from-viewing-or-reporting-bug-issues/12169.rss">Banned from viewing or reporting bug issues</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Banned from viewing or reporting bug issues</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[your-name-here]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Dadster">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/d/e495f1/40.png" class="avatar"> Dadster:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>More a minor case, I suppose. When it comes to game design, with all due respect, I have a problem with something that’s designed in contradiction to common sense functional knowledge and an understanding of how the real world works, assuming that all the tools/assets necessary are available to the designer to use. Yes, I know, there are parts of the HL universe that’s not real world related, and that’s fine. There’s somewhat more leeway in that regard.</p>
<p>In the case of BM, I’m so grateful that we have the bug tracker avenue available to us, to point out these deficiencies, in hopes that they be considered for correction. The time and effort is well worth it, because in the end BM will be better for it and we all get to play an even better version of the best mod ever made.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>From this post, it’s clear that after the walls of text I wrote, you don’t seem to care what we think. You will continue to post bugs we clearly said not to post about. No amount of writing will bring you around to our view. We aren’t call of duty and we don’t give a fuck about realism. I am sorry you feel that way. I wish you luck in your bug hunting endeavors. There may be other mods that could use your clipping expertise.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/banned-from-viewing-or-reporting-bug-issues/12169/25">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/banned-from-viewing-or-reporting-bug-issues/12169/25</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2013 02:58:14 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12169-25</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/banned-from-viewing-or-reporting-bug-issues/12169.rss">Banned from viewing or reporting bug issues</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Banned from viewing or reporting bug issues</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Dadster]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="acade365">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 acade365:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Dadster, I don’t want to be offensive, but you strike me as someone with a severe case of OCD.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>More a minor case, I suppose. When it comes to game design, with all due respect, I have a problem with something that’s designed in contradiction to common sense functional knowledge and an understanding of how the real world works, assuming that all the tools/assets necessary are available to the designer to use. Yes, I know, there are parts of the HL universe that’s not real world related, and that’s fine. There’s somewhat more leeway in that regard.</p>
<p>In the case of BM, I’m so grateful that we have the bug tracker avenue available to us, to point out these deficiencies, in hopes that they be considered for correction. The time and effort is well worth it, because in the end BM will be better for it and we all get to play an even better version of the best mod ever made.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/banned-from-viewing-or-reporting-bug-issues/12169/24">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/banned-from-viewing-or-reporting-bug-issues/12169/24</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2013 02:53:48 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12169-24</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/banned-from-viewing-or-reporting-bug-issues/12169.rss">Banned from viewing or reporting bug issues</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Banned from viewing or reporting bug issues</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Cpl.1nsane]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="your-name-here">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/y/e480ec/40.png" class="avatar"> your-name-here:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>The clipping issue that you mentioned is the following:</p>
<pre><code class="lang-auto">Player can clip through entire upper portion of the fallen antenna tower.</code></pre>
<p>I am pretty sure that John marked this as resolved for one of two reasons: A) We couldn’t fix it or B ) They just added a player_clip around the object in question. AFAIK, I didn’t see John post a resolution of what was done to fix it, so he’ll have to weigh in here.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>If I mark something as resolved that usually means I’ve gone in and corrected the issue, I’d use ‘wont fix’ other wise.</p>
<p>But yes I do appreciate the effort and time to report these issues its merely that a lot are very minor or In fixing them might cause other issues that may not be readily apparent.</p>
<p>An example might be some of the railings (and chain link fences) you’ve pointed out as clipping into walls and such, this is usually done to try to fit the models into that space (since they’re modular) they don’t always fit perfectly. So it might come down to a case of the prop clipping into the wall slightly VS z-fighting issues or some such.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/banned-from-viewing-or-reporting-bug-issues/12169/23">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/banned-from-viewing-or-reporting-bug-issues/12169/23</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2013 02:47:14 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12169-23</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/banned-from-viewing-or-reporting-bug-issues/12169.rss">Banned from viewing or reporting bug issues</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Banned from viewing or reporting bug issues</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[your-name-here]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Dadster">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/d/e495f1/40.png" class="avatar"> Dadster:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>^ @ your-name-here, Developer</p>
<p>I use noclip, not only as a means to show you the existence and severity of the problem, but to also provide a useful angle in the screenshot to give your team an idea as to the location in the map where the problem resides.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>First off, a ‘useful angle’ is one that would be actually encountered in gameplay, not artificially created by sv_cheats and noclip. Secondly, I have no idea where on the maps your pictures came from because you provided zero positional data. There could be any number of places on a map where there are messed up ceiling tiles or misplaced floorboards (not that we care about those much). With each bug report, you need to be pasting the ‘getpos’ output so we know where to teleport to.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Dadster">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/d/e495f1/40.png" class="avatar"> Dadster:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>…some of them can be seen doing so from a normal perspective. That’s what caught my eye in the first place.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Sure I agree, but EVERY bug? Doubt it.  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=9" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/banned-from-viewing-or-reporting-bug-issues/12169/22">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/banned-from-viewing-or-reporting-bug-issues/12169/22</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2013 02:38:45 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12169-22</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/banned-from-viewing-or-reporting-bug-issues/12169.rss">Banned from viewing or reporting bug issues</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Banned from viewing or reporting bug issues</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[your-name-here]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="ThunderDash">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 ThunderDash:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Obviously I can’t speak for the devs on whether issues like these are ones they’ll pursue, but generally issues with static props clipping through each other are fixable. The only major barricade I can think of would be the scale of the props and the size of the area (for instance, if you have a pipe connected to a wall that’s clipping through another pipe, it might be unfixable because if you move either one of them they’d clip through the walls into the next room).</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Also keep in mind that moving the alignment of one piece on the map may cause the entire map to shift. Not saying it’s always the case, but keep it in mind.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/banned-from-viewing-or-reporting-bug-issues/12169/21">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/banned-from-viewing-or-reporting-bug-issues/12169/21</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2013 02:21:40 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12169-21</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/banned-from-viewing-or-reporting-bug-issues/12169.rss">Banned from viewing or reporting bug issues</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Banned from viewing or reporting bug issues</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[your-name-here]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Dadster">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/d/e495f1/40.png" class="avatar"> Dadster:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Concerning labeling issues as “resolved” even though they haven’t been, out of politeness, this sends the wrong message don’t you think? A person would be motivated to search out even more bugs, seeing that they are being fixed and that he’s/she’s making a contribution/difference. Maybe the better tact would be to label them as “won’t fix” with an explanation. This would also give reporters useful feedback as to what kinds of problems are most likely to be addressed and which ones won’t.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>You are correct, they should have been set to won’t fix. That’s our bad on our part. Though anyone getting messages from a bug tracker should probably have that looked at  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=9" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Dadster">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/d/e495f1/40.png" class="avatar"> Dadster:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Let me show you some bugs that I’ve found, and you tell me if they fit within your “legitimate and fixable” category.</p>
<ol>
<li>Differences in track lighting <a href="https://i.imgur.com/IAX4ZP0.jpg" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://i.imgur.com/IAX4ZP0.jpg</a>
</li>
<li>Handrails with texture z-fighting issues <a href="https://i.imgur.com/hCjbE3O.jpg" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://i.imgur.com/hCjbE3O.jpg</a>
</li>
<li>Warning signs not illuminated by flashlight <a href="https://i.imgur.com/7cA4tbd.jpg" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://i.imgur.com/7cA4tbd.jpg</a>
</li>
<li>Warning sign partially obscured <a href="https://i.imgur.com/ZZYqtK2.jpg" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://i.imgur.com/ZZYqtK2.jpg</a>
</li>
<li>Cables from electrical boxes, non-terminating <a href="https://i.imgur.com/DWVkbY4.jpg" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://i.imgur.com/DWVkbY4.jpg</a>
</li>
<li>Missing sounds from working machinery, where elsewhere for same models, sounds were present <a href="https://i.imgur.com/bjB9YJE.jpg" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://i.imgur.com/bjB9YJE.jpg</a>
</li>
<li>Handrails aligned half off edge of stairs <a href="https://i.imgur.com/5kgH7fn.jpg" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://i.imgur.com/5kgH7fn.jpg</a>
</li>
<li>Odd death poses (also, arm clipping into handrail) <a href="https://i.imgur.com/CEQamy5.jpg" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://i.imgur.com/CEQamy5.jpg</a>. Gravity dictates this scientist should’ve fallen to the ground, as he’s more off the desk than on and his shadow is wrong (I know, engine related issue) <a href="https://i.imgur.com/zFnEXMT.jpg" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://i.imgur.com/zFnEXMT.jpg</a>
</li>
<li>Cable organizer not attached to ceiling (viewable from ground) <a href="https://i.imgur.com/VOncZot.jpg" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://i.imgur.com/VOncZot.jpg</a>
</li>
<li>Tunnel support frame missing whole rear concrete pad <a href="https://i.imgur.com/EfEC02v.jpg" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://i.imgur.com/EfEC02v.jpg</a>
</li>
<li>Rails with texture z-fighting issues <a href="https://i.imgur.com/oUcmvFY.jpg" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://i.imgur.com/oUcmvFY.jpg</a> and <a href="https://i.imgur.com/2BB0uVX.jpg" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://i.imgur.com/2BB0uVX.jpg</a>
</li>
<li>Lighting anomalies, such as these:<br>
a) Warning stripes and rails <a href="https://i.imgur.com/YT9V6bA.jpg" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://i.imgur.com/YT9V6bA.jpg</a> and <a href="https://i.imgur.com/3NLrHKV.jpg" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://i.imgur.com/3NLrHKV.jpg</a><br>
b) <a href="https://i.imgur.com/URBkuXz.jpg" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://i.imgur.com/URBkuXz.jpg</a> and <a href="https://i.imgur.com/hv6NOZe.jpg" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://i.imgur.com/hv6NOZe.jpg</a>
</li>
</ol>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>It looks like most of these are on the tracker. This is what a bug tracker is for, not a forum. When John and I have spare cycles, we will review them.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/banned-from-viewing-or-reporting-bug-issues/12169/20">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/banned-from-viewing-or-reporting-bug-issues/12169/20</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2013 02:19:38 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12169-20</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/banned-from-viewing-or-reporting-bug-issues/12169.rss">Banned from viewing or reporting bug issues</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Banned from viewing or reporting bug issues</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[papernick]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Dadster, I don’t want to be offensive, but you strike me as someone with a severe case of OCD.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/banned-from-viewing-or-reporting-bug-issues/12169/19">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/banned-from-viewing-or-reporting-bug-issues/12169/19</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2013 01:41:43 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12169-19</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/banned-from-viewing-or-reporting-bug-issues/12169.rss">Banned from viewing or reporting bug issues</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Banned from viewing or reporting bug issues</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[KyuuGryphon]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Dadster">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/d/e495f1/40.png" class="avatar"> Dadster:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Further to your useful post <span class="hashtag">#16</span>, specifically concerning clipping issues, stationary objects clipping/through into other stationary objects is fixable, such as fence posts clipping into walls and pipes clipping through tunnel frame supports? Just want to be clear on this area.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Obviously I can’t speak for the devs on whether issues like these are ones they’ll pursue, but generally issues with static props clipping through each other are fixable. The only major barricade I can think of would be the scale of the props and the size of the area (for instance, if you have a pipe connected to a wall that’s clipping through another pipe, it might be unfixable because if you move either one of them they’d clip through the walls into the next room).</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/banned-from-viewing-or-reporting-bug-issues/12169/18">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/banned-from-viewing-or-reporting-bug-issues/12169/18</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2013 01:37:45 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12169-18</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/banned-from-viewing-or-reporting-bug-issues/12169.rss">Banned from viewing or reporting bug issues</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Banned from viewing or reporting bug issues</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Dadster]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>^ @ your-name-here, Developer</p>
<p>I use noclip, not only as a means to show you the existence and severity of the problem, but to also provide a useful angle in the screenshot to give your team an idea as to the location in the map where the problem resides. I don’t want them wasting their valuable time searching for them. I try and craft my screenshots carefully, so it may mean me having to use noclip to give your team the most informative view.<br>
In the case of the floating floodlights in the rocket silo, some of them can be seen doing so from a normal perspective. That’s what caught my eye in the first place.</p>
<p>==============================</p>
<p>Further to your useful post <span class="hashtag">#16</span>, specifically concerning clipping issues, stationary objects clipping/through into other stationary objects is fixable, such as fence posts clipping into walls and pipes clipping through tunnel frame supports? Just want to be clear on this area.</p>
<p>Also concerning your post <span class="hashtag">#16</span>, again, I can’t view any of your image links. Bitbucket tells me “You do not have access to the issues”. Grrrrrr!</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/banned-from-viewing-or-reporting-bug-issues/12169/17">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/banned-from-viewing-or-reporting-bug-issues/12169/17</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2013 01:11:06 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12169-17</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/banned-from-viewing-or-reporting-bug-issues/12169.rss">Banned from viewing or reporting bug issues</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Banned from viewing or reporting bug issues</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[your-name-here]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Dadster">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/d/e495f1/40.png" class="avatar"> Dadster:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Quote:<br>
Originally Posted by Dadster View Post<br>
Thank you, and I remain committed to assisting you in making BM as believable an environment as possible.</p>
<p>This is, of course, working within the bug reporting parameters set forth in your previous post.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Cool.</p>
<p>So immediately, I can tell you what NOT to post. I looked through your post history, you enjoy posting about clipping issues. <span class="bbcode-b">The only clipping issues I want to see outta you follow a single type</span>: Solid geometry on solid geometry. As I spelled out in my previous post, this means if there is any map geometry that is misplaced and can’t be moved by running into it, you should report that. Here are some acceptable bugs (in my view) that we would take action on…</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Stuff we care about:[/SIZE]</span><br>
<a href="https://bitbucket.org/bmscd/black-mesa-source/issue/367/sandbags-clipping-into-wall-2" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Sandbags clipping into the wall</a><br>
You can’t move the sandbags as they were placed there by a level designer. Therefore, this is a bug that requires a fix by the team.</p>
<p><a href="https://bitbucket.org/bmscd/black-mesa-source/issue/342/road-barrier-clipping-into-curb" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Road barrier clipping into curb</a><br>
Again, you can’t move the barrier or the road it is clipping into, therefore it is a bug that requires action from the team to fix.</p>
<p><a href="https://bitbucket.org/bmscd/black-mesa-source/issue/368/plants-grasses-clipping-through-sidewalks" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Plants-Grasses clipping through the sidewalks-curbs-objects</a><br>
Same deal here. Ask yourself, are the curb and plant affected by in-game physics? No they’re not so that’s yet another issue we’ll need to fix.</p>
<p>We also care about lighting issues. You reported some of those and we will definitely look into them. Here are some examples (for everyone else reading):</p>
<p><a href="https://bitbucket.org/bmscd/black-mesa-source/issue/329/pipe-texture-lighting-inconsistent" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Pipe texture-Lighting inconsistent</a><br>
<a href="https://bitbucket.org/bmscd/black-mesa-source/issue/453/lighting-on-rails-distinctly-different" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Lighting on rails distinctly different</a><br>
<a href="https://bitbucket.org/bmscd/black-mesa-source/issue/427/same-type-pipes-with-different-lighting" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Same type pipes with different lighting</a></p>
<p>The above are probably related to the VRAD pass (though I could be wrong). We will ask our mappers to look at these. The z-fighting issues are probably OK as well, unless you used cheats to get to those as well. We want your main focus to be on gameplay or crash issues over anything else. Those take highest priority.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">We really don’t care about the following issues:[/SIZE]</span><br>
<a href="https://bitbucket.org/bmscd/black-mesa-source/issue/445/no-collision-detection-between-objects-2" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">No collision detection between objects</a><br>
There is no normal situation in game where you would place a drill, an unknown object and a battery inside a toolbox. Therefore, we’re not going to spend manpower to fix this.</p>
<p><a href="https://bitbucket.org/bmscd/black-mesa-source/issue/433/caution-sign-partially-concealed" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Caution sign partially concealed</a><br>
This is what crosses the line into nitpick territory because it is opinion based (which is fine), but does not solve a problem that anyone actually cares about (save the reporter). We don’t want this stuff polluting the tracker.</p>
<p><a href="https://bitbucket.org/bmscd/black-mesa-source/issue/440/all-spotlights-in-rocket-silo-not-attached" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">All spotlights in rocket silo not attached</a><br>
So you used cheats to get to this. In my opinion, if you have to noclip to get a bug to manifest when it would normally go unnoticed, it’s probably not worth fixing. We have much bigger fish to fry (crash issues).</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Bug reporting protips:[/SIZE]</span></p>
<ul>
<li>If you have a correction to make to a bug report, <span class="bbcode-b">EDIT THE ORIGINAL BUG THREAD</span>. Don’t make a new one! We have enough duplicates already.</li>
<li>Before reporting, <span class="bbcode-b">ASK YOURSELF</span> if the issue you are reporting is actually a bug. If it isn’t, <span class="bbcode-b">ASK YOURSELF</span> whether or not it is even worth spending time to fix.</li>
</ul>
<p>I hope this answers your questions.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/banned-from-viewing-or-reporting-bug-issues/12169/16">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/banned-from-viewing-or-reporting-bug-issues/12169/16</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2013 23:52:44 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12169-16</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/banned-from-viewing-or-reporting-bug-issues/12169.rss">Banned from viewing or reporting bug issues</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Banned from viewing or reporting bug issues</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Dadster]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Quote:<br>
Originally Posted by Dadster View Post<br>
Thank you, and I remain committed to assisting you in making BM as believable an environment as possible.</p>
<p>This is, of course, working within the bug reporting parameters set forth in your previous post.</p>
<p>==============================</p>
<p>Concerning labeling issues as “resolved” even though they haven’t been, out of politeness, this sends the wrong message don’t you think? A person would be motivated to search out even more bugs, seeing that they are being fixed and that he’s/she’s making a contribution/difference. Maybe the better tact would be to label them as “won’t fix” with an explanation. This would also give reporters useful feedback as to what kinds of problems are most likely to be addressed and which ones won’t.</p>
<p>==============================</p>
<p>Let me show you some bugs that I’ve found, and you tell me if they fit within your “legitimate and fixable” category.</p>
<ol>
<li>Differences in track lighting <a href="https://i.imgur.com/IAX4ZP0.jpg" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://i.imgur.com/IAX4ZP0.jpg</a>
</li>
<li>Handrails with texture z-fighting issues <a href="https://i.imgur.com/hCjbE3O.jpg" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://i.imgur.com/hCjbE3O.jpg</a>
</li>
<li>Warning signs not illuminated by flashlight <a href="https://i.imgur.com/7cA4tbd.jpg" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://i.imgur.com/7cA4tbd.jpg</a>
</li>
<li>Warning sign partially obscured <a href="https://i.imgur.com/ZZYqtK2.jpg" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://i.imgur.com/ZZYqtK2.jpg</a>
</li>
<li>Cables from electrical boxes, non-terminating <a href="https://i.imgur.com/DWVkbY4.jpg" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://i.imgur.com/DWVkbY4.jpg</a>
</li>
<li>Missing sounds from working machinery, where elsewhere for same models, sounds were present <a href="https://i.imgur.com/bjB9YJE.jpg" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://i.imgur.com/bjB9YJE.jpg</a>
</li>
<li>Handrails aligned half off edge of stairs <a href="https://i.imgur.com/5kgH7fn.jpg" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://i.imgur.com/5kgH7fn.jpg</a>
</li>
<li>Odd death poses (also, arm clipping into handrail) <a href="https://i.imgur.com/CEQamy5.jpg" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://i.imgur.com/CEQamy5.jpg</a>. Gravity dictates this scientist should’ve fallen to the ground, as he’s more off the desk than on and his shadow is wrong (I know, engine related issue) <a href="https://i.imgur.com/zFnEXMT.jpg" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://i.imgur.com/zFnEXMT.jpg</a>
</li>
<li>Cable organizer not attached to ceiling (viewable from ground) <a href="https://i.imgur.com/VOncZot.jpg" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://i.imgur.com/VOncZot.jpg</a>
</li>
<li>Tunnel support frame missing whole rear concrete pad <a href="https://i.imgur.com/EfEC02v.jpg" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://i.imgur.com/EfEC02v.jpg</a>
</li>
<li>Rails with texture z-fighting issues <a href="https://i.imgur.com/oUcmvFY.jpg" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://i.imgur.com/oUcmvFY.jpg</a> and <a href="https://i.imgur.com/2BB0uVX.jpg" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://i.imgur.com/2BB0uVX.jpg</a>
</li>
<li>Lighting anomalies, such as these:<br>
a) Warning stripes and rails <a href="https://i.imgur.com/YT9V6bA.jpg" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://i.imgur.com/YT9V6bA.jpg</a> and <a href="https://i.imgur.com/3NLrHKV.jpg" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://i.imgur.com/3NLrHKV.jpg</a><br>
b) <a href="https://i.imgur.com/URBkuXz.jpg" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://i.imgur.com/URBkuXz.jpg</a> and <a href="https://i.imgur.com/hv6NOZe.jpg" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://i.imgur.com/hv6NOZe.jpg</a>
</li>
</ol>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/banned-from-viewing-or-reporting-bug-issues/12169/15">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/banned-from-viewing-or-reporting-bug-issues/12169/15</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2013 23:39:10 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12169-15</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/banned-from-viewing-or-reporting-bug-issues/12169.rss">Banned from viewing or reporting bug issues</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Banned from viewing or reporting bug issues</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[your-name-here]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>First, I want to thank you for your politely worded post. I’ve seen things like this go south very quickly. Because the links I pasted earlier had an expiration date, you’ll need to give me some time to go back and fix them. I will post new examples in this message instead for the time being.</p>
<p>I will now address your post.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Dadster">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/d/e495f1/40.png" class="avatar"> Dadster:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>It was never my intention that my bug<br>
reporting would result in being a burden to you and your team. I thought it best to report what I felt were basic, common-sense, immersion breaking flaws and let you decide which ones should be addressed.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>While I can get behind this reasoning, a large number of issues you posted were not issues that were seen easily by the naked eye. You went out of your way to find some of them. Here is a great example:</p>
<p><span alt="" class="broken-image" title="This image is broken"><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-unlink svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#unlink"></use></svg></span></p>
<p>You noclipped in order to view this (you are much higher than the tram). If you use cheats to view things at angles that aren’t normally visible, of course you will find issues like this. Normal players will not even notice issues like this (I certainly didn’t, and I have played Black Mesa for much longer than you have).</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Dadster">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/d/e495f1/40.png" class="avatar"> Dadster:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>It’s not a case of me trying to “show you up” or profess that “I’m better than you”.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I don’t know why you thought I or anyone else would feel that way. If we felt this way every time people reported a bug, we wouldn’t have even used a public tracker in the first place.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Dadster">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/d/e495f1/40.png" class="avatar"> Dadster:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>You need to know they exist, to fix what fits into your present realm or scheme, and to use the feedback going further in future endeavors.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>If our userbase consisted of people who played the game and looked at every single prop from every possible angle, then yes, you would be absolutely correct. However in reality, this is not the case and most people wouldn’t notice many of these issues. To us, they are just noise that we have to sort though (which is coincidentally why a bunch of your bugs were set to ‘RESOLVED’ / ‘WONTFIX’. Not trying to be rude, that’s why we did it.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Dadster">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/d/e495f1/40.png" class="avatar"> Dadster:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Going forward, I’ll certainly be mindful of your bug reporting outline in my future posts.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Not really much of an outline but more common sense. Just ask yourself before you report a bug whether or not it is appropriate to report.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Dadster">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/d/e495f1/40.png" class="avatar"> Dadster:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>To that end, please correct the issue of me not being able to view the exhibits you posted, so that I can fully understand your guidelines. A picture is worth a thousand words.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Unfortunately, not possible as those pictures were stored on the amazon cloud. I don’t have time right now to go back through the list of bugs to find the ones that I quoted. If you find them, feel free to PM me and I’ll post up the pictures again. For now, I will post some bugs below for you.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Dadster">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/d/e495f1/40.png" class="avatar"> Dadster:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Thank you, and I remain committed to assisting you in making BM as believable an environment as possible.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>This statement worries me because we <span class="bbcode-b">aren’t</span> trying to make BM as believable as possible. I am not entirely convinced you understand my reasons for closing the tracker down. Our number one goal is creating a fun experience. If we have to compromise in believability, we will. This is why we’re less interested in misplaced caution signs and electrical panels and more interested in issues you had with the jumping puzzles / level flow.</p>
<p>EDIT: Gathering up a list of bugs now…<br>
<div class="lightbox-wrapper"><a class="lightbox" href="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/original/2X/3/3b28a6a6281338d72085f93e5fc4af214604a067.jpeg" data-download-href="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/3b28a6a6281338d72085f93e5fc4af214604a067" title="bm_c2a2b0044.jpg"><img src="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/original/2X/3/3b28a6a6281338d72085f93e5fc4af214604a067.jpeg" alt="bm_c2a2b0044.jpg" data-base62-sha1="8rlgqUcSkRRLA1wIhGLvBpYtMOj" width="690" height="500" data-small-upload="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/optimized/2X/3/3b28a6a6281338d72085f93e5fc4af214604a067_2_10x10.png"><div class="meta"><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-far-image svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#far-image"></use></svg><span class="filename">bm_c2a2b0044.jpg</span><span class="informations">1253×940 77.9 KB</span><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-discourse-expand svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#discourse-expand"></use></svg></div></a></div></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/banned-from-viewing-or-reporting-bug-issues/12169/14">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/banned-from-viewing-or-reporting-bug-issues/12169/14</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2013 23:30:32 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12169-14</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/banned-from-viewing-or-reporting-bug-issues/12169.rss">Banned from viewing or reporting bug issues</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Banned from viewing or reporting bug issues</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Dadster]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="your-name-here">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/y/e480ec/40.png" class="avatar"> your-name-here:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>This problem aside, do you understand where I am coming from?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>It was never my intention that my bug reporting would result in being a burden to you and your team. I thought it best to report what I felt were basic, common-sense, immersion breaking flaws and let you decide which ones should be addressed. It’s not a case of me trying to “show you up” or profess that “I’m better than you”. You need to know they exist, to fix what fits into your present realm or scheme, and to use the feedback going further in future endeavors.</p>
<p>Going forward, I’ll certainly be mindful of your bug reporting outline in my future posts. To that end, please correct the issue of me not being able to view the exhibits you posted, so that I can fully understand your guidelines. A picture is worth a thousand words.</p>
<p>Thank you, and I remain committed to assisting you in making BM as believable an environment as possible.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/banned-from-viewing-or-reporting-bug-issues/12169/13">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/banned-from-viewing-or-reporting-bug-issues/12169/13</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2013 22:19:37 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12169-13</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/banned-from-viewing-or-reporting-bug-issues/12169.rss">Banned from viewing or reporting bug issues</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Banned from viewing or reporting bug issues</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[your-name-here]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Dadster">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/d/e495f1/40.png" class="avatar"> Dadster:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Thanks for your response.<br>
I can’t view any of your exhibits. I get the following error message:</p>
<p>This XML file does not appear to have any style information associated with it. The document tree is shown below.<br>
<code>AccessDenied</code>Request has expired1484625E2EC52ECD2013-03-06T11:36:52ZkUdnNwhtU+wl0NjQ+u3Baj4QTawEjmtnkBBhOE4lxvwgT8pEIBNoLxjg+ZAAo1vO2013-03-06T17:06:36Z</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>This problem aside, do you understand where I am coming from?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/banned-from-viewing-or-reporting-bug-issues/12169/12">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/banned-from-viewing-or-reporting-bug-issues/12169/12</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2013 19:11:03 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12169-12</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/banned-from-viewing-or-reporting-bug-issues/12169.rss">Banned from viewing or reporting bug issues</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Banned from viewing or reporting bug issues</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Flatline]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Dadster">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/d/e495f1/40.png" class="avatar"> Dadster:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Thanks for your response.<br>
I can’t view any of your exhibits. I get the following error message:</p>
<p>This XML file does not appear to have any style information associated with it. The document tree is shown below.<br>
<code>AccessDenied</code>Request has expired1484625E2EC52ECD2013-03-06T11:36:52ZkUdnNwhtU+wl0NjQ+u3Baj4QTawEjmtnkBBhOE4lxvwgT8pEIBNoLxjg+ZAAo1vO2013-03-06T17:06:36Z</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="your-name-here">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/y/e480ec/40.png" class="avatar"> your-name-here:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Whoops, <span class="bbcode-b">I guess the image links only last for a certain period of time before expiring</span>. The descriptions should be more than enough however.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/banned-from-viewing-or-reporting-bug-issues/12169/11">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/banned-from-viewing-or-reporting-bug-issues/12169/11</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2013 17:10:43 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12169-11</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/banned-from-viewing-or-reporting-bug-issues/12169.rss">Banned from viewing or reporting bug issues</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Banned from viewing or reporting bug issues</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Dadster]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="your-name-here">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/y/e480ec/40.png" class="avatar"> your-name-here:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Once you reply and we can talk, I’ll re-open the bug tracker for you  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=9" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Thanks for your response.<br>
I can’t view any of your exhibits. I get the following error message:</p>
<p>This XML file does not appear to have any style information associated with it. The document tree is shown below.<br>
<code>AccessDenied</code>Request has expired1484625E2EC52ECD2013-03-06T11:36:52ZkUdnNwhtU+wl0NjQ+u3Baj4QTawEjmtnkBBhOE4lxvwgT8pEIBNoLxjg+ZAAo1vO2013-03-06T17:06:36Z</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/banned-from-viewing-or-reporting-bug-issues/12169/10">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/banned-from-viewing-or-reporting-bug-issues/12169/10</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2013 17:07:20 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12169-10</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/banned-from-viewing-or-reporting-bug-issues/12169.rss">Banned from viewing or reporting bug issues</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Banned from viewing or reporting bug issues</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[your-name-here]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="ThunderDash">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 ThunderDash:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Even after getting official word on this, I feel like I should answer - I hadn’t actually used the bug reporter before I got the “Don’t have access” message. I tried accessing it anonymously, then registered for an account. Same result both times, hence why I figured it was just locked down for the time being.</p>
<p>Also, <a class="mention" href="/u/your-name-here">@your-name-here</a>; I’m getting an XML Access Denied error on all of your links. I’m not sure if that’s because they’re intended for Dadster, but figured I should mention that if that’s not the case.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Whoops, I guess the image links only last for a certain period of time before expiring. The descriptions should be more than enough however.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/banned-from-viewing-or-reporting-bug-issues/12169/9">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/banned-from-viewing-or-reporting-bug-issues/12169/9</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2013 16:38:13 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12169-9</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/banned-from-viewing-or-reporting-bug-issues/12169.rss">Banned from viewing or reporting bug issues</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Banned from viewing or reporting bug issues</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[KyuuGryphon]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Dadster">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/d/e495f1/40.png" class="avatar"> Dadster:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Yes, that’s the message I’m getting.</p>
<p>Are/were you submitting bugs anonymously, or are you a member at BitBucket? I hope your assumption is right.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Even after getting official word on this, I feel like I should answer - I hadn’t actually used the bug reporter before I got the “Don’t have access” message. I tried accessing it anonymously, then registered for an account. Same result both times, hence why I figured it was just locked down for the time being.</p>
<p>Also, <a class="mention" href="/u/your-name-here">@your-name-here</a>; I’m getting an XML Access Denied error on all of your links. I’m not sure if that’s because they’re intended for Dadster, but figured I should mention that if that’s not the case.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/banned-from-viewing-or-reporting-bug-issues/12169/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/banned-from-viewing-or-reporting-bug-issues/12169/8</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2013 16:05:10 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12169-8</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/banned-from-viewing-or-reporting-bug-issues/12169.rss">Banned from viewing or reporting bug issues</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Banned from viewing or reporting bug issues</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[your-name-here]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I should add that placing myself in your shoes, I can see how you thought these are fixable issues, but I replied to a huge number of bugs you were posting telling you that either you assigned them to the wrong category or that they just aren’t fixable. That should have set off some red flags and caused you to stop posting bugs and come here to ask about what we wanted people to look for, rather than ignoring our messages and continuing to post away.</p>
<p>The clipping issue that you mentioned is the following:</p>
<pre><code class="lang-auto">Player can clip through entire upper portion of the fallen antenna tower.</code></pre>
<p>I am pretty sure that John marked this as resolved for one of two reasons: A) We couldn’t fix it or B ) They just added a player_clip around the object in question. AFAIK, I didn’t see John post a resolution of what was done to fix it, so he’ll have to weigh in here.</p>
<p>Let me tell you about clipping issues we CAN fix:</p>
<p><a href="https://bitbucket-assetroot.s3.amazonaws.com/bmscd/black-mesa-source/1359692332.93/342/bm_c1a3c0008.jpg?Signature=cx59VYTyvBhJm4I%2B7zRD9pj3ugA%3D&amp;Expires=1362569812&amp;AWSAccessKeyId=0EMWEFSGA12Z1HF1TZ82" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Exhibit A</a><br>
<a href="https://bitbucket-assetroot.s3.amazonaws.com/bmscd/black-mesa-source/1362372376.93/382/bm_c2a2a0521.jpg?Signature=VFK1%2FFS3e6sTT%2B63nKiSKhD5N0s%3D&amp;Expires=1362570124&amp;AWSAccessKeyId=0EMWEFSGA12Z1HF1TZ82" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Exhibit B</a></p>
<p>Any <span class="bbcode-b">static</span> props that are placed inside geometry like that ARE bugs and we can fix those. Let me repeat, this only applies to <span class="bbcode-b">STATIC</span> props, meaning props that you can’t push around and can only be moved by a level designer.</p>
<p>Let’s talk about what we CAN’T fix:</p>
<p><a href="https://bitbucket-assetroot.s3.amazonaws.com/bmscd/black-mesa-source/1362432942.72/415/bm_c2a2b0006.jpg?Signature=1MCf6U8aWGGz0o7q6T0fOkNeSWo%3D&amp;Expires=1362570257&amp;AWSAccessKeyId=0EMWEFSGA12Z1HF1TZ82" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Exhibit A</a></p>
<p>The above is a weapon attached to an NPC. Objects attached to NPCs don’t run physics unless the object is dropped. We cannot fix this.</p>
<p><a href="https://bitbucket-assetroot.s3.amazonaws.com/bmscd/black-mesa-source/1359704591.3/343/bm_c1a4a0000.jpg?Signature=9ef2S3%2Bf3V6N4Fxa7aX7EeoIwpU%3D&amp;Expires=1362570376&amp;AWSAccessKeyId=0EMWEFSGA12Z1HF1TZ82" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Exhibit B</a></p>
<p>So I don’t know how that medkit got into that position. If you found it like that, then it is a bug and we need to have a level designer fix it by rotating it. If you put it in that position yourself, then it is not a bug we can fix. In games, we can’t build super-fine collision models around objects because simulating physics on those would take up a lot of processing power. The area of collision around the medkit is probably a simple box around the entire thing. You can view these by doing</p>
<pre><code class="lang-auto">vcollide_wireframe 1</code></pre>
<p>in your console.</p>
<p><a href="https://bitbucket-assetroot.s3.amazonaws.com/bmscd/black-mesa-source/1360558514.26/362/bm_c2a2c0010.jpg?Signature=yBOVsRSorFlHB68hTEVuxxtiIO8%3D&amp;Expires=1362570852&amp;AWSAccessKeyId=0EMWEFSGA12Z1HF1TZ82" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Exhibit C</a></p>
<p>Doubt we can fix this either.</p>
<p><a href="https://bitbucket-assetroot.s3.amazonaws.com/bmscd/black-mesa-source/1359525245.93/327/bm_c1a1b0002.jpg?Signature=JG5GB%2F0dm3KZwSUtBdl0Na6hRxo%3D&amp;Expires=1362571004&amp;AWSAccessKeyId=0EMWEFSGA12Z1HF1TZ82" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Exhibit D</a></p>
<p>Another one we can’t fix. A physics_prop clipping into a static prop will always result in minor clipping issues. This is normal. I will talk to an artist about the model on model collision issues you have posted to make sure I’ve given you the right information about model clipping, but I am inclined to say they will agree.</p>
<p>You also posted the following bug:<br>
<a href="https://bitbucket.org/bmscd/black-mesa-source/issue/419/door-switch-in-precarious-position" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Picture</a></p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Dadster">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/d/e495f1/40.png" class="avatar"> Dadster:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>In a real world setting, this door control switch is located too close to the platform’s edge, making it dangerous to operate, from a safety perspective. There may be other affected switches in the area.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I thought someone was trying to fuck with us after seeing this + the 30 other emails for bug reports, so please forgive me if I seem irate. As I said in one of the posts here / on the tracker, bugs like the one just above are not helpful, and it slows us down from reviewing the real issues (such as crashing, broken entities, etc).</p>
<p>Here is another one:<br>
<a href="https://bitbucket-assetroot.s3.amazonaws.com/bmscd/black-mesa-source/1362381783.71/399/bm_c2a2a0596.jpg?Signature=ONz9hXJmJZM1jVT4YNH5fk4uTIs%3D&amp;Expires=1362573383&amp;AWSAccessKeyId=0EMWEFSGA12Z1HF1TZ82" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Picture</a></p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Dadster">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/d/e495f1/40.png" class="avatar"> Dadster:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Real-world scenario, these three electrical panels are nearly impossible to reach, especially the two on the right.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>To your credit, you marked this next one as an enhancement, not as a bug. I can get behind this one as something we should consider:<br>
<a href="https://bitbucket-assetroot.s3.amazonaws.com/bmscd/black-mesa-source/1362372562.55/383/bm_c2a2a0522.jpg?Signature=BCeB9duBo93f8kjTromPGwEHR4c%3D&amp;Expires=1362573470&amp;AWSAccessKeyId=0EMWEFSGA12Z1HF1TZ82" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Picture</a></p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Dadster">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/d/e495f1/40.png" class="avatar"> Dadster:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Center this light vertically above the door.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>This next one I wasn’t clear on from the description; It was marked as an enhancement:<br>
<a href="https://bitbucket-assetroot.s3.amazonaws.com/bmscd/black-mesa-source/1362379396.93/395/bm_c2a2a0591.jpg?Signature=QATrWZjaPYyZpTBZ74tq4YsCuf8%3D&amp;Expires=1362573735&amp;AWSAccessKeyId=0EMWEFSGA12Z1HF1TZ82" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Picture</a></p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Dadster">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/d/e495f1/40.png" class="avatar"> Dadster:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>The shadows projected from these skidded objects reflect the light source that’s farther away, rather than the light source nearby.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>My gut tells me we can’t fix this either.</p>
<p>A bunch of issues that were posted revolved around realism and such. The issue with video games is, we can’t make them perfect. You’d be shocked at how much trickery goes on to give you an in-game experience. We have to resort to that in some places because otherwise we wouldn’t be able to get the game to run at a decent framerate. Sometimes we have to compromise for less than perfect due to time constraints or technical reasons.</p>
<p>To close, we do appreciate and recognize that you took the time to comb over our work with a fine toothed comb. All I ask is that you read what I wrote above and keep that in mind as you report bugs. We ask that you don’t approach issue finding from a ‘real-world’ perspective but from a gameplay / mistake perspective (mistake meaning misplaced map elements and the like, as shown above). We at a stage right now where we want to fix major, gameplay affecting issues first. When we get those resolved, we’ll do a polish pass.</p>
<p>Once you reply and we can talk, I’ll re-open the bug tracker for you  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=9" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/banned-from-viewing-or-reporting-bug-issues/12169/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/banned-from-viewing-or-reporting-bug-issues/12169/7</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2013 11:02:19 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12169-7</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/banned-from-viewing-or-reporting-bug-issues/12169.rss">Banned from viewing or reporting bug issues</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
