<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>PCI Wireless card problems</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/pci-wireless-card-problems/1816</link>
    <description>Hi all.

I recently got a D-Link DWA-552 PCI adapter, along with a DIR-655 router. Both run on 802.11 Draft N. It worked perfectly for a week. Then, I put Windows 7 on my computer. They continued to work perfectly. After deciding that Windows 7 didn&#39;t work smoothly enough, I formatted and reinstalled XP.

The card / router combo still worked fine. However, I noticed that whenever I downloaded anything, the download would pause. It would show a speed, and time remaining, but it would just freeze. I had to pause and restart the download multiple times to get it to finish with Firefox.

I did not like this at all, so since the format was fresh, I did it again. This time, I removed the card before formatting so I could put it into a virgin OS like I did the first time. Except this time, when I installed the card, it would not detect any SSID&#39;s. I put the router in the same room, and the card would still not detect it. I tried reinstalling the drivers several times, and formatted several times and reinstalled XP but it still wouldn&#39;t work. Then, I took the card out and reseated it. Now, when I start the PC, it isn&#39;t detected at all. I can&#39;t install drivers, it says I haven&#39;t physically installed the card. I have reseated it several times, but it just won&#39;t get detected. I have not tried switching PCI slots yet, as they are currently all full, and I&#39;m afraid of fudging up another card. It doesn&#39;t appear in the hardware manager either.

I&#39;m wondering if maybe it has something to do with the BIOS, or something like that. Any thoughts?

Edit: Nevermind. I took the card out again, and removed the screws and the bracket that normally screws to the case of the computer. I guess it was preventing the card from seating in the slot properly... I&#39;m not sure what I&#39;m gonna do now. I don&#39;t want to just leave the card flopping around in there... Anyways, this thread can probably be deleted now.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 13 Nov 2009 22:30:18 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Help and Support</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/pci-wireless-card-problems/1816.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>PCI Wireless card problems</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[coldroll]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>My wireless card died 2 years ago since than I use wire because it’s faster.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/pci-wireless-card-problems/1816/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/pci-wireless-card-problems/1816/5</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 13 Nov 2009 22:30:18 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-1816-5</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/pci-wireless-card-problems/1816.rss">PCI Wireless card problems</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>PCI Wireless card problems</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[sersoft]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>You don’t need a 100mbit connection on a WAN port. Your internet speed will rarely exceed 8mbps.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/pci-wireless-card-problems/1816/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/pci-wireless-card-problems/1816/4</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 13 Nov 2009 21:27:12 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-1816-4</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/pci-wireless-card-problems/1816.rss">PCI Wireless card problems</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>PCI Wireless card problems</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[sudpuzzer]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>True. I ended up just taking a screw out of the corner of my mobo, so it could flex forward a bit and allow the card to seat in the slot properly. Who knows how long that’ll last.  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/smiley.png?v=9" title=":smiley:" class="emoji" alt=":smiley:"></p>
<p>But now I have a new problem. My stupid router won’t get an IP address from my ISP unless the WAN port speed is set on 10mbps, and it should be 100mbps. It won’t connect on 100mbps. My old router connects just fine at 100mbps, but this new one won’t. So my internet is 10 times slower than it should be. Even though my wifi card is connected to the router at 300mbps.  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=9" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:">  So right now I have the old router set up again, and I’m only connected to it at 54mbps :’(</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/pci-wireless-card-problems/1816/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/pci-wireless-card-problems/1816/3</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 13 Nov 2009 05:33:21 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-1816-3</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/pci-wireless-card-problems/1816.rss">PCI Wireless card problems</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>PCI Wireless card problems</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[sersoft]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>lol Brain fart</p>
<p>Anyway it’s not rare that a wifi card dies, I lost 4 different wifi cards due to random static shocks.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/pci-wireless-card-problems/1816/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/pci-wireless-card-problems/1816/2</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 13 Nov 2009 04:06:42 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-1816-2</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/pci-wireless-card-problems/1816.rss">PCI Wireless card problems</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>PCI Wireless card problems</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[sudpuzzer]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Hi all.</p>
<p>I recently got a D-Link DWA-552 PCI adapter, along with a DIR-655 router. Both run on 802.11 Draft N. It worked perfectly for a week. Then, I put Windows 7 on my computer. They continued to work perfectly. After deciding that Windows 7 didn’t work smoothly enough, I formatted and reinstalled XP.</p>
<p>The card / router combo still worked fine. However, I noticed that whenever I downloaded anything, the download would pause. It would show a speed, and time remaining, but it would just freeze. I had to pause and restart the download multiple times to get it to finish with Firefox.</p>
<p>I did not like this at all, so since the format was fresh, I did it again. This time, I removed the card before formatting so I could put it into a virgin OS like I did the first time. Except this time, when I installed the card, it would not detect any SSID’s. I put the router in the same room, and the card would still not detect it. I tried reinstalling the drivers several times, and formatted several times and reinstalled XP but it still wouldn’t work. Then, I took the card out and reseated it. Now, when I start the PC, it isn’t detected at all. I can’t install drivers, it says I haven’t physically installed the card. I have reseated it several times, but it just won’t get detected. I have not tried switching PCI slots yet, as they are currently all full, and I’m afraid of fudging up another card. It doesn’t appear in the hardware manager either.</p>
<p>I’m wondering if maybe it has something to do with the BIOS, or something like that. Any thoughts?</p>
<p>Edit: Nevermind. I took the card out again, and removed the screws and the bracket that normally screws to the case of the computer. I guess it was preventing the card from seating in the slot properly… I’m not sure what I’m gonna do now. I don’t want to just leave the card flopping around in there… Anyways, this thread can probably be deleted now.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/pci-wireless-card-problems/1816/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/pci-wireless-card-problems/1816/1</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 13 Nov 2009 01:42:30 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-1816-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/pci-wireless-card-problems/1816.rss">PCI Wireless card problems</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
