<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>&quot;Crate Smashing Room&quot; in UC - Purple Hat issue</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/crate-smashing-room-in-uc-purple-hat-issue/14568</link>
    <description>I&#39;m having issues with the &quot;[url=&#39;https://youtu.be/kj4BpDyhFuE?t=160&#39;]crate smashing room[/url]&quot; in Unforeseen Consequences.  Beyond it being the most difficult part in the game for me (it was in the original HL too), the issue I&#39;m having is with the purple hat.

If you&#39;re holding the hat while quicksaving on the slowly swinging crates (I do a lot of quicksaving in this part), Gordon will drop the hat, invariably falling off the crates and down into the canals of death.

Gordon will apparently not drop the hat while standing on anything else, but I haven&#39;t gotten far enough to check to see if it&#39;ll happen on elevators that actually move.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 05 Jan 2016 17:30:20 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>In-game Issues</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/crate-smashing-room-in-uc-purple-hat-issue/14568.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>&quot;Crate Smashing Room&quot; in UC - Purple Hat issue</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[danielsangeo]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I’m having issues with the “<a href="https://youtu.be/kj4BpDyhFuE?t=160" data-bbcode="true">crate smashing room</a>” in Unforeseen Consequences.  Beyond it being the most difficult part in the game for me (it was in the original HL too), the issue I’m having is with the purple hat.</p>
<p>If you’re holding the hat while quicksaving on the slowly swinging crates (I do a lot of quicksaving in this part), Gordon will drop the hat, invariably falling off the crates and down into the canals of death.</p>
<p>Gordon will apparently not drop the hat while standing on anything else, but I haven’t gotten far enough to check to see if it’ll happen on elevators that actually move.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/crate-smashing-room-in-uc-purple-hat-issue/14568/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/crate-smashing-room-in-uc-purple-hat-issue/14568/1</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 05 Jan 2016 17:30:20 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14568-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/crate-smashing-room-in-uc-purple-hat-issue/14568.rss">&quot;Crate Smashing Room&quot; in UC - Purple Hat issue</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
