<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Monitor Recommendations</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/monitor-recommendations/63147</link>
    <description>I&#39;m thinking about buying a new monitor. The main use is gaming. I currently have an ASUS ROG Swift PG278Q. It&#39;s great, and there&#39;s nothing wrong with it, but it&#39;s a TN panel, and I hear the siren call of IPS/VA panel monitors. I have a 2014 Retina MacBook Pro, which I understand has an IPS panel monitor, and the colors really are a lot better than my Swift.

However, last time I bought a monitor, I tried out several IPS monitors first, and they all had this horrible &quot;IPS glow&quot; problem that&#39;s a dealbreaker for me:

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=lg0DlTbB0Vw

Have current-gen IPS monitors moved past this, or are they still all bad? Do curved IPS monitors have less of a problem with this in anyone&#39;s experience?

How about VA panels? I hear they have great contrast and that their colors are better than TN (but not as good as IPS), but that they have bad ghosting and smear problems, especially in darker scenes. They&#39;re really hard to find, too. Not many manufacturers are making VA panel monitors.

Here are my other requirements:

* 1440p
* 144Hz
* 27&quot;
* G-Sync

That narrows the field a lot. There are a few IPS monitors available with those specs, but no VA panel monitors that I could find. Anyone have recommendations?</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 08 Apr 2020 03:22:09 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Technology and Gaming</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/monitor-recommendations/63147.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Monitor Recommendations</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[geekofalltrades]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I’m thinking about buying a new monitor. The main use is gaming. I currently have an ASUS ROG Swift PG278Q. It’s great, and there’s nothing wrong with it, but it’s a TN panel, and I hear the siren call of IPS/VA panel monitors. I have a 2014 Retina MacBook Pro, which I understand has an IPS panel monitor, and the colors really are a lot better than my Swift.</p>
<p>However, last time I bought a monitor, I tried out several IPS monitors first, and they all had this horrible “IPS glow” problem that’s a dealbreaker for me:</p>
<p><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=lg0DlTbB0Vw" class="onebox" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=lg0DlTbB0Vw</a></p>
<p>Have current-gen IPS monitors moved past this, or are they still all bad? Do curved IPS monitors have less of a problem with this in anyone’s experience?</p>
<p>How about VA panels? I hear they have great contrast and that their colors are better than TN (but not as good as IPS), but that they have bad ghosting and smear problems, especially in darker scenes. They’re really hard to find, too. Not many manufacturers are making VA panel monitors.</p>
<p>Here are my other requirements:</p>
<ul>
<li>1440p</li>
<li>144Hz</li>
<li>27"</li>
<li>G-Sync</li>
</ul>
<p>That narrows the field a lot. There are a few IPS monitors available with those specs, but no VA panel monitors that I could find. Anyone have recommendations?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/monitor-recommendations/63147/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/monitor-recommendations/63147/1</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 08 Apr 2020 03:22:09 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-63147-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/monitor-recommendations/63147.rss">Monitor Recommendations</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
