<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Movement key + Reload key &#39;fires&#39; weapon</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/movement-key-reload-key-fires-weapon/10252</link>
    <description>First off massive congrats on the release, I&#39;m thoroughly enjoying it so far.

[u][b]Issue:[/b][/u]
[COLOR=&#39;SlateGray&#39;]I&#39;m however running into an issue with combinations of the movement (WASD) keys and the reload key; it causes my waepon to fire and offten keep firing until the magazine is spent (this is also the case for the crowbar, it just keeps swinging until you press the actual fire key).
Many a time I have offed a scientist by accident or given away my position to the soldiers because of this, which is a bit frustrating.

[u][b]Reproduction:[/b][/u]
[COLOR=&#39;SlateGray&#39;]Press the forward (W) or backward (S) key while pressing reload in quick combination/succession and the weapon will fire without pressing the fire key.
Wierdly, doing it again with the same movement key won&#39;t work... however if you do it next with the key for the [u]opposite[/u] direction the weapon will once again fire without pressing the fire key.


[COLOR=&#39;SlateGray&#39;]I have searched the forum and haven&#39;t seen anyone with a similar problem which might indicate that it is only local to me... possibly my Razer mouse Synapse 2.0, though I havent had issues in other programs that I can recall.

I&#39;m going to try it out in Base HL2 and see if it&#39;s present there, but if there is anyone else experiencing this could you sound off? Thanks.

E</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 16 Sep 2012 12:58:23 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>In-game Issues (Mod)</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/movement-key-reload-key-fires-weapon/10252.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Movement key + Reload key &#39;fires&#39; weapon</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Electricleash]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>First off massive congrats on the release, I’m thoroughly enjoying it so far.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-u"><span class="bbcode-b">Issue:</span></span><br>
[COLOR=‘SlateGray’]I’m however running into an issue with combinations of the movement (WASD) keys and the reload key; it causes my waepon to fire and offten keep firing until the magazine is spent (this is also the case for the crowbar, it just keeps swinging until you press the actual fire key).<br>
Many a time I have offed a scientist by accident or given away my position to the soldiers because of this, which is a bit frustrating.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-u"><span class="bbcode-b">Reproduction:</span></span><br>
[COLOR=‘SlateGray’]Press the forward (W) or backward (S) key while pressing reload in quick combination/succession and the weapon will fire without pressing the fire key.<br>
Wierdly, doing it again with the same movement key won’t work… however if you do it next with the key for the <span class="bbcode-u">opposite</span> direction the weapon will once again fire without pressing the fire key.</p>
<p>[COLOR=‘SlateGray’]I have searched the forum and haven’t seen anyone with a similar problem which might indicate that it is only local to me… possibly my Razer mouse Synapse 2.0, though I havent had issues in other programs that I can recall.</p>
<p>I’m going to try it out in Base HL2 and see if it’s present there, but if there is anyone else experiencing this could you sound off? Thanks.</p>
<p>E</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/movement-key-reload-key-fires-weapon/10252/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/movement-key-reload-key-fires-weapon/10252/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 16 Sep 2012 12:58:23 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-10252-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/movement-key-reload-key-fires-weapon/10252.rss">Movement key + Reload key &#39;fires&#39; weapon</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
