<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>GORDON DID IT</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/gordon-did-it/4145</link>
    <description>my theory is:

Gordon [i]sabotaged[/i] the experiment; he was already working for the Gman.
[u]
there are hints [b]everywhere[/b]:[/u]
-you &quot;wake up&quot; on the tram at the start of both HL2 and HL1.
-gordon was late, the plan was already in effect.
-equipment malfunctions prior to experiment
-in DECAY, Rosenburg says the AMS was sabotaged. gman&#39;s crystal, your hev suit.
-Gman is [i]always[/i] watching you, even prior to the resonance cascade.
-gordon (You) cant talk or write for [i]some[/i] reason (lolol hypnosis)
-some of Gman&#39;s dialogue seems to allude to it.
-you have an almost messianic reputation prior to HL2, which i doubt was generated by the surviving science team alone; it all fits with Gman&#39;s plan.
-even more shit

i could go on, but yeah. We know Gman used you to kill the Nihilanth and the combine. why? no clue.

i realize others may have come to this conclusion as well. It&#39;s just a [b]theory[/b], but a perfectly logical one.

so yeah, get out your tinfoil hats and go crazy</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 29 May 2010 22:55:34 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Half-Life Series</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/gordon-did-it/4145.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>GORDON DID IT</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypt]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Ballsopt">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/b/85e7bf/40.png" class="avatar"> Ballsopt:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>my theory is:</p>
<p>Gordon <span class="bbcode-i">sabotaged</span> the experiment; he was already working for the Gman.<br>
<span class="bbcode-u"><br>
there are hints <span class="bbcode-b">everywhere</span>:</span><br>
-you “wake up” on the tram at the start of both HL2 and HL1.<br>
-gordon was late, the plan was already in effect.<br>
-equipment malfunctions prior to experiment<br>
-in DECAY, Rosenburg says the AMS was sabotaged. gman’s crystal, your hev suit.<br>
-Gman is <span class="bbcode-i">always</span> watching you, even prior to the resonance cascade.<br>
-gordon (You) cant talk or write for <span class="bbcode-i">some</span> reason (lolol hypnosis)<br>
-some of Gman’s dialogue seems to allude to it.<br>
-you have an almost messianic reputation prior to HL2, which i doubt was generated by the surviving science team alone; it all fits with Gman’s plan.<br>
-even more shit</p>
<p>i could go on, but yeah. We know Gman used you to kill the Nihilanth and the combine. why? no clue.</p>
<p>i realize others may have come to this conclusion as well. It’s just a <span class="bbcode-b">theory</span>, but a perfectly logical one.</p>
<p>so yeah, get out your tinfoil hats and go crazy</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I like the theory, but you’re wrong on some parts, or these can be explained:</p>
<ol>
<li>
<p>You don’t “wake up” in Half-Life, in 2, yes, but in 1, the game just starts inn the tram.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Gordon (apparently at least) was late due to H.E.V. Training I believe.</p>
</li>
</ol>
<p>3.Although some sabotaging would probably explain the equipment malfunctions, it could also be because the place is so damn old, or just a coincidence. I say the sabotaging is most likely though.</p>
<ol start="4">
<li>
<p>I can’t say much about Decay, because I’ve only played it once on the PS2, and that was damn near a decade ago.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Yes, he was always watching Gordon, but that could mean he was making sure his “plan” goes according to plan, and he can change the outcome if Gordon does something that “G-Man” doesn’t want (The end of Half-Life 2 for example). He was also watching Adrian Shephard, Probably for similar reasons.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>How many games similar to Half-Life do you write? Gordon never really needs to, or has the opportunity to write anything, whatever it could be. And the talking, is probably not 100% part of the storyline, and merely a way for the player to feel as though he is Gordon.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>That’s probably just making sure nobody knows too much of what’s going on, but they know that some grim shit’s about to go down.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Although it is very strange that Gordon’s reputation is so great, and that you have a point that a few scientists could have spread so much, remember who the most important surviving Scientists are? Eli Vance, and Isaac Kleiner, who survived, know Gordon Freeman, and lead the uprising, could have told tons of tales about Mr. Freeman, and them ranking so high, could be why so many believe it. Although it is unusually why they assume he knows so much about combat. I don’t think many lived to see that, and survive.<br>
I don’t mean to try and say “Oh, this theory is stupid!It doesn’t make sense!” because I actually like your theory, I just think alot of aspects to it could be explained.</p>
</li>
</ol>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/gordon-did-it/4145/114">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/gordon-did-it/4145/114</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 29 May 2010 22:55:34 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-4145-114</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/gordon-did-it/4145.rss">GORDON DID IT</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>GORDON DID IT</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Gemereksi]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="therandus">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/t/53a042/40.png" class="avatar"> therandus:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>How does the g-man watch gordon through his eyes? When did that lnk develope? If he knew that gordon was the man who was conducting the experiment it seems perfectly logical that he would get to him before hand and start some ‘control’ over him. Its almost as if the g-man posesses him.</p>
<p>.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>What I said here wasn’t mean to be a theory or somehing…I didn’t want to say that the G-man controls Freeman.<br>
I was just trying to explain that this speech from the vortigaunt wasn’t to be interpreted “to the first level”,  and that it was probably a part of Valve’s irony: the “entity behind Gordon’s eyes” could be the G-man (getting a look, not controling, what Gordon do) or even just THE PLAYER HIMSELF. This speech is probably a reference to these two. And probably more to the second one.<br>
In other words, I just wanted to say that this speech can’t be easily used to extract informations about the storyline.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/gordon-did-it/4145/113">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/gordon-did-it/4145/113</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 23 May 2010 13:29:16 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-4145-113</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/gordon-did-it/4145.rss">GORDON DID IT</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>GORDON DID IT</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[DeleteThis]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>This comic will explain everything<br>
<div class="lightbox-wrapper"><a class="lightbox" href="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/original/1X/17aa3be762bcf05824b753972769b511c704aa28.jpeg" data-download-href="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/17aa3be762bcf05824b753972769b511c704aa28" title="derp.jpg"><img src="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/original/1X/17aa3be762bcf05824b753972769b511c704aa28.jpeg" alt="derp.jpg" data-base62-sha1="3nlHNIraE8IMT9Gsvf23p4dZCTm" width="690" height="500" data-small-upload="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/optimized/1X/17aa3be762bcf05824b753972769b511c704aa28_2_10x10.png"><div class="meta"><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-far-image svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#far-image"></use></svg><span class="filename">derp.jpg</span><span class="informations">1199×866 81.7 KB</span><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-discourse-expand svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#discourse-expand"></use></svg></div></a></div></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/gordon-did-it/4145/112">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/gordon-did-it/4145/112</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 23 May 2010 10:40:37 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-4145-112</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/gordon-did-it/4145.rss">GORDON DID IT</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>GORDON DID IT</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[DeleteThis]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="SkyNinja">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/s/9fc348/40.png" class="avatar"> SkyNinja:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>If Freeman gave him the cheese, how did Frohman manage to mix it up? More importantly, when did he even get close enough to do it? Wasn’t GINA on Xen sample duty?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Because Frohman is a moron, He must’ve been the one who gave Gina the sample, and Gina can’t tell the difference between cheese and dangerous extradimensional crystals</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/gordon-did-it/4145/111">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/gordon-did-it/4145/111</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 23 May 2010 09:17:39 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-4145-111</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/gordon-did-it/4145.rss">GORDON DID IT</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>GORDON DID IT</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[therandus]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Gemereksi">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/g/d6d6ee/40.png" class="avatar"> Gemereksi:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>It would be interesting (and cool)…And, at the first look, it looks like a logical theory…</p>
<p>BUT, if this is the case, then why the G-Man makes such a proposition to Gordon at the end of HL 1 (if he was already working for him?!) ? Indeed, when he talks to Gordon at this very moment, it looks like he is meeting him for the first time.</p>
<p>So I don’t think Gordon was working for the G-man for all the time, even if it looks obvious that he has been used.</p>
<p>And for the vortigaunt’s speech in HL2 (Gordon’s multiple faces and dark aspect), if think he is just refering to the fact that “the G-man is watching through Gordon’s eyes”.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Actually he may of made the proposition at the end because he may have needed too. Either way the G-man was going to make gordon work for him. he wanted him to feel like he had a choice. The reason for this (if he was controlling him) might be that gordon can break free of his control but making gordon seem like he has a choice which doesnt make it seem likes hes controlled. An example of breaking free is with the vorigant help in ep2.</p>
<p>How does the g-man watch gordon through his eyes? When did that lnk develope? If he knew that gordon was the man who was conducting the experiment it seems perfectly logical that he would get to him before hand and start some ‘control’ over him. Its almost as if the g-man posesses him.</p>
<p>The first time the G-man was actually unsettled or angry was in ep2 while at the end of half life 1 he was talking as if he already knew what was goign to happen because he knew he had control over him no matter what he did. Either way you look at this theory there can be reasons on both side. But when some ‘Control’ abilty is involved and people dont know it then anything can be a theory. Also i doubt that gordon is ‘the Bad Guy’ but more of an innocent puppet. because valves approach is that gordon is the player and they would never make the player the bad guy beacuse that doesnt make them feel good. if there the ‘Good Guy’ then it makes them happy to play that character  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=9" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"> .</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/gordon-did-it/4145/110">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/gordon-did-it/4145/110</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 23 May 2010 08:21:31 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-4145-110</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/gordon-did-it/4145.rss">GORDON DID IT</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>GORDON DID IT</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[SkyNinja]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Ballsopt">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/b/85e7bf/40.png" class="avatar"> Ballsopt:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I didn’t say Gordon is evil…why is everyone suddenly debating whether gordon is or is not evil? That’s just stupid.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I said Gordon was evil, but you said no…<br>
ANYWAY…<br>
If Freeman gave him the cheese, how did Frohman manage to mix it up? More importantly, when did he even get close enough to do it? Wasn’t GINA on Xen sample duty?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/gordon-did-it/4145/109">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/gordon-did-it/4145/109</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 23 May 2010 06:02:12 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-4145-109</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/gordon-did-it/4145.rss">GORDON DID IT</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>GORDON DID IT</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[DeleteThis]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Gordon Frohman is a moron, maybe Freeman was the one who gave him the cheese :fffuuu:</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/gordon-did-it/4145/108">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/gordon-did-it/4145/108</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 21 May 2010 04:58:55 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-4145-108</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/gordon-did-it/4145.rss">GORDON DID IT</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>GORDON DID IT</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Eion_Kilant_739]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>It was Gordon Fr<span class="bbcode-i">ohman</span> and his cheeze! Not Gordon Fr<span class="bbcode-i">eeman</span>.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/gordon-did-it/4145/107">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/gordon-did-it/4145/107</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 20 May 2010 03:38:20 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-4145-107</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/gordon-did-it/4145.rss">GORDON DID IT</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>GORDON DID IT</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Ballsopt]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Jonny Nibbz">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Jonny Nibbz:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I was really under the influence that GLaDOS’s comment, “The world outside has changed. I may be the only thing between us and them.” really seemed to have implied that the RC had occurred, and she was defending Aperture from the Combine. I also was not saying that her comment implied that Portal 2 took place centuries later. <span class="bbcode-b">Now, to get back on topic…</span></p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>EENH! wrong; my thread. im not done dissecting you.<br>
that GLaDOS comment has been discussed to death, so i don’t know why you’re even bringing it up, or adding the RC to it.<br>
where did i say anything about you saying anything about centuries later? i’m just drawing from the Portal 2 podcasts, and the other info released in conjunction.</p>
<p>/pointless derail</p>
<p>I didn’t say Gordon is evil…why is everyone suddenly debating whether gordon is or is not evil? That’s just stupid.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/gordon-did-it/4145/106">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/gordon-did-it/4145/106</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 20 May 2010 00:41:41 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-4145-106</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/gordon-did-it/4145.rss">GORDON DID IT</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>GORDON DID IT</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Jonny_Nibbz]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I was really under the influence that GLaDOS’s comment, “The world outside has changed. I may be the only thing between us and them.” really seemed to have implied that the RC had occurred, and she was defending Aperture from the Combine. I also was not saying that her comment implied that Portal 2 took place centuries later. Now, to get back on topic…</p>
<p>Maybe Gordon always was the bad person, but since we only play from a first-person view with limited knowledge about ourselves, we could be playing the constant enemy. Not only do we disregard the constant technical difficulties within Black Mesa, but in perspective, perhaps Earth was originally a Combine planet? Perhaps the Combine were attempting to retrieve their lost planet from humanity. Then that would give Gordon the extra-evil card. Perhaps that thermos in his locker was orange juice, for drinking directly after brushing his teeth…</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/gordon-did-it/4145/105">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/gordon-did-it/4145/105</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 20 May 2010 00:31:55 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-4145-105</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/gordon-did-it/4145.rss">GORDON DID IT</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>GORDON DID IT</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Ballsopt]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>None of those things implied any of those things, although the Portal 2 info released has suggested that portal 1 takes place after the events of HL2, and Portal 2 takes place centuries after Portal 1.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/gordon-did-it/4145/104">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/gordon-did-it/4145/104</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 19 May 2010 22:20:38 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-4145-104</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/gordon-did-it/4145.rss">GORDON DID IT</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>GORDON DID IT</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Jonny_Nibbz]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I would vote something about a mishap between “7 Hour War” and “Portal 1.” But I would like to explain that the reason I said “7 Hour War” was because GLaDOS’s comment implies that Chell was testing awhile after the Resonance Cascade. Considering the comment, coupled with GLaDOS’s omniscience, it implied that not only would Portal 2 occur 100 years after Portal 1, but the 7 Hour War as well. That’s my excuse.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/gordon-did-it/4145/103">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/gordon-did-it/4145/103</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 18 May 2010 21:31:35 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-4145-103</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/gordon-did-it/4145.rss">GORDON DID IT</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>GORDON DID IT</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[bipolarmike]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="bipolarmike">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/b/e99b99/40.png" class="avatar"> bipolarmike:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>…porpoise.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="rorriMAesU">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/r/bc79bd/40.png" class="avatar"> rorriMAesU:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>:what:</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Don’t worry, that was on porpoise.<br>
That was on porpoise too.<br>
And that was one was also on porpoise.<br>
And that one as well.</p>
<p>(Gordon and I share a love of riding porpoises)</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/gordon-did-it/4145/102">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/gordon-did-it/4145/102</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 18 May 2010 08:05:26 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-4145-102</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/gordon-did-it/4145.rss">GORDON DID IT</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>GORDON DID IT</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Ballsopt]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>something about him not understanding the 7 hour war?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/gordon-did-it/4145/101">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/gordon-did-it/4145/101</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 18 May 2010 06:56:11 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-4145-101</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/gordon-did-it/4145.rss">GORDON DID IT</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>GORDON DID IT</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Soup]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I’m not even sure what you’re facepalming about.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/gordon-did-it/4145/100">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/gordon-did-it/4145/100</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 17 May 2010 23:59:25 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-4145-100</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/gordon-did-it/4145.rss">GORDON DID IT</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>GORDON DID IT</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Pyroclase]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Jonny Nibbz">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Jonny Nibbz:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I saw an error with the “Gordon + Chell + Robots v Combine” theory. Chell is still in stasis for around 100 years after Portal 1, and I know GLaDOS makes a comment about her being the only thing in between you and what was outside, but 100 years after the 7 Hour War, it’s likely that Gordon will have done his thing and solved the problem.</p>
<p>So, maybe, from what was gathered from these comments, at the end of Ep 3, Gordon goes back in time with Borealis tech, somehow, and wakes up before the RC. Gordon decides that, to prevent the RC, he tries to sabotage the cart. As he does so, Past Gordon kills him, thinking he was a criminal (From APERTURE? [loljkfailidea]) and removes the crowbar, fixing the cart, unwittingly unlocking the door to hell. The sample would be the knob.</p>
<p>Totally on the spot idea, and yes, I understand it’s a horrible idea, but it would make sense. Another train of thought is, instead of sabotaging (Remove the event from your brain) he travels back to the tram, paradoxing past-Gordon from existence. He knew what was going to happen, and maybe on the Borealis he found a way to halt the RC, but when the RC occurs and he blacks out, BOOM memory loss. Yes, another failidea, but hey, maybe Gordon WAS indirectly the bad guy, and maybe instead of trying to stop the RC, he had gone back in time to try and open a larger portal and allow everything in faster, as well as the Nihilanth himself. Then there was the memory loss… again.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Jonny Nibbz">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Jonny Nibbz:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I know GLaDOS makes a comment about her being the only thing in between you and what was outside, but 100 years after the 7 Hour War, it’s likely that Gordon will have done his thing and solved the problem.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Jonny Nibbz">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Jonny Nibbz:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>100 years after the 7 Hour War</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Jonny Nibbz">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Jonny Nibbz:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>7 Hour War</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>:facepalm:</p>
<p>EDIT: bah, stupid refreshing. Just ignore my double postingness.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/gordon-did-it/4145/99">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/gordon-did-it/4145/99</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 17 May 2010 23:23:51 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-4145-99</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/gordon-did-it/4145.rss">GORDON DID IT</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>GORDON DID IT</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Pyroclase]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="James.Curse">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/j/a587f6/40.png" class="avatar"> James.Curse:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>if i was valve I would try to make a plot twist that nobody has come up with yet.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>If they did that, they’d be out of possibilities. :retard:</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/gordon-did-it/4145/98">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/gordon-did-it/4145/98</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 17 May 2010 23:21:02 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-4145-98</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/gordon-did-it/4145.rss">GORDON DID IT</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>GORDON DID IT</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[rorriMAesU]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="bipolarmike">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/b/e99b99/40.png" class="avatar"> bipolarmike:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>…porpoise…</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>:what:</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/gordon-did-it/4145/97">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/gordon-did-it/4145/97</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 17 May 2010 20:42:27 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-4145-97</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/gordon-did-it/4145.rss">GORDON DID IT</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>GORDON DID IT</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[mouserider]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Gemereksi">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/g/d6d6ee/40.png" class="avatar"> Gemereksi:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Actually, valve wanted to make Gordon the hero of the vortigaunts in HL1. It was suppoosed to be seen in the Xen chapters, with the vorts making some kind of revolution (or at least being set free) and helping Freeman.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>interesting. i didn’t know that. but most of the plot is thought up as they go along. especially the aperture science connection. like i said portal was born from a college student game project in 2005. what i’m trying to say is even the brightest mind can’t guess how is it going to end from what we’ve seen so far.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/gordon-did-it/4145/96">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/gordon-did-it/4145/96</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 17 May 2010 19:33:04 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-4145-96</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/gordon-did-it/4145.rss">GORDON DID IT</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>GORDON DID IT</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[bipolarmike]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><img src="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/original/2X/7/79fcf8dd045da861af143c0cf265ec77070f626b.jpeg" alt="" data-base62-sha1="hp9LnzyuLpmu5FcXvjdafaa1YCL" width="180" height="180"></p>
<p>Photographic and captionographic evidence that Gordon did not did it on porpoise.</p>
<p><em>rests case</em></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/gordon-did-it/4145/95">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/gordon-did-it/4145/95</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 17 May 2010 15:32:49 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-4145-95</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/gordon-did-it/4145.rss">GORDON DID IT</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>GORDON DID IT</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Gemereksi]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="mouserider">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/m/a6a055/40.png" class="avatar"> mouserider:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>let’s face it. we can’t assume anything. do you really think when half life was released they allready hat planned this whole plot of the seven hour war and the vortigaunts joining the humans?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Actually, valve wanted to make Gordon the hero of the vortigaunts in HL1. It was suppoosed to be seen in the Xen chapters, with the vorts making some kind of revolution (or at least being set free) and helping Freeman.</p>
<p>They planned to make Xen looks like a complete and complex eco system (far more than what we can see in the final product), but most of the ideas about this aspect of the game were finally cut because they ran out of time (as HL 1 had already been delayed too many times, a bit like…like…well, I forgot  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/smiley.png?v=9" title=":smiley:" class="emoji" alt=":smiley:">  ).</p>
<p>I guess that back then, Valve/Laidlaw had, for the most, no idea of the actual storyline. But they already had some major elements.<br>
From my point of view, they make a storyline as much to produce interesting twists as to recycle old but interesting ideas they couldn’t use (for any reason: time, technical limitations or just choice) before.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/gordon-did-it/4145/94">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/gordon-did-it/4145/94</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 17 May 2010 14:35:51 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-4145-94</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/gordon-did-it/4145.rss">GORDON DID IT</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>GORDON DID IT</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[wleikko]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Jonny Nibbz">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Jonny Nibbz:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>So, maybe, from what was gathered from these comments, at the end of Ep 3, Gordon goes back in time with Borealis tech, somehow, and wakes up before the RC. Gordon decides that, to prevent the RC, he tries to sabotage the cart. As he does so, Past Gordon kills him, thinking he was a criminal (From APERTURE? [loljkfailidea]) and removes the crowbar, fixing the cart, unwittingly unlocking the door to hell. The sample would be the knob.</p>
<p>Totally on the spot idea, and yes, I understand it’s a horrible idea, but it would make sense. Another train of thought is, instead of sabotaging (Remove the event from your brain) he travels back to the tram, paradoxing past-Gordon from existence. He knew what was going to happen, and maybe on the Borealis he found a way to halt the RC, but when the RC occurs and he blacks out, BOOM memory loss. Yes, another failidea, but hey, maybe Gordon WAS indirectly the bad guy, and maybe instead of trying to stop the RC, he had gone back in time to try and open a larger portal and allow everything in faster, as well as the Nihilanth himself. Then there was the memory loss… again.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I like some of your ideas. Especially, after finding Borealis, he travels back to Black Mesa to prevent RC. That’s probably because i desperatly want to see BM again… xD Ok, Gordon travels back to BM, he tries to sabotage the experiment, which, say, might explain the power failure at the begining of HL1… He almost succeeds, and seconds before the other Freeman pushes cart to the energy field, hes doing cinematic slo-mo “NOOOOOO…!!!”, unfortunatly failing to prevent him to push the cart. Old Freeman dies, new begins the game (at the start of HL1) again, thus creating an endless loop of events. You have a few seconds to play the game, just to get an idea that it started all over again, then fade out, and end credits. Applause  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/smiley.png?v=9" title=":smiley:" class="emoji" alt=":smiley:"><br>
Where would you stick G-Man in there? Lets just say hes an evil sadist who likes to watch hes favorite movie all over again…</p>
<p>I wouldn’t like it to be like this. xD<br>
But I would like to see some time travel and Black Mesa again.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/gordon-did-it/4145/93">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/gordon-did-it/4145/93</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 17 May 2010 12:48:50 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-4145-93</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/gordon-did-it/4145.rss">GORDON DID IT</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>GORDON DID IT</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Mr.Shadow]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Well, I wouldn’t hate it. I mean: Being the hero in every single videogame gets kinda boring.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/gordon-did-it/4145/92">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/gordon-did-it/4145/92</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 17 May 2010 08:39:35 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-4145-92</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/gordon-did-it/4145.rss">GORDON DID IT</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>GORDON DID IT</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[punisher1565]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Ballsopt">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/b/85e7bf/40.png" class="avatar"> Ballsopt:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>my theory is:</p>
<p>Gordon <span class="bbcode-i">sabotaged</span> the experiment; he was already working for the Gman.<br>
<span class="bbcode-u"><br>
there are hints <span class="bbcode-b">everywhere</span>:</span><br>
-you “wake up” on the tram at the start of both HL2 and HL1.<br>
-gordon was late, the plan was already in effect.<br>
-equipment malfunctions prior to experiment<br>
-in DECAY, Rosenburg says the AMS was sabotaged. gman’s crystal, your hev suit.<br>
-Gman is <span class="bbcode-i">always</span> watching you, even prior to the resonance cascade.<br>
-gordon (You) cant talk or write for <span class="bbcode-i">some</span> reason (lolol hypnosis)<br>
-some of Gman’s dialogue seems to allude to it.<br>
-you have an almost messianic reputation prior to HL2, which i doubt was generated by the surviving science team alone; it all fits with Gman’s plan.<br>
-even more shit</p>
<p>i could go on, but yeah. We know Gman used you to kill the Nihilanth and the combine. why? no clue.</p>
<p>i realize others may have come to this conclusion as well. It’s just a <span class="bbcode-b">theory</span>, but a perfectly logical one.</p>
<p>so yeah, get out your tinfoil hats and go crazy</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I almost fully agree with you, except for the fact that Valve is going to milk the suspensful character of Gordon Freeman for as long as possible.</p>
<p>In conclusion, we (we, being the consumer) can theorize all we want. But we’ll never truly know about Mr.Freeman until the big meaty cow we call Gordon Freeman runs dry of his fatty, nutritious, homogenized milk.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/gordon-did-it/4145/91">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/gordon-did-it/4145/91</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 17 May 2010 04:38:34 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-4145-91</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/gordon-did-it/4145.rss">GORDON DID IT</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>GORDON DID IT</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Jonny_Nibbz]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Not time travel specifically, but according to what all has been said in the thread, I decided to take my favorites and clump them all into some sort of randomly thrown together lego project. I don’t think in any of my stories I’ve ever incorporated time travel.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/gordon-did-it/4145/90">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/gordon-did-it/4145/90</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 17 May 2010 02:02:28 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-4145-90</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/gordon-did-it/4145.rss">GORDON DID IT</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
