<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>He is the Law!</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/he-is-the-law/560</link>
    <description>Well, they have released concept art of the new Dredd film.

[url]https://www.cinematical.com/2008/12/21/new-judge-dredd-movie-coming/[/url]
[quote]
&quot;I am the Law!&quot; Does that quote give you goosebumps or nightmares? Sylvester Stallone uttered those words as Judge Dredd in the awful 1995 sci-fi action flick, featuring Diane Lane as his partner, Rob Schneider as his comic sidekick, Armand Assante as the villain, and Max von Sydow as the Chief Justice. Now a new version of the British comic strip character will be coming to the big screen, with production scheduled to begin next year, according to an announcement at the 2000 AD web site.

Judge Dredd began life in the second issue of the magazine anthology 2000 AD. In a time when Judges are running a huge megapolis, Judge Dredd was empowered to enforce the law, sentence offenders, and carry out the punishment. The premise sounded ideal for adaptation, but the 1995 movie version, directed by Danny Cannon, was tired and generic; Schneider was especially annoying. It lacked any zip or zest; fans noted that Dredd never removed his helmet in the strip and, more importantly, complained that the dry humor was missing and the mythology was left out. Stallone himself feels that the film was &quot;a real missed opportunity,&quot; and told Uncut magazine that &quot;great potential&quot; was wasted. &quot;We shouldn&#39;t have tried to make it Hamlet; it&#39;s more Hamlet and Eggs.&quot;

The new version will be made by Rebellion and production company DNA Films; DNA also made 28 Weeks Later and Sunshine. No other details have been announced. Obviously, the right script and director are essential, but let&#39;s play &quot;what if?&quot; and try to imagine: who could be the next Judge Dredd? And does he need to keep his helmet on?
[/quote]
[url]https://io9.com/5125143/he-is-the-law-your-first-look-at-judge-dredd-movie[/url]

[img]https://cache.gawker.com/assets/images/io9/2009/01/riotjudges.jpg[/img]

[img]https://io9.com/assets/images/gallery/8/2009/01/medium_3177607848_339f27d536_o.jpg[/img]

[img]https://www.scifiupdates.com/main/images/stories/movies/concept_art/judge_dredd/judge_dredd_concept_2.jpg[/img]


I hope they put Judge Death in it, that would be so awesome.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 11 Jun 2009 16:46:34 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Off Topic</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/he-is-the-law/560.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>He is the Law!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[raw_bean]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Been reading the original strips from the beginning of 2000AD and I’d love to see a Dredd film done right. Rebellion have been really respectful of 2000AD and Dredd since they bought them, so I’m hopeful.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/he-is-the-law/560/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/he-is-the-law/560/5</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jun 2009 16:46:34 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-560-5</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/he-is-the-law/560.rss">He is the Law!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>He is the Law!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Grand_General_Hot]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Basically Dredd’s a prick.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/he-is-the-law/560/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/he-is-the-law/560/4</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jun 2009 12:28:20 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-560-4</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/he-is-the-law/560.rss">He is the Law!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>He is the Law!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[TheeGoatPig]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I have been thinking about this while listening to the old anthrax song “I am the law”. I don’t think I would like Dredd even if the movie were done right. The character just doesn’t interest me.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/he-is-the-law/560/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/he-is-the-law/560/3</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jun 2009 12:11:31 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-560-3</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/he-is-the-law/560.rss">He is the Law!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>He is the Law!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Lamsey]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Please, god, let it be better than the last travesty.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/he-is-the-law/560/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/he-is-the-law/560/2</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jun 2009 22:50:21 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-560-2</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/he-is-the-law/560.rss">He is the Law!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>He is the Law!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Grand_General_Hot]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Well, they have released concept art of the new Dredd film.</p>
<p><a href="https://www.cinematical.com/2008/12/21/new-judge-dredd-movie-coming/" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://www.cinematical.com/2008/12/21/new-judge-dredd-movie-coming/</a></p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>“I am the Law!” Does that quote give you goosebumps or nightmares? Sylvester Stallone uttered those words as Judge Dredd in the awful 1995 sci-fi action flick, featuring Diane Lane as his partner, Rob Schneider as his comic sidekick, Armand Assante as the villain, and Max von Sydow as the Chief Justice. Now a new version of the British comic strip character will be coming to the big screen, with production scheduled to begin next year, according to an announcement at the 2000 AD web site.</p>
<p>Judge Dredd began life in the second issue of the magazine anthology 2000 AD. In a time when Judges are running a huge megapolis, Judge Dredd was empowered to enforce the law, sentence offenders, and carry out the punishment. The premise sounded ideal for adaptation, but the 1995 movie version, directed by Danny Cannon, was tired and generic; Schneider was especially annoying. It lacked any zip or zest; fans noted that Dredd never removed his helmet in the strip and, more importantly, complained that the dry humor was missing and the mythology was left out. Stallone himself feels that the film was “a real missed opportunity,” and told Uncut magazine that “great potential” was wasted. “We shouldn’t have tried to make it Hamlet; it’s more Hamlet and Eggs.”</p>
<p>The new version will be made by Rebellion and production company DNA Films; DNA also made 28 Weeks Later and Sunshine. No other details have been announced. Obviously, the right script and director are essential, but let’s play “what if?” and try to imagine: who could be the next Judge Dredd? And does he need to keep his helmet on?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p><a href="https://io9.com/5125143/he-is-the-law-your-first-look-at-judge-dredd-movie" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://io9.com/5125143/he-is-the-law-your-first-look-at-judge-dredd-movie</a></p>
<p><span alt="" class="broken-image" title="This image is broken"><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-unlink svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#unlink"></use></svg></span></p>
<p><span alt="" class="broken-image" title="This image is broken"><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-unlink svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#unlink"></use></svg></span></p>
<p><span alt="" class="broken-image" title="This image is broken"><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-unlink svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#unlink"></use></svg></span></p>
<p>I hope they put Judge Death in it, that would be so awesome.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/he-is-the-law/560/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/he-is-the-law/560/1</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jun 2009 21:38:03 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-560-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/he-is-the-law/560.rss">He is the Law!</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
