<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crysis &amp; Win7</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/crysis-win7/1959</link>
    <description>I bought Crysis on Steam a couple weeks ago during a sale, and every time I change any settings, it crashes, even if it&#39;s just a simple button reassignment. Restarting the computer works every once and a while as a temporary remedy, but it&#39;s still a major pain in the ass. I&#39;ve tried updating drivers, using compatibility modes, reinstalling, cleaning the registry, defragmenting, and the patches were already applied. And interestingly enough, Warhead has no issues whatsoever. Has anyone else had this problem? Is there a permanent solution?

(If relevant) Specs:
Core2 Quad 9550 @ 3.4Ghz
Kingston 8GB DDR2 - 1066
Nvidia GTX260 Core216
Windows 7 Pro x64</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 21 Jan 2010 11:18:36 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Help and Support</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/crysis-win7/1959.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Crysis &amp; Win7</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[RandomSpoon]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>No problem, just glad it worked <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=9" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/crysis-win7/1959/28">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/crysis-win7/1959/28</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jan 2010 11:18:36 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-1959-28</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/crysis-win7/1959.rss">Crysis &amp; Win7</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Crysis &amp; Win7</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Will89]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="RandomSpoon">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/r/c57346/40.png" class="avatar"> RandomSpoon:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I was having this problem for ages until a few days ago. I don’t think it works for everyone, but what i had to do was open my anti-virus software and create an exception for my ‘Documents/MyGames/Crysis’ folder and i can now change settings without any problems.</p>
<p>I think it’s because your anti-virus software see’s it as “oh noes somethings accessing these files KILL IT!”, hence the crash.</p>
<p>Hope this helps</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Holy shit! This did it! Thanks a lot dude, this issue has been bothering me for months.</p>
<p>(Sorry 'bout the double post, but this is a significant update)</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/crysis-win7/1959/27">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/crysis-win7/1959/27</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jan 2010 04:05:45 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-1959-27</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/crysis-win7/1959.rss">Crysis &amp; Win7</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Crysis &amp; Win7</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Will89]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Again, thanks for the suggestions guys. I’d try them out, but Steam is still being a little bitch and won’t even let me start the game, even after doing a(nother) reinstall.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/crysis-win7/1959/26">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/crysis-win7/1959/26</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jan 2010 02:56:20 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-1959-26</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/crysis-win7/1959.rss">Crysis &amp; Win7</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Crysis &amp; Win7</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Sitten_duck]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>It could be that there is a corrupted file in one of the games folders. For example: When I played through and area of crysis, the game crashed while loading a new level. When I restarted the game and clicked on the “load game” button to load the saved games menu the game would crash attempting to pull up the list of saved games. If I tried to access that list to save a game it would crash trying to load the list. It was because crashing while the game was saving/changing level created a corrupted saved games file. What I had to do was go in and find the folder with the saved games. Make a copy of it incase I messed up, and then procceed to delete save files until I load up the game and it doesn’t crash when I click on the “load game” button.  It could be possible that you have a corrupted file somewhere. Maybe when the game crashed while trying to save some of your preferences, it created a corrupted preferences file. Once again, I do not know if this will fix your problem, but it did fix my save games problem. You might try making a copy of the folders somewhere and then removing some files one by one until it works.</p>
<p>Another thing you could try from the list of “I don’t know if this will help but ANYTHING at this point is worth a shot”, is trying to run it in DirectX9 mode. You can set it to directx9 mode by going to steam&gt;games tab, right click on crysis&gt;properties, click launch options, and enter “-dx9” (without the quotations of-course) into the text space provided. I had a lot of crash errors in the final battle sequence of crysis, and this fixed them up and overall made the game run a little smoother for me. I read somewhere this usually helps in reducing bugs on some systems.</p>
<p>Edit: you could track someone down who has the retail version with the 64bit exe. and see if they can’t copy the files you need and paste them into the proper folder, and see if that doesn’t work. I don’t know if the necessary files can sent by email, but if it can, you might find someone on here who might be able to help you in that regard. I can’t, I have the steam version as well.</p>
<p>Edit2: I did some reading, and some people on the steam forum seem to think that the reason 64bit version of crysis wasn’t included in steam was because the shift +tab overlay wasn’t compatible with the 64bit version. I don’t know if this is true, and I know it really doesn’t help you, but its atleast midly interesting to here why the 64bit version wasn’t included.</p>
<p>Edit3: After reading some I found this on the steam forums, it almost sounds like the work around you tried, but you mentioned Crysis Warhead, and not Crysis wars. So here’s what this guy said. If its the same post you got the idea to mess the with bins, then disregard, but if not its another idea that falls under the “I don’t know if this will help but ANYTHING at this point is worth a shot” category.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>Ok, I think I found a solution. Download the Crysis Wars Patch 1.4 detailed at <a href="https://www.crymod.com/thread.php?threadid=45328" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://www.crymod.com/thread.php?threadid=45328</a></p>
<p>Open the patch with 7zip or similar archive reader and open the data\bin64 folder. Copy the contents to a bin64 folder you can create in your crysis install location. Get the demo of crysis and find the missing 64bit dll’s and put them in the same bin64 folder you created.<br>
You can also get the new Sandbox2 editor from the modSDK package detailed on that same link.</p>
<p>After doing all this I realized that the newest patch is maybe 1.5? Oh well, I tested this workaround and it seems to work in single player mode, and it also works creating a new map in the editor and running it in the 32bit vanilla crysis game. Probably more testing needs to be done to see if this is a robust solution, but for now it might hold over until Steam gets its act together and provides us a 64bit exe.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>These are the only probable (and improbable) fixes I can find at the moment. Like I said, if nothing esle works, you may just need to partition your hard drive and put a supported 32-bit OS on it.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/crysis-win7/1959/25">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/crysis-win7/1959/25</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jan 2010 01:58:37 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-1959-25</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/crysis-win7/1959.rss">Crysis &amp; Win7</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Crysis &amp; Win7</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[RandomSpoon]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Oh btw the game is already updated to patch 1.21 but for some reason it shows 1.1</p>
<p><a href="https://forums.steampowered.com/forums/showthread.php?t=1100630" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener"><span class="bbcode-b">SOURCE (Sort of)</span></a></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/crysis-win7/1959/24">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/crysis-win7/1959/24</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 19 Jan 2010 20:20:55 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-1959-24</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/crysis-win7/1959.rss">Crysis &amp; Win7</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Crysis &amp; Win7</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Deathmonkey7]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Will89">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/w/f4b2a3/40.png" class="avatar"> Will89:</div>
<blockquote>
<p><a class="mention" href="/u/deathmonkey7">@Deathmonkey7</a>:</p>
<p>I’ve tried doing that as well, but for some reason, I’m unable to install any patches at all. Each attempt comes up with an error. I haven’t verified this, but I heard that the Steam download already includes all released patches, so there’s not really much else I can do on that front.</p>
<hr>
<p>Thanks for the replies guys. Nothing has worked so far, but at least you’re giving me better ideas than the EA support is.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Oh shit, that sucks.  I know this is the problem as I’ve tried it several times. Every time installing 1.21 breaks the game for Win7.  Perhaps you could find out what files 1.21 changes and find the 1.2 versions of those files?</p>
<p>You’d have to make sure steam isn’t automatically updating the game, though, before you do anything like that.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/crysis-win7/1959/23">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/crysis-win7/1959/23</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 19 Jan 2010 19:28:26 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-1959-23</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/crysis-win7/1959.rss">Crysis &amp; Win7</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Crysis &amp; Win7</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Will89]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Thanks for the suggestion. I’ll let you know how it goes when Steam feels like letting me play it again. Right now it’s telling me “This game is currently unavailable. Please try again later.” Piece of freakin’ shit…</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/crysis-win7/1959/22">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/crysis-win7/1959/22</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 19 Jan 2010 18:32:14 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-1959-22</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/crysis-win7/1959.rss">Crysis &amp; Win7</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Crysis &amp; Win7</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[RandomSpoon]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I was having this problem for ages until a few days ago. I don’t think it works for everyone, but what i had to do was open my anti-virus software and create an exception for my ‘Documents/MyGames/Crysis’ folder and i can now change settings without any problems.</p>
<p>I think it’s because your anti-virus software see’s it as “oh noes somethings accessing these files KILL IT!”, hence the crash.</p>
<p>Hope this helps</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/crysis-win7/1959/21">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/crysis-win7/1959/21</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 19 Jan 2010 17:41:37 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-1959-21</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/crysis-win7/1959.rss">Crysis &amp; Win7</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Crysis &amp; Win7</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Sitten_duck]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Sry that didn’t work. It sounds like you have tried everything, but just in the off chance that you forgot this more obvious one I’ll bring it up. If you have Win7 Professional or Ultimate, you could try XP compatibility mode when playing it. I don’t know if it will change anything.</p>
<p>Other than that, the only thing I can think of is partitioning your HDDs and putting XP 64/32 bit, or Win7 32bit on it and run it there. Its lame, but you just might have to do that to play some games.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/crysis-win7/1959/20">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/crysis-win7/1959/20</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 19 Jan 2010 16:15:50 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-1959-20</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/crysis-win7/1959.rss">Crysis &amp; Win7</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Crysis &amp; Win7</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Will89]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><a class="mention" href="/u/sitten_duck">@Sitten_duck</a></p>
<p>I actually just tried that yesterday. There was also an idea on a different forum to use the Crysis Wars Bin64 and merge it with certain files from the demo. Neither worked. It would hang before loading the game, just like when I tried using the Warhead Bin64.</p>
<p><a class="mention" href="/u/deathmonkey7">@Deathmonkey7</a>:</p>
<p>I’ve tried doing that as well, but for some reason, I’m unable to install any patches at all. Each attempt comes up with an error. I haven’t verified this, but I heard that the Steam download already includes all released patches, so there’s not really much else I can do on that front.</p>
<hr>
<p>Thanks for the replies guys. Nothing has worked so far, but at least you’re giving me better ideas than the EA support is.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/crysis-win7/1959/19">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/crysis-win7/1959/19</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 19 Jan 2010 16:06:29 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-1959-19</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/crysis-win7/1959.rss">Crysis &amp; Win7</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Crysis &amp; Win7</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Sitten_duck]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I have had some issues with crysis myself, which is why I can empathize with you. You mentioned that copying the 64bin from Warhead made the options work, but not the actual game. Now I know nothing about thse types of things whatsoever, but maybe the reason why the options worked after that is because both Crysis and warhead use the same options information, but the actual gameplay and stuff is different between the two so it didn’t work. You mentioned that the demo worked on 64bit, why don’t you reinstall it and copy the 64bin over to your actual folder. Because they are from the same game, they might be more compatible. But like I said, I have no knowledge over this stuff whatsoever. I’m just spitballing here, and it will probably be just a waste of time. But its worth a shot, right?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/crysis-win7/1959/18">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/crysis-win7/1959/18</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 19 Jan 2010 15:50:29 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-1959-18</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/crysis-win7/1959.rss">Crysis &amp; Win7</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Crysis &amp; Win7</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Lord_Grievous]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Brother Shrike">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Brother Shrike:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>He’s got a bit of a GPU bottleneck, though. <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/confused.png?v=9" title=":confused:" class="emoji" alt=":confused:"></p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>'tseems the grapes are sour :freeman:</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/crysis-win7/1959/17">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/crysis-win7/1959/17</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 19 Jan 2010 14:11:11 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-1959-17</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/crysis-win7/1959.rss">Crysis &amp; Win7</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Crysis &amp; Win7</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Deathmonkey7]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Oh , since you bumped the thread, I might as well add my findings.  Uninstall the game, and delete all of your user files. (located in your documents).  Re-install, and install all patches BEFORE hotfix 1.21.  The game will run perfectly.</p>
<p>Something in hotfix 1.21 does NOT like Windows 7.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/crysis-win7/1959/16">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/crysis-win7/1959/16</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 19 Jan 2010 06:55:37 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-1959-16</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/crysis-win7/1959.rss">Crysis &amp; Win7</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Crysis &amp; Win7</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Will89]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I might be bumping this thread a little, but I finally got a reply from EA. It only took a month for them to tell me to reinstall the game and install patches. Then the rep told me the game was never compatible with 64-bit operating systems because it hasn’t been “officially” tested. What kind of bullshit answer is that? Even the demo of the game had 64bit binaries and it worked perfectly fine on my PC. It’s like they’re trying to make it look like I wasn’t paying attention to compatibility issues that don’t exist, so yeah, they’re starting to piss me off.</p>
<p>Just had to let off a little steam…</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/crysis-win7/1959/15">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/crysis-win7/1959/15</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 19 Jan 2010 06:01:44 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-1959-15</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/crysis-win7/1959.rss">Crysis &amp; Win7</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Crysis &amp; Win7</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Deathmonkey7]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Same issue here. Found no fixes. I simply edited my CFG’s to the settings I wanted so I wouldn’t have to worry about changing settings and having it crash.</p>
<p>Had no issues before Windows 7.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/crysis-win7/1959/14">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/crysis-win7/1959/14</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 04 Dec 2009 20:50:05 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-1959-14</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/crysis-win7/1959.rss">Crysis &amp; Win7</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Crysis &amp; Win7</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Will89]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Will89">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/w/f4b2a3/40.png" class="avatar"> Will89:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I’ve opened a support ticket with Steam about this issue and to request the proper Bin64 directory, though I doubt they’ll do anything about it. In either case, I don’t think I’ll buying any more games through them.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>And they still haven’t given me an answer in any form. I’m normally pretty patient, but this is ridiculous.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Brother Shrike">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Brother Shrike:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>He’s got a bit of a GPU bottleneck, though. <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/confused.png?v=9" title=":confused:" class="emoji" alt=":confused:"></p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>It’s kinda intentional. I got the card at a good price, and plan on upgrading it when DX11 cards go mainstream. I just hope my processor will still be viable when that time comes around.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="MaxTheLimit">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/m/0ea827/40.png" class="avatar"> MaxTheLimit:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Uh, not really no.<br>
a single GTX 260 is a powerful enough card, the core 216 model is a bit more so.<br>
I was able to run most everything at 1920*1200 just fine.<br>
If he only has like a 22inch monitor ( which is common ) that GPU is STILL overkill.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Currently using a 23in @ 1920x1080 and a 22in @ 1680x1050. It seems to strain a little while running Cryostasis maxed out, but that’s probably from the PhysX processing, because the graphics aren’t really that spectacular.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="sersoft">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/user_avatar/leakfree.org/sersoft/40/5837_2.png" class="avatar"> sersoft:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I’ve just downgraded from 7 to XP on my laptop and my games run 100% faster.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I doubt your games run twice as fast, unless your laptop is junk and only got 2fps before then 4fps after.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="MaxTheLimit">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/m/0ea827/40.png" class="avatar"> MaxTheLimit:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>That shouldn’t be a problem if you have an XP SP2 or later disk.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Or if his laptop BIOS supports the IDE hard drive compatibility mode.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/crysis-win7/1959/13">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/crysis-win7/1959/13</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 04 Dec 2009 17:52:10 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-1959-13</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/crysis-win7/1959.rss">Crysis &amp; Win7</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Crysis &amp; Win7</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[MaxTheLimit]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="sersoft">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/user_avatar/leakfree.org/sersoft/40/5837_2.png" class="avatar"> sersoft:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I had to make a custom nLite CD and manually integrate the new sata drivers so that XP would recognize the laptop’s HDD. I wasted all night doing that but it’s worth it.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>That shouldn’t be a problem if you have an XP SP2 or later disk.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/crysis-win7/1959/12">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/crysis-win7/1959/12</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2009 21:32:45 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-1959-12</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/crysis-win7/1959.rss">Crysis &amp; Win7</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Crysis &amp; Win7</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Brother_Shrike]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>What I mean is that he has a lot of room to grow without upgrading his CPU, not that his graphics are necessarily holding him back.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/crysis-win7/1959/11">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/crysis-win7/1959/11</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2009 21:21:46 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-1959-11</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/crysis-win7/1959.rss">Crysis &amp; Win7</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Crysis &amp; Win7</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[sersoft]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I’ve just downgraded from 7 to XP on my laptop and my games run 100% faster.</p>
<p>I had to make a custom nLite CD and manually integrate the new sata drivers so that XP would recognize the laptop’s HDD. I wasted all night doing that but it’s worth it.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/crysis-win7/1959/10">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/crysis-win7/1959/10</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2009 21:21:46 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-1959-10</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/crysis-win7/1959.rss">Crysis &amp; Win7</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Crysis &amp; Win7</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[MaxTheLimit]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Uh, not really no.<br>
a single GTX 260 is a powerful enough card, the core 216 model is a bit more so.<br>
I was able to run most everything at 1920*1200 just fine.<br>
If he only has like a 22inch monitor ( which is common ) that GPU is STILL overkill.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/crysis-win7/1959/9">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/crysis-win7/1959/9</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2009 21:15:32 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-1959-9</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/crysis-win7/1959.rss">Crysis &amp; Win7</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Crysis &amp; Win7</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Brother_Shrike]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>He’s got a bit of a GPU bottleneck, though. <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/confused.png?v=9" title=":confused:" class="emoji" alt=":confused:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/crysis-win7/1959/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/crysis-win7/1959/8</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2009 20:54:30 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-1959-8</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/crysis-win7/1959.rss">Crysis &amp; Win7</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Crysis &amp; Win7</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Aze]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Will89">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/w/f4b2a3/40.png" class="avatar"> Will89:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>(If relevant) Specs:<br>
Core2 Quad 9550 @ 3.4Ghz<br>
Kingston 8GB DDR2 - 1066<br>
Nvidia GTX260 Core216<br>
Windows 7 Pro x64</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I have a kinda good pc , but when you guys post a Spec like this, I always get the feeling that I’m using a commodore 64  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/frowning.png?v=9" title=":frowning:" class="emoji" alt=":frowning:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/crysis-win7/1959/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/crysis-win7/1959/7</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2009 20:50:45 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-1959-7</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/crysis-win7/1959.rss">Crysis &amp; Win7</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Crysis &amp; Win7</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Will89]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Thanks for the replies so far, guys. As a quick update, I looked through my Crysis files and noticed that Steam didn’t install a 64 bit executable, which is is apparently included with the “retail” version of the game, and I’ve got a feeling that’s why I’m running into these problems. Just to see what would happen, I copied the Bin64 folder from Warhead to the Crysis directory and ran the Crysis64 exe from there. It started up fine and even let me change the settings without any problems, but crashed after the opening movie when starting a new game.</p>
<p>I’ve opened a support ticket with Steam about this issue and to request the proper Bin64 directory, though I doubt they’ll do anything about it. In either case, I don’t think I’ll buying any more games through them.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/crysis-win7/1959/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/crysis-win7/1959/6</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2009 18:39:08 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-1959-6</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/crysis-win7/1959.rss">Crysis &amp; Win7</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Crysis &amp; Win7</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Phat]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Pacer">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/p/9d8465/40.png" class="avatar"> Pacer:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>the original Crysis game cannot be run on a x64 operating system if it is bought and downloaded from Steam.  You’ll run into the same problem with most Valve games such as HL and HL2, Portal, and TF2.  It’s unfortunate, and annoying, yes, but you can still play the game if you install a x86 OS.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I had Vista Ult x64 since the beginning of 2007 and ever since I was able to run hl,hl2,portal,tf2 and the retail  version of Crysis (don’t know about steam version).<br>
I have  never encountered a problem like this.<br>
Have you tried reinstalling Steam? That usually works with these problems.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/crysis-win7/1959/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/crysis-win7/1959/5</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2009 10:40:49 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-1959-5</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/crysis-win7/1959.rss">Crysis &amp; Win7</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Crysis &amp; Win7</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[eternalness]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I dont think its Windows 7 64bit cause I have the Win7 Ultimate 64bit retail right now and used to run build 7000, 7057, and 7100 all in 64bit and I never encountered a problem with em.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/crysis-win7/1959/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/crysis-win7/1959/4</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2009 08:16:58 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-1959-4</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/crysis-win7/1959.rss">Crysis &amp; Win7</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
