<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>The Witcher 2: Assassins of Kings</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/the-witcher-2-assassins-of-kings/7145</link>
    <description>If you&#39;re not already following it or massively excited about it, watch the 5 launch trailers.

[url]https://www.computerandvideogames.com/301424/news/the-witcher-2-gets-five-launch-trailers/[/url]

If you are, you should know it&#39;s released on Tuesday (tomorrow)!! Now I just have to hope the postman turns up with my pre-order....</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 26 May 2011 20:07:16 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Technology and Gaming</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/the-witcher-2-assassins-of-kings/7145.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>The Witcher 2: Assassins of Kings</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[_amp_346_wirek]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Geralt is the monster killer, not lover. He just kills women with his silver pingas.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/the-witcher-2-assassins-of-kings/7145/31">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/the-witcher-2-assassins-of-kings/7145/31</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 May 2011 20:07:16 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7145-31</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/the-witcher-2-assassins-of-kings/7145.rss">The Witcher 2: Assassins of Kings</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The Witcher 2: Assassins of Kings</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Insomniac]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Someonerandm">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/s/d78d45/40.png" class="avatar"> Someonerandm:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>You mean the most blatant use of sex to sell a game? Yeah, sounds about right.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Someonerandm">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/s/d78d45/40.png" class="avatar"> Someonerandm:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>See, thats kind of the problem here. It has no real point. Its just there.</p>
<p>In any case, don’t get me wrong, I’m not complaining, it just seems like an odd feature.</p>
<p>Its what I do. Not offended though. Only obnoxious easily offended people get offended by that.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I agree, it has absolutely no point. Neither does 90% of all sex scenes in media. Most times a black screen saying “And then they had sex” would be enough to show character development. But in the end, they want to make money as well.</p>
<p>The sex in The Witcher isn’t very subtle, or refined. But it cuts the crap, which is more than I can say for most sex in media.</p>
<p>I also like to play around with the though that that might have been our society, had religion never existed.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/the-witcher-2-assassins-of-kings/7145/30">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/the-witcher-2-assassins-of-kings/7145/30</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 May 2011 19:56:39 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7145-30</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/the-witcher-2-assassins-of-kings/7145.rss">The Witcher 2: Assassins of Kings</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The Witcher 2: Assassins of Kings</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Rosie]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Ive not really had any issues with how sex was portrayed in either game and i think it was handled really well be CDProjekt. I think it fits the context and tone of the game perfectly. there was once or twice in the first game where i felt it went a bit over the top, mainly those instances were where you were talking to an NPC about something entirely unrelated and then what seems out of nowhere a wild sex card appears. this only happens once, maybe twice that i can remember right off hand (and I’m currently playing through it again) so its a very minor note.<br>
the second game they seemed to have toned it down a bit (havent been able to finish it, stuck at a point where a quest is broken in the military camp at the beginning of the necromancy bit, anyone else had this issue?) toned down in the sense that there arent as many instances but instead replaced with cut-scenes.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/the-witcher-2-assassins-of-kings/7145/29">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/the-witcher-2-assassins-of-kings/7145/29</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 May 2011 19:24:44 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7145-29</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/the-witcher-2-assassins-of-kings/7145.rss">The Witcher 2: Assassins of Kings</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The Witcher 2: Assassins of Kings</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Someonerandm]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Insomniac">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/i/bb73d2/40.png" class="avatar"> Insomniac:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>The Witcher is more<br>
-Hey, want to go behind that bush and fuck?<br>
-Sure<br>
That’s how we should see sex!</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>See, thats kind of the problem here. It has no real point. Its just there.</p>
<p>In any case, don’t get me wrong, I’m not complaining, it just seems like an odd feature.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Merode">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/m/7ab992/40.png" class="avatar"> Merode:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>People hatin’… But since you’re complaining on every single subject on this forum, Someonerandm, I’m not even mad…  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=9" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"></p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Its what I do. Not offended though. Only obnoxious easily offended people get offended by that.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/the-witcher-2-assassins-of-kings/7145/28">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/the-witcher-2-assassins-of-kings/7145/28</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 May 2011 19:00:11 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7145-28</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/the-witcher-2-assassins-of-kings/7145.rss">The Witcher 2: Assassins of Kings</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The Witcher 2: Assassins of Kings</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Insomniac]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Someonerandm">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/s/d78d45/40.png" class="avatar"> Someonerandm:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>You mean the most blatant use of sex to sell a game? Yeah, sounds about right.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>That might have been their intention. I didn’t see it that way.<br>
In pretty much all movies, books and games sex is so painfully overrated and melodramatic. The Witcher was a nice change of pace. Instead of the usual<br>
-oh I love you <em>kiss</em> <em>kiss</em> <em>pulls up shirt</em> <em>kiss</em> <em>wake up next to each other.</em></p>
<p>The Witcher is more<br>
-Hey, want to go behind that bush and fuck?<br>
-Sure<br>
That’s how we should see sex!</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/the-witcher-2-assassins-of-kings/7145/27">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/the-witcher-2-assassins-of-kings/7145/27</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 May 2011 16:39:03 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7145-27</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/the-witcher-2-assassins-of-kings/7145.rss">The Witcher 2: Assassins of Kings</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The Witcher 2: Assassins of Kings</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Merode]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Someonerandm">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/s/d78d45/40.png" class="avatar"> Someonerandm:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>You mean the most blatant use of sex to sell a game? Yeah, sounds about right.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>People hatin’… But since you’re complaining on every single subject on this forum, Someonerandm, I’m not even mad…  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=9" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"></p>
<p>In my opinion sex is just for joy. Making it a taboo subject is just plain stupid (US censored version?  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/smiley.png?v=9" title=":smiley:" class="emoji" alt=":smiley:"> ). Even my fiance to whom I’ve shown the game wasn’t offended… I think most of the people being offended by sex in this game are geeks who never or rarely had it irl…  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=9" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:">  Get over it…</p>
<p>Just my 2 cents…  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=9" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/the-witcher-2-assassins-of-kings/7145/26">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/the-witcher-2-assassins-of-kings/7145/26</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 May 2011 09:37:34 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7145-26</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/the-witcher-2-assassins-of-kings/7145.rss">The Witcher 2: Assassins of Kings</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The Witcher 2: Assassins of Kings</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Someonerandm]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Insomniac">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/i/bb73d2/40.png" class="avatar"> Insomniac:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>The portrayal of sex was the best I’ve seen in games, and most other media.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>You mean the most blatant use of sex to sell a game? Yeah, sounds about right.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/the-witcher-2-assassins-of-kings/7145/25">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/the-witcher-2-assassins-of-kings/7145/25</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 May 2011 01:34:33 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7145-25</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/the-witcher-2-assassins-of-kings/7145.rss">The Witcher 2: Assassins of Kings</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The Witcher 2: Assassins of Kings</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Insomniac]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>The witcher 1 was underrated. It dared go where no game had gone before. Its story was brutal. The dialog was better than anything bioware ever did and the approach  it took to sex I believe was approached wrongly by gamers.</p>
<p>The portrayal of sex was the best I’ve seen in games, and most other media.</p>
<p>They lost much of the brutality in story and dialog in tw2, but it’s improved in so many other ways its still GOTY so far.</p>
<p>(and if you don’t know what I mean when I say brutality. See beginning of chapter 5 and the endgame)</p>
<p>Can’t go deeper on this now. Typing on my phone and it’s 3 24 in the morning.</p>
<p>–<br>
Sent from my phone.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/the-witcher-2-assassins-of-kings/7145/24">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/the-witcher-2-assassins-of-kings/7145/24</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 May 2011 01:25:58 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7145-24</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/the-witcher-2-assassins-of-kings/7145.rss">The Witcher 2: Assassins of Kings</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The Witcher 2: Assassins of Kings</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Merode]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Well, I’m not sure about The Witcher 2 because I haven’t played it yet. If it’s as similar to the first game as they say in the reviews, I might tell you something about The Witcher 1.</p>
<p>My first attempt to play The Witcher was on a borrowed copy from my friend. It didn’t work well, I didn’t like the game at all and after five or ten minutes I gave up. Just recently (so after long, long time) I tried to play it again. I decided I’ll give it a longer try. I was surprised - this was one of the best rpgs I have played until now (version 1.5). It sucked me up like no other game for a long time and I’ve bought my own copy. I can also describe now what was wrong with the game - it’s not introducing you well to the game’s mechanics. You have to find out most of things yourself (for example, what is meditation used for?). Also, as some people mentioned it’s not simplistic - quest objectives aren’t marked on maps with big red arrows, you have to go and find them yourself (which I consider something good rather than bad). What is the best part of the game for me is the dialogs, lore and plot. The game is very mature, if naked nipples offend you, don’t play it (so many people criticising it on metacritics, while game’s box clearly states that’s 18+ and what it includes). Also the choices aren’t all black or white. You’re not choosing between obviously bad guys or obviously good guys, like in Bioware’s games. The game is thanks to that very immersive.</p>
<p>In general, I’d call it more mature “Knights of the Old Republic” in The Witcher’s world with better graphics, dialogs, choices, combat system (god, I hated kotor combat) and the game is in general more balanced. I hope The Witcher 2 is the same and won’t surprise me (buying it soon).</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/the-witcher-2-assassins-of-kings/7145/23">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/the-witcher-2-assassins-of-kings/7145/23</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 May 2011 09:45:05 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7145-23</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/the-witcher-2-assassins-of-kings/7145.rss">The Witcher 2: Assassins of Kings</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The Witcher 2: Assassins of Kings</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Deimos]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>This game is excellent, I can run it on High with a few things turned off, but no way maxed, that shits rough.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/the-witcher-2-assassins-of-kings/7145/22">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/the-witcher-2-assassins-of-kings/7145/22</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 May 2011 07:46:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7145-22</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/the-witcher-2-assassins-of-kings/7145.rss">The Witcher 2: Assassins of Kings</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The Witcher 2: Assassins of Kings</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Rosie]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>i’m running it on normal but that’s partly because of my slower computer, the game is less responsive which adds a bit of an extra challenge. one thing to note though is that the combat gets easier as the game goes on as your skills get better.  another thing to note, i’ve found that reading up on the wiki, or even better reading the books themselves would add to the game a good bit, not to say its bad if you don’t, but they do reference some events and things that happened outside of both games, and having a bit of background about the various regions is also nice.  again that’s not to say if you don’t read the books or the wiki, you’ll be at any loss, its more that they’ve added a good bit as a nod to players who have.</p>
<p>other things of note, if you prefer anything along the lines of fast travel, quest/location markers or if you dont like having multiple menus and things to keep track of, you might have some issues.  quest markers are only used in ways that make sense for what is understood in the game, so if your suppose to search and find were something is(nests of monsters in a forest for example) there isn’t going to be a marker saying “hey over here follow the red arrow” you’ll actually have to go searching and find it. on the other hand if you know where something would be (a specific person in town) there would be a marker.  also there are a lot of menus and things to manage that way as far as crafting items/potions and using inventory. for me, none of the things i stated are a problem, i don’t like how a lot of games over use the quest markers/fast travel and i enjoy all the menus instead of it all being incredibly streamlined, but that’s personal taste, i enjoy it, others i know don’t like it so again, its something simply to note.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/the-witcher-2-assassins-of-kings/7145/21">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/the-witcher-2-assassins-of-kings/7145/21</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 May 2011 06:22:26 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7145-21</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/the-witcher-2-assassins-of-kings/7145.rss">The Witcher 2: Assassins of Kings</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The Witcher 2: Assassins of Kings</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[SkyBlue]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I’d advise against Impossible because the quick-time events at one point in the opening section are too hard, and it can be a lot of work to get back to the same place. Trying to avoid spoilers: you’re running across a bridge away from something and there’s supposedly two quicktime events (the same action, but about 20 seconds later). However, the button prompt doesn’t always appear. It has appeared for some people, according to some forums, but not for others, and it didn’t appear at all for me. If you fail you die instantly (even on easy), and I only got through by memorising the exact animation. I don’t know if there’s similar points later in the game. However, if you haven’t finished the first game on the hardest difficulty, there’s not much point in trying, because you need to do stuff like gather ingredients for alchemy to make lots of potions, which you will need a lot.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/the-witcher-2-assassins-of-kings/7145/20">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/the-witcher-2-assassins-of-kings/7145/20</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 19 May 2011 12:31:01 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7145-20</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/the-witcher-2-assassins-of-kings/7145.rss">The Witcher 2: Assassins of Kings</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The Witcher 2: Assassins of Kings</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Hazzmat]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Fuskox">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/f/ea666f/40.png" class="avatar"> Fuskox:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>What difficulty are you playing on? Impossible is a hardcore mode, right? So if you die once it’s a complete restart? How hard is hard? (If you’re playing on it) Because I generally play games on the hard difficulty, but I’ve heard Witcher 2 is tough.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Yea I’d recommend the normal difficulty or else you you will die so many times and pull your hair off</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/the-witcher-2-assassins-of-kings/7145/19">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/the-witcher-2-assassins-of-kings/7145/19</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 19 May 2011 06:07:25 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7145-19</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/the-witcher-2-assassins-of-kings/7145.rss">The Witcher 2: Assassins of Kings</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The Witcher 2: Assassins of Kings</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Fuskox]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>What difficulty are you playing on? Impossible is a hardcore mode, right? So if you die once it’s a complete restart? How hard is hard? (If you’re playing on it) Because I generally play games on the hard difficulty, but I’ve heard Witcher 2 is tough.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/the-witcher-2-assassins-of-kings/7145/18">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/the-witcher-2-assassins-of-kings/7145/18</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 19 May 2011 04:34:47 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7145-18</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/the-witcher-2-assassins-of-kings/7145.rss">The Witcher 2: Assassins of Kings</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The Witcher 2: Assassins of Kings</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Rosie]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Playing it now and its quickly becoming among my top 5 games ever played.<br>
played and loved the first game, despite its shortcomings which personally were easily overlooked.</p>
<p>do you need to play the first game to enjoy the second? ultimately no but you’ll want to do some reading up in the in-game journals to get caught up with who’s who but even if you don’t you can get the overall gist.</p>
<p>the game itself is absolutely beautiful even when graphics aren’t maxed. Ive got a relatively low end laptop, for today’s standards, running it on minimum graphics and its still amazing how good it looks. will be getting a new desktop soon, but couldn’t wait to play.</p>
<p>i’m loving the combat too, its difficult enough to force you to stay on your toes and use everything you’ve got available to you in order to be successful, but not so hard you feel cheated</p>
<p>the thing i love the most about the game though, is the atmosphere and tone of the game, the whole setting is very realized and fleshed out and makes for a great experience. pretty much, if you like RPGs this game is one i’d highly recommend, of all the games released so far this year, i’d put this as best yet.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/the-witcher-2-assassins-of-kings/7145/17">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/the-witcher-2-assassins-of-kings/7145/17</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 19 May 2011 04:29:35 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7145-17</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/the-witcher-2-assassins-of-kings/7145.rss">The Witcher 2: Assassins of Kings</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The Witcher 2: Assassins of Kings</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Fuskox]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I’m getting it soon, I’ll make a post about it after some play. Very excited, loved the first Witcher.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/the-witcher-2-assassins-of-kings/7145/16">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/the-witcher-2-assassins-of-kings/7145/16</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 19 May 2011 02:59:11 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7145-16</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/the-witcher-2-assassins-of-kings/7145.rss">The Witcher 2: Assassins of Kings</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The Witcher 2: Assassins of Kings</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Katana]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I would get it now, but recently I’ve been kind of apprehensive about buying games that I can’t at least try through a demo first…a shame, because otherwise, these guys have been doing absolutely everything right.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/the-witcher-2-assassins-of-kings/7145/15">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/the-witcher-2-assassins-of-kings/7145/15</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 19 May 2011 00:45:25 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7145-15</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/the-witcher-2-assassins-of-kings/7145.rss">The Witcher 2: Assassins of Kings</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The Witcher 2: Assassins of Kings</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Fuskox]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>What specs are needed to max this thing out? The GFX look very impressive.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/the-witcher-2-assassins-of-kings/7145/14">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/the-witcher-2-assassins-of-kings/7145/14</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 18 May 2011 20:54:37 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7145-14</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/the-witcher-2-assassins-of-kings/7145.rss">The Witcher 2: Assassins of Kings</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The Witcher 2: Assassins of Kings</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Hazzmat]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Looks great but I keep dying on the first level. It’s pretty hard I guess just spamming attack in this game won’t get you far. I like it.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/the-witcher-2-assassins-of-kings/7145/13">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/the-witcher-2-assassins-of-kings/7145/13</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 18 May 2011 18:05:08 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7145-13</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/the-witcher-2-assassins-of-kings/7145.rss">The Witcher 2: Assassins of Kings</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The Witcher 2: Assassins of Kings</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[SkyBlue]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>You don’t need to have played the first game, as it introduces the world and characters very well, but obviously like any series, you will pick up on some stuff if you’ve played the first. The story and characters though are some of the best I’ve ever seen (including Enslaved). The characters are so well-written and so believable (even some of the minor characters who are just plain rude or nasty) that the world feels real.</p>
<p>The combat is also very intelligent, and quite realistic as well. You have fast attacks and powerful attacks, but the majority of the combat, especially on the higher difficulty levels, requires you to block, dodge and counter-attack to make sure you don’t get hit. Even on the easiest level, if you try to fight without defending yourself, you will die very easily and quickly. However, if you haven’t played the first game, I’d advise against trying it on hard first time round, because you will NEED to use alchemy to survive.</p>
<p>The graphics are stunning, if your PC can handle it. The attention to detail in the environments is brilliant because the world looks and feels alive. In one dev diary video they even showed how for outdoors environments they consider stuff like where the sun falls, especially in forests, as to where they put plants and paths, and it shows.</p>
<p>However, it can be demanding on your PC. My gaming laptop has an Intel  i5 2.66 Ghz (that boosts to 2.93), 4GB RAM and ATI HD545V (1GB VRAM), and it runs fine… so long as I don’t put the  resolution higher than 1024 by 768. I think the problem is with my graphics card not being able to handle the extra work required  for higher resolutions, rather than the game, but it’s just a bit odd. I can have basically all the options on or on high, so long as I don’t push the resolution. However, for people on here who are more likely to have proper desktop gaming rigs, you should easily be able to get the kind of graphics in the screenshots that <span class="bbcode-b"><span class="bbcode-u">The can</span></span> posted.</p>
<p>TL; DR: don’t need to have played the first game but you might miss some references, believable story and characters, difficult but fair combat, stunning graphics if your rig can handle it.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/the-witcher-2-assassins-of-kings/7145/12">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/the-witcher-2-assassins-of-kings/7145/12</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 18 May 2011 17:20:22 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7145-12</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/the-witcher-2-assassins-of-kings/7145.rss">The Witcher 2: Assassins of Kings</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The Witcher 2: Assassins of Kings</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[brokenfridgehinge]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Do I need to of played the first one in order to enjoy/understand this one?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/the-witcher-2-assassins-of-kings/7145/11">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/the-witcher-2-assassins-of-kings/7145/11</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 18 May 2011 14:56:21 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7145-11</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/the-witcher-2-assassins-of-kings/7145.rss">The Witcher 2: Assassins of Kings</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The Witcher 2: Assassins of Kings</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Someonerandm]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Just gonna bump this so I can ask for some review from people who bought it. Reviews seem to be very positive.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/the-witcher-2-assassins-of-kings/7145/10">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/the-witcher-2-assassins-of-kings/7145/10</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 18 May 2011 14:02:11 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7145-10</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/the-witcher-2-assassins-of-kings/7145.rss">The Witcher 2: Assassins of Kings</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The Witcher 2: Assassins of Kings</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Keresh]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>We like it rough.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/the-witcher-2-assassins-of-kings/7145/9">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/the-witcher-2-assassins-of-kings/7145/9</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 16 May 2011 22:14:58 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7145-9</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/the-witcher-2-assassins-of-kings/7145.rss">The Witcher 2: Assassins of Kings</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The Witcher 2: Assassins of Kings</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Imonfire]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Well, the first one is pretty good, but so unsmooth. Just like any eastern-european games, actually.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/the-witcher-2-assassins-of-kings/7145/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/the-witcher-2-assassins-of-kings/7145/8</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 16 May 2011 21:52:12 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7145-8</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/the-witcher-2-assassins-of-kings/7145.rss">The Witcher 2: Assassins of Kings</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The Witcher 2: Assassins of Kings</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Merode]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Keresh">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/k/85f322/40.png" class="avatar"> Keresh:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>A game from a poor country, I guess it’s not worth trying then.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>QFT  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=9" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/the-witcher-2-assassins-of-kings/7145/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/the-witcher-2-assassins-of-kings/7145/7</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 16 May 2011 19:01:53 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7145-7</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/the-witcher-2-assassins-of-kings/7145.rss">The Witcher 2: Assassins of Kings</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
