<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>[FIXED] Stuck in the closet...</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/fixed-stuck-in-the-closet/13838</link>
    <description>I&#39;m sorry I didn&#39;t get position stats,

After resonance cascade I went into the locker room the security guard following me said &quot;Grab what you need and lets go&quot; I went to Freeman&#39;s locker thinking there must be something other than the battery park (I grabbed earlier). I was trying to grab the picture of the baby thinking this must be something worth grabbing. I ended up grabbing the box on the shelf and threw it out into the main area. I turned around to grab the picture (I may have jumped), but I could not grab it. I turned to walk out and I got stuck. Jumping and shifting side to side, I am firmly rooted in place, I was unable to leave the locker . I don&#39;t think the security guard was in my way I was just stuck. I couldn&#39;t move side to side and using the jump I didn&#39;t move up or down. Crouching also didn&#39;t help.

I just thought it might be something that might be an issue

Edit: I went back to this area... I found after throwing the box out I can still move in and out however if I jump inside the closet I am unable to exit the locker and I am unable to crouch all I can do is look around

setpos 1575.088135 4127.500000 477.481781;setang 4.877058 -113.980003 -0.713881

![bm_c1a1b0015.jpg|690x500](upload://skTNYsJ70SwlCx8KKtNaO95aRvJ.jpeg)</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 07 May 2015 05:15:39 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>In-game Issues</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/fixed-stuck-in-the-closet/13838.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>[FIXED] Stuck in the closet...</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crozix]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>The same bug also applies for bm_c1a0a.<br>
It seems like the player is sucked into the suit when jumping.</p>
<p>The problem after creating a mockup locker is that the collision on the suit is causing the problem. (I had to make an mockup since hammer crashed on the real map)</p>
<p>So for devs reading this change the collision to “Not Solid” on the prop locker_suit, on the map bm_c1a0a and bm_c1a1b. (or any other places where that model is used)</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/fixed-stuck-in-the-closet/13838/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/fixed-stuck-in-the-closet/13838/2</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 07 May 2015 05:15:39 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13838-2</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/fixed-stuck-in-the-closet/13838.rss">[FIXED] Stuck in the closet...</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[FIXED] Stuck in the closet...</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Eye_con]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I’m sorry I didn’t get position stats,</p>
<p>After resonance cascade I went into the locker room the security guard following me said “Grab what you need and lets go” I went to Freeman’s locker thinking there must be something other than the battery park (I grabbed earlier). I was trying to grab the picture of the baby thinking this must be something worth grabbing. I ended up grabbing the box on the shelf and threw it out into the main area. I turned around to grab the picture (I may have jumped), but I could not grab it. I turned to walk out and I got stuck. Jumping and shifting side to side, I am firmly rooted in place, I was unable to leave the locker . I don’t think the security guard was in my way I was just stuck. I couldn’t move side to side and using the jump I didn’t move up or down. Crouching also didn’t help.</p>
<p>I just thought it might be something that might be an issue</p>
<p>Edit: I went back to this area… I found after throwing the box out I can still move in and out however if I jump inside the closet I am unable to exit the locker and I am unable to crouch all I can do is look around</p>
<p>setpos 1575.088135 4127.500000 477.481781;setang 4.877058 -113.980003 -0.713881</p>
<p><div class="lightbox-wrapper"><a class="lightbox" href="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/original/2X/c/c699af286f5edc93f02145fba0b03cf1d3a672e3.jpeg" data-download-href="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/c699af286f5edc93f02145fba0b03cf1d3a672e3" title="bm_c1a1b0015.jpg"><img src="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/optimized/2X/c/c699af286f5edc93f02145fba0b03cf1d3a672e3_2_690x500.jpeg" alt="bm_c1a1b0015.jpg" data-base62-sha1="skTNYsJ70SwlCx8KKtNaO95aRvJ" width="690" height="500" srcset="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/optimized/2X/c/c699af286f5edc93f02145fba0b03cf1d3a672e3_2_690x500.jpeg, https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/optimized/2X/c/c699af286f5edc93f02145fba0b03cf1d3a672e3_2_1035x750.jpeg 1.5x, https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/optimized/2X/c/c699af286f5edc93f02145fba0b03cf1d3a672e3_2_1380x1000.jpeg 2x" data-small-upload="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/optimized/2X/c/c699af286f5edc93f02145fba0b03cf1d3a672e3_2_10x10.png"><div class="meta"><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-far-image svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#far-image"></use></svg><span class="filename">bm_c1a1b0015.jpg</span><span class="informations">1920×1080 185 KB</span><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-discourse-expand svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#discourse-expand"></use></svg></div></a></div></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/fixed-stuck-in-the-closet/13838/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/fixed-stuck-in-the-closet/13838/1</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 06 May 2015 15:11:49 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13838-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/fixed-stuck-in-the-closet/13838.rss">[FIXED] Stuck in the closet...</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
