<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Few bugs on bm_c4a1b1 and bm_c4a2b</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/few-bugs-on-bm-c4a1b1-and-bm-c4a2b/62550</link>
    <description>Hello! Ive noticed a few bugs on Xen.
Im going to start with the more &quot;serious&quot; bugs first and then add some small bugs which mostly are small details.


My account is new so im not allowed to post more than one photo but i have multiple bugs ive found and reporting them without pictures is imposible, ive made a imgur album and added descriptions there too so you know what is what. Please take a look https://imgur.com/gallery/8IW2LjN

A bug i found is when the Gonarch is chasing you at the spider web bridge before the final bossfight, i turned back and saw Gonarch was stuck at the start of the bridge, he wasn&#39;t moving at all. The only thing he was doing was moving his leg up and down, reloading a previous save fixed it for me.

As your inside the big tree in the middle and your climbing up there&#39;s an invisible step which stops you from going further and you need to jump in order to progress, ive marked where the invisible step is.

Standing in the specific spot as the picture above if you look up you can see a barnacle which has been misplaced and half of it is floating.

On the map bm_c4a2b on the lake part you can see both from the outside and the inside some green polls used when you make a map, no idea what they are but you can clearly see them. 

Later once you get inside the cave and you make the water fill the cave before the final time there&#39;s this area i thought i needed to go but when i tried to jump on the land i realised you couldn&#39;t go up and instead you would go through the ground

Not sure if this is a bug or intentionally made this way but when you right click on HEV suit zombies with the shotgun the legs half of the suit makes a weird stretching up on the belly area 

Moving ahead where i said the invisible step is if you look at the right there&#39;s a misplaced texture which is also floating on the air 
 
Moving up there&#39;s another texture that hasn&#39;t been placed as it should&#39;ve been and it leaves a blank spot.

Few steps ahead it&#39;s the same misplaced texture down on the right which is also floating on the air 


Still in bm_c4a1b1 as you go way further you get to this area, jumping into the water seems kinda off.. to me it looks like there isn&#39;t any water effects in place and it doesn&#39;t give the feeling your underwater 

One last bug i found is when the Gonarch is chasing you at the spider web bridge before the final bossfight, i turned back and saw Gonarch was stuck at the start of the bridge, he wasn&#39;t moving at all. The only thing he was doing was moving his leg up and down, reloading a previous save fixed it for me.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 28 Aug 2019 22:35:58 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>In-game Issues</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/few-bugs-on-bm-c4a1b1-and-bm-c4a2b/62550.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Few bugs on bm_c4a1b1 and bm_c4a2b</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[maks9]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Hello! Ive noticed a few bugs on Xen.<br>
Im going to start with the more “serious” bugs first and then add some small bugs which mostly are small details.</p>
<p>My account is new so im not allowed to post more than one photo but i have multiple bugs ive found and reporting them without pictures is imposible, ive made a imgur album and added descriptions there too so you know what is what. Please take a look <a href="https://imgur.com/gallery/8IW2LjN" rel="nofollow noopener">https://imgur.com/gallery/8IW2LjN</a></p>
<p>A bug i found is when the Gonarch is chasing you at the spider web bridge before the final bossfight, i turned back and saw Gonarch was stuck at the start of the bridge, he wasn’t moving at all. The only thing he was doing was moving his leg up and down, reloading a previous save fixed it for me.</p>
<p>As your inside the big tree in the middle and your climbing up there’s an invisible step which stops you from going further and you need to jump in order to progress, ive marked where the invisible step is.</p>
<p>Standing in the specific spot as the picture above if you look up you can see a barnacle which has been misplaced and half of it is floating.</p>
<p>On the map bm_c4a2b on the lake part you can see both from the outside and the inside some green polls used when you make a map, no idea what they are but you can clearly see them.</p>
<p>Later once you get inside the cave and you make the water fill the cave before the final time there’s this area i thought i needed to go but when i tried to jump on the land i realised you couldn’t go up and instead you would go through the ground</p>
<p>Not sure if this is a bug or intentionally made this way but when you right click on HEV suit zombies with the shotgun the legs half of the suit makes a weird stretching up on the belly area</p>
<p>Moving ahead where i said the invisible step is if you look at the right there’s a misplaced texture which is also floating on the air</p>
<p>Moving up there’s another texture that hasn’t been placed as it should’ve been and it leaves a blank spot.</p>
<p>Few steps ahead it’s the same misplaced texture down on the right which is also floating on the air</p>
<p>Still in bm_c4a1b1 as you go way further you get to this area, jumping into the water seems kinda off… to me it looks like there isn’t any water effects in place and it doesn’t give the feeling your underwater</p>
<p>One last bug i found is when the Gonarch is chasing you at the spider web bridge before the final bossfight, i turned back and saw Gonarch was stuck at the start of the bridge, he wasn’t moving at all. The only thing he was doing was moving his leg up and down, reloading a previous save fixed it for me.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/few-bugs-on-bm-c4a1b1-and-bm-c4a2b/62550/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/few-bugs-on-bm-c4a1b1-and-bm-c4a2b/62550/1</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 28 Aug 2019 22:35:58 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-62550-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/few-bugs-on-bm-c4a1b1-and-bm-c4a2b/62550.rss">Few bugs on bm_c4a1b1 and bm_c4a2b</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
