<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Weird speaker sound.</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/weird-speaker-sound/582</link>
    <description>[COLOR=&#39;Green&#39;][b]Problem Solved[/b]

Today I decided to plug in my good ol&#39;PS2 a old pair of speakers (Energy 3.1e) that was next to my TV but were unused. So I plug them into my Denon 545R (also old stuff but still in wonderful condition), but the sound is really weird. It&#39;s &quot;scratched&quot; if you know what I mean. As if the sound was at a really poor quality. But they shouldn&#39;t sound bad since they are still in good condition (atleast they look so). 

Anyone got an idea? My Denon doesn&#39;t like my speakers? Wrong plugging (I&#39;ll post pics of the setup tomorrow)? HALP!

[i]Edit: Also when I use my Denon as a radio receiver, my speakers sound perfect [/i]

[COLOR=&#39;green&#39;][i]Edit 2: What is this I don&#39;t even. After 5 hours of searching, it turns out I had to plug them into the Video holes instead of Phono. Now they sound crystal clear.[/i]</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 14 Jun 2009 01:34:48 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Help and Support</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/weird-speaker-sound/582.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Weird speaker sound.</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Imonfire]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>[COLOR=‘Green’]<span class="bbcode-b">Problem Solved</span></p>
<p>Today I decided to plug in my good ol’PS2 a old pair of speakers (Energy 3.1e) that was next to my TV but were unused. So I plug them into my Denon 545R (also old stuff but still in wonderful condition), but the sound is really weird. It’s “scratched” if you know what I mean. As if the sound was at a really poor quality. But they shouldn’t sound bad since they are still in good condition (atleast they look so).</p>
<p>Anyone got an idea? My Denon doesn’t like my speakers? Wrong plugging (I’ll post pics of the setup tomorrow)? HALP!</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-i">Edit: Also when I use my Denon as a radio receiver, my speakers sound perfect </span></p>
<p>[COLOR=‘green’]<span class="bbcode-i">Edit 2: What is this I don’t even. After 5 hours of searching, it turns out I had to plug them into the Video holes instead of Phono. Now they sound crystal clear.</span></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/weird-speaker-sound/582/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/weird-speaker-sound/582/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 14 Jun 2009 01:34:48 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-582-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/weird-speaker-sound/582.rss">Weird speaker sound.</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
