<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Half-Life storyline by missions</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/half-life-storyline-by-missions/12017</link>
    <description>I have always been rather interested in how the Half-Life plot is presented, especially in HL1 and its remake. It is so subtle that it leads many to think that there is no purpose-driven plot for most of the game, but the missions that different people give you are actually incredibly logical, consistent and intuitive. When I was a kid and played Half-Life for the first time, I really only got the &quot;get to the test chamber&quot; and &quot;kill nihilanth&quot; parts of the plot; the beginning and the end. But I was a kid. Now, after years of playing and replaying Half-Life and now Black Mesa, I&#39;ve become a nerd -the kind of nerd that gets stupidly excited at the sight of charts. So I made one all about it.

I&#39;m not trying to make a point other than how much of a bunch of geniuses Valve were. I know most Half-Life and Black Mesa fans will know all of this by heart. I just think it&#39;d be fun to lay it out in such a way; I&#39;m not making the point that the game would be better off with traditional game mission levels, but quite the opposite; Valve was one of the first to elegantly fit logical and instinctive missions throughout a continuous game. Some developers today could still learn from this narrative style.

That was the point of its critical acclaim; obviously many games already had a story (some really good ones too, mostly in adventure games and RPGs), but Valve made a totally linear game feel organic. How did they do it? By refining storytelling itself for an interactive medium; by having people in the game give you missions that are simple enough and make sense but, at the same time, move the plot along quite nicely; or better yet, they make YOU actually move the plot along. Things happen all around you, but you are the one who actually advances the plot; and you may not even notice it because your actions just make so goddamn sense in a very straightforward way. In other words, you can only do one thing; but it is what you would probably do anyway, so the world feels much greater than it actually is. 

So, not only do they achieve this without the book-y medium of exposition, but they mostly dispense of the &quot;show and don&#39;t tell&quot; film mantra: they use your intuitive interaction through the game to tell a story. Still, there is a big part of &quot;show&quot;, but it is in subtle scripted sequences and semi-hidden texts; they are there if YOU look for them, which adds interaction, instead of shoving them in your face. There is literally no necessary exposition. The sequels screw this up a little, but still excel at it overall.

In this chart, plot-centric chapters (e.g. Questionable Ethics), puzzle-centric chapters (e.g. Blast Pit) and boss-centric chapters (e.g. Gonarch’s Lair) do not constitute as missions themselves since none are explicitly given; if the game wasn’t linear, they could conceivably be ignored. From a mission-centric point of view, these are just obstacles in the way of the actual objective. However, plot-crucial sub-missions (On A Rail) are not ignored, since the completion of the main mission hinges directly on these. I&#39;m including the ending too, although we don&#39;t have it yet for Black Mesa.

[b]Mission 1 - Get to the test chamber[/b]
[i]You are running late. Suit up, get to the test chamber and do your job.[/i]
Chapters: [b]Anomalous Materials[/b]
Given [by lobby desk guard]: at the beginning of [i]Chapter 2: Anomalous Materials[/i]
Fulfilled: by the end of [i]Chapter 2: Anomalous Materials[/i]

[b]Mission 2 - Get to the surface[/b]
[i]The test has opened a dimensional portal and aliens are invading. Get to the surface for help.[/i]
Chapters: [b]Unforeseen Consequences, Office Complex, We’ve Got Hostiles[/b]
Given [by scientist Eli Vance]: at the beginning of [i]Chapter 3: Unforeseen Consequences[/i]
Nullified*: by the beginning-to-two thirds through [i]Chapter 5: We’ve Got Hostiles[/i]
[i]*Partially nullified when “the help” arrive and start killing everyone; totally nullified when you get to the surface but get forced back inside by an artillery bombardment.[/i]

[b]Mission 3 - Get to the Lambda Complex[/b]
[i]The Lambda science team may be able to “end this catastrophe.” Get to them at the heart of the Lambda Complex at the other end of the facility using the decommissioned old rail system beyond the silo.[/i]
Chapters: [b]We’ve Got Hostiles, Blast Pit, Power Up, [On A Rail], Apprehension, Residue Processing, Questionable Ethics, Surface Tension, Forget About Freeman, [Lambda Core][/b]
Given [by a scientist]: at the end of [i]Chapter 5: We’ve Got Hostiles[/i]
Halted: at the beginning of [i]Chapter 8: On A Rail [b][Mission 3.1 given][/b][/i]

[INDENT][b]Mission 3.1 - Launch the rocket[/b]
[i]Lambda can close the dimensional portal with a satellite. Launch the satellite delivery rocket.[/i]
Chapters: [b]On A Rail[/b]
Given [by a scientist through a guard]: at the beginning of [i]Chapter 8: On A Rail[/i]
Fulfilled [nullified*]: by the end of [i]Chapter 8: On A Rail[/i]
[i]*Unbeknownst to you, it is technically nullified as the satellite is later blocked by Nihilanth.[/i][/INDENT]

Resumed: at the end of [i]Chapter 8: On A Rail [b][Mission 3.1 fulfilled][/b][/i]
Fulfilled: by the end of [i]Chapter 14: Lambda Core.[/i]

[b]Mission 4 - Kill the Nihilanth[/b]
[i]The portal between dimensions is being created and maintained by a single powerful being -you must kill it.[/i]
Chapters: [b]Lambda Core, Xen, Gonarch’s Lair, Interloper, Nihilanth[/b]
Given [by the Lambda science team]: at the end of [i]Chapter 14: Lambda Core[/i].
Fulfilled: by the end of [i]Chapter 18: Nihilanth[/i].

[b]Mission 5 - Choose your fate [Accept the job / Refuse and die][/b]
[i]The G-Man offers you a job -accept it or refuse and die at the hands of an alien army.[/i]
Chapters: [b]Endgame[/b]
Given [by the G-Man]: all throughout [i]Epilogue: Endgame[/i].
Fulfilled*: at the end of [i]Epilogue: Endgame.[/i]
[i]*Technically not fulfilled but nullified if refusal is chosen, as it is both deadly and non-canonical.[/i]

If I get this OCD anytime soon, I might have to calm my nerves again by trying the same thing with Half-Life 2 and episodes, although I suspect they will actually be much shorter, especially in the episodes. In Episode One, you basically have two main missions: the core stabilization and the escape from the city. Maybe the ending escort mission can be considered a plot-vital sub-mission, but that&#39;s a stretch. And, even though it is larger and feels more complex, there is also two main missions in Episode Two; reaching White Forest and defending the base, with the sub-missions of saving Alyx.

I hope that, maybe, this has helped some fans realize certain details on the structure and cohesion of the game that they might not have realized otherwise. But, honestly, most of all, I hope that really obsessive people find this kind of narrative layout as oddly soothing as I do.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 24 Jan 2013 08:45:17 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>The Cafeteria</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/half-life-storyline-by-missions/12017.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Half-Life storyline by missions</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Serza]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Mission 4.1 - Rally up with Alyx<br>
'Cos rescue teams need to be at least two-man.<br>
Chapters: Highway 17, Sandtraps, Nova Prospekt<br>
Given by Alyx at the start of Highway 17 over a radio.<br>
Fullfilled at the start of Entanglement (Rally point at the Train Depot reached)</p>
<p>Mission 4.2 - Capture Mossman<br>
'Cos everyone hates backstabbers.<br>
Chapters: Nova Prospekt, Entanglement<br>
Given by Alyx during Entanglement<br>
Fulfilled/Reactivated at the end of Entanglement when Mossman is first captured, then escapes with Eli via Combine Teleporter.</p>
<p>Mission 4.3 - Escape from Nova Prospekt<br>
'Cos you better be like “POOF, GORDON BE GONE!”<br>
Chapters: Entanglement<br>
Given by Alyx at the moment Eli is rescued<br>
Fulfilled at the end of Entanglement.</p>
<p>Mission 5 - Uprising!<br>
'Cos everyone loves Stalingrad-esque CQB fighting!<br>
Given at the start of Anticitizen One by Dr. Kleiner<br>
Chapters: Anticitizen One, “Follow Freeman!”<br>
Fulfilled at the end of “Follow Freeman!”</p>
<p>Mission 5.1 - Reach the Citadel<br>
'Cos you’re not fighting the boss the other way around.<br>
Given by Dr. Kleiner at the start of Anticitizen One<br>
Chapters: Anticitizen One, “Follow Freeman!”<br>
Fulfilled at the end of “Follow Freeman!”</p>
<p>Mission 6 - Infiltrate the Citadel<br>
Flashlight, yellow hazard suit, creeping up on you, guess who it is… too late! Whacked with the crowbar!<br>
Chapters: Our Benefactors<br>
Given by DOG at the end of “Follow Freeman!” (or Gordon, because DOG obviously shows you Alyx and Eli are there)<br>
Fulfilled at the end of Our Benefactors</p>
<p>Mission 7 - Showdown.<br>
Kill the enemy, thinking about escaping afterwards is voluntary.<br>
Given by Eli at the start of Dark Energy<br>
Chapters: Dark Energy<br>
Fulfilled at the end of Dark Energy by killing (?) Breen.</p>
<p>Mission 8 - “NOOO, ALYYYYYX!”<br>
Try to convince G-Man to save Alyx, because she’s going to die…<br>
But you fail! Damn G-Man muted you (even if you can talk during the rest of the games) so you couldn’t stand up for Alyx! She’s going to die, rest in peace.</p>
<p>Mission 9 - Wake up call!<br>
You have no idea what happened. Last thing you remember is G-Man talking to you, then something about Vortigaunts… Where the hell are you? Oh, wait, that building looks familiar…<br>
<em>Episode 1 starts</em></p>
<p>Feel free to fill in the X.1/2/3 missions for me…</p>
<p>I just love this. I blame the fact I didn’t play so long on Poison breed.</p>
<p>The first HL was genial by the fact the facility was pretty much the only real storyteller, IMHO. The second HL couldn’t afford so, but the environment still does a pretty good job at tellin the story all by itself.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/half-life-storyline-by-missions/12017/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/half-life-storyline-by-missions/12017/7</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jan 2013 08:45:17 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12017-7</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/half-life-storyline-by-missions/12017.rss">Half-Life storyline by missions</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Half-Life storyline by missions</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[BendyBread]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I really like this  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=9" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
<p>If you’re just playing Half Life/BMS as a shooter, you won’t really notice anything. It’s just shoot and progress gameplay. But once you pay attention properly and really immerse yourself you see the game has a story/plot and that it really all does lead up to things.</p>
<p>I’m not sure if I like that fact or not. All I know is that I liked it more in Half Life 2 where they kind of ‘told’ you what was happening. Call me small minded but it’s nice to have an obvious goal WITH story once in a while.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/half-life-storyline-by-missions/12017/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/half-life-storyline-by-missions/12017/6</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jan 2013 03:30:26 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12017-6</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/half-life-storyline-by-missions/12017.rss">Half-Life storyline by missions</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Half-Life storyline by missions</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Artic_Xiongmao]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Yeah, that was my point. That’s why I myself did. I already knew the storyline, but seeing it organized is still great. It puts it front and center, while in-game you are not constantly reminded of your mission.</p>
<p>Sorry anout that “wreack” thing. This is my second language after all. Errors like that slip through easily. However, hopefully you won’t see me confuse “their” with “there’re” and similar atrocities, because I learnt the language academically. I have a ridiculously terrible accent, though.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/half-life-storyline-by-missions/12017/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/half-life-storyline-by-missions/12017/5</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jan 2013 20:35:27 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12017-5</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/half-life-storyline-by-missions/12017.rss">Half-Life storyline by missions</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Half-Life storyline by missions</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypt]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Huh… I already knew all of this damn well, but for some reason seeing it organized and detailed is really nice.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Artic Xiongmao">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Artic Xiongmao:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>as opposed to the havok you wre<span class="bbcode-b">a</span>k in Nova Prospekt, which sparks the revolution.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/half-life-storyline-by-missions/12017/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/half-life-storyline-by-missions/12017/4</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jan 2013 20:18:19 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12017-4</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/half-life-storyline-by-missions/12017.rss">Half-Life storyline by missions</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Half-Life storyline by missions</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Artic_Xiongmao]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>You preserve the vehicle because if you don’t you get a Game Over, but it is just transport. The vehicle levels are not actually connected to the mission of rescuing Eli Vance; you could’ve conceivably do the whole thing walking. I wouldn’t call it an actual sub-mission inside the mission of the rescue. It takes you closer to Eli, but as a plot device it does not enable his rescue in any particular way, as opposed to the havock you wreck in Nova Prospekt, which sparks the revolution (although there is no explicit mission given to do so).</p>
<p>It’s much closer in spirit to those puzzle/boss-centric chapters; an obstacle, but instead of a wall or Tentacles or a boss, the obstacle is just the length of the road. You are there because you are going to rescue Eli Vance; the mode of transport is “just” gameplay. The same goes for your Father Gregory sub-mission, really: that’s a gameplay objective; necessary in-game, but not really plot-centric. In a way, he’s really the one making his ‘plot objective’ by escorting you, but that’s beside the point.</p>
<p>The sequels are not as ‘pure’ in this approach, certainly, but I think those sub-missions do not apply. Why? Although, from a gameplay point of view, you can’t progress without fulfilling them (like the Tentacles in Blast Pit or the whole thing in Power Up), they aren’t more than obstacles; these mini-objectives don’t further the main missions from a plot-centric point of view.</p>
<p>The rocket launch activation ENABLED the plot to happen; it was literally necessary for the main “Get to Lambda and fix it” mission to happen: for the “fix it” part to become a reality, first the Lambda team have to try and fail to close the portal with the satellite (that you launch), thus realizing that Nihilanth is maintaining it, which in turn gives you the “fix”: kill Nihilanth. The rocket sub-mission CAUSES the main mission by which it is encompassed to be possible directly from the narrative itself, thereby enabling the existence of the following missions (kill the Nihilanth, accept the job, and the whole sequel plots). It is not just a roadblock, although it may be just that from a gameplay perspective.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/half-life-storyline-by-missions/12017/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/half-life-storyline-by-missions/12017/3</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jan 2013 15:04:30 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12017-3</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/half-life-storyline-by-missions/12017.rss">Half-Life storyline by missions</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Half-Life storyline by missions</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[ysrael214]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>In Half-Life 2 -</p>
<p>You were supposed to go to Nova Prospekt until Barney interrupted you.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Mission 1</span>: -<span class="bbcode-b"> Go to Kleiner’s Lab</span><br>
<span class="bbcode-i">Meet your old friends and get your Hazard Suit on.</span><br>
Chapters: <span class="bbcode-b">Point Insertion</span><br>
<span class="bbcode-i">Given by Barney at the start of the chapter. You were supposed to get there for your Hazard Suit and to be teleported to Eli’s Lab.</span><br>
*Fullfilled by start of Chapter 2</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Mission 2</span> - <span class="bbcode-b">Go to Eli’s Lab in Black Mesa East</span><br>
<span class="bbcode-i">Go to Eli’s lab at Black Mesa East for the Civil Protection not to get you.</span><br>
Chapters: <span class="bbcode-b">A Red Letter Day, Route Kanal, Water Hazard, Black Mesa East</span><br>
<span class="bbcode-i">Given by Kleiner at start of Red Letter Day. You must go to Eli’s Lab but due to technical difficulties, you were noticed by the Administrator and identified you and you have to take the long way in going to Eli’s lab.<br>
*Fullfilled in Black Mesa East.</span></p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Mission 3 -Find your way to safety</span><br>
The Combine found you and tries to attack. D0G and the others defends the lab while you find your way out with your new weapon.<br>
Chapters: “We Don’t Go To Ravenholm”<br>
Given by Eli at the end of Black Mesa East. There is only one way out. Ravenholm.</p>
<p>*Fullfilled Mission 3 at the end of the chapter.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Mission 4 - Rescue Eli Vance</span><br>
He was taken by the Combine.<br>
Chapters: Highway 17, Sandtraps, Nova Prospekt, Entanglement<br>
Given by a Resistance citizen. You must rescue Eli at Nova Prospekt.<br>
[Mission 4.1 given too]</p>
<p>Halted Mission 4 at end of Entanglement.</p>
<p>To be continued…</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/half-life-storyline-by-missions/12017/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/half-life-storyline-by-missions/12017/2</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jan 2013 14:55:36 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12017-2</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/half-life-storyline-by-missions/12017.rss">Half-Life storyline by missions</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Half-Life storyline by missions</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Artic_Xiongmao]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I have always been rather interested in how the Half-Life plot is presented, especially in HL1 and its remake. It is so subtle that it leads many to think that there is no purpose-driven plot for most of the game, but the missions that different people give you are actually incredibly logical, consistent and intuitive. When I was a kid and played Half-Life for the first time, I really only got the “get to the test chamber” and “kill nihilanth” parts of the plot; the beginning and the end. But I was a kid. Now, after years of playing and replaying Half-Life and now Black Mesa, I’ve become a nerd -the kind of nerd that gets stupidly excited at the sight of charts. So I made one all about it.</p>
<p>I’m not trying to make a point other than how much of a bunch of geniuses Valve were. I know most Half-Life and Black Mesa fans will know all of this by heart. I just think it’d be fun to lay it out in such a way; I’m not making the point that the game would be better off with traditional game mission levels, but quite the opposite; Valve was one of the first to elegantly fit logical and instinctive missions throughout a continuous game. Some developers today could still learn from this narrative style.</p>
<p>That was the point of its critical acclaim; obviously many games already had a story (some really good ones too, mostly in adventure games and RPGs), but Valve made a totally linear game feel organic. How did they do it? By refining storytelling itself for an interactive medium; by having people in the game give you missions that are simple enough and make sense but, at the same time, move the plot along quite nicely; or better yet, they make YOU actually move the plot along. Things happen all around you, but you are the one who actually advances the plot; and you may not even notice it because your actions just make so goddamn sense in a very straightforward way. In other words, you can only do one thing; but it is what you would probably do anyway, so the world feels much greater than it actually is.</p>
<p>So, not only do they achieve this without the book-y medium of exposition, but they mostly dispense of the “show and don’t tell” film mantra: they use your intuitive interaction through the game to tell a story. Still, there is a big part of “show”, but it is in subtle scripted sequences and semi-hidden texts; they are there if YOU look for them, which adds interaction, instead of shoving them in your face. There is literally no necessary exposition. The sequels screw this up a little, but still excel at it overall.</p>
<p>In this chart, plot-centric chapters (e.g. Questionable Ethics), puzzle-centric chapters (e.g. Blast Pit) and boss-centric chapters (e.g. Gonarch’s Lair) do not constitute as missions themselves since none are explicitly given; if the game wasn’t linear, they could conceivably be ignored. From a mission-centric point of view, these are just obstacles in the way of the actual objective. However, plot-crucial sub-missions (On A Rail) are not ignored, since the completion of the main mission hinges directly on these. I’m including the ending too, although we don’t have it yet for Black Mesa.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Mission 1 - Get to the test chamber</span><br>
<span class="bbcode-i">You are running late. Suit up, get to the test chamber and do your job.</span><br>
Chapters: <span class="bbcode-b">Anomalous Materials</span><br>
Given [by lobby desk guard]: at the beginning of <span class="bbcode-i">Chapter 2: Anomalous Materials</span><br>
Fulfilled: by the end of <span class="bbcode-i">Chapter 2: Anomalous Materials</span></p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Mission 2 - Get to the surface</span><br>
<span class="bbcode-i">The test has opened a dimensional portal and aliens are invading. Get to the surface for help.</span><br>
Chapters: <span class="bbcode-b">Unforeseen Consequences, Office Complex, We’ve Got Hostiles</span><br>
Given [by scientist Eli Vance]: at the beginning of <span class="bbcode-i">Chapter 3: Unforeseen Consequences</span><br>
Nullified*: by the beginning-to-two thirds through <span class="bbcode-i">Chapter 5: We’ve Got Hostiles</span><br>
<span class="bbcode-i">*Partially nullified when “the help” arrive and start killing everyone; totally nullified when you get to the surface but get forced back inside by an artillery bombardment.</span></p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Mission 3 - Get to the Lambda Complex</span><br>
<span class="bbcode-i">The Lambda science team may be able to “end this catastrophe.” Get to them at the heart of the Lambda Complex at the other end of the facility using the decommissioned old rail system beyond the silo.</span><br>
Chapters: <span class="bbcode-b">We’ve Got Hostiles, Blast Pit, Power Up, [On A Rail], Apprehension, Residue Processing, Questionable Ethics, Surface Tension, Forget About Freeman, [Lambda Core]</span><br>
Given [by a scientist]: at the end of <span class="bbcode-i">Chapter 5: We’ve Got Hostiles</span><br>
Halted: at the beginning of <span class="bbcode-i">Chapter 8: On A Rail <span class="bbcode-b">[Mission 3.1 given]</span></span></p>
<p>[INDENT]<span class="bbcode-b">Mission 3.1 - Launch the rocket</span><br>
<span class="bbcode-i">Lambda can close the dimensional portal with a satellite. Launch the satellite delivery rocket.</span><br>
Chapters: <span class="bbcode-b">On A Rail</span><br>
Given [by a scientist through a guard]: at the beginning of <span class="bbcode-i">Chapter 8: On A Rail</span><br>
Fulfilled [nullified*]: by the end of <span class="bbcode-i">Chapter 8: On A Rail</span><br>
<span class="bbcode-i">*Unbeknownst to you, it is technically nullified as the satellite is later blocked by Nihilanth.</span>[/INDENT]</p>
<p>Resumed: at the end of <span class="bbcode-i">Chapter 8: On A Rail <span class="bbcode-b">[Mission 3.1 fulfilled]</span></span><br>
Fulfilled: by the end of <span class="bbcode-i">Chapter 14: Lambda Core.</span></p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Mission 4 - Kill the Nihilanth</span><br>
<span class="bbcode-i">The portal between dimensions is being created and maintained by a single powerful being -you must kill it.</span><br>
Chapters: <span class="bbcode-b">Lambda Core, Xen, Gonarch’s Lair, Interloper, Nihilanth</span><br>
Given [by the Lambda science team]: at the end of <span class="bbcode-i">Chapter 14: Lambda Core</span>.<br>
Fulfilled: by the end of <span class="bbcode-i">Chapter 18: Nihilanth</span>.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Mission 5 - Choose your fate [Accept the job / Refuse and die]</span><br>
<span class="bbcode-i">The G-Man offers you a job -accept it or refuse and die at the hands of an alien army.</span><br>
Chapters: <span class="bbcode-b">Endgame</span><br>
Given [by the G-Man]: all throughout <span class="bbcode-i">Epilogue: Endgame</span>.<br>
Fulfilled*: at the end of <span class="bbcode-i">Epilogue: Endgame.</span><br>
<span class="bbcode-i">*Technically not fulfilled but nullified if refusal is chosen, as it is both deadly and non-canonical.</span></p>
<p>If I get this OCD anytime soon, I might have to calm my nerves again by trying the same thing with Half-Life 2 and episodes, although I suspect they will actually be much shorter, especially in the episodes. In Episode One, you basically have two main missions: the core stabilization and the escape from the city. Maybe the ending escort mission can be considered a plot-vital sub-mission, but that’s a stretch. And, even though it is larger and feels more complex, there is also two main missions in Episode Two; reaching White Forest and defending the base, with the sub-missions of saving Alyx.</p>
<p>I hope that, maybe, this has helped some fans realize certain details on the structure and cohesion of the game that they might not have realized otherwise. But, honestly, most of all, I hope that really obsessive people find this kind of narrative layout as oddly soothing as I do.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/half-life-storyline-by-missions/12017/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/half-life-storyline-by-missions/12017/1</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jan 2013 13:47:53 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12017-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/half-life-storyline-by-missions/12017.rss">Half-Life storyline by missions</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
