<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Opposing Force Source?</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/opposing-force-source/362</link>
    <description>Hey all, I&#39;m new to the board but I&#39;ve been an avid HL player since &#39;99. I found out about this mod and was drawn to it immediately and really appreciated what they were trying to do with one of the greatest games ever made. I feel that they can make such a game even greater and I&#39;m looking forward to it&#39;s release very much. 

That being said, I loved Opposing Force. I remember waiting as a 13 year old for it to be released very impatiently. I remember the PC Gamer preview on it, it seemed that being a Marine in the game was going to add a whole other dimension of gameplay to Half-Life. I don&#39;t remember the exact wording but they mentioned that the player would have the ability to call in back up, call in air support, use the radio for whatever, and there was going to be a lot of squad action, I wasn&#39;t expecting it to be another lone-ranger solo storyline; I was really anticipating the player to go in there and simply just crush and destroy everything in his/her path as we saw the Marines in the 1st Half-Life doing.

I loved Opposing Force, but after playing it I was disappointed. Although there was a little bit more squad combat, it wasn&#39;t what I was hoping for. With that, I set out back in those days to try and start up a recreation of what Opposing Force SHOULD&#39;VE been like. It was fail (as a 14/15 year old knowing nothing about putting a mod together you would expect that), however it still even now seems like it would be a great thing to try and tackle. That is where most of my appreciation for Black Mesa Source comes from, because I&#39;ve seen what they&#39;ve done with the original, and it looks to me that they could do the same with Opposing Force. 

Now I know Black Mesa Source is all about re-making the original, whilst mine is pretty much completely rewriting it; there&#39;s no doubt in my mind that says this wouldn&#39;t be 10x cooler. What I am pretty much suggesting is that Opposing Force should be remade much more towards the way of which PC Gamer previewed it... You, Adrian Shephard, go into Black Mesa and are a part of a Marine squad; you have missions and objectives you have to complete (namely kill every person working for black mesa, mainly Freeman and other elusive field scientists, as well as hunt down groups of aliens roaming the facility), with all the aforementioned tools and capabilities at your disposal. I don&#39;t mind the solo-single player story, and I think in some instances that should remain, however I&#39;d love for some more NPC/Player interaction and content. 

My idea actually expanded the content and perspective of Half-Life in many different ways. I intended to have 3 groups of perspective to play from: Marines, Black Ops (If anyone ever remembers a long defunct single player half-life mod &quot;Black Ops&quot;?), and a special Marine detatchment I made up called Surgical Strike Squads (basically elite Marines who are on par and counter the Black Ops, making for some really great NPC vs. NPC action.). 

Each perspective featured several characters with different stories/locations/roles to play through as well, from machine gunner or sniper marines, to female assasins or elite black ops, to the simply bad ass tactical masters from the SSS; every character covering a different peice of the puzzle in the Half-Life storyline, making it more and more interesting. 

All of this being aided by the addition of each groups selection of new conventional weaponry for a better variety, to make everything more interesting. Not to mention, there were a lot of ideas I had for this mod (as well as other projects I thought up) that I still to this day (10 years later) have not seen implemented in any first person shooter yet, which would enrich the gameplay and quality of the mod.

I know it&#39;s an eye-full of ideas, but if anyone else had any recollection of the particular article in PC Gamer I&#39;m referring to, I was hoping that anyone who may in fact remember it, would clearly understand what my main source of inspiration for this was. Anyhow, I&#39;m done rambling about that. Let me know what you guys think about remaking the original Opposing Force.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 26 May 2009 16:42:30 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Half-Life Series</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/opposing-force-source/362.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Opposing Force Source?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NotToBeFound]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Myself personally, I’ve never hardly used the alien weapons in the game, I was never big on them, I always used conventional ones, dunno why, that’s just me.</p>
<p>As far as those go I don’t really have a preference on them being in the game, that would probably be better sorted out within a fan-based poll or the project team. I always thought they were kind of stupid (although fun at some points…), I mean who is gonna know how to use an alien weapon? Or how to coax a barnacle into being an extension of your hand?</p>
<p>Yeah I know the list is huge but I honestly see it opposite, I found the amount of weapons in Half-Life boring, 2 pistols an SMG and a shotgun… If anyone’s ever played Counter-Life (Where you can play half-life with Counter-Strike weapons), that to me is always fun. I love being able to switch weapons and mix it up… there’s certain points in the gameplay where certain weapons on the CS list just makes it so much fun…</p>
<p>As far as being limited to what you can carry, yes I probably would implement something like that… at the very least something similar to the way Counter-Life was, where you could carry one of everything (pistol, smg, shotgun, rifle, sniper rifle, mg etc), but more than likely the player would be limited to 2 pistols, 1 shotgun, 1 smg, and their choice of either 1 assault rifle, or 1 sniper rifle, or 1 MG. I think that’s a decent balance between fun factor and realism, as it’s not terribly unrealistic for someone to carry that amount of firepower.</p>
<p>And actually, in all reality, there’s not so many guns. There’s just ones with different attachments on them… here is the list of the type of guns:</p>
<p>Glock<br>
.357<br>
Sig P226 .357<br>
M9<br>
SOCOM<br>
Para P14</p>
<p>Remington 870 (870PM6)<br>
HK 1014<br>
Mossberg 590A1 (Spas replacement)</p>
<p>MP5Navy (MP5KA3) MP5SD3<br>
PDW<br>
TMP<br>
Mac-10</p>
<p>M-16A2 (M16A2 m/203)<br>
M-4A1 (M-4A1 m/203)<br>
G36 (G36C) (G36K GL) (G36 GL)<br>
M1A Scout (M1A Scout GL) (M1A Socom) (M1A Socom GL)<br>
Mini 14</p>
<p>M-249<br>
MG36<br>
M60-E3</p>
<p>M-40A1<br>
PSG-1<br>
M21</p>
<p>Still long, but you see that a lot of them will be the same weapons with different attachments and such, much like COD-4.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/opposing-force-source/362/29">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/opposing-force-source/362/29</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 26 May 2009 16:42:30 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-362-29</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/opposing-force-source/362.rss">Opposing Force Source?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Opposing Force Source?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[iKy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>your ideeas would better be thrown in an "7 hour war " mod…</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/opposing-force-source/362/28">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/opposing-force-source/362/28</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 26 May 2009 15:08:13 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-362-28</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/opposing-force-source/362.rss">Opposing Force Source?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Opposing Force Source?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Dias]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>With that comedicly long list of weapons, I’m assuming that you’d like a limited inventory size of three or four guns like in fear or something. Am I right?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/opposing-force-source/362/27">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/opposing-force-source/362/27</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 26 May 2009 02:35:15 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-362-27</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/opposing-force-source/362.rss">Opposing Force Source?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Opposing Force Source?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[JeffMOD]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="NotToBeFound">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/n/d9b06d/40.png" class="avatar"> NotToBeFound:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>My list of new weapons is extensive but nothing short of awesome:</p>
<p>Marines:<br>
Beretta M9<br>
MP5-Navy<br>
H&amp;K PDW<br>
Remington 870 Tactical<br>
M-16A2<br>
M-16A2/M-203<br>
M-4A1<br>
M-4A1/M-203<br>
M-249<br>
M-40A1</p>
<p>Black Ops:<br>
H&amp;K SOCOM/USP<br>
Steyr TMP<br>
MP5-SD3<br>
H&amp;K XM1014<br>
G36<br>
G36/GL<br>
G36C<br>
G36K/GL<br>
MG36<br>
H&amp;K PSG1</p>
<p>SSS:<br>
Para Ordnance P-14 .45<br>
Tactical Mac-10<br>
H&amp;K MP5KA3 (Rechamber of something more potent than 9mm, .357 Sig or .40S&amp;W?)<br>
Remington 870PM6<br>
M1A Scout EBR (All M1A’s fully auto and with 30 Round mags)<br>
M1A Scout EBR/M203<br>
M1A Socom 16 EBR<br>
M1A Socom 16 EBR/M203<br>
M60E3<br>
M21</p>
<p>With the addition of:<br>
Mossberg 590A1 (To replace SPAS-12)<br>
Ruger Mini 14<br>
Glock Remodel<br>
.357 Remodel<br>
Desert Eagle .357 Remodel<br>
Sig  P226 .357</p>
<p>You’re probably wondering, “Why so many guns?”. Why not? I figure this makes the game more interesting…</p>
<p>Not to mention, ever noticed that the way a lot of guns are skinned, they always have the same texture, decal or scatch in the same spot? To me, imagine if everytime you picked up a gun (the same gun…) it didn’t look like all of the other ones… Yeah, a lot of work, but I love authenticity and realism. Nothing shouts boring to me like picking up 15 different M16-A3’s in COD4 and seeing the same “Blue 4” or whatever it says on the side of it. Just a neat little feature that could be attempted I think.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>While the alternate skin idea is good, make sure you know the following:<br>
You’d need to code ALL of these weapons, and add all the different ammo types, model everything… It’s a lot of work. Start simple.<br>
Also, a lot of similar guns aren’t that fun. Ever wonder why HL2 has so few weapons? Variety is key, more than 3 automatic weapons/pistols/rifles/ect. are going to be boring. Go for one SMG, a shotgun, an auto rifle, two pistols, a sniper rifle, and a heavy weapon tops. (and explosives) Trust me, that much work gets boring.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/opposing-force-source/362/26">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/opposing-force-source/362/26</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 26 May 2009 00:28:30 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-362-26</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/opposing-force-source/362.rss">Opposing Force Source?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Opposing Force Source?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[iKy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>how about the alien guns?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/opposing-force-source/362/25">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/opposing-force-source/362/25</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 25 May 2009 21:52:02 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-362-25</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/opposing-force-source/362.rss">Opposing Force Source?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Opposing Force Source?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[InterloperX]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>The thing I have to say about the guns list is to try and avoid what would in the end make for repetitive gameplay.  I understand the desire to have vintage weapons, but outside of a Battlefield or Call of Duty game, it just seems out of place, especially in a Sci-Fi game.</p>
<p>Also, you’d better have a dedicated texturing team if you want all weapons to look individual, or have enough variety in textures where it “feels” like you’re always picking up a different weapon (even if same model).</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/opposing-force-source/362/24">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/opposing-force-source/362/24</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 25 May 2009 15:23:15 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-362-24</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/opposing-force-source/362.rss">Opposing Force Source?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Opposing Force Source?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NotToBeFound]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>My list of new weapons is extensive but nothing short of awesome:</p>
<p>Marines:<br>
Beretta M9<br>
MP5-Navy<br>
H&amp;K PDW<br>
Remington 870 Tactical<br>
M-16A2<br>
M-16A2/M-203<br>
M-4A1<br>
M-4A1/M-203<br>
M-249<br>
M-40A1</p>
<p>Black Ops:<br>
H&amp;K SOCOM/USP<br>
Steyr TMP<br>
MP5-SD3<br>
H&amp;K XM1014<br>
G36<br>
G36/GL<br>
G36C<br>
G36K/GL<br>
MG36<br>
H&amp;K PSG1</p>
<p>SSS:<br>
Para Ordnance P-14 .45<br>
Tactical Mac-10<br>
H&amp;K MP5KA3 (Rechamber of something more potent than 9mm, .357 Sig or .40S&amp;W?)<br>
Remington 870PM6<br>
M1A Scout EBR (All M1A’s fully auto and with 30 Round mags)<br>
M1A Scout EBR/M203<br>
M1A Socom 16 EBR<br>
M1A Socom 16 EBR/M203<br>
M60E3<br>
M21</p>
<p>With the addition of:<br>
Mossberg 590A1 (To replace SPAS-12)<br>
Ruger Mini 14<br>
Glock Remodel<br>
.357 Remodel<br>
Desert Eagle .357 Remodel<br>
Sig  P226 .357</p>
<p>You’re probably wondering, “Why so many guns?”. Why not? I figure this makes the game more interesting…</p>
<p>Not to mention, ever noticed that the way a lot of guns are skinned, they always have the same texture, decal or scatch in the same spot? To me, imagine if everytime you picked up a gun (the same gun…) it didn’t look like all of the other ones… Yeah, a lot of work, but I love authenticity and realism. Nothing shouts boring to me like picking up 15 different M16-A3’s in COD4 and seeing the same “Blue 4” or whatever it says on the side of it. Just a neat little feature that could be attempted I think.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/opposing-force-source/362/23">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/opposing-force-source/362/23</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 25 May 2009 15:17:54 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-362-23</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/opposing-force-source/362.rss">Opposing Force Source?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Opposing Force Source?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[InterloperX]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I think what Gearbox was attempting to do with the nuking of Black Mesa in Opposing Force was avoiding a conflict with what Valve intended when Nihilanth was destroyed, and whether or not that would have had just as catastrophic an effect on Black Mesa considering it was Nihilanth that was holding the connection between the two realms. (Perhaps whole chunks of the BMRF were teleported to the Xen world in the chaos, things like that).</p>
<p>Of course Valve never clarified as canon what did actually happen in the events immediately after Nihilanth’s defeat, so it is open to interpretation, but I do feel that Valve meant to have that feel like the definitive end of the BMRF.</p>
<p>Such is the issue when working with non-canon continuity.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/opposing-force-source/362/22">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/opposing-force-source/362/22</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 25 May 2009 15:13:16 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-362-22</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/opposing-force-source/362.rss">Opposing Force Source?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Opposing Force Source?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NotToBeFound]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Nah. I see what you’re saying but to me that’s too generic. I don’t ever do anything if it’s not original (at least in regard to the originality considering the goal or intent of this idea, despite it being an extension/rewrite of another story).</p>
<p>For anyone who played through Half-Life or any of it’s add-ons, that thought “What if?” or “What other stuff happened in Black Mesa while I was running around in that orage suit?”. When I played Opposing Force, I wanted to do more, I wanted more action, specifically organized with the military forces.</p>
<p>All maps and scenes for Black Mesa would pretty much be new and original… save for a few key characters or something.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/opposing-force-source/362/21">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/opposing-force-source/362/21</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 25 May 2009 14:51:49 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-362-21</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/opposing-force-source/362.rss">Opposing Force Source?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Opposing Force Source?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[JeffMOD]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Dias">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/d/4491bb/40.png" class="avatar"> Dias:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>If you took out a few of those minor details, and added a few of your own, it could be an original game. You don’t need to ride HL’s coat tails for it to be good or popular. If you could come up with all those changes, then it couldn’t be too hard to change just enough plot elements to make the story different from HL’s. Making a different plot dissociated from HL opens up more possibilities for gameplay and story elements that wouldn’t be as welcomed by HL fans who’d expect it to be truer to the source material.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>This man is right. With all the new features, It would be it’s own mod, no HL ties nessisary! Learn to map/code/model, get a team up, and figure out the storyline. Perhaps a terrorist strike on a city, and the army has to take the terrorists out, as well as find and defuse a nuke, and maybe some of the citizens have been irradated by it, or just went insane. Just a thought, don’t need to credit me if you use it as a base. :3</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/opposing-force-source/362/20">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/opposing-force-source/362/20</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 May 2009 23:04:44 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-362-20</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/opposing-force-source/362.rss">Opposing Force Source?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Opposing Force Source?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Dias]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>If you took out a few of those minor details, and added a few of your own, it could be an original game. You don’t need to ride HL’s coat tails for it to be good or popular. If you could come up with all those changes, then it couldn’t be too hard to change just enough plot elements to make the story different from HL’s. Making a different plot dissociated from HL opens up more possibilities for gameplay and story elements that wouldn’t be as welcomed by HL fans who’d expect it to be truer to the source material.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/opposing-force-source/362/19">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/opposing-force-source/362/19</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 May 2009 22:44:07 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-362-19</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/opposing-force-source/362.rss">Opposing Force Source?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Opposing Force Source?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NotToBeFound]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>HECU? The marines? They still would be, but the way in which they handle it would be different, I designed the story to be that way so that gameplay is longer, not just “half a day or one day of fighting, too many aliens, let’s nuke the place…” it’ll be a longer campaign to make it more interesting, some characters stories would actually intersect with each others.</p>
<p>For example Shephard works closely with a couple of the elite SSS guys in fighting the Black Ops, and Shephard himself later on becomes an SSS man you can play as; one of the Black Op characters you play as is in a squad who is annihilated by Shephard or the SSS and has to run and hide from them. My whole goal is to make it as intense as possible with a lot more action and replay value. If it’s even possible, I’d like to try and make for alternate paths/choices/endings, depending on the players choices (like if they go down this hallway to complete this objective, or the other hallway to avoid it), their fate will be different. Scripted cutscenes would also be kind of cool and I have seen them done, to give the mod a more cinematic feel. All of this gives the game more replay value as well.</p>
<p>It IS a lot to take on, but I’m confident it would be worth every second of effort.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/opposing-force-source/362/18">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/opposing-force-source/362/18</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 May 2009 13:51:12 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-362-18</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/opposing-force-source/362.rss">Opposing Force Source?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Opposing Force Source?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Duck]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>lol.<br>
Operation Black Mesa Source (Opposing Force Source)</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/opposing-force-source/362/17">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/opposing-force-source/362/17</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 May 2009 06:13:12 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-362-17</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/opposing-force-source/362.rss">Opposing Force Source?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Opposing Force Source?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Ballsopt]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>sooo what happened to the whole HECU being overwhelmed by alien forces?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/opposing-force-source/362/16">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/opposing-force-source/362/16</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 May 2009 04:58:53 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-362-16</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/opposing-force-source/362.rss">Opposing Force Source?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Opposing Force Source?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NotToBeFound]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>So in what way is it a remake or sequel?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Not a sequel at all. I guess remake isn’t the right word, rewrite would be the correct word.</p>
<p>Adrian Shephard goes into Black mesa (instead of being shot down), arrives at a landing base in black mesa, right outside an entrance into a parking garage. He gets off the helicopter, a grunt is waiting for him with a message to go and see the CO in his personal trailer. He goes and gets his orders, which are to go down into the parking garage which is inhabited by loads of staff, and immediately take them out, no questions asked (even against his own conscience).</p>
<p>Adrian and his squad open the huge door and ride down into the garage in an APC, storm out and start shooting all scientists and security guards. After that, they’re ordered deeper into the facility to push forward into cleaning it out section by section. I never really went any further than that in detail, but it would get more and more involved… they eventually have the black ops turn on them like always, and start combating the Black ops. With each release, a new marine, black op or SSS man’s story could be added to the mod to be played through?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/opposing-force-source/362/15">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/opposing-force-source/362/15</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 May 2009 04:11:42 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-362-15</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/opposing-force-source/362.rss">Opposing Force Source?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Opposing Force Source?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[InterloperX]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Ahh, well…  That would definitely require putting together a mod team of your own for sure.  It’s one thing to suggest doing a remake (with some creative license) of an existing game with an established fanbase and a completely different one to suggest adding a completely new chapter of your own into the Black Mesa Incident continuity.</p>
<p>Best thing I can suggest is posting bullet point the structure of the story you’d like to take gamers through as well as the features you’d like to implement, and the best place to do it would probably be the Steam community forums.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/opposing-force-source/362/14">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/opposing-force-source/362/14</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 May 2009 02:02:44 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-362-14</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/opposing-force-source/362.rss">Opposing Force Source?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Opposing Force Source?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Dias]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="NotToBeFound">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/n/d9b06d/40.png" class="avatar"> NotToBeFound:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Basically a completely new story, new characters, new perspectives, new weapons…</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>So in what way is it a remake or sequel?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/opposing-force-source/362/13">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/opposing-force-source/362/13</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 May 2009 02:01:59 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-362-13</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/opposing-force-source/362.rss">Opposing Force Source?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Opposing Force Source?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NotToBeFound]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="InterloperX">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/i/96bed5/40.png" class="avatar"> InterloperX:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>“Reload Pvt. Shepard.”  “Sorry Pvt. Shepard, I’ll get out of your way now.” etc etc.</p>
<p><img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=9" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji only-emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"></p>
<p>Seriously though, if it’s a case of not having the squad based action and air strike calls as involved as I thought you were getting at, you may as well keep track of the Opposing Force update on the moddb page and making those suggestions there.</p>
<p><a href="https://www.moddb.com/mods/operation-black-mesa" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://www.moddb.com/mods/operation-black-mesa</a></p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>No, it’s still involved believed me. I was just saying I think it would be easier to do than you think… recall Firearms or other instances in other mods I remember having the ability to rig up airstrikes in some kind of way… Basically a completely new story, new characters, new perspectives, new weapons…</p>
<p>That one you showed me looks great, but mine’s still completely different. The storyline will not be the same. You arrive in Black Mesa in one peice at a Heli-pad, you get your orders from your CO and you ride into battle in an APC and jump out killing everything in a parking garage… then it goes from there.  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=9" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/opposing-force-source/362/12">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/opposing-force-source/362/12</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 May 2009 01:59:16 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-362-12</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/opposing-force-source/362.rss">Opposing Force Source?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Opposing Force Source?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[InterloperX]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>“Reload Pvt. Shepard.”  “Sorry Pvt. Shepard, I’ll get out of your way now.” etc etc.</p>
<p><img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=9" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji only-emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"></p>
<p>Seriously though, if it’s a case of not having the squad based action and air strike calls as involved as I thought you were getting at, you may as well keep track of the Opposing Force update on the moddb page and making those suggestions there.</p>
<p><a href="https://www.moddb.com/mods/operation-black-mesa" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://www.moddb.com/mods/operation-black-mesa</a></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/opposing-force-source/362/11">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/opposing-force-source/362/11</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 May 2009 01:47:47 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-362-11</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/opposing-force-source/362.rss">Opposing Force Source?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Opposing Force Source?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NotToBeFound]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Daemonfaa">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/d/e19adc/40.png" class="avatar"> Daemonfaa:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I lol’d</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Wow that guy’s a douche.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="John Killer118">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 John Killer118:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>…WOW… all that work… all that thinking you did…<br>
No, the Black Mesa Team will not remake Opposing Force or Blue Shift.™</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>So is that one.  I gather that, I got it, and really I wasn’t just saying “hey they should to it” I said it would be cool if they would, but it’s open to other interested parties as well. FYI, I did a lot of modeling and mapping on it too, it wasn’t just “all that thinking”.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>You’d be utterly, completely wrong about that. The suggestion box is for making suggestions for how the BM devs can improve the BM experience as a Half-Life remake, whereas at best this sounds like an idea for a wildly different mod.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I meant this forum in general, and it seems like the particular forum this thread was moved to sees limited traffic compared to this one, but ok.</p>
<p>As far as the squad action I’m referring to, I guess I should’ve clarified that I didn’t have any intention of really making it anymore involved than it already was… all of the airstrike actions and radio use would be scripted sequences or binded. However I think the AI could just be tweaked to tie into the idea of more squad action and such. This could easilly be done within the Half-Life engine(s) I believe.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/opposing-force-source/362/10">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/opposing-force-source/362/10</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 May 2009 01:41:35 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-362-10</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/opposing-force-source/362.rss">Opposing Force Source?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Opposing Force Source?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Mont_Blanc]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Maybe use OF2 or ARMA for base to a mod for Opposing Force if you want really want squad action but I don’t know if they’re suited for close quarter combat.</p>
<p>Expending the content like you propose is a hell lot of work for a single mod, with all those factions.<br>
I could see somethnig like that but from a different point, like Warcraft/starcraft where you move your little squad from above, killing headcrabs, vorts and scis all around BMRF  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=9" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/opposing-force-source/362/9">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/opposing-force-source/362/9</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 May 2009 00:35:40 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-362-9</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/opposing-force-source/362.rss">Opposing Force Source?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Opposing Force Source?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[raw_bean]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="NotToBeFound">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/n/d9b06d/40.png" class="avatar"> NotToBeFound:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Right, I’ve seen all that but this is drastically different then what any of them are doing. I’m just mearly suggesting or trying to get feedback on the idea, since I would say it’s safe to assume this is the best place for feedback on such ideas.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>You’d be utterly, completely wrong about that. The suggestion box is for making suggestions for how the BM devs can improve the BM experience as a Half-Life remake, whereas at best this sounds like an idea for a wildly different mod.</p>
<p>I’d say the HL series board is probably the best place for this. [COLOR=‘Red’]Moved.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/opposing-force-source/362/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/opposing-force-source/362/8</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 20 May 2009 23:29:11 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-362-8</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/opposing-force-source/362.rss">Opposing Force Source?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Opposing Force Source?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[John_Killer118]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>…WOW… all that work… all that thinking you did…<br>
No, the Black Mesa Team will not remake Opposing Force or Blue Shift.™</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/opposing-force-source/362/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/opposing-force-source/362/7</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 20 May 2009 22:50:13 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-362-7</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/opposing-force-source/362.rss">Opposing Force Source?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Opposing Force Source?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Daemonfaa]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I lol’d</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/opposing-force-source/362/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/opposing-force-source/362/6</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 20 May 2009 22:05:54 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-362-6</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/opposing-force-source/362.rss">Opposing Force Source?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Opposing Force Source?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[The_Javid]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I’m surpised this thread hasn’t been locked</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/opposing-force-source/362/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/opposing-force-source/362/5</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 20 May 2009 21:16:16 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-362-5</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/opposing-force-source/362.rss">Opposing Force Source?</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
