<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Surface Tension Helicopter Dam Battle Crash</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/surface-tension-helicopter-dam-battle-crash/11895</link>
    <description>NOTE: I know there&#39;s probably a dozen other threads about game crashes but whatever.

Hi everyone,
   Completed the game a while back in Early October. I must say: BEST MOD EVER. But there was several crashes that made my experience not so great. Most of them were caused by too much detail, I think, that my laptop couldn&#39;t cope with. But one that stood out was the Helicopter Battle on the Dam in Surface Tension. I collected my Tau ammo from inside the building, I go out to kick the helicopter&#39;s ass, I shoot a 5 second charged blast from the Tau at the helicopter then the screen and game freeze, my screen goes dark and it shuts down all by itself. My experienced ruined: &quot; I :&#39;( just a little&quot;. So I think of some other ways to avoid this crash: Use a different gun, avoid the helicopter and run for it into the water etc. So I have posted my thoughts here I will suggest 1 thing: Take a bit of detail out of the helicopter probably. It&#39;s a great design but my laptop can&#39;t cope with the large amount of detail.
But still, great mod, hope changes like this can be made  :slight_smile:</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 24 Dec 2012 10:55:31 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>In-game Issues (Mod)</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/surface-tension-helicopter-dam-battle-crash/11895.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Surface Tension Helicopter Dam Battle Crash</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[D3lta]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Or you can bring down the options a bit so your laptop can handle it.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/surface-tension-helicopter-dam-battle-crash/11895/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/surface-tension-helicopter-dam-battle-crash/11895/2</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 24 Dec 2012 10:55:31 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11895-2</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/surface-tension-helicopter-dam-battle-crash/11895.rss">Surface Tension Helicopter Dam Battle Crash</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Surface Tension Helicopter Dam Battle Crash</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[BlackMesarulez98]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>NOTE: I know there’s probably a dozen other threads about game crashes but whatever.</p>
<p>Hi everyone,<br>
Completed the game a while back in Early October. I must say: BEST MOD EVER. But there was several crashes that made my experience not so great. Most of them were caused by too much detail, I think, that my laptop couldn’t cope with. But one that stood out was the Helicopter Battle on the Dam in Surface Tension. I collected my Tau ammo from inside the building, I go out to kick the helicopter’s ass, I shoot a 5 second charged blast from the Tau at the helicopter then the screen and game freeze, my screen goes dark and it shuts down all by itself. My experienced ruined: " I :’( just a little". So I think of some other ways to avoid this crash: Use a different gun, avoid the helicopter and run for it into the water etc. So I have posted my thoughts here I will suggest 1 thing: Take a bit of detail out of the helicopter probably. It’s a great design but my laptop can’t cope with the large amount of detail.<br>
But still, great mod, hope changes like this can be made  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=9" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/surface-tension-helicopter-dam-battle-crash/11895/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/surface-tension-helicopter-dam-battle-crash/11895/1</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 24 Dec 2012 08:54:40 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11895-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/surface-tension-helicopter-dam-battle-crash/11895.rss">Surface Tension Helicopter Dam Battle Crash</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
