<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Black Mesa vs. Half-Life 2</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/black-mesa-vs-half-life-2/13646</link>
    <description>Playing Half-Life 2 right after Black Mesa may have been a mistake. BM is a great, very pretty game and to be perfectly honest... HL2 has not held up graphically. How could it have? It&#39;s 10 years old by now. As I found myself pushing through Route Canal, fighting the urge to shut down the game and play something else, I had to stop and wonder why. I used to LOVE Half-Life 2. I even played it recently. Why does it feel so much worse now than it did before? My answer, as it turns out, is Black Mesa did it better. Let me see if I can explain why.

Black Mesa does two things so right I never even realise they were &quot;things&quot; to begin with. It does them so well, in fact, that I&#39;m now having a hard time playing most other games because I&#39;ve become aware of it. These two things are:

*Locations look like real, recognisable things. I recall playing through the original Half-Life and interpreting places as &quot;a corridor,&quot; &quot;a room,&quot; &quot;a courtyard&quot; and so on. The old engine&#39;s limitations simply didn&#39;t allow for anything more specific. Going through Black Mesa, however, is a much more stimulating experience. I can look into a window in a warehouse area (which I recognise AS a warehouse area) and see what looks like a machine shop inside. Well, that makes sense. You&#39;d want to fix broken parts on-site. I&#39;d go into a random room and think &quot;Oh! This is an office! I get it!&quot;

There is no better example of this than Residue Processing. In the original Half-Life, I HATED Residue Processing because it made me feel like I was playing Quake. It&#39;s just a series of brown hallways and corridors and conveyor belts and brown water with little visibility and it just made me feel lost and confused. Where the hell am I? Nothing looks like a thing I can recognise! Cut to Black Mesa Residue Processing. Almost immediately upon entering it, I was hit with an image... This is a water treatment plant! I know where I am! The conveyors, the water channels, the pipes and catwalks - it all looks like a living, industrial area which could have had people working in it just mere hours ago. Half-Life Residue Processing looks like &quot;a brown castle.&quot; Black Mesa Residue Processing looks like a sewage treatment plant, and that&#39;s amazing!

So as I found myself walking through Half-Life 2&#39;s Route Canal, I ended up feeling lost. Where am I? Yeah, I know it&#39;s a sewer, but what function does this part of it serve? Is it a storm drain? A black water sewer? Maintenance tunnels? I went off to the side in a tunnel and found a dead-end room walled off with bricks on five sides. What possible use could that place have had, other than to hang a Barnacle Creature off the ceiling? I found a little pool with a mesh churning the water, threatening to squish me as I swim for an opening under the surface. Why is that thing there? What is it churning? The water seemed to flow past a grate off in the distance, but where was it coming FROM? The only other entrance into this pool was the pipe I went into, but that didn&#39;t go anywhere.

A lot of locations in Half-Life 2 feel like they started off as a Wolfenstein-style maze with a skin tossed over it. Corridors twist and turn seemingly just to run me across monsters and soldiers for a bit of action. I just got up into Ravenholm and found myself in a building with circular saw blades, oxygen tanks and paint cans. Why? What possible business could have been run out of that building to require all three of those? And why is the next room over empty? Why are small wood buildings comprised of long, twisting corridors that don&#39;t join rooms together? Very few things look like something I can describe...

*Black Mesa has A LOT of doors that I can&#39;t open. You&#39;d think this would be annoying. After all, why have a door if the player can&#39;t open it? For a very simple reason - because it makes the facility feel much larger without making the playable area any bigger than it already is. The original Half-Life made the facility feel like a mile long corridor. The only doors which existed led to corridors, which only ever led to other rooms, which in turn only had one door I come in through and one door I leave through. Black Mesa&#39;s many non-interactive, locked doors are a MAJOR improvement. It makes the facility feel lived-in, like this could actually function.

I want to bring up the little checkpoint guard post in the first tunnel from Surface Tension. In Half-Life, this was a for-no-reason airlock tunnel to facilitate zone loading. Here, it&#39;s a checkpoint with sealed gate leading off in a different direction and a little lobby area where you&#39;d wait to have your papers processed. More importantly, a sealed gate leads off into a corridor somewhere deeper in the facility. Instantly, this felt believable. The corridor would lead to a mess hall, a rec room, to the locker rooms and showers. It would lead to the rest of the facility. The guard wouldn&#39;t need to walk the road to his post. He would simply come out of the tunnel and sit at his controls. The whole thing makes Black Mesa feel like I&#39;m making my way through a large, complex facility which may have MANY different routes - I&#39;m just taking the only one that&#39;s unlocked.

Half-Life 2, by contrast, doesn&#39;t do prop doors all but entirely. My entire time moving through the Route Canal felt surreal. What kind of Byzantine, Escher-esque sewer design does City 17 have? Why are all drain pipes so... &quot;Linear?&quot; They have one entrance and one exit and never branch. Occasionally they may be open at the top, but they never deviated. There are no locked doors leading to other sections that I can&#39;t access. There are almost no grates blocking off other sections of the sewers that I can&#39;t visit. There are almost no places I can&#39;t go, so I&#39;m left to assume that what I see is all there is to this sewer And I don&#39;t get why that is, frankly.

Sure, Half-Life 2 isn&#39;t just Route Canal, and indeed the &quot;I&#39;m on a boat!&quot; section is a lot better about this. The river I&#39;m sailing on keeps branching off and seems to have multiple ways to go about it. It doesn&#39;t, because every branching path is a very near dead end, but at least visually it looks like it continues on. OK, so I can&#39;t go to the left because it&#39;s blocked off, but I can see outflow pipes there, so at least I know there&#39;s a sewer system beyond those impassible grates. OK, so I can&#39;t go to the right because it&#39;s sealed by a gate, but at least I know there&#39;s more of the river in that specific direction. Hell, even Black Mesa East (the chapter) does a better job than Route Canal, if for no reason other than because that elevator ride takes you past several populated levels, suggesting the facility is larger than two rooms and a junkyard.

---

Now, there&#39;s something to point out: Black Mesa takes place just after a disaster in an operational facility while Half-Life 2 takes place a couple of decades after an apocalyptic war. Obviously, a lot of places will have fallen into ruin and become unrecognisable... Right? Well, if that&#39;s the case then why does Fallout 3 do such a better job of creating ruined but still recognisable buildings? Hell, Half-Life itself does this far better in a bunch of places. That iconic bridge during the car sequence, for instance - easily the most memorable aspect of Half-Life 2 in my mind. The problem is that outside of specific set-pieces, Half-Life 2 is just a lot of non-descript hallways.

I&#39;m not trying to slag Half-Life 2. It&#39;s a great game and one which defined a generation of FPS games. It&#39;s aged a lot better than many of its peers and is still fun to play. However, Valve seem to have abandoned the game - there&#39;s no Workshop for it, it&#39;s still plagued with crashes and stutters and it just feels old by this point. And it took Black Mesa doing Half-Life right for me to really recognise this...</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2015 14:19:04 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>The Cafeteria</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/black-mesa-vs-half-life-2/13646.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Black Mesa vs. Half-Life 2</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[JeffMOD]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>You’re spot on with that- that’s exactly what happened. The names of the engines actually came about this way too - Valve kept their new engine code in a “src” folder, because it was source code, and the copy of the code they shipped in Half-Life in the “gldsrc” folder, because it was the source code that had gone gold. They started referring to each engine by their folder name, and it just kinda stuck.<br>
It was very much an incremental build up, but it’s like any other engine versioning system - enough changes, and it’s a different engine. Think the difference between Unreal Engine 3 and Unreal Engine 4, or the IdTech 1 (Doom) engine and the IdTech 2 (Quake) engine - a lot of stuff was added, massively overhauled, incremented, or plain rebuilt from scratch with a more efficient  implementation method.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/black-mesa-vs-half-life-2/13646/37">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/black-mesa-vs-half-life-2/13646/37</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2015 14:19:04 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13646-37</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/black-mesa-vs-half-life-2/13646.rss">Black Mesa vs. Half-Life 2</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Black Mesa vs. Half-Life 2</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[KyuuGryphon]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="geekofalltrades">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/g/c2a13f/40.png" class="avatar"> geekofalltrades:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>To quote Raising the Bar:</p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>Piece by piece, the <span class="bbcode-i">Quake</span>-derived <span class="bbcode-i">Half-Life</span> engine was discarded as Valve began developing something all its own, the proprietary engine technology now known as <span class="bbcode-i">Source</span>.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I’m probably reading this too literally, but I’m not sure how to interpret that without context (i.e. “Source was built from scratch”, or “Source was gradually built off of GoldSrc until nothing of GoldSrc remained”). Having said that, I have trouble believing that Source isn’t built off of GoldSrc. I’d buy that Source began its life being built off of GoldSrc, with the GoldSrc assets gradually being phased out until very little of it remains, but not that Source was built from scratch.</p>
<p>The ancient version of Source that the Half-Life 2 leak runs on is extremely similar to GoldSrc - The flashlight behaviour (only lighting one surface at a time), +use slowing player movement, reloading weapons blocking the flashlight/+use, the bunny-hopping mechanics… There’s just way too much there that works either exactly like (or extremely closely to) GoldSrc itself.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/black-mesa-vs-half-life-2/13646/36">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/black-mesa-vs-half-life-2/13646/36</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2015 04:23:40 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13646-36</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/black-mesa-vs-half-life-2/13646.rss">Black Mesa vs. Half-Life 2</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Black Mesa vs. Half-Life 2</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[geekofalltrades]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>To quote Raising the Bar:</p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>Piece by piece, the <span class="bbcode-i">Quake</span>-derived <span class="bbcode-i">Half-Life</span> engine was discarded as Valve began developing something all its own, the proprietary engine technology now known as <span class="bbcode-i">Source</span>.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/black-mesa-vs-half-life-2/13646/35">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/black-mesa-vs-half-life-2/13646/35</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2015 23:58:54 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13646-35</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/black-mesa-vs-half-life-2/13646.rss">Black Mesa vs. Half-Life 2</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Black Mesa vs. Half-Life 2</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[JeffMOD]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>What, Source and Goldsource? No they’re not. I mean, they are <span class="bbcode-i">related</span>, but Goldsource has more relation to IDTech 2 than Source. They crammed a lot of new engine code in when they built Source.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/black-mesa-vs-half-life-2/13646/34">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/black-mesa-vs-half-life-2/13646/34</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2015 20:26:06 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13646-34</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/black-mesa-vs-half-life-2/13646.rss">Black Mesa vs. Half-Life 2</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Black Mesa vs. Half-Life 2</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[GordonCheapman]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>The old engine’s limitations simply didn’t allow for anything more specific.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I hate to break it to you, but they’re the same engine.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/black-mesa-vs-half-life-2/13646/33">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/black-mesa-vs-half-life-2/13646/33</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2015 19:44:09 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13646-33</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/black-mesa-vs-half-life-2/13646.rss">Black Mesa vs. Half-Life 2</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Black Mesa vs. Half-Life 2</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[CatzEyes93]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>interesting. I loved the boat and car scenes in the games.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/black-mesa-vs-half-life-2/13646/32">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/black-mesa-vs-half-life-2/13646/32</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2015 23:01:59 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13646-32</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/black-mesa-vs-half-life-2/13646.rss">Black Mesa vs. Half-Life 2</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Black Mesa vs. Half-Life 2</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Malidictus]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Swaggless">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/s/a698b9/40.png" class="avatar"> Swaggless:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>While I can understand and can appreciate a game that lets you take your time (I had this problem in Crysis 1… the Korean baddies were CONSTANTLY breathing down my neck. It got tiresome.), and I think Half-Life is typically pretty good with pacing it’s gameplay, something that’s supposed to be a linear adventure with high stakes should keep the pressure up fairly often. Expecially in sections about travel.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Frankly, I think we’ll just have to disagree on this one. I’ve never enjoyed games which rush me - it’s just not fun for me. I play even L4D2 in a slow, methodical fashion, searching every nook and cranny for supplies while clearing every room of zombies before moving on. Yes, it means I take longer and get hit with more hordes, but that’s why I play on a lower difficulty setting. I’ve seen some people rush through entire levels in mere minutes, and while that’s impressive… Man, I SO wouldn’t want to play like that. In fact, that’s one of the primary reasons I never cared for the Dead Rising series - don’t care for a perpetual timer. I much prefer to feel like I’m in control of the situation, which the original Half-Life and in turn Black Mesa pretty much always does well with.</p>
<p>To each his own, obviously. I would never say that Water Hazard is a bad chapter, and I really don’t have the same kinds of map design complains that I do about Ravenholm and Route Canal. Outside the confusing sewer sections, it’s mostly well-designed and very pretty. Probably be a lot prettier if I ever got a good look at the terrain, but that’s besides the point. Frankly, going through the entirety of Half-Life 2 give me only the two problem areas of Route Canal and Ravenholm, with the Antlion caves of Episode 2 being a VERY close contender for confusing, boring, uninspired level design (though with “caves,” how much can you do?).</p>
<p>I don’t mind Water Hazard, but I can do without the missile-dodging chase sequences.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/black-mesa-vs-half-life-2/13646/31">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/black-mesa-vs-half-life-2/13646/31</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2015 10:46:07 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13646-31</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/black-mesa-vs-half-life-2/13646.rss">Black Mesa vs. Half-Life 2</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Black Mesa vs. Half-Life 2</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Swaggless]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Malidictus">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/m/7bcc69/40.png" class="avatar"> Malidictus:</div>
<blockquote>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Swaggless">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/s/a698b9/40.png" class="avatar"> Swaggless:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>What does Highway 17 have? Some might say the Gunships, but the problem there is that the moment one shows up <span class="bbcode-i">you already have the weapon to defeat it in-hand!</span> You immediately have the power to defeat them. It may be difficult, but there is no gameplay-driven reason for why you should constantly be on the move, and any current sense of urgency really just comes from characters saying “You better get moving, Dr. Freeman!”.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Frankly, I prefer it that way. My biggest problem with Water Hazard is that it feels like a video arcade. After the Hunter Chopper shows up, it’s basically a racing game with utterly dreadful controls. Don’t get me wrong, I like the airboat, but the thing controls like a fridge on rollerskates. Maybe that’s realistic to an actual airboat, but it’s no fun to drive, if I have to be honest. And in general, I just don’t like games rushing me. My take on Water Hazard is entirely the reverse of yours. I don’t remember ANY of the chase scenes. I mean, I know they were there. An APC fires rockets at me on I think three separate occasions, the Chopper drops bombs on me a lot, there are a bunch of places where Barnacles hang from the ceiling, but I couldn’t even begin to tell you where any of that is in relation to anything else. I can never tell where I am on the map or even which direction I’m going. BECAUSE it’s all one giant urgent chase, I never get to look at the frankly very pretty terrain which still holds up quite well. I can’t, because if I take the wrong turn, the Hunter Chopper will shoot me.</p>
<p>By contrast, I remember all the times I had to stop quite vividly. I LOVE the APC garage. It’s one of my favourite bits in Water Hazard. I like the warehouse as well, though I’m not a huge fan of dodging the Hunter Chopper across the stockyard. I like that one bit where you have to push a washing machine on a lift to raise a platform, too. Basically, I remember all the times when I had to stop and get off the boat, because those are the times when I could look around in peace. Truth be told, I was under the impression that every time I went into a pipe, I was underground the first time I played. It wasn’t until the aforementioned washing machine segment made me look up that I realised I was in the open air with what look like highway overpasses over my head. The “pipe” I thought I was running through was just unconnected segments of pipe. Would not have noticed that. And I enjoy those sections. Don’t really like the Hunter Chopper fight because FPS games rarely do boss fights well. This one, in particular, is dull, dull, dull. Chase the thing around and shoot it about 50 000 times until you wear down all its health bars while you dodge mines over and over again. That thing literally has two actions it can take. Pull back and shoot which requires me to dodge, then fly over and drop bombs. I’m much more fond of the little landing strip area it leaves behind, to be perfectly honest.</p>
<p>The truth of the matter is I hate vehicle sections in FPS games. I HATE driving vehicles from a first person perspective and they never handle any good. The car actually handles FAAAR worse than the boat, skidding all over the place, spinning at the drop of a hat and apparently having a sticky accelerator that I can’t release once I punch the gas. That section where I have to race the trail is GOD AWFUL and I really hate it every time it comes up. I don’t think I’ve ever done that one without reloading upwards of 20 times, and usually by sheer luck. That is to say, I make it across nearly every time, but I either can’t stop and collide with something, or usually spin out and fall off the cliff. No, thank you. I’d rather treat the car like an escort quest, i.e. as something I need to ferry me from one end to the other, but that’s going to stop and let me off every time I need to do some actual work. I don’t have that luxury with the airboat, simply because Water Hazard has a lot of airboat race sections, and those I REALLY don’t like.</p>
<p>Vehicles in Half-Life 2 always felt like a gimmick to me. They felt like “Oh! Look at what our engine can do!” Unlike the Gravity Gun, however, neither of the two vehicles are very fun to use. Sluggish, imprecise controls put through tests requiring tight, responsive controls just make me irrationally angry. It makes me feel like I’m playing with one hand tied behind my back. Any game in which I spend more time fighting the controls more than I do the enemies wears out my patience really quickly. Half-Life 2’s vehicle sections aren’t quite THAT bad, but let’s just say that last time I played, I muscled through Water Hazard as fast as I could just because I wanted it to be over sooner. Or if not that, I wanted off the boat sooner, so I can engage in some of the gameplay Half-Life 2 actually does well.</p>
<p>That’s just me, though.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>While I agree the car is a bit annoying, I’ve never had real trouble with the airboat’s controls. I’ve heard a lot of people complain about how they handle… never understood it. Besides the car’s dumb skidding issues, I’ve found driving them easy and fun. XD I kinda just wanna keep on going, so I’m not a huge fan of parts that gate me, like the APC garage and Shipping Yard.</p>
<p>I guess I can understand wanthing to stop and take in the scenery, and I certainly don’t think EVERY chapter should have helicopters gunning you down, LOL. But the problem I have with the coast is that the tension drops WAAY down. When you’re getting persued and chased, it feels like you’re DOING something. Like you have a purpose. When that’s not happening, you’re just out for a leisurely sunday drive by the beach and you pull over to pick off a few stay combine trying to catch some rays before heading back to C17. XD Ravenholm has the excuse that the Combine lost track of you, and once you get to Nova Prospekt you’re always either on Combine turf or fighting in street wars. The coast has no such excuse and it just feels to me like the Combine have given up trying or something. It just feels out of place and kind of takes me out of it. Maybe the best remedy would be something that kept Eli on the players mind, or a radio in the car with rebels from the next base saying they need reinforcements or something. Not something that would nag the player per-say, just to remind players that what they’re doing is of importance. Because unlike Half-Life 1 which tries to make the player feel small, Half-Life 2 is trying to make the player feel big.</p>
<p>While I can understand and can appreciate a game that lets you take your time (I had this problem in Crysis 1… the Korean baddies were CONSTANTLY breathing down my neck. It got tiresome.), and I think Half-Life is typically pretty good with pacing it’s gameplay, something that’s supposed to be a linear adventure with high stakes should keep the pressure up fairly often. Expecially in sections about travel.</p>
<p>I guess we will just have to agree to disagree.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/black-mesa-vs-half-life-2/13646/30">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/black-mesa-vs-half-life-2/13646/30</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2015 07:32:05 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13646-30</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/black-mesa-vs-half-life-2/13646.rss">Black Mesa vs. Half-Life 2</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Black Mesa vs. Half-Life 2</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Malidictus]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Swaggless">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/s/a698b9/40.png" class="avatar"> Swaggless:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>What does Highway 17 have? Some might say the Gunships, but the problem there is that the moment one shows up <span class="bbcode-i">you already have the weapon to defeat it in-hand!</span> You immediately have the power to defeat them. It may be difficult, but there is no gameplay-driven reason for why you should constantly be on the move, and any current sense of urgency really just comes from characters saying “You better get moving, Dr. Freeman!”.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Frankly, I prefer it that way. My biggest problem with Water Hazard is that it feels like a video arcade. After the Hunter Chopper shows up, it’s basically a racing game with utterly dreadful controls. Don’t get me wrong, I like the airboat, but the thing controls like a fridge on rollerskates. Maybe that’s realistic to an actual airboat, but it’s no fun to drive, if I have to be honest. And in general, I just don’t like games rushing me. My take on Water Hazard is entirely the reverse of yours. I don’t remember ANY of the chase scenes. I mean, I know they were there. An APC fires rockets at me on I think three separate occasions, the Chopper drops bombs on me a lot, there are a bunch of places where Barnacles hang from the ceiling, but I couldn’t even begin to tell you where any of that is in relation to anything else. I can never tell where I am on the map or even which direction I’m going. BECAUSE it’s all one giant urgent chase, I never get to look at the frankly very pretty terrain which still holds up quite well. I can’t, because if I take the wrong turn, the Hunter Chopper will shoot me.</p>
<p>By contrast, I remember all the times I had to stop quite vividly. I LOVE the APC garage. It’s one of my favourite bits in Water Hazard. I like the warehouse as well, though I’m not a huge fan of dodging the Hunter Chopper across the stockyard. I like that one bit where you have to push a washing machine on a lift to raise a platform, too. Basically, I remember all the times when I had to stop and get off the boat, because those are the times when I could look around in peace. Truth be told, I was under the impression that every time I went into a pipe, I was underground the first time I played. It wasn’t until the aforementioned washing machine segment made me look up that I realised I was in the open air with what look like highway overpasses over my head. The “pipe” I thought I was running through was just unconnected segments of pipe. Would not have noticed that. And I enjoy those sections. Don’t really like the Hunter Chopper fight because FPS games rarely do boss fights well. This one, in particular, is dull, dull, dull. Chase the thing around and shoot it about 50 000 times until you wear down all its health bars while you dodge mines over and over again. That thing literally has two actions it can take. Pull back and shoot which requires me to dodge, then fly over and drop bombs. I’m much more fond of the little landing strip area it leaves behind, to be perfectly honest.</p>
<p>The truth of the matter is I hate vehicle sections in FPS games. I HATE driving vehicles from a first person perspective and they never handle any good. The car actually handles FAAAR worse than the boat, skidding all over the place, spinning at the drop of a hat and apparently having a sticky accelerator that I can’t release once I punch the gas. That section where I have to race the trail is GOD AWFUL and I really hate it every time it comes up. I don’t think I’ve ever done that one without reloading upwards of 20 times, and usually by sheer luck. That is to say, I make it across nearly every time, but I either can’t stop and collide with something, or usually spin out and fall off the cliff. No, thank you. I’d rather treat the car like an escort quest, i.e. as something I need to ferry me from one end to the other, but that’s going to stop and let me off every time I need to do some actual work. I don’t have that luxury with the airboat, simply because Water Hazard has a lot of airboat race sections, and those I REALLY don’t like.</p>
<p>Vehicles in Half-Life 2 always felt like a gimmick to me. They felt like “Oh! Look at what our engine can do!” Unlike the Gravity Gun, however, neither of the two vehicles are very fun to use. Sluggish, imprecise controls put through tests requiring tight, responsive controls just make me irrationally angry. It makes me feel like I’m playing with one hand tied behind my back. Any game in which I spend more time fighting the controls more than I do the enemies wears out my patience really quickly. Half-Life 2’s vehicle sections aren’t quite THAT bad, but let’s just say that last time I played, I muscled through Water Hazard as fast as I could just because I wanted it to be over sooner. Or if not that, I wanted off the boat sooner, so I can engage in some of the gameplay Half-Life 2 actually does well.</p>
<p>That’s just me, though.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/black-mesa-vs-half-life-2/13646/29">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/black-mesa-vs-half-life-2/13646/29</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2015 21:07:09 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13646-29</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/black-mesa-vs-half-life-2/13646.rss">Black Mesa vs. Half-Life 2</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Black Mesa vs. Half-Life 2</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypt]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Oh wow, that’s an impressive detail.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/black-mesa-vs-half-life-2/13646/28">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/black-mesa-vs-half-life-2/13646/28</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2015 18:48:16 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13646-28</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/black-mesa-vs-half-life-2/13646.rss">Black Mesa vs. Half-Life 2</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Black Mesa vs. Half-Life 2</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[CatzEyes93]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>aaaaaand now I have to fire up the game JUST to see this. thanks for the tip!</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/black-mesa-vs-half-life-2/13646/27">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/black-mesa-vs-half-life-2/13646/27</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2015 15:48:32 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13646-27</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/black-mesa-vs-half-life-2/13646.rss">Black Mesa vs. Half-Life 2</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Black Mesa vs. Half-Life 2</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[KyuuGryphon]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>… Holy crap, I never noticed that before. Well, never mind then!  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/smiley.png?v=9" title=":smiley:" class="emoji" alt=":smiley:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/black-mesa-vs-half-life-2/13646/26">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/black-mesa-vs-half-life-2/13646/26</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2015 07:22:59 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13646-26</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/black-mesa-vs-half-life-2/13646.rss">Black Mesa vs. Half-Life 2</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Black Mesa vs. Half-Life 2</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[geekofalltrades]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="ThunderDash">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 ThunderDash:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Despite that, there’s no sign of Ravenholm from outside BME (not the scrapyard, to be clear), and there’s no sign of anything from the canals (the river or the factories in the background) in Ravenholm.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Yes, there is. You can see Ravenholm on the hill behind Black Mesa East from the top of the dam, before you jump the airboat off of it.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/black-mesa-vs-half-life-2/13646/25">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/black-mesa-vs-half-life-2/13646/25</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2015 06:02:51 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13646-25</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/black-mesa-vs-half-life-2/13646.rss">Black Mesa vs. Half-Life 2</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Black Mesa vs. Half-Life 2</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[KyuuGryphon]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I get what you’re saying, but… How to put it.</p>
<p>What confuses me isn’t so much how the different environments coexist close together, but how they relate to each other spatially. For instance, in BME, you take an elevator down, and eventually leave in a direction that would put Ravenholm just down the river from the entrance. Despite that, there’s no sign of Ravenholm from outside BME (not the scrapyard, to be clear), and there’s no sign of anything from the canals (the river or the factories in the background) in Ravenholm. Granted, the passageway up to Ravenhom isn’t as high as the elevator shaft (I think? haven’t checked, actually), but it still seems really weird to me.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/black-mesa-vs-half-life-2/13646/24">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/black-mesa-vs-half-life-2/13646/24</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2015 02:33:07 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13646-24</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/black-mesa-vs-half-life-2/13646.rss">Black Mesa vs. Half-Life 2</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Black Mesa vs. Half-Life 2</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Swaggless]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="ThunderDash">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 ThunderDash:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I remember a while back, there was a thread on here about games people thought were bland or unforgettable (something along those lines). Someone sarcastically said “Half-Life 2”, and I thought they were dead serious and agreed with them   <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/frowning.png?v=9" title=":frowning:" class="emoji" alt=":frowning:"></p>
<p>Thinking about it now, a bit over a year later (I can’t believe it’s been that long already), that’s… really <span class="bbcode-i">not </span>how I’d describe my opinion of Half-Life 2. First time playing it, I absolutely loved it. No real complaints, I had a great time through the whole game. What changed it for me, though, wasn’t Black Mesa, but actually Half-Life 1 itself.</p>
<p>I could probably write paragraphs about why, but really, all it comes down to is that HL1 “works better” for me than HL2 does. All sorts of little differences throughout the game - in gameplay, in storytelling, in AI, whatever - just work a lot better for me in HL1. I think part of it was also finding out about how different the game was during early development - things like the darker, more 1984-esque atmosphere, or concepts like the Vertigo or Air Exchange chapters… I find them more intriguing than what the final game ended up being (though in some part, that’s probably <span class="bbcode-i">because </span>of the fact that they’re a “what-could-have-been”).</p>
<p>Having said all that, I’m curious - Does anyone else feel that, in terms of locations, Half-Life 2 is a bit… incoherent, for lack of a better word? Like… How to put this. Black Mesa East takes place in a building, with a cave/ravine-type area (the scrapyard) at the back. Even bearing in mind that it’s a ravine, am I the only one who feels really confused about how Ravenholm exists more or less right next to it?</p>
<p>For that matter, the coast. I know that Ravenholm was originally located by the ocean (or a lake or something), but, again, am I the only one who doesn’t get how going down some train tracks and through a building results in such a radically different environment?</p>
<p>To be fair, HL1 had issues like this, or issues with maps overlapping (the friggin’ tram line in Black Mesa Inbound doubles back on itself!), but for some reason it always stuck out to me more in HL2’s case</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I don’t think it’s that confusing. Let’s look at the coast one backwards: The car is on a dock next to a crane. So, this was a harbor where they loaded/unloaded ships. The building you battle in is a warehouse, where they stored things that were coming and going. Behind the building is a train track, where they would load the items taken off of ships onto trains, and vice-versa. I think it makes perfect sense.</p>
<p>Also, Black Mesa East was a power plant, right? It’s at the foot of a dam that once harnessed power from the lake, and it supplied power to multiple places, including Ravenholm. Also, Ravenholm was a mining town, that’s why it’s connected to everything via tunnels.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/black-mesa-vs-half-life-2/13646/23">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/black-mesa-vs-half-life-2/13646/23</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2015 01:55:08 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13646-23</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/black-mesa-vs-half-life-2/13646.rss">Black Mesa vs. Half-Life 2</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Black Mesa vs. Half-Life 2</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[KyuuGryphon]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I remember a while back, there was a thread on here about games people thought were bland or unforgettable (something along those lines). Someone sarcastically said “Half-Life 2”, and I thought they were dead serious and agreed with them   <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/frowning.png?v=9" title=":frowning:" class="emoji" alt=":frowning:"></p>
<p>Thinking about it now, a bit over a year later (I can’t believe it’s been that long already), that’s… really <span class="bbcode-i">not </span>how I’d describe my opinion of Half-Life 2. First time playing it, I absolutely loved it. No real complaints, I had a great time through the whole game. What changed it for me, though, wasn’t Black Mesa, but actually Half-Life 1 itself.</p>
<p>I could probably write paragraphs about why, but really, all it comes down to is that HL1 “works better” for me than HL2 does. All sorts of little differences throughout the game - in gameplay, in storytelling, in AI, whatever - just work a lot better for me in HL1. I think part of it was also finding out about how different the game was during early development - things like the darker, more 1984-esque atmosphere, or concepts like the Vertigo or Air Exchange chapters… I find them more intriguing than what the final game ended up being (though in some part, that’s probably <span class="bbcode-i">because </span>of the fact that they’re a “what-could-have-been”).</p>
<p>Having said all that, I’m curious - Does anyone else feel that, in terms of locations, Half-Life 2 is a bit… incoherent, for lack of a better word? Like… How to put this. Black Mesa East takes place in a building, with a cave/ravine-type area (the scrapyard) at the back. Even bearing in mind that it’s a ravine, am I the only one who feels really confused about how Ravenholm exists more or less right next to it?</p>
<p>For that matter, the coast. I know that Ravenholm was originally located by the ocean (or a lake or something), but, again, am I the only one who doesn’t get how going down some train tracks and through a building results in such a radically different environment?</p>
<p>To be fair, HL1 had issues like this, or issues with maps overlapping (the friggin’ tram line in Black Mesa Inbound doubles back on itself!), but for some reason it always stuck out to me more in HL2’s case</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/black-mesa-vs-half-life-2/13646/22">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/black-mesa-vs-half-life-2/13646/22</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2015 01:34:15 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13646-22</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/black-mesa-vs-half-life-2/13646.rss">Black Mesa vs. Half-Life 2</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Black Mesa vs. Half-Life 2</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Swaggless]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Malidictus">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/m/7bcc69/40.png" class="avatar"> Malidictus:</div>
<blockquote>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Ammat the Ankh">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Ammat the Ankh:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>The best description I ever read about HL2 is “every chapter is a map too long.”</p>
<p>I feel Route Canal and Water Hazard were too much of a slog for me to want to replay the game as much as I do the others in the series. The game gets a lot better once you get the Gravity Gun, but most parts still feel a little too long. HL1 (and by extension Black Mesa) and the episodes are much better in terms of pacing.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>“A map too long.” I like that  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=9" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:">  I don’t think I agree with you on that one, though. I’m the kind of player who can never have enough of a good game. Half-Life 2 could be twice the size and I’d still play it eagerly. I couldn’t imagine playing Black Mesa without On a Rail: Uncut and Surface Tension: Uncut. I look forward to the Hazard Course remake and even that We’ve Got Hostile: Uncut, despite there not really being much “cut” from We’ve Got Hostiles aside from vent crawling and the cantina kitchen. Now, I obviously don’t want just longer corridors and repetitive rooms, sure. This is predicated on the condition that the extra content be GOOD, which I find to be the case with both of the Uncut chapters.</p>
<p>And yet, you still have a point - Route Kanal and Water Hazard really feel like they drag on, though I suspect for different reasons. Water Hazard shares features and problems with Highway 17 - the other “vehicle section” in the game… Yet Highway 17 feels a lot less long and a lot less tedious. Gabe Newall likes to talk about contraction and expansion of space, sending the player though tight, narrow spaces then into wide, open spaces and back again. This is what Water Hazard and Highway 17 are, but that in itself is a problem: Their scale is too big. Locations are too large to explore and the routes are so long they’re slow to traverse. So why is that a problem in Water Hazard but not in Highway 17? Why does Water Hazard feel like it’s dragging on longer?</p>
<p>Counter-intuitively, I’d say it’s because there’s a lot more going on in Water Hazard. You’re ramping your boat over chasms, ramming enemies and structures, dodging rockets, swerving around bombs, racing a gunship, zooming down a complicated “track” at high speed and having to judge your steering, your speed and what’s around you - it’s an arcade racing game more so than a shooter in those sections, and that’s a problem. High-octane action is draining. If you put the player through too much at a time, you end up sucking the thrill out of it, until it feels like a chore. A complicated, attention-intensive chore. Contrast this against Highway 17. Yes, there are a few heart-poinding moments in it (GOD DAMN racing the train on the bridge!), but those are specific set-pieces. Most of Highway 17 involves fairly sedate driving on the open road. You may run over a few Antlions or stop to pull Roller Mines off your buggy, but you’re rarely in a GOGOGOGOGO! position. The chapter is no less long and involved, but it makes travel easier and less focus-intensive, which actually makes it fly by a lot faster.</p>
<p>I’d argue the reason that Water Hazard feels like it drags on for so long is it tries to do too much. It demands too much of your attention too often, and as a result… You end up realising you’re basically doing the same thing multiple times. Go out on the water, race the chopper, dodge missiles, ram wooden supports, do a jump, get into a pipe. Sail for a bit, then do it all over again about three more times. Yes, Highway 17 pretty much comes down to the same thing - drive until you find a building, clear the building, drive on - but because the actual act of driving is so much less complicated, you can almost tune out the driving sections. It’s good that they’re there because they add a sense of scope to the whole chapter, they add to the sense of immersion, but unlike the constant running the gantlet that is Water Hazard, it doesn’t make me tired to play through it.</p>
<p>The other issue is that - like Route Kanal - Water Hazard really doesn’t “look like anything.” The outside sections are pretty cool when they look like a river out in the countryside, but there are far too many samey-looking pipes and aqueducts. Worse, because I’m being chased all the time, I don’t have the chance to explore the environment and see how cool it looks. The only times I get to slow down and look around, I’m in yet another sewer level which is just so, SO very rarely interesting.</p>
<p>At the end of the day, I wouldn’t say that Water Hazard is a “map too long” so much as I’d argue it runs out of material half-way through and ends up repeating itself.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Huh, I’ve typically thought that the coast dragged on a bit here-and-there, and that Water Hazard was the<span class="bbcode-u"><span class="bbcode-b"> strongest overall chapter in the game.</span></span> <em>dodges tomatoes</em><br>
Just… let me explain.</p>
<p>These chapters get compared a lot because they are both designed around the player driving a vehicle. I agree that they hold that in-common, but I’d say the chapters are VERY different from eachother. Why? Because once you get about 10 minutes in, Water Hazard really only engages players while <span class="bbcode-i">in the boat</span>, and Highway 17 almost always engages players while they are<span class="bbcode-i"> on foot</span>. Think about some of the most memorable set pieces from Water Hazard: The tower falling down,  the APCs firing rockets at you, the choppers dropping bombs, the final battle in that gigantic empty late; All things that happen <span class="bbcode-i">while in the boat</span>. Highway 17? Operating the crane, climbing under the bridge, the battle at Lighthouse Point, all those little houses to poke through… all things that happen <span class="bbcode-i">on foot</span>. Only things I can think of where the car is involved is a few ramps early on (most notably after the crane) and the train-dodge. I think this makes Water Hazard much stronger design-wise. You use your vehicle <span class="bbcode-i">that the level was designed for</span> to solve problems. Not the guns you have <span class="bbcode-i">all the time.</span></p>
<p>That’s not to say there aren’t times you step out of your vehicle in Water Hazard. There’s the barn base, the APC garage, Shipping Warehouse, 2 pully puzzles (one for items, one to be able to continue), and the rebels who give you the boat gun. And I will agree with you, Malidictus: these areas aren’t quite as interesting or open as the coast. However, their placement (and time they take to “complete”) seems more calculated (except the garage and warehouse. Those annoy me.) to give  players a change of pace and a chance to catch their breath.</p>
<p>Finally, Water Hazard is much more dynamic and thematic. There’s an urgency to the Water Hazard chapter that gives it and inherent sense of meaning without story context. Not all players will be thinking “I gotta get to Black Mesa East!” or “I gotta get to Nova Prospekt!” through an entire chapter. I know I’m not. I’m just focusing on progressing! And Water Hazard’s use of the chopper, squads of Civil Protection officers, and APC rockets convey a sense of “I gotta get outta here! I’m a wanted man!” that Highway 17 lacks. The chopper itself is a thematic tool. Think about it. Outside of the Shipping Warehouse and the final battle… does it ever present a <span class="bbcode-i">real</span> threat to a halfway-decent player? Keep on driving and dodge 80% of the bombs and you’re fine, yet it’s there. Nagging you. And there’s nothing you can do… until you get the gun. Then <span class="bbcode-i">you’re</span> chasing <span class="bbcode-i">it</span> until it makes one final stand and you shoot it out of the sky. There’s some real growth taking place there, and I think it makes the chapter incredibly strong.</p>
<p>What does Highway 17 have? Some might say the Gunships, but the problem there is that the moment one shows up <span class="bbcode-i">you already have the weapon to defeat it in-hand!</span> You immediately have the power to defeat them. It may be difficult, but there is no gameplay-driven reason for why you should constantly be on the move, and any current sense of urgency really just comes from characters saying “You better get moving, Dr. Freeman!”.</p>
<p>I dunno, maybe it’s just a fine point, but it bugs me that the Combine’s big plan to stop you once you get to the coast is “Set up a force field, attack him with 8-10 troops, then send in one of those Gunships he just shot down!” about 3-4 times in a row, when they were dropping bombs on you and blowing up smokestacks the previous afternoon just to keep you from leaving City 17. It hardly feels like they’re even <span class="bbcode-u"><span class="bbcode-i">trying</span></span> until you get to Nova Prospekt and there are mounted guns, soldiers EVERYWHERE, and they call in two gunships at once (a really AWESOME scene, in my opinion).</p>
<p>So, that’s my feelings on the Coast Vs. Water Hazard debate. I know this is a long response, but I’ve heard people compare the two a lot over the years, and constantly praise the Coast and bash Water Hazard and I’ve never understood why.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/black-mesa-vs-half-life-2/13646/21">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/black-mesa-vs-half-life-2/13646/21</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2015 23:27:46 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13646-21</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/black-mesa-vs-half-life-2/13646.rss">Black Mesa vs. Half-Life 2</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Black Mesa vs. Half-Life 2</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Dr_Maxwell]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Ammat the Ankh">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Ammat the Ankh:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>The best description I ever read about HL2 is “every chapter is a map too long.”</p>
<p>I feel Route Canal and Water Hazard were too much of a slog for me to want to replay the game as much as I do the others in the series. The game gets a lot better once you get the Gravity Gun, but most parts still feel a little too long. HL1 (and by extension Black Mesa) and the episodes are much better in terms of pacing.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I disagree; I dislike Half-Life 2 as well but feel that everything is rushed.  I feel that each chapter is about half as long as it ideally should be.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/black-mesa-vs-half-life-2/13646/20">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/black-mesa-vs-half-life-2/13646/20</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2015 19:07:21 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13646-20</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/black-mesa-vs-half-life-2/13646.rss">Black Mesa vs. Half-Life 2</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Black Mesa vs. Half-Life 2</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Malidictus]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Ammat the Ankh">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Ammat the Ankh:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>The best description I ever read about HL2 is “every chapter is a map too long.”</p>
<p>I feel Route Canal and Water Hazard were too much of a slog for me to want to replay the game as much as I do the others in the series. The game gets a lot better once you get the Gravity Gun, but most parts still feel a little too long. HL1 (and by extension Black Mesa) and the episodes are much better in terms of pacing.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>“A map too long.” I like that  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=9" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:">  I don’t think I agree with you on that one, though. I’m the kind of player who can never have enough of a good game. Half-Life 2 could be twice the size and I’d still play it eagerly. I couldn’t imagine playing Black Mesa without On a Rail: Uncut and Surface Tension: Uncut. I look forward to the Hazard Course remake and even that We’ve Got Hostile: Uncut, despite there not really being much “cut” from We’ve Got Hostiles aside from vent crawling and the cantina kitchen. Now, I obviously don’t want just longer corridors and repetitive rooms, sure. This is predicated on the condition that the extra content be GOOD, which I find to be the case with both of the Uncut chapters.</p>
<p>And yet, you still have a point - Route Kanal and Water Hazard really feel like they drag on, though I suspect for different reasons. Water Hazard shares features and problems with Highway 17 - the other “vehicle section” in the game… Yet Highway 17 feels a lot less long and a lot less tedious. Gabe Newall likes to talk about contraction and expansion of space, sending the player though tight, narrow spaces then into wide, open spaces and back again. This is what Water Hazard and Highway 17 are, but that in itself is a problem: Their scale is too big. Locations are too large to explore and the routes are so long they’re slow to traverse. So why is that a problem in Water Hazard but not in Highway 17? Why does Water Hazard feel like it’s dragging on longer?</p>
<p>Counter-intuitively, I’d say it’s because there’s a lot more going on in Water Hazard. You’re ramping your boat over chasms, ramming enemies and structures, dodging rockets, swerving around bombs, racing a gunship, zooming down a complicated “track” at high speed and having to judge your steering, your speed and what’s around you - it’s an arcade racing game more so than a shooter in those sections, and that’s a problem. High-octane action is draining. If you put the player through too much at a time, you end up sucking the thrill out of it, until it feels like a chore. A complicated, attention-intensive chore. Contrast this against Highway 17. Yes, there are a few heart-poinding moments in it (GOD DAMN racing the train on the bridge!), but those are specific set-pieces. Most of Highway 17 involves fairly sedate driving on the open road. You may run over a few Antlions or stop to pull Roller Mines off your buggy, but you’re rarely in a GOGOGOGOGO! position. The chapter is no less long and involved, but it makes travel easier and less focus-intensive, which actually makes it fly by a lot faster.</p>
<p>I’d argue the reason that Water Hazard feels like it drags on for so long is it tries to do too much. It demands too much of your attention too often, and as a result… You end up realising you’re basically doing the same thing multiple times. Go out on the water, race the chopper, dodge missiles, ram wooden supports, do a jump, get into a pipe. Sail for a bit, then do it all over again about three more times. Yes, Highway 17 pretty much comes down to the same thing - drive until you find a building, clear the building, drive on - but because the actual act of driving is so much less complicated, you can almost tune out the driving sections. It’s good that they’re there because they add a sense of scope to the whole chapter, they add to the sense of immersion, but unlike the constant running the gantlet that is Water Hazard, it doesn’t make me tired to play through it.</p>
<p>The other issue is that - like Route Kanal - Water Hazard really doesn’t “look like anything.” The outside sections are pretty cool when they look like a river out in the countryside, but there are far too many samey-looking pipes and aqueducts. Worse, because I’m being chased all the time, I don’t have the chance to explore the environment and see how cool it looks. The only times I get to slow down and look around, I’m in yet another sewer level which is just so, SO very rarely interesting.</p>
<p>At the end of the day, I wouldn’t say that Water Hazard is a “map too long” so much as I’d argue it runs out of material half-way through and ends up repeating itself.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/black-mesa-vs-half-life-2/13646/19">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/black-mesa-vs-half-life-2/13646/19</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2015 14:11:33 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13646-19</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/black-mesa-vs-half-life-2/13646.rss">Black Mesa vs. Half-Life 2</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Black Mesa vs. Half-Life 2</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Ammat_the_Ankh]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>The best description I ever read about HL2 is “every chapter is a map too long.”</p>
<p>I feel Route Canal and Water Hazard were too much of a slog for me to want to replay the game as much as I do the others in the series. The game gets a lot better once you get the Gravity Gun, but most parts still feel a little too long. HL1 (and by extension Black Mesa) and the episodes are much better in terms of pacing.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/black-mesa-vs-half-life-2/13646/18">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/black-mesa-vs-half-life-2/13646/18</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2015 05:36:58 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13646-18</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/black-mesa-vs-half-life-2/13646.rss">Black Mesa vs. Half-Life 2</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Black Mesa vs. Half-Life 2</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[geekofalltrades]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Route Canal has always been my favorite chapter of Half-Life 2.   :huh:</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/black-mesa-vs-half-life-2/13646/17">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/black-mesa-vs-half-life-2/13646/17</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2015 22:19:15 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13646-17</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/black-mesa-vs-half-life-2/13646.rss">Black Mesa vs. Half-Life 2</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Black Mesa vs. Half-Life 2</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Malidictus]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="FalkeXY">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/user_avatar/leakfree.org/falkexy/40/4459_2.png" class="avatar"> FalkeXY:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>And Ravenholm? Come on that place is all about the creepy athmosphere thats so different from the whole rest of the game. I fucking love and hate that place at the same time. (Friggin fast zombies) I love how you feel like you fight your way through the whole town through the streets, windows, planks and rooftops and that you dont just traverse the infested streets like in RE2’s beginning.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Like I said - Ravenholm’s very atmospheric and a really cool idea. It both shows what the Combine’s regime does to people (though I’d argue Episode 2 does that better) and constitutes a very creepy, almost Resident-Evil-like survival horror section. Both the original Half-Life and Half-Life 2 are games of many themes, going from quiet exploration to survival horror to balls-out action to marvelling at alien stuff to more action again and so on. The idea of Ravenholm is great, and I definitely believe that the game benefits from having it. But the map design in that place is awful, there are no two ways about it. In fact, that map design serves to hamper the awesome theme of Ravenholm by making pretty much every location feel out-of-place and unbelievable.</p>
<p>I’m not looking for hardcore realism here, honestly I’m not. Half-Life 2 is a sci-fi action game, so a lot of creative liberty is afforded to it. I am, however, looking for immersion and a world which feels like it fits within the game’s own fictional universe. So when I run into a building the third floor of which is walled off on all sides and has no access to a lift or stairs, when I see a street both bricked up on all sides and too narrow to fit cars have cars in it anyway, when I see buildings which consist of 90% hallways and maybe one actual room… My immersion is broken, because I see the location for what it is - an FPS dungeon shaped like a town.</p>
<p>Obviously, that’s what pretty much every FPS game is, but even the original Half-Life did more to hide this. In fact, I think I’ve pinned down another reason why that is. Half-Life had a LOT of environment props. So does Black Mesa, in fact. Half-Life 2 has next to none… Which is bizarre, considering that game’s obsession with physics objects. Take Ravenholm, for instance. Aside from that one table and that one wardrobe, that place has next to no “household” props to speak of. There are buzzsaw blades, sure, and a lot of V8 engines for a town with streets too narrow to fit the kind of large American cars which would use those. A lot of meat hooks and air tanks, too. What about tables and chairs and bookshelves? What about a kitchen with a sink, or a bathroom with a bath tub and a toilet? What about an old abandoned cafe with chairs and tables strewn about outside? What about a deli full of rotting meat and a cash register I can hurl at zombies?</p>
<p>Ravenholm doesn’t feel like a town to me. It feels like a canyon made of small buildings jammed together. It doesn’t have any of the stuff an actual small town would have - we don’t even get to go into the church so I can smash zombies in the head with the church altar. now that would have been cool. It feels like a video game level. Worse, it feels like somebody made what he thought was a really cool video game level, then someone else went through it and took out all the props because… It would make the game too easy if we had too much stuff to propel? So what we ended up with is nondescript buildings jammed together into veritable hallways, themselves made up of mostly empty hallways and a few empty rooms. Man, Father Grigori must have hauled all the refrigerators, television sets, computers, bookshelves, coffee tables, couches, beds, flower pots, stoves, washing machines, sinks and countertops out of all the houses in the intervening 20 years. He left all the radiators in, though.</p>
<p>I’m not saying Ravenholm is bad. The theme and atmosphere is actually very good. However, the map design itself does A LOT to counter-act the cool theme, making it come across as boring and confusing as much as it’s scary. Again, look at something like the original Resident Evil. That entire game takes place mostly inside a single large building. However, because that is an ACTUAL building which fits to a floor plan, you end up making sense of it and growing familiar with your surroundings. You know your way around the mansion and are actively looking for ways to explore further while you face the horrors within. That’s what Ravenholm should have been like. Granted, not necessarily and indoor place, but it should have been a small town which runs us back-and-forth around it, finding ways to unblock our path through detours and backtracking. If it’s THAT small of a town that it doesn’t even have a single cafe, then rendering it as a small location that we spend a lot of time in ala Blast Pit would have been superior, in my opinion.</p>
<p>I like the idea of Ravenholm. I don’t think Half-Life 2 implements that idea very well. If ever I was going to skip a chapter in the game, Ravenholm would be it. Yes, even more so than Route Canal.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/black-mesa-vs-half-life-2/13646/16">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/black-mesa-vs-half-life-2/13646/16</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2015 13:44:39 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13646-16</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/black-mesa-vs-half-life-2/13646.rss">Black Mesa vs. Half-Life 2</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Black Mesa vs. Half-Life 2</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[FalkeXY]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I personally don’t understand most of your criticism. Just after I finished BM I bought the Orange Box and directly started playing HL2. At first I wasn’t really sure what to think about this game, mainly because Route Kanal is a very lengthy, boring and repetetive Chapter where nothing important happens (at least imho). But HL2 definitely managed to take my interest after Water Hazard. I think it’s a really awesome game that has aged extremely well. It didn’t feel like any sort of downgrade to me but just like I was continuing the story of Black Mesa. I also dont know why it’s important to you that every map needs to be 100% realistic. HL2’s design felt believable and nothing felt like it was out of place. I never thought that something made absolutely no sense, however I may just have different expectations.<br>
And Ravenholm? Come on that place is all about the creepy athmosphere thats so different from the whole rest of the game. I fucking love and hate that place at the same time. (Friggin fast zombies) I love how you feel like you fight your way through the whole town through the streets, windows, planks and rooftops and that you dont just traverse the infested streets like in RE2’s beginning.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/black-mesa-vs-half-life-2/13646/15">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/black-mesa-vs-half-life-2/13646/15</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2015 23:22:59 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13646-15</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/black-mesa-vs-half-life-2/13646.rss">Black Mesa vs. Half-Life 2</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Black Mesa vs. Half-Life 2</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Malidictus]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Ctoagu">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/c/53a042/40.png" class="avatar"> Ctoagu:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Funnily enough, I think Route Canal and Ravenholm are chapters that had quite a few bits and pieces left over from the Half Life 2 beta. After watching Valve News Network on Youtube do a playthrough of a cobbled-together beta experience, all of the maps were essentially very confusing to navigate, even for him. VNN actually called it to attention and mentioned that these maps were much more reminiscent of the way Half Life 1 worked - winding and maze-like, with little attention being paid to how the structures would make sense in a real-world standpoint.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Hmm… You know, that actually does make sense. The original Half-Life was always like this - a research facility in theory, but one which mostly played out like a prettier level from Doom. I don’t really judge Half-Life too harshly over this, however. It’s an old game from a time when this was simply how you did things. Indeed, it made some major first strides away from the “dungeons” that every other FPS game was set in, a lot to establish the fact that locations could look like real things. Half-Life is also built on a pretty limited engine, so I can give Valve a lot of leeway for simply not having the physical capability to render anything more “life-like” or to create all the extra doors, windows and props that make Black Mesa so cool. It was 1998. A lot of FPS games were still using sprites or fake-3D plane-shifting. For its time, Half-Life was revolutionary. Within the context of “a classic,” it still holds up.</p>
<p>But if Ravenholm and Route Canal were indeed leftovers from a very early Beta, then I can definitely see the resemblance. The funny thing, honestly, is that the game revisits the sewers later on (why Valve thought their game needed TWO sewer levels is beyond me, but…) and the second time around they’re actually a lot less silly and a lot less confusing. Rather than long, winding corridors seemingly built to make for a cool obstacle course, the sewers revisit consists of several large locations which run Freeman up and down across them, navigating around obstructions and usually finding ways to climb. While the environment still doesn’t make much sense in broad terms (I go into a sewer and keep going up all the time, only to emerge back onto street level O_o), the moment-to-moment locations very much do. I could recognise an arched sewer tunnel and its supporting infrastructure. There’s that very cool warehouse you have to climb along the rafters and gantry crane. There’s that destroyed winding staircase which doesn’t make a whole lot of sense but at least I know what it is. For as much as I dislike sewer levels, that chapter is sewer levels done right, at least within the context of Half-Life 2.</p>
<p>Frankly, I wish they’d taken a completely different approach with Ravenholm, something more along the lines of what was done with the original Silent Hill. Chart out the map of a city, then block off all the streets except the one you want the player to go along. At certain points, let the player go into certain buildings to move between outdoor areas, but let the player find the dead ends on his own. Come to think of it, that IS L4D in a nutshell. Yeah, seriously - if Ravenholm were built like the original L4D in terms of basic level design, it would have been ten times as good. Still just as atmosphering, but a lot less goofy if you stop to think about it. Which - unlike in L4D - you will, because Half-Life is paced a lot slower and with a lot more downtime.</p>
<p><em>edit</em><br>
The new forum UI is weird…</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/black-mesa-vs-half-life-2/13646/14">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/black-mesa-vs-half-life-2/13646/14</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2015 13:48:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13646-14</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/black-mesa-vs-half-life-2/13646.rss">Black Mesa vs. Half-Life 2</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Black Mesa vs. Half-Life 2</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Ctoagu]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Funnily enough, I think Route Canal and Ravenholm are chapters that had quite a few bits and pieces left over from the Half Life 2 beta. After watching Valve News Network on Youtube do a playthrough of a cobbled-together beta experience, all of the maps were essentially very confusing to navigate, even for him. VNN actually called it to attention and mentioned that these maps were much more reminiscent of the way Half Life 1 worked - winding and maze-like, with little attention being paid to how the structures would make sense in a real-world standpoint.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/black-mesa-vs-half-life-2/13646/13">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/black-mesa-vs-half-life-2/13646/13</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2015 02:43:14 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13646-13</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/black-mesa-vs-half-life-2/13646.rss">Black Mesa vs. Half-Life 2</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
