<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Gabe teases hint at episode 3</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/gabe-teases-hint-at-episode-3/7862</link>
    <description>Let the wild speculation on release date begin 
[url=&#39;https://www.metro.co.uk/tech/games/876280-valve-tease-half-life-2-episode-three-reveal&#39;]https://www.metro.co.uk/tech/games/876280-valve-tease-half-life-2-episode-three-reveal[/url]</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 28 Dec 2011 03:07:19 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Half-Life Series</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/gabe-teases-hint-at-episode-3/7862.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Gabe teases hint at episode 3</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[RedShirt]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="SassyRobot">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 SassyRobot:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>This is just your first post and you’ve already gone full retard.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Never go full retard. You’ll go home empty handed.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>I don’t want to get my all caps rage on like you have been but WHY ARE YOU ASKING VALVE HERE?!</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Here it’s just entertaining, it would be funny if he did pull this on Valve’s boards. I’d flag the post just to see if they went all anonymous/medieval on him. IP trace, MAC ID flagging, close his steam account and ban him from ever opening another. Then pass the IP and MAC ID along to friends and associates at other companies to do the same. Lather, Rinse, Repeat.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/gabe-teases-hint-at-episode-3/7862/143">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/gabe-teases-hint-at-episode-3/7862/143</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 28 Dec 2011 03:07:19 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7862-143</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/gabe-teases-hint-at-episode-3/7862.rss">Gabe teases hint at episode 3</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Gabe teases hint at episode 3</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Siggs]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>What a great read. Glad I came in here now</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/gabe-teases-hint-at-episode-3/7862/142">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/gabe-teases-hint-at-episode-3/7862/142</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 27 Dec 2011 15:15:13 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7862-142</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/gabe-teases-hint-at-episode-3/7862.rss">Gabe teases hint at episode 3</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Gabe teases hint at episode 3</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Kent_Slak]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>You see Forthegz, you have the right to have your opinion, but it’s just so wrong, at least for me, and probably for everyone else here.</p>
<p>Valve makes great games, and the first half life was one of the best pc games of that time, same goes with Half life 2, it may not have been the best Graphics (who young people only play games that hardly run on their computers), HL always have a unique way of playing, action based game with puzzle’s and the Gravity gun, it’s one of the best weapons in games till today. And we must not forget a fucking great storyline which for me personaly is the best. + Soundtrack is great.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/gabe-teases-hint-at-episode-3/7862/141">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/gabe-teases-hint-at-episode-3/7862/141</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 27 Dec 2011 09:00:15 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7862-141</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/gabe-teases-hint-at-episode-3/7862.rss">Gabe teases hint at episode 3</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Gabe teases hint at episode 3</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Madcat1030]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><span class="bbcode-i">Episode three, done<br>
That’s what we all want to hear<br>
So release it now.</span></p>
<p><img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=9" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji only-emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/gabe-teases-hint-at-episode-3/7862/140">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/gabe-teases-hint-at-episode-3/7862/140</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 26 Dec 2011 17:31:12 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7862-140</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/gabe-teases-hint-at-episode-3/7862.rss">Gabe teases hint at episode 3</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Gabe teases hint at episode 3</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Maxey]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Honestly, back in 2004, Source wasn’t even the most technologically advanced engine either. The first CryEngine was a lot more advanced in almost all aspects. Only thing Source had going for itself at the time was the advanced facial animation and physics because other than that, CryEngine 1 and idTech 4 had Source beat at its own game in pretty much anything else.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/gabe-teases-hint-at-episode-3/7862/139">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/gabe-teases-hint-at-episode-3/7862/139</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 26 Dec 2011 16:42:21 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7862-139</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/gabe-teases-hint-at-episode-3/7862.rss">Gabe teases hint at episode 3</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Gabe teases hint at episode 3</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Mabilis]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="TrantaLocked">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/t/7feea3/40.png" class="avatar"> TrantaLocked:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Source was never more powerful or intuitive than other top-notch engines; it was and is just an engine that works.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>While I agree with the rest of your post, I disagree with this. Don’t you remember? the source engine was released in 2004.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/gabe-teases-hint-at-episode-3/7862/138">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/gabe-teases-hint-at-episode-3/7862/138</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 26 Dec 2011 15:50:59 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7862-138</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/gabe-teases-hint-at-episode-3/7862.rss">Gabe teases hint at episode 3</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Gabe teases hint at episode 3</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Jack_Freeman]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="forthegz">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/f/94ad74/40.png" class="avatar"> forthegz:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>MASS Effect 3 WINS<br>
SKYRIM WINS<br>
FALLOUT 3 and NV WINS<br>
[COLOR=‘Red’]MW2/Blackops/3 WINS[/SIZE]<br>
BATTLEFIELD 3 WINS<br>
DRAGON AGE WINS<br>
GTA4 WINS<br>
GTA5 PROBABLY WINS<br>
STAR WARS:TOR WINS<br>
GUILD WARS 2 WINS</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Get out of here… Now.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/gabe-teases-hint-at-episode-3/7862/137">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/gabe-teases-hint-at-episode-3/7862/137</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 26 Dec 2011 14:22:30 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7862-137</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/gabe-teases-hint-at-episode-3/7862.rss">Gabe teases hint at episode 3</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Gabe teases hint at episode 3</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Collision]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="forthegz">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/f/94ad74/40.png" class="avatar"> forthegz:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>wall of crap</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Polititians would be envious of the amount of shit you can spit out.</p>
<p>That entire post is full of not only the normal amount of faggotry, but ‘facts’ pulled from your arse.</p>
<p>You opinion =/= fact.</p>
<p>Simply put, you are a collosal fuckwit, who has no idea what they are talking about.</p>
<p>Please do the world a favour and don’t reproduce (doubt it will be much of a challenge for you).</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/gabe-teases-hint-at-episode-3/7862/136">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/gabe-teases-hint-at-episode-3/7862/136</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 26 Dec 2011 13:48:15 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7862-136</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/gabe-teases-hint-at-episode-3/7862.rss">Gabe teases hint at episode 3</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Gabe teases hint at episode 3</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Kent_Slak]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Just for a simple info</p>
<p>In our Country the leading gaming magazine has rated Half life 2 with a score od 97 out of 100, which is the highest rated game in Slovenia, no call of duty or crysis</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/gabe-teases-hint-at-episode-3/7862/135">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/gabe-teases-hint-at-episode-3/7862/135</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 26 Dec 2011 10:55:36 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7862-135</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/gabe-teases-hint-at-episode-3/7862.rss">Gabe teases hint at episode 3</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Gabe teases hint at episode 3</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[TrantaLocked]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>forthegz, while I don’t agree with you at all, if any of those problems were actually problems, Half-Life 1 alone makes up for all of them.</p>
<p>For one, Valve doesn’t run by due dates. They aren’t like Activision/Infinity Ward where they release a new sequel every year. They put more effort than the industry on average does into creating genuinely fun and intriguing games. No, they aren’t gods, and not all of their games are classics. They are known, however, for being consistent and loyal to the PC gaming industry.</p>
<p>The hype you are suggesting exists around the new engine doesn’t exist. Like you said, it IS just a new engine. Source was never more powerful or intuitive than other top-notch engines; it was and is just an engine that works.</p>
<p>We still don’t know any thing about the next Half-Life. Maybe it will be similar to the 2011 engine, or maybe it will completely destroy the Battlefield 3 engine in terms of physics and movement. Whatever happens, it won’t be just about the engine, it will be about the game as a whole. In the end, you are still in first person mode carrying along some weapons like every other FPS, including the ones you named that “win.”</p>
<p>To answer you’re question about what they have been working on: <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/List_of_games_developed_by_Valve" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/List_of_games_developed_by_Valve</a></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/gabe-teases-hint-at-episode-3/7862/134">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/gabe-teases-hint-at-episode-3/7862/134</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 26 Dec 2011 09:16:57 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7862-134</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/gabe-teases-hint-at-episode-3/7862.rss">Gabe teases hint at episode 3</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Gabe teases hint at episode 3</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Ry_amp_955_n]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Smat">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/s/e47c2d/40.png" class="avatar"> Smat:</div>
<blockquote>
<p><img src="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/original/3X/c/7/c71c87d70958b8fa050686014d78021e5e1f0637.gif" alt="" data-base62-sha1="spq8SsTXwm6mXxyTmg2966zDlrx" width="330" height="248"></p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>holy fuck i lol’d.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/gabe-teases-hint-at-episode-3/7862/133">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/gabe-teases-hint-at-episode-3/7862/133</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 26 Dec 2011 08:28:41 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7862-133</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/gabe-teases-hint-at-episode-3/7862.rss">Gabe teases hint at episode 3</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Gabe teases hint at episode 3</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[11dog11]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Bah">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/b/82dd89/40.png" class="avatar"> Bah:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I did not bother to read your post, however I was greatly impressed with its extraordinary length and varied, if not entirely correct, use of punctuation.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>LOL, that’s the funniest shit I’ve heard all day.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/gabe-teases-hint-at-episode-3/7862/132">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/gabe-teases-hint-at-episode-3/7862/132</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 26 Dec 2011 04:14:59 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7862-132</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/gabe-teases-hint-at-episode-3/7862.rss">Gabe teases hint at episode 3</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Gabe teases hint at episode 3</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Bah]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="forthegz">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/f/94ad74/40.png" class="avatar"> forthegz:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Gabe is a dickhead for making us wait and being a shady snake about it in general.</p>
<p>Facts:</p>
<p>Valve has no current games at the top rank in any genre.<br>
Crysis 1/2 Fallout 3/NV now Skyrim/ and MW2/3 Battlefield 3(online and single player) all beat the shit out of any fps valve has ever made. If you disagree, you’re simply wrong and i’m sorry.</p>
<p>L4D is a bad game most professional gamers agree 100% its not even close to a solid competitive game, its a fun stoner game for killing zombies and if you want that… Dead Island is much much better.</p>
<p>Portal 1 and 2 are fun, but also shallow due to the fact that you can beat them in 4 to 6 hours easily AND seeing as they are so linear replay value is about 0%.</p>
<p>So what does Valve do? Currently the most important thing Valve has done over the last few years is have STEAM boom into the best online store around, which is fantastic… but then again that is not making great games that is just selling me great games made by other companies.</p>
<p>If you look at the complete list of every project Valve has worked on over the last 5 years… and compare it to ANY OTHER COMPANY they fail. EVERY game they’ve made based on the source engine should not count 100% as a new game. Also most of these games are repeats of older games, DOD:Source, CS:Source even TF:2 which was fantastic before they ruined it with all of the weapons and silly hats is just a LIGHT arena based FPS. When I say repeats of OLDER games that means… BESIDES DEVELOPING IT USING THE NEW ENGINE they do NOT NEED TO THINK ABOUT ANYTHING… NO MENTAL PLANNING… SAME MAPS… NEW GRAPHICS SAME GUNS NEW GRAPHICS… NO NEW CHARACTERS NO NEW ANYTHING…</p>
<p>Now with saying LIGHT, let me explain. MOST of the games Valve makes are LIGHT, as in not taking much of a toll on computers to run and also being LIGHT in development. They tend to be SHORTER and MORE LINEAR. Half Life 2 COMBINED with its Episodes is probably only 60% of fallout 3 or NV and probably only 30% of Skyrim.</p>
<p>Which leads me to ask… Valve… you make linear light fps games based off of the same engine you’ve been using since 2004 just constantly updated (obviously)… atleast hurry up… whats taking so long? I mean Fallouts/ Skyrim/ and RPG’s like Mass Effect and Dragon Age are all games that are SHIT TONS longer and heavier than anything you’ve made…and those are being made FASTER than valve makes ANYTHING. so why are you taking so long to make… ANYTHING ELSE. I’m not even talking about HL3… ANYTHING make ANYTHING…</p>
<p>Valve does not have enough money to quickly develop amazing games? WRONG they have shitloads of money and should be able to develop as quickly as Activation/EA games/Bio…  but they don’t… why?</p>
<p>I know someone is thinking… OH its DOTA2 they have been working so hard on its going to be so good and blah blah… WRONG… DOTA2 is GOING TO BE A MOBA… MOBAS are as LIGHT AS THEY COME… the only time consuming process is making sure you make balanced choices when creating champions and gear. the actual development of the game should be something a shitty no name company can do… WAIT… Riot games already WoW’d the Moba genre with League of Legends… so whats up Valve… can you even compete with LoL? not so sure.</p>
<p>So why do they take so long… HERE is the point the HUGE point im making that should be understood all around…</p>
<p>NO MATTER how GOOD or AMAZING or ‘GROUND BREAKING’ the HL3 engine will be or how great of a single player game its going to be… THERE IS NO WAY it is going to be worth the wait we’ve already had to sit through… I mean like i said its not a cure for cancer or aids its a PROBABLY VERY LINEAR… VERY SHORT (8 hours tops ) FPS game with a STORYLINE THEY HAVE BEEN COOKING UP for 6 years. I’m going to enjoy it, but after my 8 hour play time it’s going to get uninstalled and probably NEVER played again.</p>
<p>So why they are taking so long and being so shady?</p>
<p>because they don’t give a fuck. They are LOST. They lost the race… they are no in 1st they can’t come back… there is a photo of Gabe playing WoW… and honestly that probably says alot more than you would think… He is RICHER than he ever could of imagined and probably does not even LEAD valve as effectively as he should. Hence LONG WAITS and UNNECESSARILY SHADY dealings about something that is almost 100% NOT going to be ground breaking in any way.</p>
<p>so if HL3 is going to be just anything linear single player game with a very short play time on a new engine… and DOTA 2 is just a moba… its JUST a moba… ITS JUST A MOBA… then what are they working on? WHAT ARE THEY DOING? AND WHY ARE THEY SO SHADY ABOUT THINGS THAT LOGICALLY SPEAKING ARE NOT EVEN THAT EXCITING?</p>
<p>HL has a HUGE fanbase… but in all seriousness… Valve missed their window and once that HL fanbase dies they die and will become the OWNERS of an ONLINE market that SELLS OTHER COMPANIES GAMES because every other company has already surpassed them by being polite and accurate with their release dates and upfront about what they are working on and MAKE BETTER GAMES.</p>
<p>Sorry for the rant but if you understand what I’m saying… i mean its not a lie its not some bullshit its extremely disappointing facts about Valve and their clear lack of giving a fact about gaming or were it is going and sadly they are left in the dust…</p>
<p>IF YOU DO NOT BELIEVE ME… when HL3 comes out… enjoy your 8 hour playtime and then you will realize… WOW this ENGINE is JUST ANOTHER FPS ENGINE… bodies fall in a realistic way… it looks good… it feel smooth. THANKS already been perfected… and since they have nothing else besides a linear single player with CS:GO OMG ANOTHER CS… NAHHHH and no other ground breaking games coming out… THEY LOSE.</p>
<p>MASS Effect 3 WINS<br>
SKYRIM WINS<br>
FALLOUT 3 and NV WINS<br>
MW2/Blackops/3 WINS<br>
BATTLEFIELD 3 WINS<br>
DRAGON AGE WINS<br>
GTA4 WINS<br>
GTA5 PROBABLY WINS<br>
STAR WARS:TOR WINS<br>
GUILD WARS 2 WINS</p>
<p>and any other PC GAMER COVER games… coming out within the next year are PROBABLY going to be better than HL3.</p>
<p>so PZ</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I did not bother to read your post, however I was greatly impressed with its extraordinary length and varied, if not entirely correct, use of punctuation.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/gabe-teases-hint-at-episode-3/7862/131">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/gabe-teases-hint-at-episode-3/7862/131</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 26 Dec 2011 02:21:15 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7862-131</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/gabe-teases-hint-at-episode-3/7862.rss">Gabe teases hint at episode 3</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Gabe teases hint at episode 3</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Surplus]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Maxey">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/user_avatar/leakfree.org/maxey/40/4358_2.png" class="avatar"> Maxey:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>lol</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>me too</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/gabe-teases-hint-at-episode-3/7862/130">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/gabe-teases-hint-at-episode-3/7862/130</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 26 Dec 2011 00:52:42 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7862-130</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/gabe-teases-hint-at-episode-3/7862.rss">Gabe teases hint at episode 3</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Gabe teases hint at episode 3</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Maxey]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="forthegz">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/f/94ad74/40.png" class="avatar"> forthegz:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Gabe is a dickhead for making us wait and being a shady snake about it in general.</p>
<p>Facts:</p>
<p>Valve has no current games at the top rank in any genre.<br>
Crysis 1/2 Fallout 3/NV now Skyrim/ and MW2/3 Battlefield 3(online and single player) all beat the shit out of any fps valve has ever made. If you disagree, you’re simply wrong and i’m sorry.</p>
<p>L4D is a bad game most professional gamers agree 100% its not even close to a solid competitive game, its a fun stoner game for killing zombies and if you want that… Dead Island is much much better.</p>
<p>Portal 1 and 2 are fun, but also shallow due to the fact that you can beat them in 4 to 6 hours easily AND seeing as they are so linear replay value is about 0%.</p>
<p>So what does Valve do? Currently the most important thing Valve has done over the last few years is have STEAM boom into the best online store around, which is fantastic… but then again that is not making great games that is just selling me great games made by other companies.</p>
<p>If you look at the complete list of every project Valve has worked on over the last 5 years… and compare it to ANY OTHER COMPANY they fail. EVERY game they’ve made based on the source engine should not count 100% as a new game. Also most of these games are repeats of older games, DOD:Source, CS:Source even TF:2 which was fantastic before they ruined it with all of the weapons and silly hats is just a LIGHT arena based FPS. When I say repeats of OLDER games that means… BESIDES DEVELOPING IT USING THE NEW ENGINE they do NOT NEED TO THINK ABOUT ANYTHING… NO MENTAL PLANNING… SAME MAPS… NEW GRAPHICS SAME GUNS NEW GRAPHICS… NO NEW CHARACTERS NO NEW ANYTHING…</p>
<p>Now with saying LIGHT, let me explain. MOST of the games Valve makes are LIGHT, as in not taking much of a toll on computers to run and also being LIGHT in development. They tend to be SHORTER and MORE LINEAR. Half Life 2 COMBINED with its Episodes is probably only 60% of fallout 3 or NV and probably only 30% of Skyrim.</p>
<p>Which leads me to ask… Valve… you make linear light fps games based off of the same engine you’ve been using since 2004 just constantly updated (obviously)… atleast hurry up… whats taking so long? I mean Fallouts/ Skyrim/ and RPG’s like Mass Effect and Dragon Age are all games that are SHIT TONS longer and heavier than anything you’ve made…and those are being made FASTER than valve makes ANYTHING. so why are you taking so long to make… ANYTHING ELSE. I’m not even talking about HL3… ANYTHING make ANYTHING…</p>
<p>Valve does not have enough money to quickly develop amazing games? WRONG they have shitloads of money and should be able to develop as quickly as Activation/EA games/Bio…  but they don’t… why?</p>
<p>I know someone is thinking… OH its DOTA2 they have been working so hard on its going to be so good and blah blah… WRONG… DOTA2 is GOING TO BE A MOBA… MOBAS are as LIGHT AS THEY COME… the only time consuming process is making sure you make balanced choices when creating champions and gear. the actual development of the game should be something a shitty no name company can do… WAIT… Riot games already WoW’d the Moba genre with League of Legends… so whats up Valve… can you even compete with LoL? not so sure.</p>
<p>So why do they take so long… HERE is the point the HUGE point im making that should be understood all around…</p>
<p>NO MATTER how GOOD or AMAZING or ‘GROUND BREAKING’ the HL3 engine will be or how great of a single player game its going to be… THERE IS NO WAY it is going to be worth the wait we’ve already had to sit through… I mean like i said its not a cure for cancer or aids its a PROBABLY VERY LINEAR… VERY SHORT (8 hours tops ) FPS game with a STORYLINE THEY HAVE BEEN COOKING UP for 6 years. I’m going to enjoy it, but after my 8 hour play time it’s going to get uninstalled and probably NEVER played again.</p>
<p>So why they are taking so long and being so shady?</p>
<p>because they don’t give a fuck. They are LOST. They lost the race… they are no in 1st they can’t come back… there is a photo of Gabe playing WoW… and honestly that probably says alot more than you would think… He is RICHER than he ever could of imagined and probably does not even LEAD valve as effectively as he should. Hence LONG WAITS and UNNECESSARILY SHADY dealings about something that is almost 100% NOT going to be ground breaking in any way.</p>
<p>so if HL3 is going to be just anything linear single player game with a very short play time on a new engine… and DOTA 2 is just a moba… its JUST a moba… ITS JUST A MOBA… then what are they working on? WHAT ARE THEY DOING? AND WHY ARE THEY SO SHADY ABOUT THINGS THAT LOGICALLY SPEAKING ARE NOT EVEN THAT EXCITING?</p>
<p>HL has a HUGE fanbase… but in all seriousness… Valve missed their window and once that HL fanbase dies they die and will become the OWNERS of an ONLINE market that SELLS OTHER COMPANIES GAMES because every other company has already surpassed them by being polite and accurate with their release dates and upfront about what they are working on and MAKE BETTER GAMES.</p>
<p>Sorry for the rant but if you understand what I’m saying… i mean its not a lie its not some bullshit its extremely disappointing facts about Valve and their clear lack of giving a fact about gaming or were it is going and sadly they are left in the dust…</p>
<p>IF YOU DO NOT BELIEVE ME… when HL3 comes out… enjoy your 8 hour playtime and then you will realize… WOW this ENGINE is JUST ANOTHER FPS ENGINE… bodies fall in a realistic way… it looks good… it feel smooth. THANKS already been perfected… and since they have nothing else besides a linear single player with CS:GO OMG ANOTHER CS… NAHHHH and no other ground breaking games coming out… THEY LOSE.</p>
<p>MASS Effect 3 WINS<br>
SKYRIM WINS<br>
FALLOUT 3 and NV WINS<br>
MW2/Blackops/3 WINS<br>
BATTLEFIELD 3 WINS<br>
DRAGON AGE WINS<br>
GTA4 WINS<br>
GTA5 PROBABLY WINS<br>
STAR WARS:TOR WINS<br>
GUILD WARS 2 WINS</p>
<p>and any other PC GAMER COVER games… coming out within the next year are PROBABLY going to be better than HL3.</p>
<p>so PZ</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>lol</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/gabe-teases-hint-at-episode-3/7862/129">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/gabe-teases-hint-at-episode-3/7862/129</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 26 Dec 2011 00:06:54 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7862-129</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/gabe-teases-hint-at-episode-3/7862.rss">Gabe teases hint at episode 3</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Gabe teases hint at episode 3</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[RedShirt]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="arizzi">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/a/b19c9b/40.png" class="avatar"> arizzi:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Its one of those surprisingly common cases where the person is just so stupid, ignorant, or idiotic that it seems a daunting task to even attempt to correct him fully.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>What he did there I suppose could be referred to as a <a href="https://rationalwiki.org/wiki/Gish_gallop" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Gish Gallup</a>. I do enjoy the occasional flame and troll, but there is a time and a place. This forum is neither, but I really wanted to put this, ahem, person in their place. I figured that a systematic dismantling was in order, a gallup of my own if you will.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/gabe-teases-hint-at-episode-3/7862/128">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/gabe-teases-hint-at-episode-3/7862/128</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 26 Dec 2011 00:01:16 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7862-128</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/gabe-teases-hint-at-episode-3/7862.rss">Gabe teases hint at episode 3</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Gabe teases hint at episode 3</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[seeker7125]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="E-Nelson">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/e/34f0e0/40.png" class="avatar"> E-Nelson:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Registered by</p>
<p>David Hassen<br>
PO Box 459<br>
Drums, PA 18222<br>
US<br>
570-708-8780</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Like I said, probably troll, but still fun  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=9" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
<p><a href="https://kotaku.com/5870308/heres-your-weekly-instalment-of-half+life-3-trolling" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://kotaku.com/5870308/heres-your-weekly-instalment-of-half+life-3-trolling</a></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/gabe-teases-hint-at-episode-3/7862/127">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/gabe-teases-hint-at-episode-3/7862/127</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 25 Dec 2011 21:54:54 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7862-127</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/gabe-teases-hint-at-episode-3/7862.rss">Gabe teases hint at episode 3</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Gabe teases hint at episode 3</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[E-Nelson]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="seeker7125">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/s/50afbb/40.png" class="avatar"> seeker7125:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Probably old old news… Probably trolling but I like the festive snowflakes lol</p>
<p><a href="https://www.black-aperture.com/" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://www.black-aperture.com/</a></p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Registered by</p>
<p>David Hassen<br>
PO Box 459<br>
Drums, PA 18222<br>
US<br>
570-708-8780</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/gabe-teases-hint-at-episode-3/7862/126">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/gabe-teases-hint-at-episode-3/7862/126</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 25 Dec 2011 21:07:44 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7862-126</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/gabe-teases-hint-at-episode-3/7862.rss">Gabe teases hint at episode 3</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Gabe teases hint at episode 3</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[kitor]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>There’s already thread about it<br>
<a href="https://forums.blackmesasource.com/showthread.php?t=10913" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://forums.blackmesasource.com/showthread.php?t=10913</a></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/gabe-teases-hint-at-episode-3/7862/125">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/gabe-teases-hint-at-episode-3/7862/125</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 25 Dec 2011 21:07:14 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7862-125</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/gabe-teases-hint-at-episode-3/7862.rss">Gabe teases hint at episode 3</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Gabe teases hint at episode 3</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[seeker7125]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Probably old old news… Probably trolling but I like the festive snowflakes lol</p>
<p><a href="https://www.black-aperture.com/" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://www.black-aperture.com/</a></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/gabe-teases-hint-at-episode-3/7862/124">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/gabe-teases-hint-at-episode-3/7862/124</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 25 Dec 2011 20:10:31 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7862-124</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/gabe-teases-hint-at-episode-3/7862.rss">Gabe teases hint at episode 3</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Gabe teases hint at episode 3</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[TheOneAndOnly]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>forthegz made me lol</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/gabe-teases-hint-at-episode-3/7862/123">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/gabe-teases-hint-at-episode-3/7862/123</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 25 Dec 2011 20:05:06 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7862-123</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/gabe-teases-hint-at-episode-3/7862.rss">Gabe teases hint at episode 3</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Gabe teases hint at episode 3</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[arizzi]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Its one of those surprisingly common cases where the person is just so stupid, ignorant, or idiotic that it seems a daunting task to even attempt to correct him fully.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/gabe-teases-hint-at-episode-3/7862/122">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/gabe-teases-hint-at-episode-3/7862/122</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 25 Dec 2011 19:51:31 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7862-122</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/gabe-teases-hint-at-episode-3/7862.rss">Gabe teases hint at episode 3</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Gabe teases hint at episode 3</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[lithium.bb]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="forthegz">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/f/94ad74/40.png" class="avatar"> forthegz:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>CS:GO OMG ANOTHER CS…</p>
<p>…</p>
<p>MW2/Blackops/3 WINS</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/gabe-teases-hint-at-episode-3/7862/121">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/gabe-teases-hint-at-episode-3/7862/121</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 25 Dec 2011 16:27:49 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7862-121</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/gabe-teases-hint-at-episode-3/7862.rss">Gabe teases hint at episode 3</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Gabe teases hint at episode 3</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Smat]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Disturbulator">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/d/cc9497/40.png" class="avatar"> Disturbulator:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>And that, right there.<br>
Is an internet bitchslap.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p><img src="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/original/3X/c/7/c71c87d70958b8fa050686014d78021e5e1f0637.gif" alt="" data-base62-sha1="spq8SsTXwm6mXxyTmg2966zDlrx" width="330" height="248"></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/gabe-teases-hint-at-episode-3/7862/120">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/gabe-teases-hint-at-episode-3/7862/120</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 25 Dec 2011 10:27:39 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7862-120</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/gabe-teases-hint-at-episode-3/7862.rss">Gabe teases hint at episode 3</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Gabe teases hint at episode 3</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[brokenfridgehinge]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>tl;dr faggot.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/gabe-teases-hint-at-episode-3/7862/119">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/gabe-teases-hint-at-episode-3/7862/119</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 25 Dec 2011 10:13:15 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7862-119</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/gabe-teases-hint-at-episode-3/7862.rss">Gabe teases hint at episode 3</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
