<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Tomonobu Itagaki is Back, New Team and New Game.</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/tomonobu-itagaki-is-back-new-team-and-new-game/417</link>
    <description>Pompous and outspoken he may be, but there&#39;s no question his game developing philosophy should be embraced by more game companies (particularly the ones that pump out a game with the substance consisting of all flash and lacking sorely in game mechanics).

Responsible for creating the Dead or Alive fighting series as well as reviving the classic Ninja Gaiden games into a 3D incarnation that has been lauded as one of the most challenging and polished 3D action game experiences by reviewers everywhere, his resume is indeed impressive.

Following a falling out with former employer Tecmo, Itagaki-san&#39;s future in the video game industry was in question.  The reason for his falling out with Tecmo being that they did not meet the contractual agreement of honouring a bonus he was supposed to receive once a certain number of Ninja Gaiden 2 units were sold he filed a lawsuit and promptly left the company.

I&#39;m definitely looking forward to his future projects as I have a great appreciation in regards to his sensibilities in game development and the types of gamers he seeks to appease, he has very little tolerance for fluff.

Here&#39;s an interview with 1Up.com concerning his future projects and the new development team he has put together.

[url]https://www.1up.com/do/feature?cId=3174393[/url]</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 27 May 2009 08:05:40 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Technology and Gaming</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/tomonobu-itagaki-is-back-new-team-and-new-game/417.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Tomonobu Itagaki is Back, New Team and New Game.</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crunchy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I loved Ninja Gaiden 2.  It’s one of my all time favorite games.  Beat it on Mentor but then Master Ninja shamed me :meh:</p>
<p>Anyway, I’m interested to see what else Itagaki can do.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/tomonobu-itagaki-is-back-new-team-and-new-game/417/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/tomonobu-itagaki-is-back-new-team-and-new-game/417/2</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 27 May 2009 08:05:40 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-417-2</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/tomonobu-itagaki-is-back-new-team-and-new-game/417.rss">Tomonobu Itagaki is Back, New Team and New Game.</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Tomonobu Itagaki is Back, New Team and New Game.</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[InterloperX]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Pompous and outspoken he may be, but there’s no question his game developing philosophy should be embraced by more game companies (particularly the ones that pump out a game with the substance consisting of all flash and lacking sorely in game mechanics).</p>
<p>Responsible for creating the Dead or Alive fighting series as well as reviving the classic Ninja Gaiden games into a 3D incarnation that has been lauded as one of the most challenging and polished 3D action game experiences by reviewers everywhere, his resume is indeed impressive.</p>
<p>Following a falling out with former employer Tecmo, Itagaki-san’s future in the video game industry was in question.  The reason for his falling out with Tecmo being that they did not meet the contractual agreement of honouring a bonus he was supposed to receive once a certain number of Ninja Gaiden 2 units were sold he filed a lawsuit and promptly left the company.</p>
<p>I’m definitely looking forward to his future projects as I have a great appreciation in regards to his sensibilities in game development and the types of gamers he seeks to appease, he has very little tolerance for fluff.</p>
<p>Here’s an interview with <a href="http://1Up.com" rel="nofollow noopener">1Up.com</a> concerning his future projects and the new development team he has put together.</p>
<p><a href="https://www.1up.com/do/feature?cId=3174393" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://www.1up.com/do/feature?cId=3174393</a></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/tomonobu-itagaki-is-back-new-team-and-new-game/417/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/tomonobu-itagaki-is-back-new-team-and-new-game/417/1</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 27 May 2009 03:59:01 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-417-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/tomonobu-itagaki-is-back-new-team-and-new-game/417.rss">Tomonobu Itagaki is Back, New Team and New Game.</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
