<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crash after electrocuting Gargantua in Power Up</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/crash-after-electrocuting-gargantua-in-power-up/14233</link>
    <description>So, as subject states, the game crashes to desktop at the end of the electrocution animation. First crash so far, no other unknown issues (that sprint animation thing though... &gt;_&lt;).

I used the search function on this forum, couldn&#39;t find any related topics, so I thought I&#39;d make one and check if I&#39;m the only one. I also checked but couldn&#39;t find a .dmp file - the folder is there, but the dump file is not (two other, unrelated dumps are).

Running this on my laptop, Win 8.1, forced on dedicated gfx chip rather than integrated, no mods or tweaks, default settings except 1920x1080 with vsync on. I know this isn&#39;t much to go on, but hey, gotta start somewhere right? Maybe someone else has the same issue and can contribute more data. =3


[edit:] Second run through did not crash the game. I&#39;m not sure, but it seems the game paused a fraction of a second right before the music started playing, pretty much at the same moment as the game crashed the previous time. If you want me to, I can try to reproduce the issue by running through a few more times? [/edit]</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 18 Jun 2015 11:48:12 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>In-game Issues</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/crash-after-electrocuting-gargantua-in-power-up/14233.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Crash after electrocuting Gargantua in Power Up</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Jake_R]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>So, as subject states, the game crashes to desktop at the end of the electrocution animation. First crash so far, no other unknown issues (that sprint animation thing though… &gt;_&lt;).</p>
<p>I used the search function on this forum, couldn’t find any related topics, so I thought I’d make one and check if I’m the only one. I also checked but couldn’t find a .dmp file - the folder is there, but the dump file is not (two other, unrelated dumps are).</p>
<p>Running this on my laptop, Win 8.1, forced on dedicated gfx chip rather than integrated, no mods or tweaks, default settings except 1920x1080 with vsync on. I know this isn’t much to go on, but hey, gotta start somewhere right? Maybe someone else has the same issue and can contribute more data. =3</p>
<div class="sepquote">
<span class="smallfont">Edit:</span>
<br>
<br>
<p> Second run through did not crash the game. I’m not sure, but it seems the game paused a fraction of a second right before the music started playing, pretty much at the same moment as the game crashed the previous time. If you want me to, I can try to reproduce the issue by running through a few more times? </p>
</div>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/crash-after-electrocuting-gargantua-in-power-up/14233/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/crash-after-electrocuting-gargantua-in-power-up/14233/1</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jun 2015 11:48:12 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14233-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/crash-after-electrocuting-gargantua-in-power-up/14233.rss">Crash after electrocuting Gargantua in Power Up</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
