<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>A little report</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/a-little-report/10109</link>
    <description>First of all, tremendous work and congratulatory remarks to all of the BMS team.

I loved this game as a dire HL fan and it would have easily been worth a respectable ammount of money.

Since BM has easy access to updating their game through steam, I figure I&#39;d like to point out a few things that seemed wrong.

Note that I&#39;ve played under the &quot;Normal&quot; difficulty.

[COLOR=&#39;DarkOrange&#39;]- Human grunts and apaches seem to have far too much firepower.

I&#39;m not sure if it&#39;s because grunts shoot auto, but 2-3 of them at once can pretty much instantly get you down to 0. While this seems about the same as the original game, grunts didn&#39;t have the ability to move and shoot at once, making them much more dangerous and effective.

The apache is a monster. It has increased fire rate, lightning-fast maneuverability, has no restricted shooting angle and takes more punishment than a strider. In the original game, it was a deadly opponent aswell but it did have proper weaknesses, such as being unable to shoot without facing you and flying around slowly. I would be okay with its new behavior if it didn&#39;t have that much health. 

It almost seems very silly that an osprey only takes 4 mp5 grenades before going down, creating a ridiculous contrast between the former and the apache.

[COLOR=&#39;DarkOrange&#39;]- Black Mesa gameplay options do not seem to stay

Things like auto-aim, viewbob slider and the train fail-safe aren&#39;t remembered if you exit and start the game again.

[COLOR=&#39;DarkOrange&#39;]- Disabling noise doesn&#39;t work

I can see the grains fine even with the noise shader deactivated

[COLOR=&#39;DarkOrange&#39;]- HL1 style movement ignores +walk

While I understand valve botched +walk heavily in HL2, it would have been a very useful movement to have back. I know +speed mimics it, but it seems too fast to be considered &quot;walking&quot;

-[COLOR=&#39;DarkOrange&#39;] Disabling blood/radiation on view models

Since there are plenty of customizable options, I figure this one wouldn&#39;t be asking too much for. While it can look pretty, I prefer seeing my arms clean at all times.

[COLOR=&#39;DarkOrange&#39;]- Drowning

It seems strange that you only lose 2 health points per tick when drowning. I think it would be a threat again if it were brought up back to the HL2 damage (10)

[COLOR=&#39;DarkOrange&#39;]- Zombie barney turning into a torso

When a zombie guard gibs into a torso, it becomes a scientist torso, and the leg gibs change aswell. Seems like a bug.

[COLOR=&#39;DarkOrange&#39;]- Bullsquids seem to have an extra [url=&#39;https://www.sourceop.com/hell-met/squideye.jpg&#39;]eyeball into their eyes[/url]

Not sure if a bug, Just checking.

[COLOR=&#39;DarkOrange&#39;]- The flashlight seems to create alot of graphic lag, and it seems to interact badly with [url=&#39;https://www.sourceop.com/hell-met/bmflash.jpg&#39;]the view model[/url].

[COLOR=&#39;DarkOrange&#39;]- The first garg seems very unresponsive during its special sequences, such as kneeling into the doorway.

[COLOR=&#39;DarkOrange&#39;]- Crowbar does not 1shot barnacles

[COLOR=&#39;DarkOrange&#39;]- Handgrenades feel generally useless and not worth the effort

I would suggest having them thrown at the same force HL2 grenades are thrown at all times.

[COLOR=&#39;DarkOrange&#39;]- The ichthyosaur

It seems to have too few health. A single shotgun double-blast kills one. It also seems to have a strangely large attack range, hitting you from several meters away.

[COLOR=&#39;DarkOrange&#39;]- Option to make the crossbow aim sensitivity scale with the zoom.

Pretty self-explanatory. Having no reduced sensitivity pretty much makes the scope unuseable.

[COLOR=&#39;DarkOrange&#39;]- The gauss laser shot seems to spawn from under the [url=&#39;https://www.sourceop.com/hell-met/gauss.jpg&#39;]barrel emitter[/url].

[COLOR=&#39;DarkOrange&#39;]- The tentacle behavior seems inconsistent

They simply hit stuff all the time without stopping. They never calm down and gently sing like the original did. I figure that&#39;s a pretty important way to know if a player is silent enough and doing well.

[COLOR=&#39;DarkOrange&#39;]- Alien creatures such as the bullsquid, tentacle, alien grunt, garg and controller are lacking interesting sounds.

They do not seem very distinctive at all, nor anything like the original game. The only noise I could remember was one of the garg&#39;s which sounded like a generic stock roar sound anyway. 

And while I very appreciate the consistency between the HL2 vortigaunts and the alien slaves, they certainly could use proper pain/death sounds, rather than going &quot;SHUR&quot; everytime they eat a shotgun blast to the face.

[COLOR=&#39;DarkOrange&#39;]- Option to toggle mp5 burst and single fire mode

[COLOR=&#39;DarkOrange&#39;]- Headcrab walking animation

Something seems off with it. Was it done on purpose? I believe sticking with the stock HL2 crab was a wise choice, though that walk doesn&#39;t seem normal.

[COLOR=&#39;DarkOrange&#39;]- Hivehand seems cartoonish

A personal nitpick of mine, but it feels like the texture belongs to TF2. The low-definition hivehand might have been a better choice to base it on, rather than the HD one. That poor, poor hivehand.

[COLOR=&#39;DarkOrange&#39;]- Strange lag in specific spots

My computer runs any source game very fine, though BMS seems to have a few harsh spots such as[url=&#39;https://www.sourceop.com/hell-met/fps1.jpg&#39;]here[/url]. I also had very lower frame-rates when I reloaded the game during the [url=&#39;https://www.sourceop.com/hell-met/fps2.jpg&#39;]final teleporter sequence[/url]

And finally, as meaningless as it is, I&#39;m not really a fan of the view model positioning and overall animations, but I know it&#39;s here to stay. However I would love to see the non-experimental weaponry slapped on valve&#39;s HL2 anims.[/SIZE]

-

Again, outstanding work and I look forward seeing the game made better. Please do not interpret this thread as whining, this was definitely worth the wait.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 16 Sep 2012 05:05:42 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>The Cafeteria</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/a-little-report/10109.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>A little report</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Hell-met]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Oh, that.</p>
<p>thank you</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/a-little-report/10109/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/a-little-report/10109/8</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 16 Sep 2012 05:05:42 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-10109-8</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/a-little-report/10109.rss">A little report</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>A little report</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Tuskin38]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Hell-met">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/h/ecb155/40.png" class="avatar"> Hell-met:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>well I don’t want iron sights enabled</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Iron sight sticky is a separate option under the 357’s iron-sight toggle, you can enable it without enabling iron-sights.</p>
<p>It will make it so the crossbow’s scope is toggle instead of hold.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/a-little-report/10109/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/a-little-report/10109/7</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 16 Sep 2012 04:52:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-10109-7</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/a-little-report/10109.rss">A little report</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>A little report</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Lemonz_amp_amp_orang]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>i agree with all points, especially the ones on the mp5 semi option and crossbow scope sensitivity</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/a-little-report/10109/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/a-little-report/10109/6</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 16 Sep 2012 04:27:23 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-10109-6</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/a-little-report/10109.rss">A little report</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>A little report</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Hell-met]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Bloodshot">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/b/839c29/40.png" class="avatar"> Bloodshot:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>The crossbow scope already is toggleable, click on iron-sight sticky in the black mesa options.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>well I don’t want iron sights enabled</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/a-little-report/10109/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/a-little-report/10109/5</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 16 Sep 2012 04:13:32 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-10109-5</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/a-little-report/10109.rss">A little report</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>A little report</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[BobTheHeadcrap]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I agree with all these points.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/a-little-report/10109/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/a-little-report/10109/4</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 16 Sep 2012 03:57:57 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-10109-4</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/a-little-report/10109.rss">A little report</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>A little report</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Starscre4M]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>the crossbow’s aim sensitivity scale with the zoom is a must<br>
I played on normal and also agree with the ichthyosaur, they should have more health<br>
same for osprey, I just used one charged gauss shoot on it to take it down, didn’t have the chance to use my rocket launcher <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=9" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"></p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Bloodshot">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/b/839c29/40.png" class="avatar"> Bloodshot:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>And the gameplay options seem to stay fine for me when I modify them even after restart, though I’ll check again to be sure.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>here it restarts every time I launch again</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/a-little-report/10109/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/a-little-report/10109/3</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 16 Sep 2012 02:57:01 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-10109-3</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/a-little-report/10109.rss">A little report</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>A little report</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Bloodshot]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>The crossbow scope already is toggleable, click on iron-sight sticky in the black mesa options.</p>
<p>And the gameplay options seem to stay fine for me when I modify them even after restart, though I’ll check again to be sure.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/a-little-report/10109/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/a-little-report/10109/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 16 Sep 2012 02:40:38 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-10109-2</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/a-little-report/10109.rss">A little report</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>A little report</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Hell-met]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>First of all, tremendous work and congratulatory remarks to all of the BMS team.</p>
<p>I loved this game as a dire HL fan and it would have easily been worth a respectable ammount of money.</p>
<p>Since BM has easy access to updating their game through steam, I figure I’d like to point out a few things that seemed wrong.</p>
<p>Note that I’ve played under the “Normal” difficulty.</p>
<p>[COLOR=‘DarkOrange’]- Human grunts and apaches seem to have far too much firepower.</p>
<p>I’m not sure if it’s because grunts shoot auto, but 2-3 of them at once can pretty much instantly get you down to 0. While this seems about the same as the original game, grunts didn’t have the ability to move and shoot at once, making them much more dangerous and effective.</p>
<p>The apache is a monster. It has increased fire rate, lightning-fast maneuverability, has no restricted shooting angle and takes more punishment than a strider. In the original game, it was a deadly opponent aswell but it did have proper weaknesses, such as being unable to shoot without facing you and flying around slowly. I would be okay with its new behavior if it didn’t have that much health.</p>
<p>It almost seems very silly that an osprey only takes 4 mp5 grenades before going down, creating a ridiculous contrast between the former and the apache.</p>
<p>[COLOR=‘DarkOrange’]- Black Mesa gameplay options do not seem to stay</p>
<p>Things like auto-aim, viewbob slider and the train fail-safe aren’t remembered if you exit and start the game again.</p>
<p>[COLOR=‘DarkOrange’]- Disabling noise doesn’t work</p>
<p>I can see the grains fine even with the noise shader deactivated</p>
<p>[COLOR=‘DarkOrange’]- HL1 style movement ignores +walk</p>
<p>While I understand valve botched +walk heavily in HL2, it would have been a very useful movement to have back. I know +speed mimics it, but it seems too fast to be considered “walking”</p>
<p>-[COLOR=‘DarkOrange’] Disabling blood/radiation on view models</p>
<p>Since there are plenty of customizable options, I figure this one wouldn’t be asking too much for. While it can look pretty, I prefer seeing my arms clean at all times.</p>
<p>[COLOR=‘DarkOrange’]- Drowning</p>
<p>It seems strange that you only lose 2 health points per tick when drowning. I think it would be a threat again if it were brought up back to the HL2 damage (10)</p>
<p>[COLOR=‘DarkOrange’]- Zombie barney turning into a torso</p>
<p>When a zombie guard gibs into a torso, it becomes a scientist torso, and the leg gibs change aswell. Seems like a bug.</p>
<p>[COLOR=‘DarkOrange’]- Bullsquids seem to have an extra <a href="https://www.sourceop.com/hell-met/squideye.jpg" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">eyeball into their eyes</a></p>
<p>Not sure if a bug, Just checking.</p>
<p>[COLOR=‘DarkOrange’]- The flashlight seems to create alot of graphic lag, and it seems to interact badly with <a href="https://www.sourceop.com/hell-met/bmflash.jpg" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">the view model</a>.</p>
<p>[COLOR=‘DarkOrange’]- The first garg seems very unresponsive during its special sequences, such as kneeling into the doorway.</p>
<p>[COLOR=‘DarkOrange’]- Crowbar does not 1shot barnacles</p>
<p>[COLOR=‘DarkOrange’]- Handgrenades feel generally useless and not worth the effort</p>
<p>I would suggest having them thrown at the same force HL2 grenades are thrown at all times.</p>
<p>[COLOR=‘DarkOrange’]- The ichthyosaur</p>
<p>It seems to have too few health. A single shotgun double-blast kills one. It also seems to have a strangely large attack range, hitting you from several meters away.</p>
<p>[COLOR=‘DarkOrange’]- Option to make the crossbow aim sensitivity scale with the zoom.</p>
<p>Pretty self-explanatory. Having no reduced sensitivity pretty much makes the scope unuseable.</p>
<p>[COLOR=‘DarkOrange’]- The gauss laser shot seems to spawn from under the <a href="https://www.sourceop.com/hell-met/gauss.jpg" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">barrel emitter</a>.</p>
<p>[COLOR=‘DarkOrange’]- The tentacle behavior seems inconsistent</p>
<p>They simply hit stuff all the time without stopping. They never calm down and gently sing like the original did. I figure that’s a pretty important way to know if a player is silent enough and doing well.</p>
<p>[COLOR=‘DarkOrange’]- Alien creatures such as the bullsquid, tentacle, alien grunt, garg and controller are lacking interesting sounds.</p>
<p>They do not seem very distinctive at all, nor anything like the original game. The only noise I could remember was one of the garg’s which sounded like a generic stock roar sound anyway.</p>
<p>And while I very appreciate the consistency between the HL2 vortigaunts and the alien slaves, they certainly could use proper pain/death sounds, rather than going “SHUR” everytime they eat a shotgun blast to the face.</p>
<p>[COLOR=‘DarkOrange’]- Option to toggle mp5 burst and single fire mode</p>
<p>[COLOR=‘DarkOrange’]- Headcrab walking animation</p>
<p>Something seems off with it. Was it done on purpose? I believe sticking with the stock HL2 crab was a wise choice, though that walk doesn’t seem normal.</p>
<p>[COLOR=‘DarkOrange’]- Hivehand seems cartoonish</p>
<p>A personal nitpick of mine, but it feels like the texture belongs to TF2. The low-definition hivehand might have been a better choice to base it on, rather than the HD one. That poor, poor hivehand.</p>
<p>[COLOR=‘DarkOrange’]- Strange lag in specific spots</p>
<p>My computer runs any source game very fine, though BMS seems to have a few harsh spots such as<a href="https://www.sourceop.com/hell-met/fps1.jpg" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">here</a>. I also had very lower frame-rates when I reloaded the game during the <a href="https://www.sourceop.com/hell-met/fps2.jpg" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">final teleporter sequence</a></p>
<p>And finally, as meaningless as it is, I’m not really a fan of the view model positioning and overall animations, but I know it’s here to stay. However I would love to see the non-experimental weaponry slapped on valve’s HL2 anims.[/SIZE]</p>
<ul>
<li>
</li></ul>
<p>Again, outstanding work and I look forward seeing the game made better. Please do not interpret this thread as whining, this was definitely worth the wait.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/a-little-report/10109/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/a-little-report/10109/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 16 Sep 2012 02:17:09 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-10109-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/a-little-report/10109.rss">A little report</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
