<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Favorite moment</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/favorite-moment/10098</link>
    <description>[i]What moment from Black Mesa sticks in your mind more than any other?[/i]

I have to say I was just blown away by the level of detail and animation of the anti-mass spectrometer. Also killing the Garg in Power Up was such a tense and satisfying moment, and the music in the aftermath was just perfect.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 19 Sep 2012 04:03:25 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>The Cafeteria</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/favorite-moment/10098.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Favorite moment</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Joe_Freeman]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Office Complex when leading the huge group of survivors, On a Rail when comming out from the tunnels and launching the rocket, going through the destroyed buildings in Surface Tension, and the last time in the surface before going into Lambda Complex.</p>
<p>Also the ambush in On a Rail was epic. I don’t know why I liked it so much, maybe because you’re not alone.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/favorite-moment/10098/35">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/favorite-moment/10098/35</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 19 Sep 2012 04:03:25 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-10098-35</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/favorite-moment/10098.rss">Favorite moment</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Favorite moment</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[MrFob]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Wow, too many to make it easy to choose.<br>
Apart from the beginning when you just go “WOW, look at that!!!” every 30 seconds, I think the best one was the end of QE, from the moment you shut down the surgical unit right through to the beginning of surface tension. I went into the ambush with my glock and with a lot of luck (I am actually not such a good shooter gamer), I managed to take all the marines out with my 9mm pistol practically without taking damage. When the guy comes in afterwards and goes “I can’t believe what you just did”, I just thought “yeah mate, neither can I, actually.” Brilliant experience right there.<br>
Also, when you bring that one guard from the underground bunker all the way through to the large armory later on and meet up with the other guard, they have a really nce little chat which was awesome.<br>
Coming out at the cliff side is great too but I saw that one in some video already unfortunately so it wasn’t really new at that point.<br>
IU think the final battle at the lambda teleporter is really great as well. The scene with the scientists before the battle was really nice, I always love it when the dev team put in some more dialogue and gave the characters (however brief their appearance) a bit more personalty. During the fight itself, my framerate dropped suddenly (for the first and only time) so I had quite a hard time with the battle. It went so far that by the end of it I was down to about 25 health and had to time my positioning just right to be able to jump through the teleport right on time and excape the two grunts.</p>
<p>There are many more of course but these are the main ones from the top of my head. It’s just a fantastic experience over all.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/favorite-moment/10098/34">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/favorite-moment/10098/34</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 19 Sep 2012 03:14:24 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-10098-34</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/favorite-moment/10098.rss">Favorite moment</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Favorite moment</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[warpedfreeman]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I liked the part of the planes Fight in Forget About Freeman, The fights against the assassins, the Cliff section of Surface Tension , and many more, i mean the hole game in general  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=9" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/favorite-moment/10098/33">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/favorite-moment/10098/33</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 18 Sep 2012 22:27:01 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-10098-33</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/favorite-moment/10098.rss">Favorite moment</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Favorite moment</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[the_prospektor]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I’m in the process of playing Black Mesa to death (as if) and every time I hear Eli’s voice I like it more and more. At first I was a little put off by it, not really liking how it sounded. But as I kept coming back to that scene, it became apparent that the VA really studied the voice behind Eli and tried his best to match his mannerisms and overall tone. The guy did a good job for coming real close to Eli (at least a younger version of him).</p>
<p>The elevator scene right after the cascade where you send a group of scientists to their deaths (albeit unintentionally) gave me chills. It really made me feel like I had just accidentally killed people.</p>
<p>Alsooooooooo, the “DIE FREEMAN” on the wall is spelled right, unlike the first game! It makes the HECU guys look less idiotic.</p>
<p>While the ally system leaves a lot to be desired (annoyances like a guard being lit up by vortiguants/HECU and not turning around to shoot them), I still find it worth the effort to bring a guard or two with me as backup.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/favorite-moment/10098/32">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/favorite-moment/10098/32</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 18 Sep 2012 22:17:43 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-10098-32</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/favorite-moment/10098.rss">Favorite moment</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Favorite moment</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[pinkribbonscars]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Gordon shoving his hand up the Hivehands butt :retard:</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/favorite-moment/10098/31">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/favorite-moment/10098/31</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 18 Sep 2012 22:06:18 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-10098-31</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/favorite-moment/10098.rss">Favorite moment</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Favorite moment</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Gunsofglory]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Seeing the wreck of the anti-mass Spectrometer. I stared at that thing for like a min.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/favorite-moment/10098/30">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/favorite-moment/10098/30</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 18 Sep 2012 22:02:37 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-10098-30</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/favorite-moment/10098.rss">Favorite moment</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Favorite moment</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[jone4s]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>the bombing of the distant building complex in the background of the cliff side… that was absolutely unexpected and i was like Wooow!! oO</p>
<p>incredible progamming skills, whoever did this…</p>
<p>and then the fight in the questionable ethics lobby… it was pretty hard, but rewarding… genious idea… so so good…</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/favorite-moment/10098/29">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/favorite-moment/10098/29</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 18 Sep 2012 21:04:40 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-10098-29</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/favorite-moment/10098.rss">Favorite moment</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Favorite moment</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[LifeSuks]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>There was this absolutely awesome moment, I don’t know, sometime around the middle of Forget about Freeman where you are towning around the sewers and come upon one of the automated turrets. A headcrab was ambling towards me and, simply having had it out, I hit it with the TAU cannon.</p>
<p>The head crab happened to be just in the right position in front of the turret that, after being hit by the tau cannon, was blown backward into the turret, knocking it over. I really enjoyed that.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/favorite-moment/10098/28">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/favorite-moment/10098/28</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 18 Sep 2012 20:51:17 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-10098-28</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/favorite-moment/10098.rss">Favorite moment</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Favorite moment</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Pyroclase]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Spudz">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/s/9fc348/40.png" class="avatar"> Spudz:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Also killing the Garg in Power Up was such a tense and satisfying moment, and the music in the aftermath was just perfect.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I wish. I must have spent ten minutes trying to hit that button. I kept trying to lure the Garg closer thinking it wasn’t in the right place for the scripted sequence, I never noticed those damn plugs.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/favorite-moment/10098/27">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/favorite-moment/10098/27</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 18 Sep 2012 20:44:27 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-10098-27</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/favorite-moment/10098.rss">Favorite moment</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Favorite moment</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[raiseer]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Most things I liked most are already said here (repeatedly), so I’ll spare you these and talk about “the little things” I liked most:</p>
<ul>
<li>When I first saw the tiny cockroaches. I have to confess, I was a tiny-little-bit disappointed that I couldn’t stomp them  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=9" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:">  But I loved that they included them.</li>
<li>The first time I saw the disfigured faces of the scientists killed by headcrabs. Really well done.</li>
<li>At QE, when you walk into the room where the scientists blew themselves up with the tau cannon, and you see those smoking boots  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=9" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:">
</li>
<li>Last but not least: No fucking leeches in the water! I hated those so much. Thanks for killing them off.</li>
</ul>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/favorite-moment/10098/26">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/favorite-moment/10098/26</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 18 Sep 2012 20:33:31 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-10098-26</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/favorite-moment/10098.rss">Favorite moment</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Favorite moment</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Floyd]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>So many different parts of the mod that were beautifully done, but by <span class="bbcode-i">far</span> my favourite was Questionable Ethics.</p>
<p>The original level in Half-Life was a flat and flavourless experience and one of my least favourite levels in the game along with Residue Processing. I was astounded when Black Mesa turned it into one of the most beautiful, creepy and detailed levels in the entire game.</p>
<p>The ethics and the realisation that the aliens were being experimented on went completely over my head in the original. This time though, the lighting, the ambient screams in the background had me on edge throughout the entire level. Also it was great from a player’s point of view to be able to see and admire the effort that went into the models and animation when you saw the Xenians tied down on operating tables and in cages.</p>
<p>Not only was the level hugely expanded upon but also the dialogue, which was brilliantly done throughout the entire game and which also plugged large gaps in the logic of Half-Life. It was in this level that it was noticeable most.</p>
<p>Finally, the detail seemed far greater than any other level, at least to me. Not only were the maps detailed and informative but they were accurate and intriguing, leading me through the level so I could check out the Xenian flora room.</p>
<p>And what better way to end the level than with an enormous laser punching a hole in the wall? My mouth dropped when I saw this. I remember years ago lengthy discussions we had about how BM was going to solve this particular problem. None of us guessed the solution and it was one of the most jaw-dropping moments, alongside perhaps ST’s cliff-face, where the technological advancement and prowess of BM was shown over the dated and clumsy graphics of Half-Life.</p>
<p>Beautifully done guys, beautifully done.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/favorite-moment/10098/25">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/favorite-moment/10098/25</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 18 Sep 2012 16:43:26 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-10098-25</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/favorite-moment/10098.rss">Favorite moment</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Favorite moment</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Drowning_witch]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>my favorite moment is the whole freaking mod except when I saw that on a rail was butchered.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/favorite-moment/10098/24">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/favorite-moment/10098/24</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 16 Sep 2012 19:48:08 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-10098-24</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/favorite-moment/10098.rss">Favorite moment</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Favorite moment</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[David_VI]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I can’t pick a moment, there are too many for different reasons!</p>
<p>But starting was amazing, I really didn’t expect the quality and atmosphere. Inbound was amazing, I was like a child on a train, running to each window to look out at what was happening… grinning all along. Same with most of the first two chapters, playing with things, hearing people speak. SO IMMERSIVE!</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/favorite-moment/10098/23">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/favorite-moment/10098/23</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 16 Sep 2012 19:35:52 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-10098-23</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/favorite-moment/10098.rss">Favorite moment</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Favorite moment</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[noncebasher]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>The resonance cascade in the test chamber felt pretty epic and the final fight of questionable ethics</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/favorite-moment/10098/22">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/favorite-moment/10098/22</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 16 Sep 2012 12:59:17 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-10098-22</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/favorite-moment/10098.rss">Favorite moment</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Favorite moment</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[derrderrderr]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="dinnsfire5">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/d/76d3ee/40.png" class="avatar"> dinnsfire5:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Equipping the Hivehand definitely my favorite.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Poor Hivehand.</p>
<p>“There’s ALWAYS Time for Lubricant!”</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/favorite-moment/10098/21">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/favorite-moment/10098/21</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 16 Sep 2012 11:57:45 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-10098-21</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/favorite-moment/10098.rss">Favorite moment</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Favorite moment</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[derrderrderr]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I loved the conversations with security and science team staff in the Sector C test labs (I thought the in depth discussion about the merit of recreating past work and improving upon it, in particular, was priceless).<br>
So many subtle nods and jokes about character details really made the staff into real people for me, and made their fates in the ensuing disaster genuinely upset me as a result.</p>
<p>Also, the choked, gurgling noises the zombies make is unnerving as hell. :fffuuu:</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/favorite-moment/10098/20">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/favorite-moment/10098/20</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 16 Sep 2012 11:56:12 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-10098-20</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/favorite-moment/10098.rss">Favorite moment</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Favorite moment</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[9Kbits]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>The most memorable moment for me would have to be the tram ride at the very beginning. Every 2 seconds I was flipping out over the sheer detail put into everything and the top-notch, hi-res graphics. That initial moment of wonder and excitement stuck with me just like the tram ride from the original. Simply brilliant.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/favorite-moment/10098/19">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/favorite-moment/10098/19</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 16 Sep 2012 11:10:13 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-10098-19</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/favorite-moment/10098.rss">Favorite moment</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Favorite moment</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Vibez]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Damn, it’s hard really to pick only few. Probably second playthrough will reveal true winners. But, as for now:</p>
<ul>
<li>Sector C test labs - I felt like in Mass Effect series, you could literally talk to everyone for good 30-45 minutes before even the ‘real’ game started. Fantastic mood builder.</li>
<li>Blast Pit - I never realy liked the area in original HL. Ram and Joel made the best out of it. Final encounter with tentacles with Blast Pit 3 track in the background was so fuckin’ epic!</li>
<li>Questionable Ethics - this is by far my most favourite. Whole complex looks so damn beautiful, and has that feel of hidden importance. + the tests, + little puzzles + tau! + final encounter with HECU, + that little Xen room (:O). Everything seems perfect in that chapter.</li>
<li>Every single map design on the surface. Everytime when I see them I get the weirdest boner (and I don’t wanna talk about what happens on that cliff section :3)</li>
<li>New tripmine puzzles. That music! Blew up the whole place a couple of times just to have that feel again and sneak around a little bit more!</li>
<li>That very awkward first hivehand contact…</li>
<li>That drum’n’basy track at the end of Forget About Freeman fight. Joel, I love you.</li>
</ul>
<p>Of course there was many many more. More still to come!</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/favorite-moment/10098/18">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/favorite-moment/10098/18</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 16 Sep 2012 10:49:30 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-10098-18</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/favorite-moment/10098.rss">Favorite moment</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Favorite moment</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[dky.tehkingd.u]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>So many parts were my favorite. TOO many parts were my favorite.</p>
<p>But I guess if you force me at gunpoint to choose one, I’d pick the HOLY CRAP INTENSE PART of Questionable Ethics.</p>
<p>I won’t say what it is here since it’s too spoilerific. But anyone who’s played would probably know what I mean.  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=9" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/favorite-moment/10098/17">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/favorite-moment/10098/17</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 16 Sep 2012 10:00:46 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-10098-17</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/favorite-moment/10098.rss">Favorite moment</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Favorite moment</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[dinnsfire5]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Equipping the Hivehand definitely my favorite.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/favorite-moment/10098/16">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/favorite-moment/10098/16</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 16 Sep 2012 09:54:13 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-10098-16</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/favorite-moment/10098.rss">Favorite moment</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Favorite moment</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[jessiestorm88]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I loved the part in surface tension where you see the jets fly over and bomb part of the facility in the distance and you see the shock wave come toward you then hear it rumbling the entire cliff side as it passes. That was seriously amazing.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/favorite-moment/10098/15">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/favorite-moment/10098/15</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 16 Sep 2012 06:25:30 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-10098-15</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/favorite-moment/10098.rss">Favorite moment</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Favorite moment</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Bloodshot]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Here’s a list of my fav’s so far:</p>
<p>The whole Questionable Ethics chapter, especially the ending battle, the hardest, but by far my favorite HECU battle so far. Also releasing the Agrunts and watching them take down the HECU.</p>
<p>The first outside area of We’ve got Hostiles - it was such an “Ohhhh Shit” moment when you step out side to try and flank the soldiers, and then you see a shitload of mortars launch in the distance and you know if you stay there you are gonna die.</p>
<p>The gargantua in power up, when you sit in the doorway thinking your safe, and then he KNEELS DOWN and sticks his hand in to burn you  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/smiley.png?v=9" title=":smiley:" class="emoji" alt=":smiley:"></p>
<p>The falling elevator in Unforeseen Consequences, the one that YOU are in. That was a really nice touch, adding that whole new sequence and letting us fall to what we think will cause at least some injury.</p>
<p>The emergence from the tunnel to see the entire 3D REAL GEOMETRY SKYBOX of Surface Tension. That thing was beautiful and mind-blowing.</p>
<p>The helicopter showdown, it was hard but satisfying to take down that heli, especially since the damn thing didn’t even give me a chance to look around when I was on the dam.</p>
<p>The Garbage Compactor scene. I am a huge sucker for traps, and this one takes the cake. I actually got squished the first few times on purpose just to watch this damn thing crush all those boxes.</p>
<p>And yes, the Hornet Gun</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/favorite-moment/10098/14">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/favorite-moment/10098/14</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 16 Sep 2012 06:08:02 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-10098-14</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/favorite-moment/10098.rss">Favorite moment</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Favorite moment</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[geekofalltrades]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>^ Seconding the Garg chase in Surface Tension.  I also really enjoyed melting a hole through the wall with the laser in Questionable Ethics.  My mouth made a perfect “O” when I saw the molten, red-hot material dripping down in the aftermath.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/favorite-moment/10098/13">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/favorite-moment/10098/13</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 16 Sep 2012 06:05:19 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-10098-13</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/favorite-moment/10098.rss">Favorite moment</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Favorite moment</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Disturbulator]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Falling out of the vent infront of that gargantua at the tail end of Surface Tension as the suspence music kicked into gear scared me shitless.</p>
<p>That heli showdown on the cliff was perfectly delivered. And the air strike afterwords was even better.</p>
<p>And I laughed like hell when I grabbed that Hornet Gun.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/favorite-moment/10098/12">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/favorite-moment/10098/12</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 16 Sep 2012 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-10098-12</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/favorite-moment/10098.rss">Favorite moment</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Favorite moment</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Brent]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I can name so many favorite parts of the game.</p>
<p>The tram ride was exceptionally cool, but I was even more amazed at the research facility! For the first time in a long time, I really felt like I was a part of the game world I was in and had genuine interest in the characters on screen. I went around to every single NPC I could fine and ravaged every bit of dialog out of them that I could. Valve definitely pioneered in you being able to interact in a world to the level of believably that they did, but Black Mesa wins in making you truly want to explore that world.</p>
<p>But the Resonance Cascade was even better! I did not expect it to be so frantic and terrifying. For the first time, the Resonance Cascade was actually terrifying, and watching it take place put me in a state of awe I haven’t felt in such a long time.</p>
<p>Seeing the aftermath was absolutely incredible, and I truly felt alone and helpless playing these parts. Watching that headcrab zombie pick up the security guard and strangle him to death was one of the coolest and most memorable things I’ve ever seen in a game.</p>
<p>I could go on forever, but to keep my ramblings short, I really loved the Xen labs in Questionable Ethics. That level was always a good level for me to simply blow aliens and soldiers away, but with all the subtle tweaks made to it, that level came alive in such an engrossing way. But out of all of the additions, the recreated Xen habitat was so intriguing.</p>
<p>And the second time you fight the gargantua too. That was so fucking cool.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/favorite-moment/10098/11">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/favorite-moment/10098/11</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 16 Sep 2012 04:55:17 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-10098-11</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/favorite-moment/10098.rss">Favorite moment</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
