<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Reoccurring crash on directx 9</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/reoccurring-crash-on-directx-9/11121</link>
    <description>I can&#39;t run black mesa in directx 9 on my computer. I have reinstalled and redownloaded multiple times. I have checked the md5, all files are there. I have even copied the installer over to another computer along with the 7z and it ran great. However, on my computer the game initializes, then the screen goes white before I even see a loading screen. I get the message that says hl2.exe has stopped working. I have the full source sdk and the 2007 base installed, and my mindump from one of these crashes can be found here: [url]goo.gl/FAWU0[/url]. I have tried -dxlevel 90/95/98, along with -window, -fullscreen, and +mat_level 90/95/98. None of those worked. My game will launch if I use -dxlevel 79/80/81, and I get the problems associated with the game not being optimized for these versions. The directx diagnostic tells me I have dx11 installed, and I&#39;m running windows 7. My computer has an Intel quad-core i7 at 2.97 ghz, along with an ati Raedon HD 5750 installed, and my screen resolution is 2560 by 1440.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 25 Sep 2012 02:08:17 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>In-game Issues (Mod)</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/reoccurring-crash-on-directx-9/11121.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Reoccurring crash on directx 9</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[lexa2]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Thanks for posting details on your PC specs.<br>
As far as I could see specs are pretty decent and you shouldn’t get any problems with playing BM on this PC. What possibly could be problematic (although I highly doubt it) is the screen resolution which is pretty high in your case. Try “-windowed -x 0 -y 0 -width 1024-height 768” as the game commandline parameters and check if it helps.</p>
<p>What else to check/try:</p>
<ol>
<li>Turn off Steam community in game - it’s known to cause problems sometimes.</li>
<li>Change your GPU driver. If you’ve got a bit outdated version installed - download latest one manually from AMD site and install it. If you do have the very latest version - try rolling back to something like 12.6, which is known to generally work pretty well with BM.</li>
<li>Make sure you don’t have any “d3d9.dll interceptors/injectors” running in the background. DXtory, FRAPS, MSI Afterburner, D3Doverrider - any of them could possibly cause a crash in hl2.exe upon d3d initialization.</li>
<li>Try runing Steam and hl2.exe with the Administrator access rights, or try setting “Windows XP (SP3)” compatibility in Steam and hl2.exe settings.</li>
<li>Try temporarily disable DEP protection for hl2.exe or even for the entire system (would require reboot) and check if that helps.</li>
<li>Try downloading and installing latest available DirecrX redist from Microsoft Downloads website.</li>
</ol>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/reoccurring-crash-on-directx-9/11121/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/reoccurring-crash-on-directx-9/11121/2</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 25 Sep 2012 02:08:17 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11121-2</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/reoccurring-crash-on-directx-9/11121.rss">Reoccurring crash on directx 9</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Reoccurring crash on directx 9</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Nitro]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I can’t run black mesa in directx 9 on my computer. I have reinstalled and redownloaded multiple times. I have checked the md5, all files are there. I have even copied the installer over to another computer along with the 7z and it ran great. However, on my computer the game initializes, then the screen goes white before I even see a loading screen. I get the message that says hl2.exe has stopped working. I have the full source sdk and the 2007 base installed, and my mindump from one of these crashes can be found here: goo.gl/FAWU0. I have tried -dxlevel 90/95/98, along with -window, -fullscreen, and +mat_level 90/95/98. None of those worked. My game will launch if I use -dxlevel 79/80/81, and I get the problems associated with the game not being optimized for these versions. The directx diagnostic tells me I have dx11 installed, and I’m running windows 7. My computer has an Intel quad-core i7 at 2.97 ghz, along with an ati Raedon HD 5750 installed, and my screen resolution is 2560 by 1440.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/reoccurring-crash-on-directx-9/11121/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/reoccurring-crash-on-directx-9/11121/1</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 24 Sep 2012 20:23:18 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11121-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/reoccurring-crash-on-directx-9/11121.rss">Reoccurring crash on directx 9</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
