<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>PayPal</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/paypal/12214</link>
    <description>Hi guys.

So... I decided to actually buy Mass Effect and use the discount. BUT.
My card is total crap, unable to buy online (not VISA or MasterCard), so I want to try my luck via PayPal.

That&#39;s where my problem starts. I want to get a Personal account, yet I seem unable to find registration form for this kind for my country (Czech Republic), with only Premier and Business being options, however if I click my country to be United States (sheesh, what a lie. But hopefully in the future...), Personal account becomes an option.

Does anyone have an idea how to solve my situation? Also, while at the asking questions part, does anyone have any idea whether or not does PayPal work with Maestro cards?

Thanks in advance,
Serza</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2013 04:20:09 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Help and Support</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/paypal/12214.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>PayPal</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[papernick]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I pay my monthly spotify subscription with a US paypal account (I’m in Argentina). As long as you don’t go over a certain quantity of money (I think it’s 100 bucks per payment or per month, I’m not sure), you don’t have to get your card verified by paypal.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/paypal/12214/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/paypal/12214/4</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2013 04:20:09 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12214-4</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/paypal/12214.rss">PayPal</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>PayPal</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Serza]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Thanks for the swift answer. I’ll have to see if the same can be done on my end. If not, it might be a good time to tell the bank they’re a bunch of two-bit backstabbing badguys and go look elsewhere.</p>
<p>Bad news, still a news, and I thank you once again for the information.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/paypal/12214/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/paypal/12214/3</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2013 21:44:52 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12214-3</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/paypal/12214.rss">PayPal</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>PayPal</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Bolteh]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>As far as I know, you can’t link Maestro cards to a PayPal account.</p>
<p>For a long while I simply topped up PayPal through wire transfers from my bank account to my PayPal account (i.e.: put €50 on it, when that €50 was spent, I topped the account up again).</p>
<p>Not sure about your first question, though. Could be that PayPal only allows business accounts in Czech Republic.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/paypal/12214/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/paypal/12214/2</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2013 21:17:10 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12214-2</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/paypal/12214.rss">PayPal</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>PayPal</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Serza]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Hi guys.</p>
<p>So… I decided to actually buy Mass Effect and use the discount. BUT.<br>
My card is total crap, unable to buy online (not VISA or MasterCard), so I want to try my luck via PayPal.</p>
<p>That’s where my problem starts. I want to get a Personal account, yet I seem unable to find registration form for this kind for my country (Czech Republic), with only Premier and Business being options, however if I click my country to be United States (sheesh, what a lie. But hopefully in the future…), Personal account becomes an option.</p>
<p>Does anyone have an idea how to solve my situation? Also, while at the asking questions part, does anyone have any idea whether or not does PayPal work with Maestro cards?</p>
<p>Thanks in advance,<br>
Serza</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/paypal/12214/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/paypal/12214/1</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2013 21:08:26 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12214-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/paypal/12214.rss">PayPal</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
