<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Linux vs OSX</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/linux-vs-osx/3329</link>
    <description>OKay, so I thought it would be interesting if we started a Linux vs OSX thread, we all agree that these are the less popular Operating systems but which do you guys think is better? 

Neither have direct x and neither are very compatible, I personally think both are great and have dual WUbi&#39;ed Ubuntu.

Lets not bring Microsoft or windows anywhere near this thread and ignore the fact you need to buy OSX with the hardware, this thread is just about the OS themselves.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Apr 2010 19:45:24 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Off Topic</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/linux-vs-osx/3329.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Linux vs OSX</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Jingles]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Linux can theoretically run anything, but OSX will have Valve support soon. SO tough call really.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/linux-vs-osx/3329/38">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/linux-vs-osx/3329/38</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 03 Apr 2010 19:45:24 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3329-38</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/linux-vs-osx/3329.rss">Linux vs OSX</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Linux vs OSX</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[danielsangeo]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Which operating system do you think is better for gaming?  I don’t do much gaming and when I do, it’s primarily Valve/Steam games (click my little stats box to see how much I play) but when I get the urge to do (like last night  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=9" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:">  ), I want to be able to do it and not be limited on the choices I have or the limitations of the system.</p>
<p>Which is better for gaming?  OSX or Linux?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/linux-vs-osx/3329/37">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/linux-vs-osx/3329/37</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 03 Apr 2010 18:21:41 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3329-37</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/linux-vs-osx/3329.rss">Linux vs OSX</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Linux vs OSX</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[OldDirtyBastard]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>None. Personal Computers suck. All of them.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/linux-vs-osx/3329/36">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/linux-vs-osx/3329/36</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 03 Apr 2010 17:53:31 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3329-36</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/linux-vs-osx/3329.rss">Linux vs OSX</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Linux vs OSX</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Bolteh]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>OSX doesn’t strip the user from any authority at all. It merely hides things for the regular user that has no need for authority. You can easily mess around in OSX if you really wanted to, but unlike Linux (which is built with the sole purpose of people messing around) and Windows (which messes around even if you don’t want to), the default OS doesn’t let you mess around by accident.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/linux-vs-osx/3329/35">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/linux-vs-osx/3329/35</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 03 Apr 2010 11:27:10 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3329-35</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/linux-vs-osx/3329.rss">Linux vs OSX</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Linux vs OSX</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Comrade_Tiki]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I much prefer Linux over OSX. The debian packages are very nicely organized within Ubuntu, as are all of the applications’ menus. Nautilus, the directory browser, is a breeze to navigate the filesystem with. When I first installed Ubuntu and started looking at the software for download, it was like emerging from a Borg maturation chamber and being plugged into the collective mind. Every once in a while there’d be some issue with the synaptic link, and I’d go google the precise issue if I didn’t understand it, and the answer was already there alongside its solution.</p>
<p>OSX takes the “user-friendly” approach, which means strip the user of authority to do anything interesting, and give them a lot of animated icons. When I first had to use use OSX at the university, it felt like my hands were replaced with feet and my feet were replaced with two left hands. And I was expected to practice karate. I suppose I could make up some new moves that way… but it’s just not going to be effective. Also, using Safari for the first time was like replacing one arm with a knub and one leg with a tentacle, and being expected to ride an offroad bicycle. But the good news is, all the trees are padded. (The ground, however, isn’t.)</p>
<p>…I can’t resist:<br>
Using Windows Vista is like wearing plastic bags and trying to ride a motorcycle through an automated car wash, with the soap suds artificially flavoured to taste like blackberries. But it’s not quite right, they taste more like unripened blackberries.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/linux-vs-osx/3329/34">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/linux-vs-osx/3329/34</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 03 Apr 2010 10:39:16 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3329-34</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/linux-vs-osx/3329.rss">Linux vs OSX</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Linux vs OSX</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[lambda]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I am a defiantly pro-OSX, but linux is cool too<br>
It is accessible, and nice to look at  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/smiley.png?v=9" title=":smiley:" class="emoji" alt=":smiley:"> .<br>
And steam will come to it to, that is going to be so awesome.<br>
I work 50%windows 50%OSX</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/linux-vs-osx/3329/33">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/linux-vs-osx/3329/33</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 03 Apr 2010 07:16:56 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3329-33</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/linux-vs-osx/3329.rss">Linux vs OSX</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Linux vs OSX</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Jingles]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Half Life 1 on Gameboy Advance xD That would be quite fun actually.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/linux-vs-osx/3329/32">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/linux-vs-osx/3329/32</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 27 Mar 2010 16:21:42 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3329-32</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/linux-vs-osx/3329.rss">Linux vs OSX</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Linux vs OSX</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[sersoft]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>At this rate, we’ll be able to port the source engine to mobile phones and portable consoles.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/linux-vs-osx/3329/31">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/linux-vs-osx/3329/31</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 27 Mar 2010 16:04:56 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3329-31</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/linux-vs-osx/3329.rss">Linux vs OSX</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Linux vs OSX</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Oddbio]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Interesting. So I guess that limits the games that will be available, but I do know Team Fortress 2 will be available for sure.</p>
<p>Also there is some more evidence than that.<br>
The game Postal III is being released for Linux, and it is using the Source engine. So I believe that would mean that they would have to have the source engine working with Linux.<br>
Also, a while back there were job postings on the steam website of positions for software engineers to <span class="bbcode-b">“port Windows-based games to the Linux platform.”</span><br>
<a href="https://www.valvesoftware.com/job-SenSoftEngineer.html" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://www.valvesoftware.com/job-SenSoftEngineer.html</a><br>
and also some linux .so files started showing up in some source game directories or something.</p>
<p>But, there is still plenty of reason to be doubtful. For instance, the software engineer could be working on other games (postal III for instance). Also I guess just because they can get a working Linux build of the source engine (and if the post that Bolteh mentioned is correct then they already have one) that doesn’t necessarily mean that they will release it for all Half-Life 2 games/mods.</p>
<p>However, I am big a supporter of Linux, and as such I choose to remain optimistic.<br>
<img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=9" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji only-emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/linux-vs-osx/3329/30">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/linux-vs-osx/3329/30</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 27 Mar 2010 15:52:53 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3329-30</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/linux-vs-osx/3329.rss">Linux vs OSX</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Linux vs OSX</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Bolteh]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Source engine is being ported over, correct. However, a lot of mods use additional coding that probably won’t work on iSource (hoho). I think it’s a given that BMS won’t be compatible with iSource.</p>
<p>And the only evidence that Valve is thinking about Linux, is the LinkedIn post of Chris Green stating that they are looking for Mac/Linux engineers. Apart from that, no mention was mad of anything Linux related.</p>
<p>And I somehow doubt they’d support an open source OS anyway.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/linux-vs-osx/3329/29">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/linux-vs-osx/3329/29</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 27 Mar 2010 13:13:20 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3329-29</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/linux-vs-osx/3329.rss">Linux vs OSX</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Linux vs OSX</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Oddbio]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Just thought I’d throw a little fire into the discussion and mention that the source engine is being ported to OSX. I think sometime this April. so all half-life 2 mods/games (including black mesa source) can be run natively on mac, and they won’t need to purchase a mac version, if you have the windows one you get the mac one.</p>
<p>However, just as they have been very quiet about this up until now, they have made no mention of Linux support, but there is strong evidence that they will eventually release it for Linux.</p>
<p>When that day comes I can say goodbye to windows forever   <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/smiley.png?v=9" title=":smiley:" class="emoji" alt=":smiley:"></p>
<p>oh… and, Linux FTW!</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/linux-vs-osx/3329/28">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/linux-vs-osx/3329/28</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 27 Mar 2010 05:31:30 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3329-28</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/linux-vs-osx/3329.rss">Linux vs OSX</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Linux vs OSX</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Dr_Perky]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>^this basically</p>
<p>I dual boot Ubuntu and Windows. I use Ubuntu for general use(web-browsing and such) because I find it much simplier. and I really only use windows for steam. If Valve ever releases a linux source port i’d probably use Ubuntu as my only OS.</p>
<p>and my experience with Mac OSX I can say its not bad but Linux is far superior in terms of compatibility and price of the OS and software.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/linux-vs-osx/3329/27">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/linux-vs-osx/3329/27</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 20 Mar 2010 04:20:58 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3329-27</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/linux-vs-osx/3329.rss">Linux vs OSX</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Linux vs OSX</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Brother_Shrike]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Technically it’s not emulated. I only lost ~10 fps in HL2DM and I’m pretty sure that had more to do with me running a compositing WM on a crappy computer than it had to do with wine.</p>
<p>And disregarding my avatar, linux technically isn’t unix based, either.</p>
<p>I would be using linux 100% if it wasn’t for games. And I play mostly valve games and old games anyway, so if Valve ports source to linux, I would be able to run most of my games between wine and native binaries.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/linux-vs-osx/3329/26">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/linux-vs-osx/3329/26</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 14 Mar 2010 06:10:43 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3329-26</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/linux-vs-osx/3329.rss">Linux vs OSX</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Linux vs OSX</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Cameron_D]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>But that is expected - its emulated.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/linux-vs-osx/3329/25">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/linux-vs-osx/3329/25</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 14 Mar 2010 03:45:54 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3329-25</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/linux-vs-osx/3329.rss">Linux vs OSX</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Linux vs OSX</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Level]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Cameron :smiley:">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Cameron :smiley: :</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Wine.<br>
Steam runs fine, haven’t tried playing games yet though.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>You lost a lot of frames per second.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/linux-vs-osx/3329/24">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/linux-vs-osx/3329/24</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 14 Mar 2010 03:19:45 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3329-24</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/linux-vs-osx/3329.rss">Linux vs OSX</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Linux vs OSX</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Cameron_D]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Wine.<br>
Steam runs fine, haven’t tried playing games yet though.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/linux-vs-osx/3329/23">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/linux-vs-osx/3329/23</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 14 Mar 2010 02:34:41 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3329-23</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/linux-vs-osx/3329.rss">Linux vs OSX</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Linux vs OSX</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Firebringer]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I’ve used Linux for a while and I liked it. If it wasn’t for games, I’d be using Linux. Maybe valve will port their games to Linux too.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/linux-vs-osx/3329/22">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/linux-vs-osx/3329/22</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 14 Mar 2010 02:25:55 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3329-22</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/linux-vs-osx/3329.rss">Linux vs OSX</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Linux vs OSX</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Level]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I used linux for a while (drive failed, didn’t bother reinstalling it), and it’s a solid operating system, works well, but I’d rather use OS X any day. Both are Unix OS’s, and for the most part OS X is simple and just works. If OS X would work on my laptop (audio and wireless don’t work) I would have used it, because both are a better programming environment then windows.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/linux-vs-osx/3329/21">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/linux-vs-osx/3329/21</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 14 Mar 2010 02:21:19 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3329-21</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/linux-vs-osx/3329.rss">Linux vs OSX</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Linux vs OSX</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Surplus]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I haven’t really used either as my main computer and my knowlege of both is about the same.  I’ve used osx more but not by much and I just installed Ubuntu on one of my PCs (because for some reason windows won’t even start).  So far they’re just about equal imo, I don’t know much about their stability because I haven’t used them very long.  Sure you can say one is “more user friendly” but that really depends on the user.  I like hot-keys shortcuts and stuff, I don’t like dicking around with dragging and dropping and shit. That pretty much just nullifies any advantage that osx has.  i’ve heard some stories about linix being really hard but Ubuntu has been pretty easy, it had Firefox already installed and installing wine and flash and stuff is as simple as copy and paste xD.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/linux-vs-osx/3329/20">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/linux-vs-osx/3329/20</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 14 Mar 2010 02:03:15 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3329-20</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/linux-vs-osx/3329.rss">Linux vs OSX</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Linux vs OSX</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[gugamilare]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Jingles">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/j/46a35a/40.png" class="avatar"> Jingles:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Linux…the less popular Operating systems…</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="CTID">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/user_avatar/leakfree.org/ctid/40/4984_2.png" class="avatar"> CTID:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>No.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>No indeed. Jingles, you are forgetting many other less popular operating systems: FreeBSD and other BSDs, OpenSolaris, Haiku, ReactOS, Chrome (it is not a Linux in the usual sense) and others that I don’t remember or don’t know. So Linux is not the less popular OS, it is actually one of the most popular, 3rd place on desktops.</p>
<p>I don’t know anything about Mac OS at all, so I can’t say anything else other than I love Linux. People who use OSX around here are very, very rare.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/linux-vs-osx/3329/19">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/linux-vs-osx/3329/19</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 14 Mar 2010 01:52:09 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3329-19</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/linux-vs-osx/3329.rss">Linux vs OSX</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Linux vs OSX</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[DONT_CALL_ME_A_VORT]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>So much for keeping Windows out of the discussion…Linux ftw!</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/linux-vs-osx/3329/18">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/linux-vs-osx/3329/18</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 14 Mar 2010 01:01:28 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3329-18</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/linux-vs-osx/3329.rss">Linux vs OSX</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Linux vs OSX</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Cameron_D]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Its not as user-friendly as windows.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/linux-vs-osx/3329/17">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/linux-vs-osx/3329/17</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 12 Mar 2010 11:09:50 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3329-17</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/linux-vs-osx/3329.rss">Linux vs OSX</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Linux vs OSX</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Chrillen]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="CTID">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/user_avatar/leakfree.org/ctid/40/4984_2.png" class="avatar"> CTID:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Linux completely skullfucks OSX and Windows. The only reason I use Windows is because I’m a gamer, and every game I play needs it.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>So? It’s still not as popular as Windows, and I don’t see how you can disagree with that.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/linux-vs-osx/3329/16">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/linux-vs-osx/3329/16</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 12 Mar 2010 07:00:04 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3329-16</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/linux-vs-osx/3329.rss">Linux vs OSX</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Linux vs OSX</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Cameron_D]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Linux is awesome.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/linux-vs-osx/3329/15">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/linux-vs-osx/3329/15</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 12 Mar 2010 05:17:20 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3329-15</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/linux-vs-osx/3329.rss">Linux vs OSX</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Linux vs OSX</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[danielsangeo]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Gordon">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/g/3da27b/40.png" class="avatar"> Gordon:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Have you <span class="bbcode-i">used</span> OS X?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Yes.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/linux-vs-osx/3329/14">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/linux-vs-osx/3329/14</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 12 Mar 2010 03:46:46 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3329-14</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/linux-vs-osx/3329.rss">Linux vs OSX</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
