<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Girlfriend</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/girlfriend/1596</link>
    <description>Ok so I have this girlfriend, and right now I&#39;m kinda in a weird situation. I really like her, but I don&#39;t really love her if you know what I mean. We fool around a lot, but we don&#39;t have that much in common. She tells me she&#39;s really falling for me, and I feel bad that I don&#39;t feel the same way, but also she&#39;s kinda weird in that she can be really forward with other guys too.

There&#39;s been a few situations where she&#39;s come really close to cheating on me, but sometimes it&#39;s hard to tell with the situation. :^/

I feel like I can&#39;t really talk to her like I would be able to, you know best friends and more than friends kinda thing, and I don&#39;t really want to leave her at the same time because I don&#39;t want to be alone. At the same time I don&#39;t feel like I&#39;m being true to her by staying with her when I&#39;m pretty sure this won&#39;t be long lasting relationship.

Any advice?</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 10 Oct 2009 10:30:46 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Off Topic</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/girlfriend/1596.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Girlfriend</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Lolipopman]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>This is the knd of situation you usually see in movies… But movies are also unrealistic… Your standing in some deep shit.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/girlfriend/1596/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/girlfriend/1596/4</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 10 Oct 2009 10:30:46 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-1596-4</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/girlfriend/1596.rss">Girlfriend</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Girlfriend</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Mont_Blanc]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Tought situation there dude. I would say you should talk to her, your concerns about her behaviors with other guys and what are your feelings. If you’re so sure this won’t last long, you have nothing to lose. Was she a good friend before you dated her because if that’s right and you broke up, there’s a good chance your friendship might be over.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/girlfriend/1596/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/girlfriend/1596/3</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 10 Oct 2009 10:28:36 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-1596-3</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/girlfriend/1596.rss">Girlfriend</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Girlfriend</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Paddy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Do what everyman does. Bite the bullet.</p>
<p>Marry her.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/girlfriend/1596/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/girlfriend/1596/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 10 Oct 2009 10:10:42 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-1596-2</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/girlfriend/1596.rss">Girlfriend</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Girlfriend</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[intooblivion]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Ok so I have this girlfriend, and right now I’m kinda in a weird situation. I really like her, but I don’t really love her if you know what I mean. We fool around a lot, but we don’t have that much in common. She tells me she’s really falling for me, and I feel bad that I don’t feel the same way, but also she’s kinda weird in that she can be really forward with other guys too.</p>
<p>There’s been a few situations where she’s come really close to cheating on me, but sometimes it’s hard to tell with the situation. :^/</p>
<p>I feel like I can’t really talk to her like I would be able to, you know best friends and more than friends kinda thing, and I don’t really want to leave her at the same time because I don’t want to be alone. At the same time I don’t feel like I’m being true to her by staying with her when I’m pretty sure this won’t be long lasting relationship.</p>
<p>Any advice?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/girlfriend/1596/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/girlfriend/1596/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 10 Oct 2009 09:27:29 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-1596-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/girlfriend/1596.rss">Girlfriend</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
