<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Cartoon Family Wars</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/cartoon-family-wars/2588</link>
    <description>It&#39;s the Simpsons 20th Anniversary this year, to think twenty years ago it was considered a risky thing to try and push a cartoon family on American audiences, after a decade of silence, and now, arguably, we are seeing too many from American Dad to the Goode Family to The Cleveland Show. Some are, in fairness, terrible but some we couldn&#39;t possibly live without. So from as early to the Flintstones to as modern as the Browns…

Which Cartoon Family do you think is the best and why?
Which Cartoon Family do you think is the worst and why?
Which Cartoon Family is overrated? And which Cartoon Family do you think deserves more love?

My favorite cartoon series is South Park, but without having a family to nominate (Although the Marshes are pretty intense) I’ll have to be boring and say The Simpsons, with Family Guy a close second and the Flintstones third (Though I am torn to put the Hill’s there). Why the Simpsons? Well if you can forget the awful movie and the down turn this show has had recently, back in the early days it almost always delivered with the best cast of characters on the box

The worst that’s a toughie, it’d be unfair to say the Browns, maybe the Jetsons? For reasons I don’t know, for being a futuristic rip off of the Flintstones or something?

I think the Hill’s deserve more love. It always seems to be rejected here in the UK to Z-Channels or on at ridiculously late times</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 18 May 2010 23:28:12 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Off Topic</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/cartoon-family-wars/2588.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Cartoon Family Wars</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Ramirezoid]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Simpsons debuted in 1986 on the Tracy Ullman show.</p>
<p>Hanna Barbera cannot rip off its own cartoons.</p>
<p>OP is a fag.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/cartoon-family-wars/2588/14">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/cartoon-family-wars/2588/14</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 18 May 2010 23:28:12 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2588-14</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/cartoon-family-wars/2588.rss">Cartoon Family Wars</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Cartoon Family Wars</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Fuskox]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I love the Marshes from South Park, namely, Randy. He’s the epitome of the stereotypical American Man. Just love how prideful he is, and how hypocritical he is as well. I can’t believe I didn’t see the Marshes on the list -_-</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/cartoon-family-wars/2588/13">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/cartoon-family-wars/2588/13</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 18 May 2010 23:02:30 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2588-13</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/cartoon-family-wars/2588.rss">Cartoon Family Wars</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Cartoon Family Wars</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Dr_Perky]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I’ve got to say The Simpsons will always be my favourite (I never watch past season 10) the older episodes have a charm that was lost in the newer ones. Futurama comes in second (another example of Matt Greoning’s ability to make quality cartoons.)</p>
<p>King of the Hill is good a much more down to earth cartoon nothing in it could not be done in a live-action Sitcom.</p>
<p>Honestly Family Guy has become very sad to be when the flashbacks and aside jokes were new to the show it was a nice change of pace now it seems all they can do is jam 5 minutes of bad stories between fifteen minutes of those jokes, which have become exceedingly tasteless. McFarlene’s spin-off aren’t good either.</p>
<p>I find Squidbillies to be entertaining in a very simplistic, crude way.</p>
<p>Also Frisky Dingo had a delightful art style and wonderful storytelling (haven’t seen season 2 yet need to go out and buy it. I miss Sealab 2021 it was a lovely mess of a show spoofing the old 80’s cartoons that I watched re-runs of as a kid. Robot Chicken is always fun for a laugh as well.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/cartoon-family-wars/2588/12">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/cartoon-family-wars/2588/12</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 22 Jan 2010 02:18:28 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2588-12</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/cartoon-family-wars/2588.rss">Cartoon Family Wars</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Cartoon Family Wars</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Winged_One]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I use to be a die-hard Simpsons fan, but stopped watching after the movie (which wasn’t all that bad, tbh).  Just got tired and boring for me.  Family Guy is where it’s at now.</p>
<p>For some reason, I hate American Dad.  It’s just really stupid.</p>
<p>The Cleveland show is really overrated.  Not nearly as funny as I thought it would be.</p>
<p>And King of the Hill needs moh respect.  While I stopped religiously watching it a while back, it’s still pretty good, and I watch it from time to time when it’s on.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/cartoon-family-wars/2588/11">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/cartoon-family-wars/2588/11</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Jan 2010 22:47:30 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2588-11</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/cartoon-family-wars/2588.rss">Cartoon Family Wars</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Cartoon Family Wars</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Mr.Shadow]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <ol>
<li>Family guy</li>
<li>American Dad (seriously: who can’t love a man that works for the CIA and hides an alien up his addic and has this huge, oversized chin :retard <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=9" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:">
</li>
<li>Simpsons which are overrated. The jokes are predictable and it most of the time has the same damn plot device, called marriage problems :meh:</li>
</ol>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/cartoon-family-wars/2588/10">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/cartoon-family-wars/2588/10</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Jan 2010 22:15:02 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2588-10</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/cartoon-family-wars/2588.rss">Cartoon Family Wars</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Cartoon Family Wars</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Elpants]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Best: The Hill Family of King of the Hill, This show is hard to get into, I have been watching and paying attention for 6+ years now. The Hills are this typical, but dysfunctional family. Bobby Hill (the kid) while being this overweight, annoying child still has the kind of imagination and well-rounded goodwill about him. The humor may not be in your face, but subtle and believable.</p>
<p>Worst: American Dad/Cleveland Brown, both these, <em>try</em> too hard, their only redeeming quality is Seth’s off the wall humor. They try to show this dysfunctional family that in the end will stay together to get through the episode but they both try to be the Simpsons more than Family Guy ever did.</p>
<p>Most overrated: Simpsons. Yeah, they are good and the original but better things have come along.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/cartoon-family-wars/2588/9">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/cartoon-family-wars/2588/9</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Jan 2010 07:44:24 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2588-9</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/cartoon-family-wars/2588.rss">Cartoon Family Wars</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Cartoon Family Wars</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[bigfan421]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <ol>
<li>the Simpsons 'nuff said.</li>
<li>American Dad. the whole fucking family is a stereotype of americanisms</li>
<li>Family Guy is overrated. ffs, they released “s,s,s,s Dark side” months before airing the damn thing. IMO, the Flintstones need more love, their most recent “appearance” was in a Seth MacFarlane short animation FFS (god-damn you Seth MacFarlane)</li>
</ol>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/cartoon-family-wars/2588/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/cartoon-family-wars/2588/8</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Jan 2010 05:43:16 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2588-8</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/cartoon-family-wars/2588.rss">Cartoon Family Wars</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Cartoon Family Wars</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Dr_Strangelove]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I’d have to say Mike Judges shows were the best. I love how they are always parodies of certain types of people like the teenage metalhead and the Texas conservative.</p>
<p>The Simpsons and Futurama are a close second. I love how many characters there are and how much you can know about them. It’s a shame Futurama got cancelled.</p>
<p>By far the worst are the Family Guy spin offs. I liked the first seasons of Family Guy, and I could overlook the fact the it was pretty damn similar to the Simpsons. Then, after the show went down the tubes, they decided to make a show using the most unineresting character and give it the exact same fucking premise. I honestly thought it was some elaborate joke at first.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/cartoon-family-wars/2588/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/cartoon-family-wars/2588/7</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Jan 2010 05:29:35 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2588-7</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/cartoon-family-wars/2588.rss">Cartoon Family Wars</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Cartoon Family Wars</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[danielsangeo]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>If computer animated movies count, I’d have to go with the Parr family from the Incredibles.</p>
<p>But, if were sticking strictly to television shows, that’s a toughie.  I differ depending on how I’m rating it.  For the most realistic cartoon family, I’d have to go with King of the Hill.  The most fun, I’d have to go with American Dad.  The funniest is Futurama.</p>
<p>I dunno.  I don’t know if I have a “best”, though.  I guess I’d go with Futurama because I’ve seen every episode of that (haven’t seen the movies, though, and almost afraid to).</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/cartoon-family-wars/2588/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/cartoon-family-wars/2588/6</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Jan 2010 05:14:25 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2588-6</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/cartoon-family-wars/2588.rss">Cartoon Family Wars</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Cartoon Family Wars</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Rossman]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>The Simpsons, but now I hate them. Every single show has gotten to be shit lately. The Simpsons died to me a couple of years ago, once season 11 ended. They use to have some pop culture references in their older seasons which wasn’t bad, but in these last three seasons it has gotten too much. All of the lame pop culture joke and debate with politics is getting old, real fast.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/cartoon-family-wars/2588/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/cartoon-family-wars/2588/5</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jan 2010 17:29:42 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2588-5</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/cartoon-family-wars/2588.rss">Cartoon Family Wars</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Cartoon Family Wars</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[MaxTheLimit]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>The Fry family on Futurama. Farnsworth, his old grandpa Philip J Fry, and the little clone fella. Best cartoon. Tales of interest are the ones that get me.</p>
<p>The worst is King of the hill. I’ve never seen any other show where the entire cast is made up of characters that are totally unlikeable. Every character is representative of someone who I would find annoying in real life. It’s not done in a funny way where it is funny to hate them ( meg, or zoidberg ) it’s all just sigh inducing annoyance for me.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/cartoon-family-wars/2588/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/cartoon-family-wars/2588/4</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jan 2010 14:57:02 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2588-4</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/cartoon-family-wars/2588.rss">Cartoon Family Wars</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Cartoon Family Wars</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[JamestheDoc]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>My favorite cartoon family is the Hills from King of the Hill.  I loved the subtle southern comedy and references to popular American culture through a simpler and more conservative Texan mindset.  None of the stories were ridiculous (like involving aliens or zombies), and even though the situations got out of hand it was never something out of the line of possibility.</p>
<p>I tell ya whut.</p>
<p>What’s the worst?  I’d have to say Family Guy.  At first it was great, but over time the formula just became tiring (ridiculous situation cut up by random non-sequeters) and the characters turned into place-holders or retards.</p>
<p>What’s overrated?</p>
<p>I’d say Family Guy, again.  It’s on life-support and people are just too scared to pull the plug.</p>
<p>What deserves more love?</p>
<p>I’d have said King of the Hill, but it was canceled.  I like American Dad though, the writers don’t use the Family Guy formula and each episode has a unique plot, while poking fun at the super-conservative American mindset, liberalism and individualism.  It makes for interesting comedy to see all these things collide in situations such as the rapture or having flashbacks from a Vietnam reenactment at a golf course.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/cartoon-family-wars/2588/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/cartoon-family-wars/2588/3</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jan 2010 14:54:59 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2588-3</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/cartoon-family-wars/2588.rss">Cartoon Family Wars</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Cartoon Family Wars</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Bolteh]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Best. I’d have to go with Family Guy. mainly because I don’t watch that many cartoons, so the selection is limited. Family Guy always manages to cheer me up with (albeit cheap) humor.</p>
<p>Worst: The Simpsons. I never really found them funny in the first place, but while the first few seasons were acceptable, the last few were absolutely horribly unoriginal.</p>
<p>Overrated: The Simpsons (see above). Needs more love: Goku’s family from DBZ!!</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/cartoon-family-wars/2588/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/cartoon-family-wars/2588/2</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jan 2010 14:47:07 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2588-2</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/cartoon-family-wars/2588.rss">Cartoon Family Wars</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Cartoon Family Wars</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Codgin]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>It’s the Simpsons 20th Anniversary this year, to think twenty years ago it was considered a risky thing to try and push a cartoon family on American audiences, after a decade of silence, and now, arguably, we are seeing too many from American Dad to the Goode Family to The Cleveland Show. Some are, in fairness, terrible but some we couldn’t possibly live without. So from as early to the Flintstones to as modern as the Browns…</p>
<p>Which Cartoon Family do you think is the best and why?<br>
Which Cartoon Family do you think is the worst and why?<br>
Which Cartoon Family is overrated? And which Cartoon Family do you think deserves more love?</p>
<p>My favorite cartoon series is South Park, but without having a family to nominate (Although the Marshes are pretty intense) I’ll have to be boring and say The Simpsons, with Family Guy a close second and the Flintstones third (Though I am torn to put the Hill’s there). Why the Simpsons? Well if you can forget the awful movie and the down turn this show has had recently, back in the early days it almost always delivered with the best cast of characters on the box</p>
<p>The worst that’s a toughie, it’d be unfair to say the Browns, maybe the Jetsons? For reasons I don’t know, for being a futuristic rip off of the Flintstones or something?</p>
<p>I think the Hill’s deserve more love. It always seems to be rejected here in the UK to Z-Channels or on at ridiculously late times</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/cartoon-family-wars/2588/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/cartoon-family-wars/2588/1</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jan 2010 14:35:59 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2588-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/cartoon-family-wars/2588.rss">Cartoon Family Wars</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
