<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>&quot;Access is denied&quot; when executing &quot;Copy File&quot; in Hammer compile</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/access-is-denied-when-executing-copy-file-in-hammer-compile/15356</link>
    <description>Since moving my games over to a new SSD, Black Mesa&#39;s Hammer doesn&#39;t seem to want to work properly. I gave Black Mesa a fresh install for the new drive, so I thought it would be fine, but no luck.
On a fresh install, all of Black Mesa&#39;s expert compile options in Hammer are blank, and after copying them over from another game, it all works fine except for &quot;Copy File&quot;.

It keeps giving me an &quot;Access is denied&quot; error. The map itself is compiling fine, but it just can&#39;t copy the map file to the maps folder for some reason.
When using non-expert compiles it works perfectly, and I double checked over all of the settings I put in for Expert and nothing is off. They&#39;re the same options I use for Portal 2 and were the same as in HL2 as well.

And of course, I&#39;ve scoured multiple pages on Google with varying search criteria, and no luck. Anyone know anything about this, or do I just have to make bms/maps the home for my VMFs so that it doesn&#39;t have to copy anywhere?</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 24 Apr 2018 00:36:13 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Help!</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/access-is-denied-when-executing-copy-file-in-hammer-compile/15356.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>&quot;Access is denied&quot; when executing &quot;Copy File&quot; in Hammer compile</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crawfish]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Since moving my games over to a new SSD, Black Mesa’s Hammer doesn’t seem to want to work properly. I gave Black Mesa a fresh install for the new drive, so I thought it would be fine, but no luck.<br>
On a fresh install, all of Black Mesa’s expert compile options in Hammer are blank, and after copying them over from another game, it all works fine except for “Copy File”.</p>
<p>It keeps giving me an “Access is denied” error. The map itself is compiling fine, but it just can’t copy the map file to the maps folder for some reason.<br>
When using non-expert compiles it works perfectly, and I double checked over all of the settings I put in for Expert and nothing is off. They’re the same options I use for Portal 2 and were the same as in HL2 as well.</p>
<p>And of course, I’ve scoured multiple pages on Google with varying search criteria, and no luck. Anyone know anything about this, or do I just have to make bms/maps the home for my VMFs so that it doesn’t have to copy anywhere?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/access-is-denied-when-executing-copy-file-in-hammer-compile/15356/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/access-is-denied-when-executing-copy-file-in-hammer-compile/15356/1</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 24 Apr 2018 00:36:13 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-15356-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/access-is-denied-when-executing-copy-file-in-hammer-compile/15356.rss">&quot;Access is denied&quot; when executing &quot;Copy File&quot; in Hammer compile</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
