<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>2 bugs: A framerate drop and a Crossbow HUD disruption</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/2-bugs-a-framerate-drop-and-a-crossbow-hud-disruption/10240</link>
    <description>1. After the ambush at the end of Questionable Ethics, there were 2 soldiers left above the room, shooting at me from up there. I noticed that killing the one closer to the central desk (relatively speaking) consistently resulted in a catastrophic drop in framerate. I speculate that it might have something to do with his ragdoll dropping from such a high place. The only way I could reliably kill him and play afterwards was to kill him with the TAU and gib him. So it&#39;s not a crippling bug, but you might want to look into it.

2. Quick-saving while I have the crossbow equipped crashes most of the HUD. Invariably. The crosshairs, HUD ammo symbols (not the numbers) and the &quot;Saved...&quot; message disappear, and do not re-appear when I equip another weapon. To make them come back I have to re-load a saved game (not quick-load)

Apart from that the game is an absolute gem. I call it a game, not a mod. It is no longer a mod.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 16 Sep 2012 12:39:32 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>In-game Issues (Mod)</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/2-bugs-a-framerate-drop-and-a-crossbow-hud-disruption/10240.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>2 bugs: A framerate drop and a Crossbow HUD disruption</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Preda]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <ol>
<li>
<p>After the ambush at the end of Questionable Ethics, there were 2 soldiers left above the room, shooting at me from up there. I noticed that killing the one closer to the central desk (relatively speaking) consistently resulted in a catastrophic drop in framerate. I speculate that it might have something to do with his ragdoll dropping from such a high place. The only way I could reliably kill him and play afterwards was to kill him with the TAU and gib him. So it’s not a crippling bug, but you might want to look into it.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Quick-saving while I have the crossbow equipped crashes most of the HUD. Invariably. The crosshairs, HUD ammo symbols (not the numbers) and the “Saved…” message disappear, and do not re-appear when I equip another weapon. To make them come back I have to re-load a saved game (not quick-load)</p>
</li>
</ol>
<p>Apart from that the game is an absolute gem. I call it a game, not a mod. It is no longer a mod.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/2-bugs-a-framerate-drop-and-a-crossbow-hud-disruption/10240/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/2-bugs-a-framerate-drop-and-a-crossbow-hud-disruption/10240/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 16 Sep 2012 12:39:32 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-10240-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/2-bugs-a-framerate-drop-and-a-crossbow-hud-disruption/10240.rss">2 bugs: A framerate drop and a Crossbow HUD disruption</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
