<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>BMS Revamp Sound Mod</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/bms-revamp-sound-mod/12418</link>
    <description>![](upload://pYMgCTV0RBZeCtDLteYahgXgHPC.jpeg)

~BLACK MESA SOUNDSKIN~

[COLOR=&#39;Lime&#39;]VIDEO[/SIZE]

[url]https://vimeo.com/72267215[/url]

This shows some of what the pack does. You can compare it with other videos if you are not sure what you are watching or hearing.

I have made a sound Mod specifically designed to go with the sounds scripts in the animation revamp. This is not just thrown together it has taken me a very long time and hours and hours and some more hours to modify and create. It is designed to work with the sounds included in the animation revamp release and Black Mesa and you need to install the animation Revamp pack before adding this pack. This Pack does not consider any of your current sound Mods and is intended to work as a third layer on a fresh BMS install.

Although I would also suggest you install the particle improvement pack also for extra enhancement too.

And this sound pack as the icing on the cake.

The Download link is below.  This is now named Black Mesa Soundskin It is catchier and does what it says on the tin....

[COLOR=&#39;Lime&#39;]ABSOLUTE FINAL UNTIL XEN[/SIZE]

[url]https://www.mediafire.com/download/0j7ivknvv09uqb7/SOUNDSKIN+ABSOLUTE+FINAL+UNTIL+XEN+V1.rar[/url]

This alters a lot of sounds found in the animation Revamp pack and in Black Mesa... If you like it is a companion piece to both the Animation Mod and Black Mesa it compiles some sounds from other sound mods but most of it is my own work and balanced and cleaned up so as to not have inconsistancies.


[b][u]Change List.[/u][/b]

1. New Magnum Shoot sound
2. New Magnum Cock and release sounds***
3. Modified Crossbow shoot sound - you can now here an arrow whistling away
4. New Crossbow Reload sound - Tension drastring***
5. Crowbar now has more variation in sound hits and swing misses
6. Gluon uses BMS Deafault sound but Classic Half Life Spin Down noise merged seamlessly
7. Hivehand Classic but rebalanced so it is not so loud
8. M4 New Grenade Launcher sound Modern compressed Tube and Whoosh and modified pitch and volume of the close tube sound when reloading the nade launcher***
9. New Satchel Detonator Tone and click
10. New Shotgun Sound for shooting and reloading - Very Meaty***
11. Classic Tau canon but smoothed (Credit - Xalener) 
12. Classic tripmine sound HL1 but merged with Black mesa one
13. Improved explosion sounds
14. New Snark Hunting sounds My own design***
15. New Sniper sound - it now echoes around (merged and modified original)***
16. Classic Item Noises HL1 some merged with Black Mesa ones
17. Classic Houndeye and Ichthyosaur sounds
18. New sounds for growls and Melee attacks for Alien grunts***
19. Complete Alien controller sound re-design***
20. New Bullsquid Pain and die sounds***
21. HL2 Zombie sounds
22. One Tentacle bash reverted to HL1 sound and cleaned it up to keep continuity the distant sounds have also been altered
23. Garg has new pain sounds HL1 style
24. Improved Helicopter Hover sounds and cleaned up (Credit - HECU Marine)
25. Added Original Vox to Retinal scanners but balanced the volume of Vox (Credit Ysreli214)
26. Added Original Vox voice to countdown for rocket launch and omitted music from Blast pit***
27. New Horror Short music stings with a modern musical feel at key moments***
28. Some soundscape improvements ditant fighting and explosions (Credit HECU Marine)
29. Lowered the level of the Teleport Machine in Lambda core (It is still very loud just not deafening)***
30. Added Heartbeat sound that will play occasionly when shocked by a houndeye
31. Half life 1 Alarm sounds volume increase (Credit - HECU Marine)
32. Bloodshots Gib sounds and Body Impact Mod incorporated
33. Ceiling Turret Sound Akin to HL1 And if you destroy one it will now make an explode noise***
34. New Gunfire sounds for the Black Ops Assassins
35. New Flare Sound Effect***
36. New 50.cal Gun Sounds use Black Mesa Default as the Base***
37. Rebalanced the volume of Glock shoot sound as it is a bit too loud in IIOPN pack
38. Added missing zombie swipe noise that was missing from files BMS Install
39. Improved the mine explosion sound
40. New distant shockwave explosion in ST***
41. New Final Hit in apprehension before gordon gets knocked out***
42. Increased volume of the trams trundling on the tracks
43. New Vort pain sounds and recreated the threat line &quot;DIE!&quot; in HL2 vort dialogue
44. Added the missing ambient sounds folder (Credit Strelok)
45. Muted the idle HECU Marines (Credit Strelok)
46. Lowered the volume of the explosions in Faf (this was because HECU Marine had them too loud)
47. Rebalanced Soundtrack apart from tracks running on the game volume those have been omitted.*** (Please set your music volume to maximum)
48. New m4 shoot sound
49. New Tow sounds
50. New RPG sounds
51. Mortar script fix
52. Hivehand script fix and new sounds
53. New Long Jump Module sounds credit Acoma but I have altered the sound.
54. Explosions do not change volume any more
55. Yeah... Many Many more

*** = personally what I feel are Highlights of this pack

[COLOR=&#39;Lime&#39;]MP5/M4 ADD ON AND PATCH UPDATE[/SIZE]

[url]https://www.mediafire.com/download/zdtp7ncq3kj4q77/PATCHV3.rar[/url]

This is for existing users of the original final release as an update. Sounds for the M4/MP5 are available to swap whichever you are deciding to use.. 
________________________________________________________________________________________________________

And that is it... The pack is a mixture of classic and new you can download the file use windows or winrar to unzip extract and listen to the sounds yourself pick and choose or have them all.

Put the folder in your root BMS folder and copy and replace to install all

Enjoy!!!  :slight_smile: 

[b][u]You need the Animation Revamp Pack for it to work 100% here and you need to install this first!!!.. The download link is in the Video Description[/u][/b]

[url]https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=TaMAR1A9jg8[/url]

The particle effects can be found here although this is a reccomendation and not required

Download:
[url]https://dl.dropbox.com/s/t6zqp3t6q075tct/bm_particle_improvements_pack1.rar[/url]

animation Revamp by - IIOPN
Particle effects Pack by - DSD

This Soundpack Mainly Me but Credit also must go to Halferuga for some classic sounds  / Ysreli214 for long jump module and retinal scanners. Hecu Marine and inspiring me to update the Horror stings and some of his pack but re-edited some originals as HECU Marine clipped some sounds and distorted them.. Xalener for the work done on the tau canon.. I felt this was superior to what I did so included this in the pack. I also Added Bloodshots sounds to the pack for Gibbing and Body Impacts. Streloks muted Marines and missing ambient sounds folder. Credit to Acoma for the long jump module sounds which I have edited

These 3 mods combined should improve the core experience of Black Mesa and take it to new heights... Please note that using these mods with custom maps have caused instability in game... So I reccomend only using these 3 mods combined with the default Black Mesa install without expansion projects.

Comments and feedback welcome I hope you enjoy this on a fresh play through

[b][u]Things not being done[/u][/b]

Not changing HECU Marines Voices
Not Altering the M4 Reload, RPG sounds or Glock provided by IIopn if it&#39;s not in my folders that means it is staying.
Not Altering the Assasins voices
Not Altering the Vorts although the Vorts in HL2 should have sounded different... The vorts will stay as HL2 sounding Vorts
Not Altering ground sentry turrets
Not Altering Headcrabs
Not Adding any in game music from HL1 or HL2.

You are responsible for backing up your own files.... Do this by copying your BMS/sound and script folders to another location on your hard disk to revert back to default copy and paste these folders back in too overwrite all my hard work  :frowning: 

This is a Community Project...This work is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution 3.0 Unported License

[u][b]Things I wanted to do but could not do or did not get around to doing.[/b][/u]

More Original Vox lines
Cockroach scuttling sounds when cockroaches are present</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2014 21:24:10 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Black Mesa</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/bms-revamp-sound-mod/12418.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>BMS Revamp Sound Mod</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Ronster]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>This will reverse it back to normal, but please be aware anyone else back up your sound and script folders before installing this sound mod as then you can revert the changes yourself for whatever you do not like. as sound is picky I appreciate that.</p>
<p>Grunts idle sounds restored link below.</p>
<p><a href="https://www.mediafire.com/?vi65th7uw6oo9ot" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://www.mediafire.com/?vi65th7uw6oo9ot</a></p>
<p>Glad you are enjoying it  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=9" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/bms-revamp-sound-mod/12418/74">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/bms-revamp-sound-mod/12418/74</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2014 21:24:10 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12418-74</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/bms-revamp-sound-mod/12418.rss">BMS Revamp Sound Mod</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>BMS Revamp Sound Mod</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Garlopa]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>How can I make grunt idle sounds play again? thats the only thing I didn’t like</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/bms-revamp-sound-mod/12418/73">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/bms-revamp-sound-mod/12418/73</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2014 20:41:38 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12418-73</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/bms-revamp-sound-mod/12418.rss">BMS Revamp Sound Mod</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>BMS Revamp Sound Mod</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Ronster]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>OK I have managed to escape thus far from any flooding but it is still a very real possibility it can happen again. But I have now done a full update on the pack and changed quite a bit more as I paniced a bit last week.</p>
<p>The Full update will be on the first post of the thread. Any issues please let me know</p>
<p>If you are an existing user get the update [COLOR=‘Lime’]PATCH</p>
<p>If you are a new user a full updated release will be available as [COLOR=‘Lime’]ABSOLUTE FINAL UNTIL XEN</p>
<p>It comes with the M4 shoot sound as default if you are using the MP5 a new sound scheme is present there for it at the root. I have altered the long animation sounds and the shoot sounds.<br>
You can swap between them as and if you choose between the mp5 or the m4.</p>
<p>It’s been a lot of work but I am a lot more pleased with the new version and it has been improved quite a bit overall.</p>
<p>Thanks for trying it out and I hope you enjoy it!</p>
<p>PS dragunov I tried to improve on the 357 sound and give it more echo as per your request. I think it is a bit better now.</p>
<p>Certain soundscripts did not work so I have done all I could do within what is working to add and alter sound but in some instances where there is no sound I have managed to add sound but in others the code just simply is not there to play a sound and this is something I can do nothing about in terms of npc’s.</p>
<p>As for the realase there were a few wrinkles that needed ironing out… So there are new links but nothing major has been altered…There will be no more updates to this as of now unless someone reports a major probelm.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/bms-revamp-sound-mod/12418/72">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/bms-revamp-sound-mod/12418/72</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 08 Feb 2014 09:04:40 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12418-72</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/bms-revamp-sound-mod/12418.rss">BMS Revamp Sound Mod</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>BMS Revamp Sound Mod</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Ronster]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Got a bit of time off and I have made a few further changes to this pack and will be sharing them on this post in the form of a patch.</p>
<p>A few things I have managed to improve are as follows</p>
<ol>
<li>Hivehand Buzz script fix and sound alteration added phase effect to make it sound a bit more alien and bug impact noise has had a change in pitch</li>
<li>Weapon explosion sounds will no longer sound different depending on where you a situated in relation to the explosion</li>
<li>Improved / changed a few sounds crossbow shoot shotgun double and fixed tripmine deploy and activate sounds as I did not do this properly.</li>
<li>will patch trash compactor door noise but will put sound  in the redundant folder labelled “Continuity Error”</li>
<li>a few ambient sound alterations</li>
<li>trying to fix Helicopter rotor blades between hover and idle (I am testing this now)</li>
<li>new TOW shoot sound and deploy and retire sounds</li>
<li>I will alter Access Denied as per Dadster request</li>
<li>shuffling the zombie sounds about a bit</li>
<li>new shoot and die sound for ground sentry turrets</li>
<li>Bull chicken sound improvements</li>
</ol>
<p>And I think that is about it… Has anyone got any suggestions or something in my pack that they really did not like, or something from the vanilla game that bothers you sound wise?</p>
<p>I will put the patch up in the next few days.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b"><span class="bbcode-u">Quick update</span></span></p>
<p>Things are progressing nicely and have made some nice improvements especially the hivehand and explosion volumes are no longer effected by the players position.</p>
<p>So for bullsquids have better sounds now than I had done previously and the splat attack is mixed with the acid burn noise which I think is quite a nice touch.</p>
<p>Zombies have been greatly improved upon from my last iteration they are now more quiet creatures akin to Half life 1 zombies but if you burn them they scream like HL2 zombies and this works ever so well in my opinion.</p>
<p>I am going to be looking at some soundscapes and plan to make a few minor adjustments but nothing radical but I will be putting rat sqeaks in on a rail in the tunnels and I also plan on putting cockroaches scuttling in we’ve got hostiles room with the cockroaches.</p>
<p>I would like to add a horror sting when the ichy eats the scientist but cannot seem to locate the sound the scientist being eaten makes in the files but it’s in there somewhere.</p>
<p>I have also improved the Gauss canon overcharge noise slightly</p>
<p>But I am holding off releasing anything until I can get an answer on various instances of when gordon get’s hit by Alien grunts kicked by assassins clawed by a vortigaunt  or tail whipped by bullsquids. There is no sound in any of these instances as in being on the receiving end of it, and I am waiting to find out if script entry’s to play sounds can be added at these points, as I think this would really make a great improvement.</p>
<p>But in turn to the melee hit I also need to add swooshes to the assassins kicks and alien grunt punches and barges.</p>
<p>The last thing that has me wondering if the houndeye tinnitus option in the menu does anything? I assume this refers to <span class="bbcode-b">sonic.damage</span> but I doubt this is working</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/bms-revamp-sound-mod/12418/71">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/bms-revamp-sound-mod/12418/71</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2014 15:12:31 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12418-71</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/bms-revamp-sound-mod/12418.rss">BMS Revamp Sound Mod</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>BMS Revamp Sound Mod</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Ronster]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>no probs in an ideal world… I would hope for the core experience improvements and the cut content restored also… Fingers crossed eh  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=9" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/bms-revamp-sound-mod/12418/70">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/bms-revamp-sound-mod/12418/70</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 27 Aug 2013 20:18:10 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12418-70</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/bms-revamp-sound-mod/12418.rss">BMS Revamp Sound Mod</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>BMS Revamp Sound Mod</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[TheDragonMask]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Hmm, well thanks for the reply, it’s too bad because I was interested in the changes, but I since I can’t use it with additional maps it’s definitely a deal breaker.  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/frowning.png?v=9" title=":frowning:" class="emoji" alt=":frowning:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/bms-revamp-sound-mod/12418/69">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/bms-revamp-sound-mod/12418/69</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 27 Aug 2013 20:07:19 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12418-69</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/bms-revamp-sound-mod/12418.rss">BMS Revamp Sound Mod</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>BMS Revamp Sound Mod</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Ronster]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Yes indeed I had the same problem I am not sure what is causing the problem if it is just too much strain on the engine with all these elements combined and the uncut maps?</p>
<p>The uncut maps are more ambitious in scope in some ways in terms of how much is going on at a map level and these mods make more going on at a core level.</p>
<p>Feel free to swap out the sounds you do not like for something else sorry you do not like the magnum sound I really like that sound so It’s a matter of taste I guess.</p>
<p>The original Half life sound can be heard here<br>
<a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=FoFS4YxK9SI" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=FoFS4YxK9SI</a></p>
<p>I really did not want to touch the female vox lines that the team did I only wanted to bring back the classic male vox where appropriate.</p>
<p>I have not tested it but you should be able to use most of what is in this pack without the animation revamp as this is only sound files, meaning that the animations are probably more intensive so far as memory usuage goes and my sound files will do little to hinder performance.</p>
<p>Sorry It turns you off it but that is the way it is at the moment.</p>
<p>I don’t know about this or atleast all that much but I can only hope that the port to 2013 SDK with multi-core support may improve performance and make this all a non issue but we are all still using 2007… Unless a dev confirms that all these mods can harmonize under their current build in 2013 then take it as they don’t work together and may never work together due to engine resources.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/bms-revamp-sound-mod/12418/68">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/bms-revamp-sound-mod/12418/68</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 27 Aug 2013 18:31:10 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12418-68</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/bms-revamp-sound-mod/12418.rss">BMS Revamp Sound Mod</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>BMS Revamp Sound Mod</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[TheDragonMask]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>When I installed this it seemed to kill STUncut. I liked some of the changes like a louder alarm after the resonance cascade, but the part in the OP about “Please note that using these mods with custom maps have caused instability in game…” turned me off, along with the (IMO) awful revolver sounds. Sorry but it sounds like they were pulled from some old western, too dramatic, and the sound isn’t nearly as clean as everything else. Oh yeah, I also like the idea of having old VOX sounds, but if it doesn’t replace <span class="bbcode-b">everything</span> it’s just gonna seem off. I didn’t test it, but isn’t the part where the military takes over the VOX voice a new line added in BM?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/bms-revamp-sound-mod/12418/67">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/bms-revamp-sound-mod/12418/67</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 27 Aug 2013 18:05:11 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12418-67</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/bms-revamp-sound-mod/12418.rss">BMS Revamp Sound Mod</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>BMS Revamp Sound Mod</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Dragunov2]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Indeed!</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/bms-revamp-sound-mod/12418/66">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/bms-revamp-sound-mod/12418/66</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 19 Aug 2013 00:43:53 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12418-66</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/bms-revamp-sound-mod/12418.rss">BMS Revamp Sound Mod</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>BMS Revamp Sound Mod</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Ronster]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>exactly and totally canon…to bring the atmosphere of desert night</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/bms-revamp-sound-mod/12418/65">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/bms-revamp-sound-mod/12418/65</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 18 Aug 2013 19:43:13 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12418-65</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/bms-revamp-sound-mod/12418.rss">BMS Revamp Sound Mod</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>BMS Revamp Sound Mod</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Dadster]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>You’d think with it being such a large area, that some cricket sounds would be appropriate in the rail yard in Text’s B2 map.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/bms-revamp-sound-mod/12418/64">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/bms-revamp-sound-mod/12418/64</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 18 Aug 2013 19:41:16 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12418-64</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/bms-revamp-sound-mod/12418.rss">BMS Revamp Sound Mod</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>BMS Revamp Sound Mod</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Ronster]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Text should put the crickets singing too… I already mentioned this to him before but he shrugged it off… Nevermind…</p>
<p>I swapped that link… I will do it again…</p>
<p>I will fix the credit…</p>
<p>Yeah I think i did just over 2 weeks more or less solid on this soundpack… Thanks for the feedback… I really don’t plan to revisit this or do any updates until a later time… I think It’s brought the sound up a notch with the new animations and particles anyway which is what I set out to do… Depending on what the animation revamp does I may have to update it… But like I said I want to call it here on this pack for the time being at least for now.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/bms-revamp-sound-mod/12418/63">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/bms-revamp-sound-mod/12418/63</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 18 Aug 2013 19:34:51 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12418-63</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/bms-revamp-sound-mod/12418.rss">BMS Revamp Sound Mod</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>BMS Revamp Sound Mod</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Dadster]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Liking it a lot.</p>
<p>One suggestion, the vox at the end of retinalscanner_access_denied01.wav comes in a little too early. The voice overlaps the double-beep sound. I think it would be better if it followed the double-beep sound.</p>
<p>I think TextFAMGUY1 could use some of the distant battle sounds in the train yard for OaR Uncut map B2. I think he mentioned that he didn’t have a lot available to him to choose from.</p>
<p>A reminder that the link in the OP for the Particle Enhancement mod is still broken. You should replace it with the working link I provided.</p>
<p>Also, in your OP you give credit to “Xalena”. Did you mean “Xalener” instead?</p>
<p>Thanks for doing this. I’ve done some sound packs for other games, so I KNOW this was a lot of work.</p>
<p>Well done !</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/bms-revamp-sound-mod/12418/62">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/bms-revamp-sound-mod/12418/62</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 17 Aug 2013 17:49:20 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12418-62</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/bms-revamp-sound-mod/12418.rss">BMS Revamp Sound Mod</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>BMS Revamp Sound Mod</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Ronster]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>So I have noticed there is a problem with one sound that I put in the pack…</p>
<p>The trash compactor sound…</p>
<p>Actually let me rephrase it… There is nothing wrong with the sound I have made… It sounds a lot more clunky on start up and has more  impact… But the problem is the trash compactor… Which are doors… Stop and start about 4 times… Breaking the looped sound I have made… So I am not updating the pack… Because the trash compactor should not stop and start 4 times… It should only slow down so that is not my fault that the doors or whatever entity they are stop then start again.</p>
<p>This is just one of those things so if you backed up your files you can replace the original sound of which I based the sound off anyway… I only added a start up noise…But it’s not a major issue and I am not updating the pack for this… I’ll wait until I lay my keen eyes on a gonarch before that happens.</p>
<p>How are you finding the pack DADSTER?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/bms-revamp-sound-mod/12418/61">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/bms-revamp-sound-mod/12418/61</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 17 Aug 2013 09:34:16 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12418-61</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/bms-revamp-sound-mod/12418.rss">BMS Revamp Sound Mod</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>BMS Revamp Sound Mod</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Dadster]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>@ Ronster</p>
<p>I just checked and the link for the optional Particle Improvements Pack 1 mod on the first page is still not working. I think it’s best that you replace that link with the one that I provided.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/bms-revamp-sound-mod/12418/60">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/bms-revamp-sound-mod/12418/60</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2013 23:22:31 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12418-60</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/bms-revamp-sound-mod/12418.rss">BMS Revamp Sound Mod</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>BMS Revamp Sound Mod</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Ronster]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Thanks for that…</p>
<p>Hope you enjoy it</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/bms-revamp-sound-mod/12418/59">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/bms-revamp-sound-mod/12418/59</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2013 22:07:52 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12418-59</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/bms-revamp-sound-mod/12418.rss">BMS Revamp Sound Mod</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>BMS Revamp Sound Mod</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Dadster]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>@ Ronster</p>
<p>Downloading now.</p>
<p>Also, the link for the optional Particle Improvements Pack 1 mod on the first page is not working. Here’s a working link for it:</p>
<p><a href="https://dl.dropbox.com/s/t6zqp3t6q075tct/bm_particle_improvements_pack1.rar" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://dl.dropbox.com/s/t6zqp3t6q075tct/bm_particle_improvements_pack1.rar</a></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/bms-revamp-sound-mod/12418/58">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/bms-revamp-sound-mod/12418/58</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2013 19:24:02 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12418-58</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/bms-revamp-sound-mod/12418.rss">BMS Revamp Sound Mod</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>BMS Revamp Sound Mod</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Ronster]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Ok done a video for the people who requested it… If you notice a stutter that is my computer suffering from lack of RAM whilst trying to run the game and capture video…</p>
<p>If somone else has a powerful rig it would be better but you wanted to see my computer try to capture video and run the game you got it… I suggest somone who requested me to make a video makes a video now otherwise I will consider it rude.</p>
<p>It’s not that bad but it does stutter in a few places. Video in the first post.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/bms-revamp-sound-mod/12418/57">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/bms-revamp-sound-mod/12418/57</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2013 15:05:19 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12418-57</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/bms-revamp-sound-mod/12418.rss">BMS Revamp Sound Mod</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>BMS Revamp Sound Mod</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Ronster]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Yes you can sort of…</p>
<p>some of it will not work though for instance the reload sound for the crossbow 357 and mp5 shooting probably will be a bit odd… But apart from that yes all other sounds should work…</p>
<p>You will have to test it but it is only sound files… The few instances I named above will be lost… Or not sound as they did when using the animation revamp which is what inspired me to do this in the first place… But I went a bit further lol</p>
<p>Use Daleks mp5 for the default BM one…The majority of what I have done will work.</p>
<p>Just make sure you back up your sound and script folder in case…</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/bms-revamp-sound-mod/12418/56">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/bms-revamp-sound-mod/12418/56</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 11 Aug 2013 16:11:45 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12418-56</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/bms-revamp-sound-mod/12418.rss">BMS Revamp Sound Mod</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>BMS Revamp Sound Mod</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Dragunov2]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>No problem!</p>
<p>So we can use this package with the normal version aswell (Uncut maps included?), so without the animation revamp?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/bms-revamp-sound-mod/12418/55">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/bms-revamp-sound-mod/12418/55</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 11 Aug 2013 15:22:21 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12418-55</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/bms-revamp-sound-mod/12418.rss">BMS Revamp Sound Mod</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>BMS Revamp Sound Mod</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Ronster]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Ok so I am updating the link in the first post and this will be the proper final update on this project… I feel the work is now done and I have ironed out a couple of wrinkles and also had a change of heart on part of the main bulk of work I did on the soundtrack balancing amongst doing some new things.</p>
<p>That is all there is to say… It would be nice though if people who are downloading and using the pack were to say something about using it? but if there is nothing to be said then perhaps there is no problems so that is good… Either that or people hate it lol.</p>
<p>Oh well nevermind.</p>
<p>Thanks for your support anyhow Dargunov  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=9" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/bms-revamp-sound-mod/12418/54">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/bms-revamp-sound-mod/12418/54</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 11 Aug 2013 07:06:25 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12418-54</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/bms-revamp-sound-mod/12418.rss">BMS Revamp Sound Mod</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>BMS Revamp Sound Mod</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Dragunov2]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Not really, played the mod as usual without problems (finished the mod this way), but also read using the animation revamp, highers the possibility on crashes</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/bms-revamp-sound-mod/12418/53">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/bms-revamp-sound-mod/12418/53</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2013 11:50:42 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12418-53</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/bms-revamp-sound-mod/12418.rss">BMS Revamp Sound Mod</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>BMS Revamp Sound Mod</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Ronster]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Dragunov2">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/d/f08c70/40.png" class="avatar"> Dragunov2:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Gonna use your mod, sure!</p>
<p>But first they need to solve the hickups and crashes</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>There is not any issues with the animation revamp mod or the particle pack or my sound mod that makes Black Mesa any more unstable.</p>
<p>The problem only arises in the uncut maps… Your comment is a bit misleading Dragonuv… All these mod elements work very well combined… it is only when running the uncut maps that the game becomes very unstable.</p>
<p>I had a couple of crashes over a 3 week period with pretty heavy useage I would consider that quite normal running black mesa with these 3 mods combined and unaffecting.</p>
<p>were you getting lots of crashes before installing the uncut maps?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/bms-revamp-sound-mod/12418/52">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/bms-revamp-sound-mod/12418/52</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2013 10:13:37 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12418-52</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/bms-revamp-sound-mod/12418.rss">BMS Revamp Sound Mod</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>BMS Revamp Sound Mod</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Dragunov2]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Gonna use your mod, sure!</p>
<p>But first they need to solve the hickups and crashes</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/bms-revamp-sound-mod/12418/51">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/bms-revamp-sound-mod/12418/51</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2013 01:42:14 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12418-51</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/bms-revamp-sound-mod/12418.rss">BMS Revamp Sound Mod</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>BMS Revamp Sound Mod</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Ronster]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>no worries I had the same problem… So I totally understand… I wanted to test out the uncut maps and held off until I thought I finished this project… Now I have realised that I still have more to do… But the mods work fine with the default black mesa install or atleast a lot better.</p>
<p>The Uncut maps gave me a lot of problems crashing out on load screens and freezing so perhaps let that be something to take note of… when using these other mods combined… You learn as you go with these things… Best to keep some things seperate until the issues somehow get resolved.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/bms-revamp-sound-mod/12418/50">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/bms-revamp-sound-mod/12418/50</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2013 21:09:21 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12418-50</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/bms-revamp-sound-mod/12418.rss">BMS Revamp Sound Mod</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
