<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Tactical Intervention</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/tactical-intervention/7070</link>
    <description>So.... who&#39;s got a beta key? One of my friends gave me one, and the closed beta starts in 30 mins.

Maybe we can share our thoughts here. If there are some, who can play it...

Quick overview: TI is the new project by Minh Le, the creator of Counter Strike. It now goes into the closed beta, and it will be later released as a Free2Play Shooter.

He has added the things, which he couldn&#39;t implement in Counter Strike.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 06 May 2011 21:44:11 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Technology and Gaming</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/tactical-intervention/7070.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Tactical Intervention</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[tenebrae]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I was just playing this and so far I gotta say it’s pretty good. I had a few laggy bits, but overall it runs quite smooth, much better than I was expecting for day 1 of the beta. Graphically it’s not the most impressive thing out there, but it still looks good. Certainly better than CSS looks. The HUD also looks great. The way it presents all the important information without it being distracting is nice. The shooting mechanics feel similar to CS, which is to say that trigger control is a must for consistent accuracy. Weapon selection is minimal right now. I’m assuming more will be added. Overall it does feel like a more feature-rich CS, and that makes me happy 'cause I’ve always loved CS, but have somewhat lost interest as it feels outdated and lacking in comparison to some of the newer shooters. Some of the new features aren’t exactly innovative, like a sprint function, quick-melee, and leveling system. They are, however, implemented well and feel like an improvement over CS. There’s leaning, which I’ve never been a fan of, and I’m still not crazy about it in this game, but if you press the lean keys simultaneously then you enter blind-fire mode which allows you to blindly shoot around corners or over counter tops, etc. Hostages can be used as human sheilds. The store contains weapons, attachments, and all kinds of gear. The great thing about the gear is that everything actually does something useful, rather than just change the look of your character. Headphones will reduce the noise of flashbangs, helmets actually protect you at the cost of some visibility, even the gloves will increase your knife speed. Speaking of the knife, it’s still a separate weapon, so CS style knife fights can still commence. Overall I’d say there’s room for improvement, but it’s off to a great start.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/tactical-intervention/7070/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/tactical-intervention/7070/4</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 06 May 2011 21:44:11 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7070-4</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/tactical-intervention/7070.rss">Tactical Intervention</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Tactical Intervention</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[JohnWorfin]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>what things?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/tactical-intervention/7070/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/tactical-intervention/7070/3</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 06 May 2011 17:20:41 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7070-3</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/tactical-intervention/7070.rss">Tactical Intervention</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Tactical Intervention</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[HawaK]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>edit:forget it</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/tactical-intervention/7070/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/tactical-intervention/7070/2</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 06 May 2011 13:04:24 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7070-2</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/tactical-intervention/7070.rss">Tactical Intervention</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Tactical Intervention</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[DiePoente]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>So… who’s got a beta key? One of my friends gave me one, and the closed beta starts in 30 mins.</p>
<p>Maybe we can share our thoughts here. If there are some, who can play it…</p>
<p>Quick overview: TI is the new project by Minh Le, the creator of Counter Strike. It now goes into the closed beta, and it will be later released as a Free2Play Shooter.</p>
<p>He has added the things, which he couldn’t implement in Counter Strike.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/tactical-intervention/7070/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/tactical-intervention/7070/1</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 06 May 2011 11:35:59 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7070-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/tactical-intervention/7070.rss">Tactical Intervention</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
