<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>did we really need all of these base combat mechanic changes?</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/did-we-really-need-all-of-these-base-combat-mechanic-changes/10600</link>
    <description>you know what i&#39;ve been waiting for the mod for a while like everyone else and was happy to get my hands on it. although i was a bit dissapointed with how many alterations they did, i was hoping it would get the same treatment as halo combat evolved and after all if i wanted a whole new black mesa oriented game i would be following the operation lambda mod. but in the end its not so bad(although the ammount of load screens are, and thats an engine issue) the one thing that&#39;s killing me about this remake is the combat mechanics.

if it ain&#39;t broke don&#39;t fix it, so why the hell did they make so many changes to the base combat mechanics? the originals were fine and a lot of stuff is just so screwed up right now. and its not that i didnt want change, believe me i wanted change and love all of the additions to gameplay like ADS, actual 02 counter, sprint, crowbar hitting head crabs in the air. but its the base combat mechanic changes that i just cant stand.

crowbar- well its now almost completely useless minus headcrabs. sucks against zombies with how they fight, barnacles your better off shooting if you get caught in one and even the houndeye cant be fought with it. houndeye especially is bugging me since it was never meant to be a hard enemy, just a low level one and as the game progresses you work your way up to harder ones.

pistol- would have prefered HD texture pack style but ah well. also heavily nerfed, you need a lot more bullets now to kill most enemies severely weakening it, and using it would just waste ammo(i&#39;ll explain latter)

revolver- one of the few weapons i&#39;m happy with, still extremely powerful and the ADS is great for it, not a lot of changes to its mechanics.

m4- cant really tell that much power difference but it was nerfed to hell with ammo. now only supports 150 bullets which makes sharing ammo with the pistol a complete pain, wouldn&#39;t be so bad if you didn&#39;t have to use the pistol for all the enemies the crowbar would normally handle. the actual magazine size has also been reduced to a mere 30 bullets which is useless for storming a bunch of enemies at once, kill one marine, head back reload, kill another wash rinse and repeat. its so annoying and breaks combat, its just not fun at all

shotgun- so far i cant tell that much difference with it, still deadly at close range so that&#39;s a plus.

none of the base mechanic changes were needed and most of them suck, some people will probably think its fine for now but i wonder how much they will think that once death match comes out especially with the m16 changes. now onto the actual enemy changes 

zombies- harder to kill, and will more often than not hit you if you try and melee them.

headcrabs- about the same

houndeye- way more powerful than it should be and its even worse since it now shakes up player vision.

barnacles- harder to kill with pistol and crowbar

vortigaunts- much shorter charge time and its annoying as hell since it also obstructs your vission. and on a side note who thought it was a good idea to give them a crotch piece?

the tentacle mouthed thing- i absolutely hate this enemy now, its not that its hard to kill its the way it does the damage, instead of the normal spit thing it now lobes acid in your direction which is extremely annoying and has far to much of a range.


i just have to wonder who the hell thought it was a good idea to change the base mechanics, nothing needed tweaking and everything was fine as far as balance goes except maybe the laser gun in death match and i havn&#39;t gotten to see that yet. but seriously there are so many changes this is half way to being a differnt franchise entirely in terms of gameplay, it dosent resemble the first half-lifes gameplay OR the second. so what was the point? all they did was screw up balance and once deathmatch comes out i have a feeling so many people will hate the changes to all of the weapons, m16 and pistol especially.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2013 16:28:37 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>The Cafeteria</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/did-we-really-need-all-of-these-base-combat-mechanic-changes/10600.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>did we really need all of these base combat mechanic changes?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[ojcoolj]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="skyace65">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/s/90ced4/40.png" class="avatar"> skyace65:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>A i cant code</p>
<p>B modifying a mod probobly isnt the best idea and could cause instability</p>
<p>C any changes i make to have it more like the original wont get carried over to deathmatch</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Shit you are an idiot</p>
<p>And Half Life is still around. You want to play Half Life? Go play Half life. Just because this game is different to the original doesn’t make it bad</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/did-we-really-need-all-of-these-base-combat-mechanic-changes/10600/93">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/did-we-really-need-all-of-these-base-combat-mechanic-changes/10600/93</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2013 16:28:37 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-10600-93</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/did-we-really-need-all-of-these-base-combat-mechanic-changes/10600.rss">did we really need all of these base combat mechanic changes?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>did we really need all of these base combat mechanic changes?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[KyuuGryphon]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Oh no, another thread about the balancing. Someone needs to keep me out of these, help</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="skyace65">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/s/90ced4/40.png" class="avatar"> skyace65:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>you know what i’ve been waiting for the mod for a while like everyone else and was happy to get my hands on it. although i was a bit dissapointed with how many alterations they did, i was hoping it would get the same treatment as halo combat evolved and after all if i wanted a whole new black mesa oriented game i would be following the operation lambda mod. but in the end its not so bad(although the ammount of load screens are, and thats an engine issue) the one thing that’s killing me about this remake is the combat mechanics.</p>
<p>if it ain’t broke don’t fix it, so why the hell did they make so many changes to the base combat mechanics? the originals were fine and a lot of stuff is just so screwed up right now. and its not that i didnt want change, believe me i wanted change and love all of the additions to gameplay like ADS, actual 02 counter, sprint, crowbar hitting head crabs in the air. but its the base combat mechanic changes that i just cant stand.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Are we playing the same mod? The changes that they’ve made to how things work are a lot better. Are there minor problems? Yes, but as a whole, I would say it’s a much better experience as a result. I honestly think Black Mesa works and feels much better than Half-Life 2 does. Your mileage may vary (and apparently does), but that’s how I feel.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="skyace65">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/s/90ced4/40.png" class="avatar"> skyace65:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>crowbar- well its now almost completely useless minus headcrabs. sucks against zombies with how they fight, barnacles your better off shooting if you get caught in one and even the houndeye cant be fought with it. houndeye especially is bugging me since it was never meant to be a hard enemy, just a low level one and as the game progresses you work your way up to harder ones.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Crowbar - “Sucks against zombies”? No it doesn’t. Hell, the crowbar’s better against zombies in BM than it was in Half-Life. I’ll agree about Barnacles though, I find it kind of off-putting how it takes about four crowbar hits to kill. Are you sure you’re using the crowbar right?</p>
<p>“Houndeyes were never meant to be a hard enemy”? Well, okay, first off, you don’t know for certain that those were Valve’s intentions. Second off, there’s a difference between an easy enemy and completely useless, which is pretty much how they were in Half-Life. In BM, they’re actually a threat. Headcrabs are easy enemies without being a waste of space, it makes sense that Houndeyes would be stronger than them (they’re bigger, and you start encountering them a bit later on).</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="skyace65">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/s/90ced4/40.png" class="avatar"> skyace65:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>pistol- would have prefered HD texture pack style but ah well. also heavily nerfed, you need a lot more bullets now to kill most enemies severely weakening it, and using it would just waste ammo(i’ll explain latter)</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Which is exactly the same as in Half-Life 2. It takes two shots on a Headcrab, like both HL1 and 2, around half a dozen shots on Barnacles, like Half-Life 2, and several headshots on zombies, like Half-Life 2.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="skyace65">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/s/90ced4/40.png" class="avatar"> skyace65:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>m4- cant really tell that much power difference but it was nerfed to hell with ammo. now only supports 150 bullets which makes sharing ammo with the pistol a complete pain, wouldn’t be so bad if you didn’t have to use the pistol for all the enemies the crowbar would normally handle. the actual magazine size has also been reduced to a mere 30 bullets which is useless for storming a bunch of enemies at once, kill one marine, head back reload, kill another wash rinse and repeat. its so annoying and breaks combat, its just not fun at all</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>The MP5 does the same damage per bullet at the pistol does, so I’ll agree with it being a bit underpowered. Your comment about the shared ammo pool is moot, as the crowbar isn’t as underpowered as you seem to think it is.</p>
<p>Also, “storming a bunch of enemies at once” is not how you’re supposed to play this game. I’m pretty sure the Half-Life manual actually said something along those lines, I’ll have to dig it out and take a look at some point.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="skyace65">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/s/90ced4/40.png" class="avatar"> skyace65:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>none of the base mechanic changes were needed and most of them suck, some people will probably think its fine for now but i wonder how much they will think that once death match comes out especially with the m16 changes. now onto the actual enemy changes</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Most of the mechanic changes were done to make the game more balanced, and some of the ones you’re claiming are a problem just aren’t true, like the crowbar. The MP5 is a much better weapon than it was in Half-Life - In Half-Life, the bullets scattered all over the damn place. It was never supposed to be a long-range weapon. In BM, you can use it at a longer range, and it’s still pretty effective up close against one opponent. You shouldn’t be using it against groups, except the grenade launcher.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="skyace65">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/s/90ced4/40.png" class="avatar"> skyace65:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>zombies- harder to kill, and will more often than not hit you if you try and melee them.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Then you’re doing something wrong. While I’ve found that it’s a bit awkward trying to aim at security guard zombies due to their gait, overall the zombies are way easier to dodge in BM than they were in Half-Life.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="skyace65">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/s/90ced4/40.png" class="avatar"> skyace65:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>houndeye- way more powerful than it should be and its even worse since it now shakes up player vision.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>A sole Houndeye is perfectly well balanced. I agree, a single pack of them handled poorly shouldn’t kill you immediately, but they’re a much better enemy than in Half-Life, both difficulty-wise and balancing-wise. They’re fun to fight against instead of just a nuisance (they can still be annoying, but in Half-Life they were just kinda there).</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="skyace65">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/s/90ced4/40.png" class="avatar"> skyace65:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>barnacles- harder to kill with pistol and crowbar</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>The crowbar, definitely. Harder to kill with the pistol than in HL1? Yes. Harder to kill with the pistol in HL2? Definitely not.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="skyace65">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/s/90ced4/40.png" class="avatar"> skyace65:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>vortigaunts- much shorter charge time and its annoying as hell since it also obstructs your vission. and on a side note who thought it was a good idea to give them a crotch piece?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Are you kidding? Vorts do so little damage, there’s no point. Their health is really low as well, they don’t stand a chance against… Anything, really.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="skyace65">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/s/90ced4/40.png" class="avatar"> skyace65:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>the tentacle mouthed thing- i absolutely hate this enemy now, its not that its hard to kill its the way it does the damage, instead of the normal spit thing it now lobes acid in your direction which is extremely annoying and has far to much of a range.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>The spread of the Bullsquid acid should be a bit tighter, in my opinion, as-is it can be painfully annoying to dodge sometimes. They also have too little health, I think. Other than that, they’re fine.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="skyace65">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/s/90ced4/40.png" class="avatar"> skyace65:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>i just have to wonder who the hell thought it was a good idea to change the base mechanics, nothing needed tweaking and everything was fine as far as balance goes except maybe the laser gun in death match and i havn’t gotten to see that yet. but seriously there are so many changes this is half way to being a differnt franchise entirely in terms of gameplay, it dosent resemble the first half-lifes gameplay OR the second. so what was the point? all they did was screw up balance and once deathmatch comes out i have a feeling so many people will hate the changes to all of the weapons, m16 and pistol especially.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>No, there were a lot of problems with balance in Half-Life’s singleplayer. The pistol’s nigh-on identical to how it was in both games (other than the barnacle/zombie damage, they’re pretty much the same), the MP5’s a much better weapon overall (albeit still underpowered), and it’s very, very similar to Half-Life 2’s gameplay, only improved (the weapons feel more useful and the difficulty in BM is more consistent). It’s a blend between both games, I have no idea where you’re getting some of these claims from.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/did-we-really-need-all-of-these-base-combat-mechanic-changes/10600/92">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/did-we-really-need-all-of-these-base-combat-mechanic-changes/10600/92</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 12 Feb 2013 19:51:18 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-10600-92</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/did-we-really-need-all-of-these-base-combat-mechanic-changes/10600.rss">did we really need all of these base combat mechanic changes?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>did we really need all of these base combat mechanic changes?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[frogger143]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="JeffMOD">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/user_avatar/leakfree.org/jeffmod/40/4333_2.png" class="avatar"> JeffMOD:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Maybe not, but that’s how it was in HL, too.  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=9" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"></p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I think that was partially the point, and I think people might be forgetting, HL was made in '99, and game design then wasn’t exactly ‘balanced’, but was most definitely fun. We’ve been spoiled as of late with things that are ‘new’, and some of us older gamer’s might get a little disappointed about the way things have been changed, while newer people might not know it at all.</p>
<p>Personally, I think Black Mesa was a good honest change over while doing it’s darnedest to keep to the original feel and purpose as the game the best they could. Hell, half the time I’m playing it, I almost wish I never played Half-Life or forgot everything about the game so that Black Mesa is truly a ‘fresh experience’. There are times I hate having that, ‘Oh snap I know whats coming ahead’, knowledge. But the developers has still done a great job.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/did-we-really-need-all-of-these-base-combat-mechanic-changes/10600/91">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/did-we-really-need-all-of-these-base-combat-mechanic-changes/10600/91</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 10 Feb 2013 23:14:39 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-10600-91</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/did-we-really-need-all-of-these-base-combat-mechanic-changes/10600.rss">did we really need all of these base combat mechanic changes?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>did we really need all of these base combat mechanic changes?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[JeffMOD]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Maybe not, but that’s how it was in HL, too.  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=9" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/did-we-really-need-all-of-these-base-combat-mechanic-changes/10600/90">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/did-we-really-need-all-of-these-base-combat-mechanic-changes/10600/90</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 10 Feb 2013 17:26:44 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-10600-90</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/did-we-really-need-all-of-these-base-combat-mechanic-changes/10600.rss">did we really need all of these base combat mechanic changes?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>did we really need all of these base combat mechanic changes?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[CatzEyes93]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I cant disagree with the original post. The game is definitely a different game and there are going to be some that are not joyous over every change. Ya cant fault him for it.</p>
<p>For me, I think the only thing that I didn’t like to begin with, and never got used to even over the long haul, was the placement of the weapons / aliens. I know they worked hard to mix it up and make it unique, but for me it never seemed right. I either never had the right weapon at the right stage of the game, or when a new alien was introduced I wasn’t forced to try a different tactic due to previous weapons being ineffectual.</p>
<p>Originally, an intro to a new weapon always seemed to set you up for an intro to a new alien. This gave you time to play with and learn how each weapon could serve a specific purpose. Here, it seemed we were given a new weapon but no valid reason to use it over the others already in your cache.</p>
<p>For example, getting the hive hand was an awesome moment, (props for the butt rape scene!) but was it really the weapon of choice for the fire fight directly after?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/did-we-really-need-all-of-these-base-combat-mechanic-changes/10600/89">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/did-we-really-need-all-of-these-base-combat-mechanic-changes/10600/89</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 10 Feb 2013 15:14:09 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-10600-89</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/did-we-really-need-all-of-these-base-combat-mechanic-changes/10600.rss">did we really need all of these base combat mechanic changes?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>did we really need all of these base combat mechanic changes?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[warpedfreeman]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="xtobix">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 xtobix:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>when it comes to deathmatch bm should be a 1:1 remake concerning the weapons, gamespeed and movement… otherwise it will be shit and i won’t play it.<br>
configs are fine but too many different game-styles / balancing-settings are bad for the community. there should be one great standard (original HL) which should be taken for singleplayer, public and competetive matches. everything else should be done with mods.</p>
<p>seriously i was more than dissappointed because of all these unnecessary gameplaychanges… i played it through one time… and did not touch it since then… and i loved the original so much… now bm ruined everything that was so great about half-life. i can only hope they will patch the bad balancing at some point…</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>sorry but its imposible that BM could be a 20/20 remake; some things must be obligatory changed.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/did-we-really-need-all-of-these-base-combat-mechanic-changes/10600/88">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/did-we-really-need-all-of-these-base-combat-mechanic-changes/10600/88</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 10 Feb 2013 15:05:51 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-10600-88</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/did-we-really-need-all-of-these-base-combat-mechanic-changes/10600.rss">did we really need all of these base combat mechanic changes?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>did we really need all of these base combat mechanic changes?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[fury]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>when it comes to deathmatch bm should be a 1:1 remake concerning the weapons, gamespeed and movement… otherwise it will be shit and i won’t play it.<br>
configs are fine but too many different game-styles / balancing-settings are bad for the community. there should be one great standard (original HL) which should be taken for singleplayer, public and competetive matches. everything else should be done with mods.</p>
<p>seriously i was more than dissappointed because of all these unnecessary gameplaychanges… i played it through one time… and did not touch it since then… and i loved the original so much… now bm ruined everything that was so great about half-life. i can only hope they will patch the bad balancing at some point…</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/did-we-really-need-all-of-these-base-combat-mechanic-changes/10600/87">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/did-we-really-need-all-of-these-base-combat-mechanic-changes/10600/87</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 10 Feb 2013 14:52:22 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-10600-87</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/did-we-really-need-all-of-these-base-combat-mechanic-changes/10600.rss">did we really need all of these base combat mechanic changes?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>did we really need all of these base combat mechanic changes?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Feldheld]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I like a challenge. The worst thing you can do to a game, is make it too easy. That’s why WoW is going down btw. They listened to the whiners.</p>
<p>If it is too difficult for you, play it on easy or normal mode.</p>
<p>Some things have become easier in BMS compared to HL1, some harder, in sum it has become a little harder which is good because it used to be too easy.</p>
<p>Headcrabs and zombies are easier to kill now. Crowbar rules.</p>
<p>Houndeyes pose a much bigger challenge cause they home in very quickly in groups, have a way shorter charging time but do a little less damage with one charge. Also they take more damage. I deal with them in two ways, depending on the situation: MP5, one mag is enough for 3 of them. Or satchel charges, exploding barrels, hand grenades, whatever the situation prefers.</p>
<p>Bull squibs, they die easier now (2 shotgun rounds to the ugly face, or one 'nade) but do much more damage, and much more spash damage now. Takes a lot of movement skill to avoid their acid spray while trying to get a shot at them. Bottom line though they seem to be a bit easier to me than in HL1.</p>
<p>Soldiers, didnt change much. If anything they got a bit easier in 1 on 1 but they increased their numbers a bit. Also their tactical behaviour is more aggressive, they home in on you faster and in bigger numbers.</p>
<p>Black ops, not much difference, maybe a bit easier now.</p>
<p>Barnackles, harder to kill, takes 8 pistol rounds instead of 4, but only one shotgun or .357 magnum round, also no more one-hitting them with the crowbar.</p>
<p>In general, it mostly takes some time to get used to the new mechanics, just like it was when we played HL1 the first time. For a mod, BMS is very well balanced.</p>
<p>The only thing that annoys me sometimes is the HL physics engine that often interfers with my movement in very unpredictable and unnatural ways. There is so much stuff littering the ground, barrels, boxes, traffic cones, palettes. You want to run or jump behind a cover but you get somehow glued to a traffic cone that lies in your way and extremely slows you down for no good reason. Thats why Ive come to clean the battlefield if possible before I attack.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/did-we-really-need-all-of-these-base-combat-mechanic-changes/10600/86">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/did-we-really-need-all-of-these-base-combat-mechanic-changes/10600/86</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 19 Dec 2012 08:37:25 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-10600-86</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/did-we-really-need-all-of-these-base-combat-mechanic-changes/10600.rss">did we really need all of these base combat mechanic changes?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>did we really need all of these base combat mechanic changes?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Dr_Maxwell]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Of course we needed all these base combat changes.  Otherwise the game might actually have some redeeming quality besides looking nice.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/did-we-really-need-all-of-these-base-combat-mechanic-changes/10600/85">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/did-we-really-need-all-of-these-base-combat-mechanic-changes/10600/85</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 14 Dec 2012 07:57:03 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-10600-85</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/did-we-really-need-all-of-these-base-combat-mechanic-changes/10600.rss">did we really need all of these base combat mechanic changes?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>did we really need all of these base combat mechanic changes?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[MSKyuuni]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I disagree. I played on easy because I think I’m a complete and utter noob (and I am slightly) but really when it comes down to it, I just wanted something I could manage, experiencing a good remake where I’d have a great amount of challenge without getting frustrated. That said, I did have to cheat a couple of times and most of the aliens were pathetic.<br>
Combat hasn’t changed at all for me though I kind of wish Houndeyes charged a little bit slower or at least had a short delay; at bare minimum, maybe you should possibly TRY to use the whole charging sound, dammit. Headcrabs were also too fast for anything except a well-timed crowbar hit, though I think that’s just crappy reflexes. Every other NPC was great, except the soldiers and their magical MP5s of accuracy. Barnacles take four pistol rounds on easy, just like HL1. Bullsquids are badass, just like HL1. Zombies are disturbing and not too hard to kill, just like HL1 and honestly, I’m used to killing Ichthyosaurs with 2 bolts because I played both games on easy.</p>
<p>The only weapon I can possibly complain about is the MP5 (excuse me, OP, it’s not an M4 or an M16, it’s an MP5) because it’s so fast it feels uncontrollable and you can’t hold many M203 rounds, but it’s way more accurate than HL1 or 2. It’s just that it’s way too fast, just so it could be burst-fire. Whose idea was that, anyway? It was a good weapon in HL1 because it was slow enough to use properly.</p>
<p>My main point though, is that you aren’t a wimpy pussy if you play on easy. Easy is for if you maybe aren’t so great or if you want to see every lovely aspect without huge amounts of challenge and frustration. As someone said, Deus Ex: Human Revolution explicitly said that easy mode wasn’t it’s way of saying “lolololol n00b” but for if you wanted to just experience the narrative.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/did-we-really-need-all-of-these-base-combat-mechanic-changes/10600/84">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/did-we-really-need-all-of-these-base-combat-mechanic-changes/10600/84</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 14 Dec 2012 07:37:20 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-10600-84</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/did-we-really-need-all-of-these-base-combat-mechanic-changes/10600.rss">did we really need all of these base combat mechanic changes?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>did we really need all of these base combat mechanic changes?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[SirEgon]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Skyface65, did you even play the game? First of all, you say that the crowbar is horrible against zombies in Black Mesa and great in Half-Life 1. In reality, zombies were harder in hl1 because of their long melee range. Killing zombies has been exactly the same throughout all of the Half-Life series: Hit twice, back up, hit twice, back up. In Black Mesa, it’s even EASIER, because of their nerfed melee range.</p>
<p>As for the Glock 17, I saw no real difference to it’s mechanics, except for the removal of the useless alt fire and nerfed max ammo, which I’ve personally never had a problem with.</p>
<p>As for the 357 Magnum, the decreased max ammo takes away some of how the weapon was over-powered.</p>
<p>So you say that the Mp5 (whose name you got wrong twice), is horrible in Black Mesa because of the nerfed ammo. First of all, the ammo the clip supported in Hl1 seemed to be very overpowered, and I’m glad it was reduced to 30. You say the max ammo of 150 that it shares with the Glock is bad, but, seriously, I rarely ever saw the ammo counter go below 100. You get Mp5 clips out the wazoo in WGH!</p>
<p>As for the Spas-12, no comment either.</p>
<p>As for the zombies, houndeyes, barnacles, bullsquids, and vortigaunts…<br>
As I said, zombies were practically not changed at all.<br>
The houndeyes were changed for the better. Honestly, they rarely ever got a chance to do damage in Hl1.<br>
As for the barnacles, there wasn’t really much change. They were always easy to avoid, and even if you do get caught in one, just shoot it instead of crowbaring it when you finally reach it so you can take even more falling damage.<br>
I honestly didn’t even notice the changes to the bullsquid until you brought it up.<br>
You say the vort’s charge time was decreased, well, yeah, of course. In Hl1, you easily kill them before they even damage you. Also, the vorts seemed to have a rather dumb AI in Black Mesa.</p>
<p>I’m not surprised you didn’t complain about the Ichthyosaur, because what Black Mesa did there seems to be exactly what you want for every other enemy in the game. That cute little fella was nerfed a lot in Black Mesa. Two crossbow hits, a full Glock clip, or ten hits with the crowbar (each hit resets his attack, making it so he can’t do any damage at all)</p>
<p>If the weapons don’t get changed in the deathmatch remake, so what? As far as I can see, that’s a good thing! Judging by how much Black Mesa singleplayer felt like Hl1 singleplayer, deathmatch is going to be perfect.</p>
<p>I, personally, play with a modified version of the skill.cfg. Mostly increased enemy’s health, like the Ichthyosaur. I’ve also decreased and increased the health of the HECU Marines and Vortigaunts, in order to bring back the feeling of “On a Rail,” which was intended in Hl1 to make the player think, “Holy $#*%! Aliens are invading and not even our own military can stop them!”</p>
<p>While there were some things I didn’t like at first, overall Black Mesa captured the feel of Half-Life perfectly.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/did-we-really-need-all-of-these-base-combat-mechanic-changes/10600/83">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/did-we-really-need-all-of-these-base-combat-mechanic-changes/10600/83</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 14 Dec 2012 02:56:10 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-10600-83</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/did-we-really-need-all-of-these-base-combat-mechanic-changes/10600.rss">did we really need all of these base combat mechanic changes?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>did we really need all of these base combat mechanic changes?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[GordonReturns]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Edit - After looking back over the topic, I never saw the OP reply to my counter-arguments…so I am not gonna argue again.  I assumed he was still going at it because it was still alive.  If a mod wants, they can delete my post.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/did-we-really-need-all-of-these-base-combat-mechanic-changes/10600/82">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/did-we-really-need-all-of-these-base-combat-mechanic-changes/10600/82</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2012 20:43:35 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-10600-82</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/did-we-really-need-all-of-these-base-combat-mechanic-changes/10600.rss">did we really need all of these base combat mechanic changes?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>did we really need all of these base combat mechanic changes?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[targ]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="skyace65">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/s/90ced4/40.png" class="avatar"> skyace65:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>i just have to wonder who the hell thought it was a good idea to change the base mechanics</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p><a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Video_game_remake" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Video_game_remake</a></p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="skyace65">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/s/90ced4/40.png" class="avatar"> skyace65:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>but seriously there are so many changes this is half way to being a differnt franchise entirely in terms of gameplay, it dosent resemble the first half-lifes gameplay OR the second.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p><img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/expressionless.png?v=9" title=":expressionless:" class="emoji" alt=":expressionless:"> wat</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="skyace65">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/s/90ced4/40.png" class="avatar"> skyace65:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>all they did was screw up balance and once deathmatch comes out i have a feeling so many people will hate the changes to all of the weapons, m16 and pistol especially.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>You’re assuming all the weapons will behave exactly the same in single and multiplayer versions; they very likely will not. If you’re criticizing the single player experience based on how well you think it will carry over to multiplayer, you’re doing it wrong.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/did-we-really-need-all-of-these-base-combat-mechanic-changes/10600/81">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/did-we-really-need-all-of-these-base-combat-mechanic-changes/10600/81</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2012 19:06:24 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-10600-81</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/did-we-really-need-all-of-these-base-combat-mechanic-changes/10600.rss">did we really need all of these base combat mechanic changes?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>did we really need all of these base combat mechanic changes?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[sm00t]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Behold…The aftermath of a (GREAT) mod still to be finished…</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/did-we-really-need-all-of-these-base-combat-mechanic-changes/10600/80">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/did-we-really-need-all-of-these-base-combat-mechanic-changes/10600/80</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 21 Nov 2012 18:31:23 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-10600-80</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/did-we-really-need-all-of-these-base-combat-mechanic-changes/10600.rss">did we really need all of these base combat mechanic changes?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>did we really need all of these base combat mechanic changes?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Android11x]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>behold, a player complaining about a game because of his own skill level</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/did-we-really-need-all-of-these-base-combat-mechanic-changes/10600/79">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/did-we-really-need-all-of-these-base-combat-mechanic-changes/10600/79</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 21 Nov 2012 17:54:41 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-10600-79</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/did-we-really-need-all-of-these-base-combat-mechanic-changes/10600.rss">did we really need all of these base combat mechanic changes?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>did we really need all of these base combat mechanic changes?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Dragunov2]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Even on easy, the soldiers are sometimes challenging</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/did-we-really-need-all-of-these-base-combat-mechanic-changes/10600/78">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/did-we-really-need-all-of-these-base-combat-mechanic-changes/10600/78</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 13 Nov 2012 01:05:08 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-10600-78</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/did-we-really-need-all-of-these-base-combat-mechanic-changes/10600.rss">did we really need all of these base combat mechanic changes?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>did we really need all of these base combat mechanic changes?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[saivert]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I played Black Mesa the first time on easy. I even think easy is the default difficulty unless you pick something else. I had a blast. I did die on easy too but it never got frustrating. And I died just because I kept rushing some encounters. As soon as I stepped back and took an overview of the situation it never was a problem.</p>
<p>Play it on easy and stop complaining. That is what easy is for. I always play single player games on easy the first time around. I did play Medal of Honor Warfighter on Normal just because someone had said it was easy and I got about half through the campaign before I switched to easy.<br>
Black Mesa is obviously a lot more difficult on Normal, so Hard is for those who really want to test their skills.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/did-we-really-need-all-of-these-base-combat-mechanic-changes/10600/77">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/did-we-really-need-all-of-these-base-combat-mechanic-changes/10600/77</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Nov 2012 22:40:20 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-10600-77</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/did-we-really-need-all-of-these-base-combat-mechanic-changes/10600.rss">did we really need all of these base combat mechanic changes?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>did we really need all of these base combat mechanic changes?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[BendyBread]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="RicheyEdwards">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/r/46a35a/40.png" class="avatar"> RicheyEdwards:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Ah see, I never even got close enough to know that they still do that. The only way they can effectively tail whip you is by charging you to get close enough in the first place, so I’d definitely like to see that added at some point.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I miss charging bullsquid. I mean that was the whole purpose of the “bull” part, to charge at you like one.<br>
Now they won’t melee unless you put yourself in that range. It’s quite sad.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/did-we-really-need-all-of-these-base-combat-mechanic-changes/10600/76">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/did-we-really-need-all-of-these-base-combat-mechanic-changes/10600/76</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Nov 2012 21:29:43 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-10600-76</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/did-we-really-need-all-of-these-base-combat-mechanic-changes/10600.rss">did we really need all of these base combat mechanic changes?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>did we really need all of these base combat mechanic changes?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[SirEgon]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="skyace65">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/s/90ced4/40.png" class="avatar"> skyace65:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>A i cant code</p>
<p>B modifying a mod probobly isnt the best idea and could cause instability</p>
<p>C any changes i make to have it more like the original wont get carried over to deathmatch</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>A You don’t need to know how to code, you just need to know how to change numbers.</p>
<p>B Nothing wrong with modding a mod</p>
<p>C You’re completely right</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/did-we-really-need-all-of-these-base-combat-mechanic-changes/10600/75">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/did-we-really-need-all-of-these-base-combat-mechanic-changes/10600/75</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Nov 2012 18:30:30 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-10600-75</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/did-we-really-need-all-of-these-base-combat-mechanic-changes/10600.rss">did we really need all of these base combat mechanic changes?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>did we really need all of these base combat mechanic changes?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[RicheyEdwards]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Lance_of_Longinus">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/l/779978/40.png" class="avatar"> Lance_of_Longinus:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Actually that is incorrect, they will tail whip you if you get in melee range.<br>
I hope they code the charge attack in an update, I really missed that.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Ah see, I never even got close enough to know that they still do that. The only way they can effectively tail whip you is by charging you to get close enough in the first place, so I’d definitely like to see that added at some point.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/did-we-really-need-all-of-these-base-combat-mechanic-changes/10600/74">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/did-we-really-need-all-of-these-base-combat-mechanic-changes/10600/74</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 23 Sep 2012 17:22:04 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-10600-74</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/did-we-really-need-all-of-these-base-combat-mechanic-changes/10600.rss">did we really need all of these base combat mechanic changes?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>did we really need all of these base combat mechanic changes?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Lance_of_Longinus]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="RicheyEdwards">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/r/46a35a/40.png" class="avatar"> RicheyEdwards:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Again, I hope you’re joking. These things <span class="bbcode-i">only</span> spit now, the acid barely does any damage unless you somehow manage to let yourself get hit by every globule of it, and on top of that, it’s incredibly easy to dodge and down. I think the only time one of these hit me on my last playthrough was the one that’s directly behind you when you pop out of the pipe in Blast Pit, because I forgot he was there.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Actually that is incorrect, they will tail whip you if you get in melee range.<br>
I hope they code the charge attack in an update, I really missed that.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/did-we-really-need-all-of-these-base-combat-mechanic-changes/10600/73">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/did-we-really-need-all-of-these-base-combat-mechanic-changes/10600/73</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 23 Sep 2012 17:15:04 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-10600-73</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/did-we-really-need-all-of-these-base-combat-mechanic-changes/10600.rss">did we really need all of these base combat mechanic changes?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>did we really need all of these base combat mechanic changes?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[RicheyEdwards]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I really have no Earthly clue how you’ve come to some of the thoughts you have, so I’ll just go through them one by one.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="skyace65">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/s/90ced4/40.png" class="avatar"> skyace65:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>crowbar- well its now almost completely useless minus headcrabs. sucks against zombies with how they fight, barnacles your better off shooting if you get caught in one and even the houndeye cant be fought with it. houndeye especially is bugging me since it was never meant to be a hard enemy, just a low level one and as the game progresses you work your way up to harder ones.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>The crowbar is exactly how it’s always been. It’s great for headcrabs, zombies and barnacles - if you’re getting hit, that’s your fault. It’s fairly easy to kill dozens of these without taking a single hit. Houndeyes most certainly can be fought with it, even Vortigaunts, even on <span class="bbcode-i">Hard</span> - you’ll probably take a hit or two, but it kills them pretty fast. The Houndeye is fantastic now - it’s actually a threat. In the original it was little more than a nuisance; I love the change there.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="skyace65">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/s/90ced4/40.png" class="avatar"> skyace65:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>pistol- would have prefered HD texture pack style but ah well. also heavily nerfed, you need a lot more bullets now to kill most enemies severely weakening it, and using it would just waste ammo(i’ll explain latter)</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I much prefer the glock, myself. It hasn’t been nerfed at all. It’s still has absolutely dead-on accuracy and downs most things with but a few headshots.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="skyace65">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/s/90ced4/40.png" class="avatar"> skyace65:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>m4- cant really tell that much power difference but it was nerfed to hell with ammo. now only supports 150 bullets which makes sharing ammo with the pistol a complete pain, wouldn’t be so bad if you didn’t have to use the pistol for all the enemies the crowbar would normally handle. the actual magazine size has also been reduced to a mere 30 bullets which is useless for storming a bunch of enemies at once, kill one marine, head back reload, kill another wash rinse and repeat. its so annoying and breaks combat, its just not fun at all</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I can see your point here but I prefer the change, personally. I only tend to use it for long-range engagements, so the smaller clip size isn’t really a problem for me. I’m not a gun nut, but I don’t believe a 50-round magazine for an MP5 is standard. Regardless, if you’re charging into rooms unloading clips into HECU legs/chests, that there is your problem. It’s still more than capable of popping heads.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="skyace65">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/s/90ced4/40.png" class="avatar"> skyace65:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>zombies- harder to kill, and will more often than not hit you if you try and melee them.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Simply not true. If you’re getting hit whilst meleeing them, you’re getting greedy with your swings.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="skyace65">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/s/90ced4/40.png" class="avatar"> skyace65:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>houndeye- way more powerful than it should be and its even worse since it now shakes up player vision.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Like I said, I think the Houndeye buff actually benefits the experience - especially the fact that they now attack in packs. It’s turned a fairly meek, pointless enemy into a real threat and I love that. I don’t want <span class="bbcode-i">any</span> hostile alien creature to feel like it’s merely there for show during the early levels.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="skyace65">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/s/90ced4/40.png" class="avatar"> skyace65:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>barnacles- harder to kill with pistol and crowbar</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Pistol, I actually agree. They are a bit too much of a bullet sponge for my liking. But they’re still easy to crowbar.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="skyace65">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/s/90ced4/40.png" class="avatar"> skyace65:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>vortigaunts- much shorter charge time and its annoying as hell since it also obstructs your vission. and on a side note who thought it was a good idea to give them a crotch piece?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I hope you’re joking. These guys have been nerfed into oblivion. They do something pitiful like 10 damage per hit, even on Hard. Only their first shot is somewhat of a challenge to dodge (and even then, it’s quite easy if you’re right next to cover,) and then you can pop them before they get another chance because they die so fast. And the crotch piece is a part of their slave chains get up, just so you know.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="skyace65">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/s/90ced4/40.png" class="avatar"> skyace65:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>the tentacle mouthed thing- i absolutely hate this enemy now, its not that its hard to kill its the way it does the damage, instead of the normal spit thing it now lobes acid in your direction which is extremely annoying and has far to much of a range.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Again, I hope you’re joking. These things <span class="bbcode-i">only</span> spit now, the acid barely does any damage unless you somehow manage to let yourself get hit by every globule of it, and on top of that, it’s incredibly easy to dodge and down. I think the only time one of these hit me on my last playthrough was the one that’s directly behind you when you pop out of the pipe in Blast Pit, because I forgot he was there.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/did-we-really-need-all-of-these-base-combat-mechanic-changes/10600/72">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/did-we-really-need-all-of-these-base-combat-mechanic-changes/10600/72</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 23 Sep 2012 14:17:18 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-10600-72</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/did-we-really-need-all-of-these-base-combat-mechanic-changes/10600.rss">did we really need all of these base combat mechanic changes?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>did we really need all of these base combat mechanic changes?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Bloodshot]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Lumbergh">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/l/51bf81/40.png" class="avatar"> Lumbergh:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I dislike the saving excuse as well. I’ve found that with each death and quick load, while I’m more likely to improve my tactics based on the meta-gamed knowledge gained (which is itself a problem - Gordon wouldn’t get any do-overs), I’m less likely to execute them well because I’m irritated, and I feel dramatically less like Gordon Freeman in Black Mesa than than a guy hammering on a keyboard and angrily staring at a computer screen. Buzz-kill. When it goes on too long, it inevitably ends with rage-quitting.</p>
<p>So yeah, it’s not like your game’s over when you die, thanks to saves, but your immersion level goes down the toilet by about the tenth time in a row. Hate that.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I’m not trying to be mean, but that’s what easy is for. Hell, look at a game like Deus Ex - Human revolution - they TELL you the easy difficulty is for people who want to experience the narrative. Some enemies on normal could be tweaked a little though.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/did-we-really-need-all-of-these-base-combat-mechanic-changes/10600/71">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/did-we-really-need-all-of-these-base-combat-mechanic-changes/10600/71</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 23 Sep 2012 03:59:24 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-10600-71</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/did-we-really-need-all-of-these-base-combat-mechanic-changes/10600.rss">did we really need all of these base combat mechanic changes?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>did we really need all of these base combat mechanic changes?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[YouKnow]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Wildfire">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/w/e99b99/40.png" class="avatar"> Wildfire:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I am of the view that it is unforgiving when a <em>single</em> encounter, badly handled, will kill you.  Certainly if you continously handle encounters badly you should die - but arranging the game so a <em>single</em> badly handled encounter kills you means the player is required to be perfect or nearly perfect in his play.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Perfection is only required of the player if they want to beat the game without dying, which seems fitting to me.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Wildfire">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/w/e99b99/40.png" class="avatar"> Wildfire:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>With regard to quicksaves, saving is a mechanism outside the game narrative.  It should not be used to compensate for the game being unforgiving, because it takes the user out of the game.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I don’t see what narrative has to do with anything.  I see saving as a gameplay mechanic, personally.  I don’t see how it takes one out of the game, considering it’s part of the game, but if you’re really worried about death breaking narrative immersion, you can always play on easy, and if that fails, there’s god mode.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Wildfire">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/w/e99b99/40.png" class="avatar"> Wildfire:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Perhaps games should be balanced such that saving isn’t <em>quite</em> necessary.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I’d consider dying part of the game and therefore saving a necessity.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/did-we-really-need-all-of-these-base-combat-mechanic-changes/10600/70">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/did-we-really-need-all-of-these-base-combat-mechanic-changes/10600/70</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 23 Sep 2012 03:33:59 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-10600-70</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/did-we-really-need-all-of-these-base-combat-mechanic-changes/10600.rss">did we really need all of these base combat mechanic changes?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>did we really need all of these base combat mechanic changes?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Lumbergh]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I dislike the saving excuse as well. I’ve found that with each death and quick load, while I’m more likely to improve my tactics based on the meta-gamed knowledge gained (which is itself a problem - Gordon wouldn’t get any do-overs), I’m less likely to execute them well because I’m irritated, and I feel dramatically less like Gordon Freeman in Black Mesa than than a guy hammering on a keyboard and angrily staring at a computer screen. Buzz-kill. When it goes on too long, it inevitably ends with rage-quitting.</p>
<p>So yeah, it’s not like your game’s over when you die, thanks to saves, but your immersion level goes down the toilet by about the tenth time in a row. Hate that.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/did-we-really-need-all-of-these-base-combat-mechanic-changes/10600/69">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/did-we-really-need-all-of-these-base-combat-mechanic-changes/10600/69</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 22 Sep 2012 16:15:44 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-10600-69</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/did-we-really-need-all-of-these-base-combat-mechanic-changes/10600.rss">did we really need all of these base combat mechanic changes?</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
