<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Online cheaters</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/online-cheaters/14874</link>
    <description>I&#39;ve been playing HL1 (and the series as a whole) for a LONG time. We still play HL1 and Opposing Force on LAN regularly, simply because shooting each other with crazy weapons over and over is some of the best gaming fun around.

I love BM, and recently tried the online gameplay. The maps are great, the gameplay is different and slower, but still awesome.

However, there are cheaters around that mess up the entire game. First because there arent many servers, but second because there seems to be nothing stopping them. What the hell guys? The anti cheater security does nothing, and there&#39;s no way of voting someone out...

That&#39;s not normal, and pretty unacceptable these days.

Just thought I&#39;d mention it, in case nobody knew about it.


FIx it.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 26 Jul 2016 22:11:58 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>The Cafeteria</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/online-cheaters/14874.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Online cheaters</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[_RLS_Flow]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Spiffmeister">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/s/f04885/40.png" class="avatar"> Spiffmeister:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>This is interesting! Especially since I didn’t mention any name of anyone cheating. Luckily, situations like these usually sort themselves out.</p>
<p>It’s all about choices, I think.</p>
<p>Banned accounts are public, because the cheater got busted. That’s not a choice. It’s bad form to act like it is.<br>
Going of the defensive with a huge “rage” rant refusing to reply to rage with some incoherent arguments demanding a discussion with arguments is not even a choice either. It’s being pushed into a corner after being busted whilst cheating. Not a choice.</p>
<p>What IS a choice, is calling people autist and dumb. Bad form when you want a serious discussion.<br>
What IS a choice is messing up a good game with bad play. Bad form when you apparently do care about the game and see the need for improvement.<br>
What IS a choice, is calling virtual accounts “kids”, thereby trying to discredit their statements, a method already used by the ancient Romans. Bad form when you want to be taken seriously yourself.</p>
<p>Just my thoughts.</p>
<p>I hope the accused cheater gets a right spanking and loses his favourite PJ’s when there is proof, or that he helps make the game better if there isn’t proof. EIther way, hopefully the game benefits!</p>
<p>In any case, I did my part. <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=9" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>v952 explained his position so that is the end of that. Also when it comes to the game benefiting this part may actually be true. v952 already attempted to contact the developer team to fix many of the multiplayer bugs (for example the game not calling SupressHostEvents properly resulting in double sound effects on high latency servers).</p>
<p>Also to further improve this thread I would advice people not to childishly call out other players for cheating without any kind of evidence. Keep the community friendly, would you?. Thanks in advance.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/online-cheaters/14874/16">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/online-cheaters/14874/16</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jul 2016 22:11:58 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14874-16</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/online-cheaters/14874.rss">Online cheaters</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Online cheaters</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Spiffmeister]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>This is interesting! Especially since I didn’t mention any name of anyone cheating. Luckily, situations like these usually sort themselves out.</p>
<p>It’s all about choices, I think.</p>
<p>Banned accounts are public, because the cheater got busted. That’s not a choice. It’s bad form to act like it is.<br>
Going of the defensive with a huge “rage” rant refusing to reply to rage with some incoherent arguments demanding a discussion with arguments is not even a choice either. It’s being pushed into a corner after being busted whilst cheating. Not a choice.</p>
<p>What IS a choice, is calling people autist and dumb. Bad form when you want a serious discussion.<br>
What IS a choice is messing up a good game with bad play. Bad form when you apparently do care about the game and see the need for improvement.<br>
What IS a choice, is calling virtual accounts “kids”, thereby trying to discredit their statements, a method already used by the ancient Romans. Bad form when you want to be taken seriously yourself.</p>
<p>Just my thoughts.</p>
<p>I hope the accused cheater gets a right spanking and loses his favourite PJ’s when there is proof, or that he helps make the game better if there isn’t proof. EIther way, hopefully the game benefits!</p>
<p>In any case, I did my part. <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=9" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/online-cheaters/14874/15">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/online-cheaters/14874/15</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 25 Jul 2016 17:58:54 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14874-15</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/online-cheaters/14874.rss">Online cheaters</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Online cheaters</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[_RLS_Flow]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Van.Hallgate">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/user_avatar/leakfree.org/van.hallgate/40/4991_2.png" class="avatar"> Van.Hallgate:</div>
<blockquote>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="&quot;[RLS">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 "[RLS:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Flow"]Well I don’t know why people in this thread blaming v952 or me for cheating, If you think you have some proof, bring it up now.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I believe I don’t use specific nick or server name, and I do believe that we play “normal” a few times together (even few seconds ago).The main subject is that the problem exists, and the question - is it possible to stop it, or fix it somehow?<br>
Maybe some other gamers will provide more info, some specific data, anything, or they will just share this thread with others, that thinks the same, give some suggestions, that will help the devs.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Well you see there is a problem, The devs aren’t giving much love to the multiplayer currently and there are a large amount of bugs from clientside prediction to just your viewmodel disappearing (also spectators weapons showing), These bugs should be the first thing to be fixed.</p>
<p>Also the game advertises itself as being VAC protected and that may or may not be enough to stop most of the cheaters. However from personal experience I have not seen any cheaters in this game.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/online-cheaters/14874/14">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/online-cheaters/14874/14</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 24 Jul 2016 18:49:05 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14874-14</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/online-cheaters/14874.rss">Online cheaters</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Online cheaters</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Van.Hallgate]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="&quot;[RLS">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 "[RLS:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Flow"]Well I don’t know why people in this thread blaming v952 or me for cheating, If you think you have some proof, bring it up now.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I believe I don’t use specific nick or server name, and I do believe that we play “normal” a few times together (even few seconds ago).<br>
The main subject is that the problem exists, and the question - is it possible to stop it, or fix it somehow?<br>
Maybe some other gamers will provide more info, some specific data, anything, or they will just share this thread with others, that thinks the same, give some suggestions, that will help the devs.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/online-cheaters/14874/13">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/online-cheaters/14874/13</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 24 Jul 2016 18:37:18 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14874-13</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/online-cheaters/14874.rss">Online cheaters</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Online cheaters</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[_RLS_Flow]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Well I don’t know why people in this thread blaming v952 or me for cheating, If you think you have some proof, bring it up now.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/online-cheaters/14874/12">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/online-cheaters/14874/12</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 24 Jul 2016 17:42:26 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14874-12</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/online-cheaters/14874.rss">Online cheaters</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Online cheaters</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[_RLS_Flow]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="RedEye">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/user_avatar/leakfree.org/redeye/40/4899_2.png" class="avatar"> RedEye:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Did you just create an account to shill for a blatant cheater broadcast? That’s some dedication…<br>
pass</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>“Yes he is cheating! but I wont watch him play because I already can tell from him killing me he is cheating!”<br>
Is this really the level we are at ? Like I dont know if you have personally some butthurt or just jumping on the bandwagon but<br>
you really should construct some argument to why you think he (v952) is cheating.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/online-cheaters/14874/11">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/online-cheaters/14874/11</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 24 Jul 2016 17:32:40 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14874-11</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/online-cheaters/14874.rss">Online cheaters</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Online cheaters</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[AsinoEsel]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I don’t think we just accuse anyone for cheating without proof. I am not denying that there may be cheaters in Black Mesa, but come on, if I were a script kiddie wanting to test out my new 1337 hax I would most definitely not use them in Black Mesa… <strong>If</strong> there are cheaters in Black Mesa, that’s sad (even sadder than in other games).<br>
I’m curious to see how this develops.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/online-cheaters/14874/10">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/online-cheaters/14874/10</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 24 Jul 2016 17:31:24 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14874-10</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/online-cheaters/14874.rss">Online cheaters</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Online cheaters</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Van.Hallgate]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I can tell that this is true (what Spiffmeister said), there is one public server with few gamers online, and whole clan - I believe they run this server - they have it with some tweaks.<br>
I doesn’t matter if some guy broadcasting it, if server have some “upgrades” for clan.<br>
This is really hard to achieve to kill them, even when few gamers are against one of them. The latency is ok (almost the same for all players), so it’s not the thing.<br>
For now it’s a problem, because not so much players play online (public servers), and if you do - you will sooner or later get on their server, and get mad.<br>
For me now it’s a challenge, but first I was suprised, and I see quite a few people, that just quit becouse of that.<br>
It will be such a shame to see only empty servers because of this kind of cheating.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/online-cheaters/14874/9">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/online-cheaters/14874/9</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 24 Jul 2016 17:28:11 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14874-9</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/online-cheaters/14874.rss">Online cheaters</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Online cheaters</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[RedEye]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Did you just create an account to shill for a blatant cheater broadcast? That’s some dedication…<br>
pass</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/online-cheaters/14874/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/online-cheaters/14874/8</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 24 Jul 2016 17:13:06 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14874-8</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/online-cheaters/14874.rss">Online cheaters</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Online cheaters</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[_RLS_Flow]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>This thread indeed got interesting, I think however I will wait until some proof of any cheating will appear.<br>
If you are butthurting because of V952 reking you, as said, you can join his broadcast.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/online-cheaters/14874/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/online-cheaters/14874/7</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 24 Jul 2016 17:05:19 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14874-7</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/online-cheaters/14874.rss">Online cheaters</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Online cheaters</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[AsinoEsel]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Did you just create an account just to reply to this thread? That’s some dedication…<br>
Secondly, why are you saying “you guys”? Am I being talked to? I’m confused.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/online-cheaters/14874/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/online-cheaters/14874/6</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 24 Jul 2016 17:03:57 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14874-6</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/online-cheaters/14874.rss">Online cheaters</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Online cheaters</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[RedEye]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>This thread just got interesting.<br>
A vac banned cheaters says he has another account, or 2 or 4. ( I bet the cheater only has one other account, wink)<br>
A proven cheater says he is not going to reply to rage and then does just the opposite with a reply.</p>
<p>grabs popcorn</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/online-cheaters/14874/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/online-cheaters/14874/5</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 24 Jul 2016 16:22:30 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14874-5</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/online-cheaters/14874.rss">Online cheaters</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Online cheaters</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[_RLS_V952]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Wow, you guys are… so-so… I really don’t wanna sound rude, but if it’s hard for you to press WASD, scroll mwheel for bunny hopping and placing the mouse crosshair over the enemy - you’re autistic. Moreover, these kids are too slow and it’s extremely hard NOT to hit them. It’s like there’re 3 standing still players, I’m killing all of them, and they call me a cheater. WOW. SO HARD TO HIT STANDING STILL PLAYERS!</p>
<p>Btw, don’t wanna call you dumb (not you guys exactly, I’m referencing this to all kids who rage when getting killed), but you can’t even type “status”, browse steam profile and READ. You must be 1st grade pupil, if you can’t read. It’s clearly saying why and where I have a VAC ban. It’s not a secret, you know. Therefore, I play with my secondary account because dumb United Gamers sourcemod plugin kick players if they have a VAC ban, and most of the time it’s the only server with players.</p>
<p>Funny thing is that I do public broadcasts! These kids know about that, BUT they don’t join it because AFRAID to see no cheats on screen! How bad is that? It just pisses me off, because it proofs that humanity will not invent AI during near 200 years.</p>
<p>P.S.: How dare people who camp the only spot for 10 minutes and then randomly die to their own tripmines can call somebody a cheater?<br>
P.P.S.: I don’t want to create holywar here, and I excuse for every offended person, but in my opinion UG is retarded since they make such beautiful game as BMS look silly by adding some one-textured killboxes. They can’t make HQ maps, but want to show off and just keep on pasting some shit on their servers. One one hand, some people have slow PCs and can’t afford themselves playing on stock maps (because of detail level), on the other hand if your PC isn’t fast enough to run BMS - why do you even play it? That’s just not clear enough for me.<br>
P.P.P.S.: I’m not going to reply to rage. If you wanna have some constructive talking right here - make arguments. You have no arguments to blame me as cheater.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/online-cheaters/14874/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/online-cheaters/14874/4</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 24 Jul 2016 15:44:02 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14874-4</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/online-cheaters/14874.rss">Online cheaters</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Online cheaters</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Spiffmeister]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Like I said, I’ve been gaming for a long time <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=9" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"> I’ve been playing online and over LAN for the better part of 2 decades.  I’m not just a rager, spotting cheaters is second nature.</p>
<p>Absurd reaction times, instakills and pretty much only instakills, or instead of taking my word for it, you can just go online right now and see for yourself. There’s only 1 server online and it’s always ruined by the same player, who has multiple banned accounts for cheating and just makes new ones.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/online-cheaters/14874/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/online-cheaters/14874/3</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 23 Jul 2016 09:52:59 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14874-3</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/online-cheaters/14874.rss">Online cheaters</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Online cheaters</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[AsinoEsel]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I haven’t encountered a single cheater in Black Mesa…<br>
I know, this may sound silly, but are you absolutely sure the player in question was cheating? Did he just blatantly aimbot everyone?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/online-cheaters/14874/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/online-cheaters/14874/2</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jul 2016 16:15:38 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14874-2</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/online-cheaters/14874.rss">Online cheaters</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Online cheaters</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Spiffmeister]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I’ve been playing HL1 (and the series as a whole) for a LONG time. We still play HL1 and Opposing Force on LAN regularly, simply because shooting each other with crazy weapons over and over is some of the best gaming fun around.</p>
<p>I love BM, and recently tried the online gameplay. The maps are great, the gameplay is different and slower, but still awesome.</p>
<p>However, there are cheaters around that mess up the entire game. First because there arent many servers, but second because there seems to be nothing stopping them. What the hell guys? The anti cheater security does nothing, and there’s no way of voting someone out…</p>
<p>That’s not normal, and pretty unacceptable these days.</p>
<p>Just thought I’d mention it, in case nobody knew about it.</p>
<p>FIx it.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/online-cheaters/14874/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/online-cheaters/14874/1</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jul 2016 15:56:11 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14874-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/online-cheaters/14874.rss">Online cheaters</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
