<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:discourse="http://www.discourse.org/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>General Development - Leakfree</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/c/general-development/7</link>
    <description>Topics in the &#39;General Development&#39; category General Source Engine discussions &amp;amp; questions.</description>
    
      <lastBuildDate>Mon, 27 Jul 2020 16:55:05 +0000</lastBuildDate>
      <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/c/general-development/7.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
        <item>
          <title>Does anyone have the VMFs for the Xen levels?</title>
          <dc:creator><![CDATA[Macclutcheon]]></dc:creator>
          <category>Black Mesa</category>
          <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Not sure if this is the right place to post this, but I’m not sure where else to ask. I’m trying to make a mod and I need the VMFs for every level of the game. I have the earthbound levels (someone had them up for download), but I can’t find the Xen ones. I would decompile them myself but I haven’t been able to get BSPSource working for some reason (will try fighting with it more later if I have to), and I even tried rolling back to the public beta version to get the VMFs but I can’t seem to find them.</p>
<p>Like I said, someone had put up the earthbound levels files in a repository online, so I was wondering if anyone might know where I could get the ones for the Xen levels. Whether that’s a direct download of the VMFs, or tips on how to find the files, I don’t care.</p>
            <p><small>2 posts - 2 participants</small></p>
            <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/does-anyone-have-the-vmfs-for-the-xen-levels/63373">Read full topic</a></p>
          ]]></description>
          <link>https://leakfree.org/t/does-anyone-have-the-vmfs-for-the-xen-levels/63373</link>
          <pubDate>Mon, 27 Jul 2020 16:55:05 +0000</pubDate>
          <discourse:topicPinned>No</discourse:topicPinned>
          <discourse:topicClosed>No</discourse:topicClosed>
          <discourse:topicArchived>No</discourse:topicArchived>
          <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-topic-63373</guid>
          <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/does-anyone-have-the-vmfs-for-the-xen-levels/63373.rss">Does anyone have the VMFs for the Xen levels?</source>
        </item>
        <item>
          <title>How to get models from bms</title>
          <dc:creator><![CDATA[phys]]></dc:creator>
          <category>Black Mesa</category>
          <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Hi!<br>
I’m currently trying to get the v_hands.mdl model from bms for a gmod addon.<br>
If anyone could help me that’d be great!</p>
<p>At the moment I current have the model in hlmv.<br>
<div class="lightbox-wrapper"><a class="lightbox" href="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/original/2X/c/cdd62d2aa8afd8663c35c1bfc9b72fa051cf4373.jpeg" data-download-href="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/cdd62d2aa8afd8663c35c1bfc9b72fa051cf4373" title="image"><img src="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/original/2X/c/cdd62d2aa8afd8663c35c1bfc9b72fa051cf4373.jpeg" alt="image" data-base62-sha1="tmUKDXHXa90G2Q8Ta0WTqpcdRGX" width="453" height="500" data-small-upload="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/optimized/2X/c/cdd62d2aa8afd8663c35c1bfc9b72fa051cf4373_2_10x10.png"><div class="meta"><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-far-image svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#far-image"></use></svg><span class="filename">image</span><span class="informations">483×533 53.8 KB</span><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-discourse-expand svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#discourse-expand"></use></svg></div></a></div></p>
            <p><small>2 posts - 2 participants</small></p>
            <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/how-to-get-models-from-bms/63349">Read full topic</a></p>
          ]]></description>
          <link>https://leakfree.org/t/how-to-get-models-from-bms/63349</link>
          <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jul 2020 01:00:51 +0000</pubDate>
          <discourse:topicPinned>No</discourse:topicPinned>
          <discourse:topicClosed>No</discourse:topicClosed>
          <discourse:topicArchived>No</discourse:topicArchived>
          <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-topic-63349</guid>
          <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/how-to-get-models-from-bms/63349.rss">How to get models from bms</source>
        </item>
        <item>
          <title>Interloper Restoration Project</title>
          <dc:creator><![CDATA[Open_Source_Forever]]></dc:creator>
          <category>General Development</category>
          <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Hi. New at mapping here. I’m thinking of adding the 2 missing tentacle nests to Interloper. I was wondering if you guys would be able to tell me what area of BMS’ interpretation of the chapter best corresponds to where those 2 nests were in the original game, so I know where to put them? The other missing part (the Manta Puzzle section) will be added at a later date.</p>
            <p><small>2 posts - 2 participants</small></p>
            <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/interloper-restoration-project/63321">Read full topic</a></p>
          ]]></description>
          <link>https://leakfree.org/t/interloper-restoration-project/63321</link>
          <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jun 2020 07:12:16 +0000</pubDate>
          <discourse:topicPinned>No</discourse:topicPinned>
          <discourse:topicClosed>No</discourse:topicClosed>
          <discourse:topicArchived>No</discourse:topicArchived>
          <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-topic-63321</guid>
          <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/interloper-restoration-project/63321.rss">Interloper Restoration Project</source>
        </item>
        <item>
          <title>Custom choreography problem</title>
          <dc:creator><![CDATA[freemon]]></dc:creator>
          <category>Source 1</category>
          <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Hello guys,</p>
<p>I made a custom .vcd choreography with Faceposer (the one in SFM).<br>
Everything works right inside Faceposer : gestures, speech and lipsinc.<br>
Rebuilding scenes.image seems to works well too.</p>
<p>My next step is to make it works in-game using Hammer.<br>
For that, i use 3 entities :</p>
<ul>
<li>logic_choreographed_scene (the custom choreography itself)</li>
<li>npc_citizen (which plays the custom choreography)</li>
<li>func_button (which fire the choreography to be played by the npc_citizen)</li>
</ul>
<p>BUT, in-game, after compiling my map, and when pressing the button : the choreography doesn’t play.<br>
Instead i have an error that says that my custom .vcd is missing from scenes.image.</p>
<p>I have tryed many things, and it’s still not working…<br>
Do you guys have an idea of what’s going on ?<br>
I know there is a trick or a workaround, but actually i’m stuck.</p>
<p>Any help would be appreciated</p>
<p>Thanks</p>
            <p><small>3 posts - 2 participants</small></p>
            <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/custom-choreography-problem/63249">Read full topic</a></p>
          ]]></description>
          <link>https://leakfree.org/t/custom-choreography-problem/63249</link>
          <pubDate>Tue, 12 May 2020 22:42:03 +0000</pubDate>
          <discourse:topicPinned>No</discourse:topicPinned>
          <discourse:topicClosed>No</discourse:topicClosed>
          <discourse:topicArchived>No</discourse:topicArchived>
          <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-topic-63249</guid>
          <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/custom-choreography-problem/63249.rss">Custom choreography problem</source>
        </item>
        <item>
          <title>Uploading mod creates blank workshop item?</title>
          <dc:creator><![CDATA[digivee]]></dc:creator>
          <category>General Development</category>
          <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I’ve tried uploading two different mods now, and both of them create blank 0.000 MB workshop items.</p>
<p>I’m following the tutorials to the best of my ability, the item seems to hang at 25%, where the program claims I have unsaved changes and asks if I wish to discard them.</p>
<p>What the workshop looks like<br>
<img src="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/original/2X/7/7aa49a539fafef5dd950751284775f372109dafa.png" alt="" data-base62-sha1="huWUveb5dF13MSi12PZZgvSZlay" width="576" height="286"></p>
<p>the warning I get<br>
<div class="lightbox-wrapper"><a class="lightbox" href="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/original/2X/3/30cc444365543bfd9e3fb45e9336c8a8da6ac383.png" data-download-href="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/30cc444365543bfd9e3fb45e9336c8a8da6ac383" title=""><img src="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/original/2X/3/30cc444365543bfd9e3fb45e9336c8a8da6ac383.png" alt="" data-base62-sha1="6XGyArzI6dvlFgRFaYNQui8R2L1" width="666" height="500" data-small-upload="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/optimized/2X/3/30cc444365543bfd9e3fb45e9336c8a8da6ac383_2_10x10.png"><div class="meta"><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-far-image svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#far-image"></use></svg><span class="filename"></span><span class="informations">1024×768 8.33 KB</span><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-discourse-expand svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#discourse-expand"></use></svg></div></a></div></p>
            <p><small>1 post - 1 participant</small></p>
            <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/uploading-mod-creates-blank-workshop-item/62995">Read full topic</a></p>
          ]]></description>
          <link>https://leakfree.org/t/uploading-mod-creates-blank-workshop-item/62995</link>
          <pubDate>Fri, 13 Mar 2020 22:55:52 +0000</pubDate>
          <discourse:topicPinned>No</discourse:topicPinned>
          <discourse:topicClosed>No</discourse:topicClosed>
          <discourse:topicArchived>No</discourse:topicArchived>
          <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-topic-62995</guid>
          <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/uploading-mod-creates-blank-workshop-item/62995.rss">Uploading mod creates blank workshop item?</source>
        </item>
        <item>
          <title>My Outline For An Opposing Force Remake</title>
          <dc:creator><![CDATA[Admiral_Sakai]]></dc:creator>
          <category>Source 1</category>
          <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Got to thinking about how Opposing Force could be updated and expanded for Black Mesa a while back as part of a conversation I had with <a class="mention" href="/u/tjhl">@TJHL</a>, and this was the end result of it. It’s certainly not something I intend to seriously <em>make</em>, although if I end up releasing one-off Opposing Force levels I will certainly be making them with this in mind; it’s more meant to spur discussion of what an Opposing Force BM remake would actually be like as a more interpretive project instead of rotely recreating the original levels with HD textures, and show that such an exercise could indeed be possible and produce good results. I’m not actively recruiting people to make this become a reality, although if somebody like HECU Collective or Tripmine Studios looked at it and took some of its ideas to heart I wouldn’t exactly be unhappy.</p>
<p>This writeup is more focused on story and the thematic progression of maps than on gameplay and environmental details, simply because those are the elements that are more relevant on the full-game scale, although I won’t hesitate to bring up smaller details if I think they are particularly important or interesting.</p>
<p>In terms of changes to overall lore, while I am generally operating under my theories that the military was not sent in to cover up the existence of the BMRF and that there is no specific reason for the Black Ops to exist, I don’t think I will be going out of my way to state that to be the case in this hypothetical game, so I think it’s safe to ignore both statements (it’s actually really easy to switch between regular Marines and Black Ops without changing the story or gameplay, which is one of the reasons I find them superfluous).</p>
<p>The one thing that probably <em>is</em> worth mentioning is that I am operating under the assumption that Shepard and his squad are better-trained and better-equipped than the regular Marines, which is why he can navigate the place alone and prevail against hordes of Xenians when even large squads of other troops are at serious risk of getting wiped out by those same enemies. I personally think that this is because only Shepard and his squad are HECU and the other Marines are just Marines, but that again is unlikely to come up directly in-game.</p>
<p>I <em>am</em> assuming, because it would be hard to make an Opposing Force remake without them, that Race X enemies would be available to put in the game even though there is currently no implementation of them in Black Mesa. The first place I would look to try to create them would be to re-model old HL2 enemies like antlions that might still exist in the BM code, but even that’s a longshot.</p>
<p>So, without further ado, let’s begin with</p>
<p><strong>Welcome to Black Mesa</strong></p>
<details>
<summary>
(Show)</summary>
<p>Most of what I would change in the first part of this chapter are relatively nitpicky things. I’d like to make it more clear that the facility Shepard wakes up in is in fact Black Mesa’s dedicated on-site hospital wing, and make it clearer that the random “SCIENCE!!!” hazards that make up much of the early gameplay are due to medical equipment of various kinds.</p>
<p>One issue is the dialogue where a scientist says there’s a rumor going around that the military isn’t actually here to rescue anyone. Given that this is taking place during Day 2 of the disaster, during roughly the same period as Surface Tension or Questionable Ethics at the absolute earliest, one would think that the military’s motives would be better known by that point. It would of course be possible to just cut that dialogue out, but then that leaves the question of why the scientists are helping Shepard’s squad at <em>all</em> and haven’t even, like, restrained him. I think the best option would be to have some of the other soldiers already up and around and having talked with the scientists and agreed to help them. Shepard in particular I think should be tasked with going somewhere and doing something, the others having been too injured to do so immediately. What that <em>is</em> is not strictly necessary to the game progression, really, but I am sort of thinking it has to do with that big chemical plant later in the level (see below)- either it’s in danger of leaking and directly threatening the safe area in the clinic, or whatever hazard it produces is blocking everyone’s escape route. I think this objective is first given in the hospital itself, then the radio near the crash site adds urgency to it because evac orders are coming in and everyone at the hospital is still stuck.</p>
<p>Given how late in the invasion this is, I think there should also be more obvious signs of fighting outside the immediate area of the hospital wing- no close interaction with other soldiers or NPCs, but a lot of frenetic background action and destruction. Inside the clinic it should be clear everyone knows it’s a mess, with scientists gathering around the windows looking at the chaos. Perhaps they know they can’t stay here for long and that’s why Shepard has to go to the chemical plant? Perhaps background combat noise in the radio transmission at the crash site indicates the Xenians have indeed found the survivors and that route needs to be cleared RITE NAO?</p>
<p>The other big thing first introduced in this level is that “Shepard’s squad” (the only friendly military encountered in the game) is made of specific soldiers with different models, and these soldiers are <em>persistent</em> through the use of env_globals. While some are “found” for specific scenes so there’s always enough to dispense plot-critical dialogue and some are “lost” or “killed” offscreen so there is never an unmanageable crowd of them, there is a buffer zone of a few who will appear later on <em>if and only if</em> they didn’t get killed in their previous appearance. Some of these soldiers are the ones who appear in the hospital.</p>
<p>Finally, I would like to establish that the random industrial area explored in the second half of the level which connects to the tram tunnels is either a chemical weapons decommissioning facility, a chemical weapons <em>development</em> facility, or a chemical weapons development facility concealed <em>within</em> a decommissioning facility. This provides a purpose and identity for the area, allows it to plausibly threaten or obstruct the movement of the people in the hospital wing, and makes an early hint that all is not kosher at BMRF as far as its actual operations go.</p>
<p>I think the level should end with Shepard succeeding in whatever it was he needed to do to clear the way, but getting cut off from the way back. Perhaps this is where the instruction to try to link up through the transit system comes?</p>
</details>
<p><strong>"We Are Pulling Out"</strong></p>
<details>
<summary>
(Show)</summary>
<p>Not much to say about the tram-platform portion of this level other than that I was specifically thinking of the scene where Race X were first introduced when I created the control room in pd_c2a4h: I think those are in fact one and the same area.</p>
<p>In the original game the “we are pulling out” dialogue just cuts off, but in BM it ends with “Oh shit, no! Nononono! -explosion-”. That seems an odd thing to say to Xenians, so perhaps the speaker was killed or at least chased off by accidental friendly fire?</p>
<p>I actually have no strong feelings on what to do with the “where’s Freeman” scene; if these were Shepard’s squad I’d probably cut it out since the whole point of them is that they’re the only military <em>not</em> hostile to the scientists, but these are I think the only time Shepard really interacts with Marines who are <em>not</em> part of his squad, so it could go either way.</p>
<p>One thing I <em>would</em> like to see is for the Osprey that G-Man prevents Shepard from boarding to be shot down or crash not long after, indicating that G-Man had reason for preventing Shepard from getting on it.</p>
</details>
<p><strong>Missing In Action</strong></p>
<details>
<summary>
(Show)</summary>
<p>Not a fan of the area with the flame jets and exploding boxes as I thought it served little purpose aside from adding additional length to the level.</p>
<p>In fact, a <em>lot</em> of this chapter is kind of pointless. Not every chapter needs to be particularly story-rich, but those that aren’t should at least be aesthetically or mechanically distinct or have some kind of major setpiece in them or something?</p>
<p>I discuss a possible different structure for it <a href="https://forums.blackmesasource.com/t/fiddling-around-with-missing-in-action/15263" rel="nofollow noopener">here</a> although that’s more gameplay  and small-scale design than story.</p>
<p>Pit drones are first introduced in this chapter so maybe we could do something with that? Or the fact that this is contemporaneous with Forget About Freeman or early in Lambda Core and so the military should be getting its ass handed to it?</p>
</details>
<p><strong>Friendly Fire</strong></p>
<details>
<summary>
(Show)</summary>
<p>I’d like to change the way that the (Black Ops / regular Marines; let’s just call them Bad Guys)  are introduced in this chapter. Instead of the conversation over the nuke being the first encounter with them, I’d like for the friendly soldiers to come charging out of the building you were stuck in in Missing In Action, along <em>with</em> the two scientists encountered in the level (maybe make a neat setpiece of this with them having to push through a big alien onslaught) and towards a Bad Guy emplacement, still thinking the Bad Guys are friendly; then they get gunned down as they gape in confusion.</p>
<p>After that, it’s just a matter of pushing through a Bad Guy held area to get underground and escape the bombing.</p>
<p>Actually, now that I think about it, knowing that this entrance to the lower levels of the complex is <em>there</em>, and that there are supposedly friendly forces holed up inside of it, and the threat of getting wiped out by airstrikes, might make a good motivation for Missing In Action. If so I’d want to really play up the severity and threat of the strikes, and make them a much bigger threat than the aliens in that level. It even makes sense that the scientists found would be pointing that area out- even if Shepard’s guys don’t know what that <em>means</em>, it does after all lead into the Lambda Complex.</p>
</details>
<p><strong>We Are Not Alone</strong></p>
<details>
<summary>
(Show)</summary>
<p>I have… some problems with this chapter.</p>
<p>For one thing, the timing is a little off in that it feels like Shepard is going faster through the relatively small Friendly Fire and Missing In Action chapters than Freeman goes through Forget About Freeman and the much larger Lambda Core.</p>
<p>For another, I feel like Xen in general is ‘cheapened’ with overuse in small, insignificant levels, and characters should not be jumping in and out of it willy-nilly without something particularly impactful happening.</p>
<p>That also applies to the specific method by which Shepard gets into Xen- I was never a fan of portals just… randomly <em>appearing</em> in places, and thought the cameo of Gordon (or, I suppose, of Shepard <em>to</em> Gordon) was a little gratuitous.</p>
<p>Now, I <em>was</em> getting ready to say that the game would be better served by cutting this area out completely and transitioning directly to Crush Depth, but there <em>is</em> one other thing I was considering: While they are mechanically very helpful, and are used very effectively to foreshadow and build up the Gonarch fight, I didn’t like the story implications of the supply capsules teleporting into BM’s Xen. The final fight in the portal room always implied, to me at least, that the Xenians had broken through into the very last safe portion of the BMRF and the Lambda Team were literally making their final stand as they struggled to get the portal open with no regard to their own safety; this was <em>badass</em>, but having someone have obviously survived to keep sending those capsules kind of undercut that whole sentiment. If Not Alone instead showed that the capsules were being sent out by some kind of automated system in a Lambda Complex actively being sacked, and Shepard got sent to Xen by being somehow caught up in it, this would be fixed.</p>
<p>This actually provides an interesting way for Shepard to get <em>back</em>, as well- put together a few large setpieces of <em>massive</em> numbers of Xenian troops gearing up to teleport to Earth, and have him hitch a ride. Perhaps this might be the area Freeman ends up in if he refuses G-Man’s offer?</p>
<p>This <em>does</em> make the time discrepancy even worse, but honestly that’s a minor issue and it’s possible that just changing the actual length and environmental conditions of FF and MIA could make them feel of commensurate length to FAF and LC.</p>
<p>I guess since all of this is hypothetical I don’t really <em>have</em> to make a decision either way, really, to cut or just drastically alter the level.</p>
</details>
<p><strong>Crush Depth</strong></p>
<details>
<summary>
(Show)</summary>
<p>Mostly fine the way it is, TBH, although I always had a huge problem with the scientists here using teleporters for such ludicrously mundane things as going to an observation area a dozen yards away and would replace that with some kind of minisub or just broken <em>doors</em>. The xen-hopping portal-spam is also pretty bad, but also pretty non-essential to the core of what the level <em>is</em>.</p>
<p>After the very frenetic elements of Friendly Fire and possibly Not Alone, a slower and more quiet chapter is a good idea, although I’d like to play up the completely ruined, completely Xenian-controlled state of the Facility, so I think that there should be more patrolling Xen troops and fewer ichies than in the original.</p>
<p>One thing I considered doing in my <a href="https://forums.blackmesasource.com/t/dy-lasers-prototype/15376/8" rel="nofollow noopener">dy_lasers devblog thread</a> that might be applicable here was having the Xenians be seen to react to the fact that human scientists were experimenting on them in biodome areas. That might be interesting to put here, but the hydrofauna labs mostly studied the nonsentient Xenians so I don’t think they’d have as much to react <em>to</em>.</p>
</details>
<p><strong>Vicarious Reality</strong></p>
<details>
<summary>
(Show)</summary>
<p>Again mostly fine, not-strongly-story-focused chapter. One thing to keep in mind, though, would be that this chapter and the next should show the Xenians getting challenged for control of the facility more and more by Race X. In this chapter they start making inroads, and then in…</p>
</details>
<p><strong>Pit Worm’s Lair</strong></p>
<details>
<summary>
(Show)</summary>
<p>… they are really shown to be prevailing over the Xenians. Basically Surface Tension over again, possibly with additional setpieces like Race X ripping away Xenian biomatter and spraying on their own.</p>
<p>One <em>major</em> change I am thinking of would be to move the garg-at-the-dam scene from the end of Foxtrot Uniform to the end of this level. The reason for that is that I wanted to change the way that scene itself goes, so that the entire dam gets blown up (and, since the whole theme of the previous two chapters is “surprised Xenians and resurgent Race X”, maybe make it Race X that blows up the Garg and not the humans) and, most importantly, Shepard gets <em>knocked unconscious</em> at the end of it instead of just jumping into a pipe.<br>
The reason for <em>this</em> is that I want to fast-forward Shepard’s timeline past Freeman’s as Freeman spends a long time in the Xen levels, so that Shepard wakes up in the desert <em>after</em> the Nihilanth has been killed (perhaps, since the thing is after all telepathic, Shepard somehow receives direct information about its demise while unconscious).<br>
<em>This</em> in turn heralds another transition in story, so that…</p>
</details>
<p><strong>Foxtrot Uniform</strong></p>
<details>
<summary>
(Show)</summary>
<p>… takes place in a <em>very</em> different environment, well in the aftermath of at least the Xenian portion of the invasion, where human forces have come <em>back</em> (I’d sort of like to think of them being completely unaware of Freeman’s actions and thinking “Yep! Just took some airstrikes to turn this around!”) and are now trying to lock down the ruined base.</p>
<p>I feel like the Bad Guys should be <em>doing</em> something <em>with</em> the base, maybe gathering up documents and scientist prisoners or something, to show how much they are in control. They could of course be fighting Race X, but I feel like that would have gotten kind of played at this point? We <em>just saw</em> the Xenians push the military back, so I feel like this’d kind of be a “cut off the ingress point before the military is overwelmed <em>again</em>? We really <em>are</em> just a substitute Freeman” moment.</p>
<p>Also, this chapter is really hard to differentiate from</p>
</details>
<p><strong>The Package</strong></p>
<details>
<summary>
(Show)</summary>
<p>While I feel very confident about the changes I’d made previously to the game’s storyline, that leaves the whole nuke plot with some holes in it. The human forces are <em>winning</em> (winning because losing would be repetitive still counts as winning, okay?), so why would they decide to nuke the whole base <em>now</em>?</p>
<p>I mean, I suppose I <em>could</em> change the previous chapters to feature ragtag bands of military survivors (both Shepard’s squad and the Bad Guys) in a ruined base amidst a turf war between the Xenians and Race X, and skip the whole unconsciousness-and-Nihilanth bit entirely, but that seems less dramatic and also fits less with the enemy distributions and environment of the original 1999 incarnation of both chapters.</p>
<p>The two chapters are also really similar aesthetically- perhaps, since we literally broke the dam somewhere in Uniform, have one chapter but not the other be partially flooded? I don’t know. The whole thing is kind of a mess and I don’t have an easy answer. I’d actually seriously considered making it so that the Bad Guys were preparing to either invade Xen or kick the nuke there, but… why would Shepard care enough to stop that by closing the portal? I think some sort of justification needs to be added in previous chapters why the nuke is still being <em>considered</em> and why the gene worm portal is such a big deal if the government has things in hand again, but damned if I know what that would be.</p>
</details>
            <p><small>1 post - 1 participant</small></p>
            <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/my-outline-for-an-opposing-force-remake/62882">Read full topic</a></p>
          ]]></description>
          <link>https://leakfree.org/t/my-outline-for-an-opposing-force-remake/62882</link>
          <pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2020 02:51:07 +0000</pubDate>
          <discourse:topicPinned>No</discourse:topicPinned>
          <discourse:topicClosed>No</discourse:topicClosed>
          <discourse:topicArchived>No</discourse:topicArchived>
          <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-topic-62882</guid>
          <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/my-outline-for-an-opposing-force-remake/62882.rss">My Outline For An Opposing Force Remake</source>
        </item>
        <item>
          <title>Help me finish my first-ever sound mod (Sound.cache problem?)</title>
          <dc:creator><![CDATA[TheLostSkeleton]]></dc:creator>
          <category>Black Mesa</category>
          <description><![CDATA[
            <p>So I’m not a total newbie; I’ve been doing some form of game development since 1998, but I’ve never done tons of Source modding before so I don’t understand the finer details.</p>
<p>I’ve gotten as far as generating a VPK for my sound mod. That local VPK works in Black Mesa just fine, but when I feed it through the Publishing Tool and try to subscribe to my own mod, suddenly it stops working and the console gets flooded with error messages like</p>
<blockquote>
<p>Cannot figure out which search path sound\npc\alien_slave\vort_bm_alert01.wav came from.  Absolute path is D:\Steam\steamapps\workshop\content\362890\1969844684\Classic Alien Slave Voice.vpk\sound\npc\alien_slave\vort_bm_alert01.wav<br>
Failed to load sound</p>
</blockquote>
<p>Searching these forums suggests I might need to build a soundcache to include with my VPK. Black Mesa seems to automatically generate a soundcache for my VPK after loading it the first time, so I point the Publishing Tool at the folder with the VPK + sound.cache file, but, again, the console is flooded with search path errors when it comes back down off the workshop.</p>
<p><a href="https://forums.blackmesasource.com/t/custom-audio-not-playing-in-workshop-ugc/15329" rel="nofollow noopener">Another thread from two years ago</a> mentions a console command called “snd_buildcache”. So, instead of using the sound.cache file generated for my VPK, I copy all of my sound files in the proper folder structure in to bms and build a cache.</p>
<p>This leaves me with</p>
<blockquote>
<p>bms\aslave\sound.cache (664kb)</p>
</blockquote>
<p>Which was built from</p>
<blockquote>
<p>bms\aslave\sound\npc\alien_slave\ (62 files, 11.7mb)</p>
</blockquote>
<p>I repack my VPK, publish it, and yet again, it’s the same story: the local VPK I generated works fine for me, but trying to pull it off the workshop doesn’t work because it’s yelling about search path errors.</p>
<p>What am I missing?</p>
<p>For reference, here’s my VPK: <a href="https://drive.google.com/open?id=1RGveUu4_udRaPQTaqYW5wAf6Txk0JSSn" rel="nofollow noopener">https://drive.google.com/open?id=1RGveUu4_udRaPQTaqYW5wAf6Txk0JSSn</a></p>
            <p><small>2 posts - 1 participant</small></p>
            <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/help-me-finish-my-first-ever-sound-mod-sound-cache-problem/62800">Read full topic</a></p>
          ]]></description>
          <link>https://leakfree.org/t/help-me-finish-my-first-ever-sound-mod-sound-cache-problem/62800</link>
          <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2020 20:23:40 +0000</pubDate>
          <discourse:topicPinned>No</discourse:topicPinned>
          <discourse:topicClosed>No</discourse:topicClosed>
          <discourse:topicArchived>No</discourse:topicArchived>
          <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-topic-62800</guid>
          <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/help-me-finish-my-first-ever-sound-mod-sound-cache-problem/62800.rss">Help me finish my first-ever sound mod (Sound.cache problem?)</source>
        </item>
        <item>
          <title>Adding Player.BulletDamage sound entry in game_sounds_player.txt?</title>
          <dc:creator><![CDATA[Ed1]]></dc:creator>
          <category>Source 1</category>
          <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Moved my initial post to this topic since I figured it’s more appropriate here.</p>
<hr>
<p>Unfortunately game_sounds_player.txt doesn’t have a sound entry for when the player gets hit by bullets or getting bitch slapped with a gun, wanted to add the player hurt sounds whenever you get hit in the campaign. Half Life 2 didn’t have this either though so I’m not sure how this could be done. Haven’t dealt with the Hammer editor before, only tweaks I’ve ever done were editing the script files, amongst other things.</p>
<p>I’ve found <a href="https://sourceenginesnippets.blogspot.com/2013/12/the-working-entity.html" rel="nofollow noopener">this post</a> from a blog that seems to have what I’m looking for but have no idea where the player.cpp file is.</p>
            <p><small>3 posts - 2 participants</small></p>
            <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/adding-player-bulletdamage-sound-entry-in-game-sounds-player-txt/62778">Read full topic</a></p>
          ]]></description>
          <link>https://leakfree.org/t/adding-player-bulletdamage-sound-entry-in-game-sounds-player-txt/62778</link>
          <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jan 2020 08:45:15 +0000</pubDate>
          <discourse:topicPinned>No</discourse:topicPinned>
          <discourse:topicClosed>No</discourse:topicClosed>
          <discourse:topicArchived>No</discourse:topicArchived>
          <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-topic-62778</guid>
          <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/adding-player-bulletdamage-sound-entry-in-game-sounds-player-txt/62778.rss">Adding Player.BulletDamage sound entry in game_sounds_player.txt?</source>
        </item>
        <item>
          <title>Buildcubemaps Delay</title>
          <dc:creator><![CDATA[Admiral_Sakai]]></dc:creator>
          <category>Source 1</category>
          <description><![CDATA[
            <p>When running the ‘buildcubemaps’ console command to, well, build cubemaps for the first time in an execution of the game, the game will hang for up to several minutes before starting the process. All subsequent attempts to build cubemaps start immediately. This was not occurring before the Xen Beta.</p>
            <p><small>1 post - 1 participant</small></p>
            <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/buildcubemaps-delay/62398">Read full topic</a></p>
          ]]></description>
          <link>https://leakfree.org/t/buildcubemaps-delay/62398</link>
          <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2019 16:33:13 +0000</pubDate>
          <discourse:topicPinned>No</discourse:topicPinned>
          <discourse:topicClosed>No</discourse:topicClosed>
          <discourse:topicArchived>No</discourse:topicArchived>
          <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-topic-62398</guid>
          <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/buildcubemaps-delay/62398.rss">Buildcubemaps Delay</source>
        </item>
        <item>
          <title>Black Mesa Sound Effects Copyright Question</title>
          <dc:creator><![CDATA[The_Sink_God]]></dc:creator>
          <category>Black Mesa</category>
          <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Hi. I noticed a thread on this forum mentioning that most of the sound effects in the game (bms_sounds_misc) were royalty free and that the license.txt mentioned a CC BY-NC license. I just wanted to clarify since my project is a bit different than the one mentioned in the post:<br>
I’m working on a project that involves making an underground facility in UE4, that would be controllable by users. They could run “experiments”, operate shipments, security, etc and control the facility’s systems. I wanted to use some sounds from the black mesa files since they fit in perfectly. The game will be free to use, <em>but I will accept donations</em> if the user chooses to (this is all considering the project comes through with anything - it’s very early in development).<br>
My question is, am I okay to use some sound effects from the game files under this, would I need to not accept donations at all, am I not allowed to use the sound effects, etc?</p>
            <p><small>2 posts - 2 participants</small></p>
            <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/black-mesa-sound-effects-copyright-question/62315">Read full topic</a></p>
          ]]></description>
          <link>https://leakfree.org/t/black-mesa-sound-effects-copyright-question/62315</link>
          <pubDate>Sat, 08 Jun 2019 05:08:33 +0000</pubDate>
          <discourse:topicPinned>No</discourse:topicPinned>
          <discourse:topicClosed>No</discourse:topicClosed>
          <discourse:topicArchived>No</discourse:topicArchived>
          <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-topic-62315</guid>
          <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/black-mesa-sound-effects-copyright-question/62315.rss">Black Mesa Sound Effects Copyright Question</source>
        </item>
        <item>
          <title>BMPD: Pre-Disaster Surface Tension</title>
          <dc:creator><![CDATA[TJHL]]></dc:creator>
          <category>Source 1</category>
          <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Before map C was released for <a href="https://forums.blackmesasource.com/t/bmpd-pre-disaster-apprehension/15406" rel="nofollow noopener">PD: APP</a>, I was side-tracked with a little bit of surface tension, but with PD: APP essentially done, I’ll now be completely focusing of Surface Tension.</p>
<p>I’ve been working on this in parts. Conveniently, Surface Tension has three “Sections”, which I’ve named ‘The Drains’ (A-C), ‘The Ridge’ (D-F), and ‘The Streets’ (G-I).</p>
<p>I’ve completed the first pass on ‘The Ridge’ (I’m calling it that because there is the same ridge in the skybox for all three maps), and am now on the streets (aka STU), before I go back to the drainage canals, because of how wonky they are in terms of level transition.</p>
            <p><small>15 posts - 5 participants</small></p>
            <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/bmpd-pre-disaster-surface-tension/62304">Read full topic</a></p>
          ]]></description>
          <link>https://leakfree.org/t/bmpd-pre-disaster-surface-tension/62304</link>
          <pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2019 22:56:43 +0000</pubDate>
          <discourse:topicPinned>No</discourse:topicPinned>
          <discourse:topicClosed>No</discourse:topicClosed>
          <discourse:topicArchived>No</discourse:topicArchived>
          <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-topic-62304</guid>
          <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/bmpd-pre-disaster-surface-tension/62304.rss">BMPD: Pre-Disaster Surface Tension</source>
        </item>
        <item>
          <title>Unusual Dark Splodges In Lighting</title>
          <dc:creator><![CDATA[Admiral_Sakai]]></dc:creator>
          <category>General Development</category>
          <description><![CDATA[
            <p>In a couple of maps I’ve made I’m noticing these weird areas that are much darker than their surroundings with no clear explanation. Here’s a particularly egregious example from pd_c1a2b:<br>
<div class="lightbox-wrapper"><a class="lightbox" href="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/original/2X/1/156dfafd8c4acc59dfbd5aaff4081dd7755caf5e.jpeg" data-download-href="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/156dfafd8c4acc59dfbd5aaff4081dd7755caf5e" title=""><img src="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/optimized/2X/1/156dfafd8c4acc59dfbd5aaff4081dd7755caf5e_2_690x388.jpeg" alt="" width="690" height="388" srcset="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/optimized/2X/1/156dfafd8c4acc59dfbd5aaff4081dd7755caf5e_2_690x388.jpeg, https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/optimized/2X/1/156dfafd8c4acc59dfbd5aaff4081dd7755caf5e_2_1035x582.jpeg 1.5x, https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/optimized/2X/1/156dfafd8c4acc59dfbd5aaff4081dd7755caf5e_2_1380x776.jpeg 2x" data-small-upload="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/optimized/2X/1/156dfafd8c4acc59dfbd5aaff4081dd7755caf5e_2_10x10.png"><div class="meta"><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-far-image svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#far-image"></use></svg><span class="filename"></span><span class="informations">1920×1080 315 KB</span><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-discourse-expand svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#discourse-expand"></use></svg></div></a></div></p>
<p><div class="lightbox-wrapper"><a class="lightbox" href="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/original/2X/6/60abeb3f5b4b59c908bc6f6b4a1b55559fea7308.jpeg" data-download-href="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/60abeb3f5b4b59c908bc6f6b4a1b55559fea7308" title=""><img src="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/optimized/2X/6/60abeb3f5b4b59c908bc6f6b4a1b55559fea7308_2_690x388.jpeg" alt="" width="690" height="388" srcset="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/optimized/2X/6/60abeb3f5b4b59c908bc6f6b4a1b55559fea7308_2_690x388.jpeg, https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/optimized/2X/6/60abeb3f5b4b59c908bc6f6b4a1b55559fea7308_2_1035x582.jpeg 1.5x, https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/optimized/2X/6/60abeb3f5b4b59c908bc6f6b4a1b55559fea7308_2_1380x776.jpeg 2x" data-small-upload="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/optimized/2X/6/60abeb3f5b4b59c908bc6f6b4a1b55559fea7308_2_10x10.png"><div class="meta"><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-far-image svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#far-image"></use></svg><span class="filename"></span><span class="informations">1920×1080 313 KB</span><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-discourse-expand svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#discourse-expand"></use></svg></div></a></div></p>
<p>and here it is with mat_fullbright 2:</p>
<p><div class="lightbox-wrapper"><a class="lightbox" href="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/original/2X/d/d310bee9db4c3bfce6517f5c0650df1faf02c5c8.jpeg" data-download-href="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/d310bee9db4c3bfce6517f5c0650df1faf02c5c8" title=""><img src="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/optimized/2X/d/d310bee9db4c3bfce6517f5c0650df1faf02c5c8_2_690x388.jpeg" alt="" width="690" height="388" srcset="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/optimized/2X/d/d310bee9db4c3bfce6517f5c0650df1faf02c5c8_2_690x388.jpeg, https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/optimized/2X/d/d310bee9db4c3bfce6517f5c0650df1faf02c5c8_2_1035x582.jpeg 1.5x, https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/optimized/2X/d/d310bee9db4c3bfce6517f5c0650df1faf02c5c8_2_1380x776.jpeg 2x" data-small-upload="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/optimized/2X/d/d310bee9db4c3bfce6517f5c0650df1faf02c5c8_2_10x10.png"><div class="meta"><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-far-image svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#far-image"></use></svg><span class="filename"></span><span class="informations">1920×1080 151 KB</span><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-discourse-expand svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#discourse-expand"></use></svg></div></a></div></p>
<p><div class="lightbox-wrapper"><a class="lightbox" href="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/original/2X/f/f3c837e4c146fa7c70798459110e26c3da57bdf0.jpeg" data-download-href="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/f3c837e4c146fa7c70798459110e26c3da57bdf0" title=""><img src="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/optimized/2X/f/f3c837e4c146fa7c70798459110e26c3da57bdf0_2_690x388.jpeg" alt="" width="690" height="388" srcset="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/optimized/2X/f/f3c837e4c146fa7c70798459110e26c3da57bdf0_2_690x388.jpeg, https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/optimized/2X/f/f3c837e4c146fa7c70798459110e26c3da57bdf0_2_1035x582.jpeg 1.5x, https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/optimized/2X/f/f3c837e4c146fa7c70798459110e26c3da57bdf0_2_1380x776.jpeg 2x" data-small-upload="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/optimized/2X/f/f3c837e4c146fa7c70798459110e26c3da57bdf0_2_10x10.png"><div class="meta"><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-far-image svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#far-image"></use></svg><span class="filename"></span><span class="informations">1920×1080 177 KB</span><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-discourse-expand svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#discourse-expand"></use></svg></div></a></div></p>
<p>Removing and re-doing the brush or texture in question or the surrounding brushes doesn’t do anything to change the phenomenon, and copying the brush or moving it to a new location will cause it to not be affected. Changing the lightmap resolution makes the dark spot blurrier or sharper just like any other lighting effect but doesn’t seem to do anything about the underlying dark area:</p>
<p><div class="lightbox-wrapper"><a class="lightbox" href="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/original/2X/2/22d2a330014589298e6372770e9b7a3820abbc95.jpeg" data-download-href="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/22d2a330014589298e6372770e9b7a3820abbc95" title=""><img src="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/optimized/2X/2/22d2a330014589298e6372770e9b7a3820abbc95_2_690x388.jpeg" alt="" width="690" height="388" srcset="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/optimized/2X/2/22d2a330014589298e6372770e9b7a3820abbc95_2_690x388.jpeg, https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/optimized/2X/2/22d2a330014589298e6372770e9b7a3820abbc95_2_1035x582.jpeg 1.5x, https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/optimized/2X/2/22d2a330014589298e6372770e9b7a3820abbc95_2_1380x776.jpeg 2x" data-small-upload="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/optimized/2X/2/22d2a330014589298e6372770e9b7a3820abbc95_2_10x10.png"><div class="meta"><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-far-image svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#far-image"></use></svg><span class="filename"></span><span class="informations">1920×1080 153 KB</span><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-discourse-expand svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#discourse-expand"></use></svg></div></a></div></p>
<p>It’s possible to brighten these areas with a light_spot pointed directly at them, but obviously that means putting a bunch of pointless lights in the map.</p>
<p>Does anybody know what this might be about?</p>
            <p><small>9 posts - 4 participants</small></p>
            <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/unusual-dark-splodges-in-lighting/62240">Read full topic</a></p>
          ]]></description>
          <link>https://leakfree.org/t/unusual-dark-splodges-in-lighting/62240</link>
          <pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2019 00:38:00 +0000</pubDate>
          <discourse:topicPinned>No</discourse:topicPinned>
          <discourse:topicClosed>No</discourse:topicClosed>
          <discourse:topicArchived>No</discourse:topicArchived>
          <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-topic-62240</guid>
          <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/unusual-dark-splodges-in-lighting/62240.rss">Unusual Dark Splodges In Lighting</source>
        </item>
        <item>
          <title>Has Anyone Been Able To Get Propper To Work In Black Mesa?</title>
          <dc:creator><![CDATA[AdmiralSakai]]></dc:creator>
          <category>Black Mesa</category>
          <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I’m using the SDK 2013 version from tuxxi and the proper Propper entities (ha ha) are showing up in Hammer, but the tool itself exits immediately after being run with an error code of -1073741819.</p>
            <p><small>4 posts - 3 participants</small></p>
            <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/has-anyone-been-able-to-get-propper-to-work-in-black-mesa/62153">Read full topic</a></p>
          ]]></description>
          <link>https://leakfree.org/t/has-anyone-been-able-to-get-propper-to-work-in-black-mesa/62153</link>
          <pubDate>Thu, 14 Feb 2019 01:49:45 +0000</pubDate>
          <discourse:topicPinned>No</discourse:topicPinned>
          <discourse:topicClosed>No</discourse:topicClosed>
          <discourse:topicArchived>No</discourse:topicArchived>
          <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-topic-62153</guid>
          <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/has-anyone-been-able-to-get-propper-to-work-in-black-mesa/62153.rss">Has Anyone Been Able To Get Propper To Work In Black Mesa?</source>
        </item>
        <item>
          <title>Replacing NPC Models - Mini-Tutorial &amp; Discovery Log</title>
          <dc:creator><![CDATA[Admiral_Sakai]]></dc:creator>
          <category>General Development</category>
          <description><![CDATA[
            <p><div class="lightbox-wrapper"><a class="lightbox" href="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/original/2X/d/d0483a45db940fcc543dcbe038100e555db1af2d.jpeg" data-download-href="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/d0483a45db940fcc543dcbe038100e555db1af2d" title="20190123145124_1"><img src="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/optimized/2X/d/d0483a45db940fcc543dcbe038100e555db1af2d_2_690x388.jpeg" alt="20190123145124_1" data-base62-sha1="tIy3LQmAP2LV2yFZuDVnuZb8ctD" width="690" height="388" srcset="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/optimized/2X/d/d0483a45db940fcc543dcbe038100e555db1af2d_2_690x388.jpeg, https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/optimized/2X/d/d0483a45db940fcc543dcbe038100e555db1af2d_2_1035x582.jpeg 1.5x, https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/optimized/2X/d/d0483a45db940fcc543dcbe038100e555db1af2d_2_1380x776.jpeg 2x" data-small-upload="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/optimized/2X/d/d0483a45db940fcc543dcbe038100e555db1af2d_2_10x10.png"><div class="meta"><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-far-image svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#far-image"></use></svg><span class="filename">20190123145124_1</span><span class="informations">1920×1080 351 KB</span><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-discourse-expand svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#discourse-expand"></use></svg></div></a></div></p>
<p>This Xen-bloodied guard is the first thing I’ve done with a technique I’ve just discovered for replacing the character models on NPCs by keyvalue- i.e., using values settable on an NPC-by-NPC basis in the hammer editor.</p>
<p>Those of you familiar with Black Mesa modding will be aware that this can already be done with the character manifest, a script file that the game consults and, if it finds a name matching the NPC in the map, will give the NPC features as described in the entry in the file. This is used to set hair, glasses, face shapes, etc., and can in fact set the body model of the NPC. In the vanilla game this is mostly just used to switch between the normal (clean) and ‘hurt’ (bloody) models for scientists and security guards, but you can put any model you want in there and have, for instance, an entity that is programmatically a security guard and will use a guard’s AI and dialogue, but looks like a Marine and has a Marine’s animations- or a completely custom model you made yourself. Azure Sheep uses this functionality to make its ‘maintenance worker’ and ‘Barniel’ NPCs by putting a custom model over a security guard or a security model over a female scientist, respectively.</p>
<p>The problem is that the character manifest does not integrate well with the Workshop mod download system and cannot just reference multiple files the way, say, a map list can. This means you have to manually install mods which modify it, and additionally multiple mods which do so must be manually merged in a text editor else they will overwrite each other. This is not a problem for Azure Sheep which uses its own executable to launch and (I <em>think</em>!) inserts a separate game path entirely, but for a plug-and-play mod like pre-disaster is just not workable.</p>
<p>However, there is a work-around that allows the model an NPC uses to be specified in the Hammer editor <em>within a specific map</em>. This will <em>override</em> the default model of the NPC and also any model specified in the character manifest. All you need to do is turn off the “smart-edit” option in the NPC’s properties window and add a key with the name “model” and the value “/path/to/your/model”- for instance, the guard above has models/humans/guard_xend.mdl, which is just the guard_hurt model with a different texture where the red blood has been turned yellow. That’s really all there is to it.</p>
<p>A few things I am still looking into:</p>
<ul>
<li>I think the Hammer editor will in many circumstances fail to preserve the added model keyvalue over things like changing the entity class. This is kind of annoying but I don’t think will occur super-commonly so I am tempted to just live with it. Might be possible to add this keyvalue more formally by modifying the game’s FGD.</li>
<li>One thing to look out for is that not all models have the same animations, and sometimes the NPC you’ve changed the model of will try to programmatically call an animation its new model doesn’t have. I remember there being problems specifically with security guards and soldiers having different run animations and thus being unable to move. I haven’t tested this but in theory if you make a new model with animations that have the same names the NPC will work properly. Since many NPCs have the same skeleton to them it may even be possible to directly copy animation files while making the model.</li>
<li>I am not sure how character-manifest-defined bodygroup elements (hair, glasses, face flex, etc) react when the model of the NPC is changed, or if it is possible to change elements from either the old or new model by adding some other keyvalues in Hammer.</li>
<li>It is actually possible to change NPC models semi-dynamically in the game engine by firing the “addoutput” input at them with a new “model /path/to/model” parameter. However, this requires the game to be saved and reloaded to take effect, so I do not think it’ll find much use. It’s <em>possible</em> the engine can be commanded to update those models and only those models in a timely manner through, say, a console command, but I doubt it.</li>
</ul>
<p>On the other hand, though, this has opened up a number of new directions for Black Mesa modding to take:</p>
<ul>
<li><strong>It will now be possible to add construction worker, office worker, and other NPCs to Pre-Disaster maps, as well as ‘Otis’ model security guards if someone ever makes a model for them. This was possible before, but only by using the compatibility-breaking overrides to the character manifest.</strong></li>
<li>If I can get the animation issues ironed out (or just have them standing still) I can now add friendly Marine NPCs to high-security areas of the facility who will respond like security guards when talked to.</li>
<li>It is now possible to add fully-functional office worker, construction worker, and other models to canon BM maps just by editing the maps themselves- this means that incompatibility issues will only arise if another mod edits <em>those specific maps</em>, not any other mod trying to edit any other elements of the character manifest.</li>
<li>Opposing Force remake authors can now make HECU NPCs who will follow the player like guards would, and Black-Ops NPCs who are reskinned Marines. This was possible before, but not in a workshop-compatible</li>
<li>Similarly, this simplifies somewhat the modifications that would be required to add female versions of guard or Marine NPCs and makes them workshop-supportable. However such NPCs would still have the male combat/idle dialogue. I <em>think</em> it might be possible to use response contexts and custom soundscape files to replace dialogue wholesale, but I don’t know for sure.</li>
</ul>
            <p><small>3 posts - 2 participants</small></p>
            <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/replacing-npc-models-mini-tutorial-discovery-log/62109">Read full topic</a></p>
          ]]></description>
          <link>https://leakfree.org/t/replacing-npc-models-mini-tutorial-discovery-log/62109</link>
          <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jan 2019 23:52:58 +0000</pubDate>
          <discourse:topicPinned>No</discourse:topicPinned>
          <discourse:topicClosed>No</discourse:topicClosed>
          <discourse:topicArchived>No</discourse:topicArchived>
          <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-topic-62109</guid>
          <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/replacing-npc-models-mini-tutorial-discovery-log/62109.rss">Replacing NPC Models - Mini-Tutorial &amp; Discovery Log</source>
        </item>
        <item>
          <title>Finding Reference Material To Supplement Level Design</title>
          <dc:creator><![CDATA[systack]]></dc:creator>
          <category>Source 1</category>
          <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I’m very new this this forum (so I hope I’m posting this in the right section) but a long time follower (and player) of the Black Mesa Source project. As someone who’s started going through the motions of level design, I’m curious as to where the Black Mesa community finds reference images to help design their levels.</p>
<p>I’ve personally been wanting to design a level based around a nuclear power plant (original, I know), but I’ve been struggling to find comprehensive reference images/videos on the web, any advice?</p>
<p>Apologies in advance if this is the wrong section.</p>
            <p><small>2 posts - 2 participants</small></p>
            <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/finding-reference-material-to-supplement-level-design/62102">Read full topic</a></p>
          ]]></description>
          <link>https://leakfree.org/t/finding-reference-material-to-supplement-level-design/62102</link>
          <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jan 2019 21:20:02 +0000</pubDate>
          <discourse:topicPinned>No</discourse:topicPinned>
          <discourse:topicClosed>No</discourse:topicClosed>
          <discourse:topicArchived>No</discourse:topicArchived>
          <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-topic-62102</guid>
          <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/finding-reference-material-to-supplement-level-design/62102.rss">Finding Reference Material To Supplement Level Design</source>
        </item>
        <item>
          <title>Use of sound effects question</title>
          <dc:creator><![CDATA[Its]]></dc:creator>
          <category>Black Mesa</category>
          <description><![CDATA[
            <p>no clue where to post stuff yet.<br>
So I’m new to these forums though I’ve been following Back Mesa since before it’s Steam release and I’m getting more comfortable with Hammer but I’ve also been working on Making things for Doom as well and I had a thought of using sound effects from BMS in a custom Doom map but I hate the idea of stepping on toes and I’m still learning these forums, I couldn’t find a simple answer but could I use the BMS sfx in my project or is that a big no no.</p>
<p>Sorry if this was put in the wrong topic.</p>
            <p><small>4 posts - 3 participants</small></p>
            <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/use-of-sound-effects-question/62063">Read full topic</a></p>
          ]]></description>
          <link>https://leakfree.org/t/use-of-sound-effects-question/62063</link>
          <pubDate>Mon, 07 Jan 2019 12:47:10 +0000</pubDate>
          <discourse:topicPinned>No</discourse:topicPinned>
          <discourse:topicClosed>No</discourse:topicClosed>
          <discourse:topicArchived>No</discourse:topicArchived>
          <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-topic-62063</guid>
          <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/use-of-sound-effects-question/62063.rss">Use of sound effects question</source>
        </item>
        <item>
          <title>Are there any plans/support for the multiplayer/coop mode?</title>
          <dc:creator><![CDATA[Roald]]></dc:creator>
          <category>Black Mesa</category>
          <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Hello I am new to this community and not that much familair with half-life.<br>
I am more known to counter strike and the overlapping mapping tool Hammer SDK.<br>
So I was wondering what the multiplayer gamemode looks like and what are the plans?<br>
What gamemodes are there to play? and would there be room for fresh new gamemodes?<br>
Remembering HL I can only remember (team) deathmatch is that true?<br>
Are there any tutorials on how to implent existing (and new) gamemodes?</p>
<p>I was thinking about some kind of coop survival mode where you fight waves of Xenian bots with 1/2/3 other players. Each wave will increase the ammount of bots and add new/better Xenians. You will gain money on killing them that allows you to buy weapons and equipment troughout the map (and perhaps open new doors/rooms). The gamemode will contain a leaderboard that shows a ranking of highest wave you reached and perhaps highest ammount of kills/exp or money you gained.<br>
I am not into scripting so is there like a support thing for this or people who are interesting on working on something like this? Is there also a way to playtest your map?</p>
<p>EDIT: here a idea I worked out and its like the CoD Black Ops zombie mode:<br>
<div class="lightbox-wrapper"><a class="lightbox" href="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/original/2X/d/db9ebf965b0344eceb7f740b9ca763cfcba68743.jpeg" data-download-href="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/db9ebf965b0344eceb7f740b9ca763cfcba68743" title=""><img src="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/optimized/2X/d/db9ebf965b0344eceb7f740b9ca763cfcba68743_2_375x500.jpeg" alt="" width="375" height="500" srcset="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/optimized/2X/d/db9ebf965b0344eceb7f740b9ca763cfcba68743_2_375x500.jpeg, https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/optimized/2X/d/db9ebf965b0344eceb7f740b9ca763cfcba68743_2_562x750.jpeg 1.5x, https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/optimized/2X/d/db9ebf965b0344eceb7f740b9ca763cfcba68743_2_750x1000.jpeg 2x" data-small-upload="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/optimized/2X/d/db9ebf965b0344eceb7f740b9ca763cfcba68743_2_10x10.png"><div class="meta"><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-far-image svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#far-image"></use></svg><span class="filename"></span><span class="informations">3120×4160 3.6 MB</span><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-discourse-expand svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#discourse-expand"></use></svg></div></a></div><br>
<div class="lightbox-wrapper"><a class="lightbox" href="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/original/2X/d/d559ebc9fe13fe61c98381eb37b19f93a142a6dd.jpeg" data-download-href="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/d559ebc9fe13fe61c98381eb37b19f93a142a6dd" title=""><img src="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/optimized/2X/d/d559ebc9fe13fe61c98381eb37b19f93a142a6dd_2_375x500.jpeg" alt="" width="375" height="500" srcset="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/optimized/2X/d/d559ebc9fe13fe61c98381eb37b19f93a142a6dd_2_375x500.jpeg, https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/optimized/2X/d/d559ebc9fe13fe61c98381eb37b19f93a142a6dd_2_562x750.jpeg 1.5x, https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/optimized/2X/d/d559ebc9fe13fe61c98381eb37b19f93a142a6dd_2_750x1000.jpeg 2x" data-small-upload="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/optimized/2X/d/d559ebc9fe13fe61c98381eb37b19f93a142a6dd_2_10x10.png"><div class="meta"><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-far-image svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#far-image"></use></svg><span class="filename"></span><span class="informations">3120×4160 3.66 MB</span><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-discourse-expand svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#discourse-expand"></use></svg></div></a></div></p>
<p>The map will consist of different areas and each area I gave a color. You will start at the pink area in the tram (with breakable windows and perhaps if possible edit the model so there is a shutter in the ceiling). The tram will make it’s way on the train track as far as possible. You will have to spend money on opening new gates and doors to reach a new area for the tram to move. Some areas are more expensive then others because of some factors like the size of the area and the equipment that can be found there. When you open one door of one area, all the doors and gates of that area open simultaneously. So you buy the area, not the specific door. The tram track is attached to the colors in the order: pink/blue/red/purple. If you open all areas the train will go in circles arround the map.</p>
<p>So the Xenians will spawn in waves. Each higher wave bring in more and better xenians. The Xenians will spawn in non playable area from where they can enter the map. When a new area gets opened also new spawnpoints will be triggered. I am not sure how these bots would react on a moving tram… would they be smart enough to jump on it or crawl trough the windows? Perhaps instead of the tram it got to become some kind of platform.</p>
<p>Troughout the map there will be standard buy spots with certain equipment and weapons (pistols, smg, shotguns, grenades, health, ammo boxes and etc). Also there will be special boxes that give a random weapon which can be a special weapon and cost more.</p>
<p>Instead of COOP it can also be Multiplayer with a few survivors and others are Xenians and they have like ‘x’ tickets each wave OR 50/50 and when a player dies he joins the Xenians. When the Xenians tickets run out they lose or when all survivors are dead.</p>
            <p><small>4 posts - 3 participants</small></p>
            <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/are-there-any-plans-support-for-the-multiplayer-coop-mode/62060">Read full topic</a></p>
          ]]></description>
          <link>https://leakfree.org/t/are-there-any-plans-support-for-the-multiplayer-coop-mode/62060</link>
          <pubDate>Sun, 06 Jan 2019 19:08:06 +0000</pubDate>
          <discourse:topicPinned>No</discourse:topicPinned>
          <discourse:topicClosed>No</discourse:topicClosed>
          <discourse:topicArchived>No</discourse:topicArchived>
          <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-topic-62060</guid>
          <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/are-there-any-plans-support-for-the-multiplayer-coop-mode/62060.rss">Are there any plans/support for the multiplayer/coop mode?</source>
        </item>
        <item>
          <title>Document Generation Tutorial</title>
          <dc:creator><![CDATA[Admiral_Sakai]]></dc:creator>
          <category>Black Mesa</category>
          <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Several people have asked how I am making the documents that I have been using in pre-disaster chapters, so I thought I’d put together a quick tutorial on the subject.</p>
<p><strong>Software Needed</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>
<a href="https://www.libreoffice.org/" rel="nofollow noopener">LibreOffice</a> with the ‘Draw’ component, or any similar word processor with vector drawing functionality. A PhD student where I work uses PowerPoint for this. This tutorial assumes basic familiarity with the functionality of these types of programs.</li>
<li>
<a href="https://www.gimp.org/" rel="nofollow noopener">GIMP</a>. If you have Photoshop or another relatively heavy-duty image editing tool that will also work but GIMP is free. This tutorial assumes familiarity with common image-manipulation functions in these sort of programs</li>
<li>
<a href="https://nemesis.thewavelength.net/index.php?p=41" rel="nofollow noopener">VTFEdit</a>. Having some knowledge of Source engine material creation will be helpful.</li>
<li>The Black Mesa release of the Hammer editor (duh).</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>Making Paper Documents</strong><br>
This is typically best done in Draw, with text boxes. If you want you can compose the actual text in the standard word processor and paste it over, but the next step requires copying and pasting the resulting document into GIMP and only the drawing editors can typically do that.<br>
<div class="lightbox-wrapper"><a class="lightbox" href="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/original/2X/6/61077b5a129914f16de5a981639ac814b83245aa.png" data-download-href="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/61077b5a129914f16de5a981639ac814b83245aa" title="image"><img src="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/optimized/2X/6/61077b5a129914f16de5a981639ac814b83245aa_2_690x373.png" alt="image" data-base62-sha1="dQmllUcRsCVi6XOhSYssTaBpzBw" width="690" height="373" srcset="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/optimized/2X/6/61077b5a129914f16de5a981639ac814b83245aa_2_690x373.png, https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/optimized/2X/6/61077b5a129914f16de5a981639ac814b83245aa_2_1035x559.png 1.5x, https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/optimized/2X/6/61077b5a129914f16de5a981639ac814b83245aa_2_1380x746.png 2x" data-small-upload="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/optimized/2X/6/61077b5a129914f16de5a981639ac814b83245aa_2_10x10.png"><div class="meta"><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-far-image svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#far-image"></use></svg><span class="filename">image</span><span class="informations">1918×1038 192 KB</span><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-discourse-expand svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#discourse-expand"></use></svg></div></a></div><br>
Stuff like the Black Mesa logo and paper formats (technical reports, memos, etc) I tend to copy from other documents to try to keep it consistent. The source documents I use are stored in the VPKs of the pre-disaster mods in case other people want access to them for this purpose.</p>
<p>One thing I find useful is designing the entire document at twice the size it would actually be IRL- for instance instead of an 8.5 x 11 page with 12-point font I use a 17 x 22 page with 24-point font. This makes the resulting image crisper because of how Source handles texture resolutions (see below).</p>
<p>Figures and graphs are typically things I find by typing a few terms vaguely related to the topic of the document into Google Images or Google Scholar. It can have a white or transparent background, either one works. Most of the handwritten annotations on documents are just another text box with a ‘handwritten’ font; anything more complicated than that is a subject we’ll get to later on.</p>
<p><strong>Processing Typed Documents In GIMP</strong><br>
Once you have your document looking the way you want it, you’ll want to have ready a blank paper texture in GIMP. You could just use a flat white rectangle, but actual paper does have some texture to it so I use a file called paper_big.tga that I got off of Google Images and keep in the ‘materialsrc’ folder of the VPKs. There are also a couple of different notebook and graph papers in there, and you can find other paper backgrounds online.<br>
Whatever you use, it’s a good idea to make sure it’s sized at or a little under a power of 2 (1024, 2048, 4096, etc) along its long axis- I’ll explain why in a later section.</p>
<p>Hit Ctrl-A to select the entire page area in your drawing processor and paste it into GIMP. This will produce a new layer with your text converted to an image- you may need to move and resize it to match the dimensions of the paper, although obviously blowing it up too large will make the image blurry.</p>
<p><div class="lightbox-wrapper"><a class="lightbox" href="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/original/2X/4/48825c3d31c6aec2de3a8d268b1c63df7ef44b58.png" data-download-href="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/48825c3d31c6aec2de3a8d268b1c63df7ef44b58" title="image"><img src="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/optimized/2X/4/48825c3d31c6aec2de3a8d268b1c63df7ef44b58_2_690x373.png" alt="image" data-base62-sha1="alrFL6O7ORWkYK64tvugYEV33fO" width="690" height="373" srcset="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/optimized/2X/4/48825c3d31c6aec2de3a8d268b1c63df7ef44b58_2_690x373.png, https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/optimized/2X/4/48825c3d31c6aec2de3a8d268b1c63df7ef44b58_2_1035x559.png 1.5x, https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/optimized/2X/4/48825c3d31c6aec2de3a8d268b1c63df7ef44b58_2_1380x746.png 2x" data-small-upload="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/optimized/2X/4/48825c3d31c6aec2de3a8d268b1c63df7ef44b58_2_10x10.png"><div class="meta"><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-far-image svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#far-image"></use></svg><span class="filename">image</span><span class="informations">1919×1040 638 KB</span><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-discourse-expand svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#discourse-expand"></use></svg></div></a></div><br>
Finally, you will want to run the ‘color to alpha’ filter with white selected as the alpha color. This will get rid of any white backgrounds on figures or drawings for you, but it will also allow a little bit of the paper background to show through in areas that were not perfectly black. This goes a long way to making it look as though the text is actually printed onto the background instead of just floating artificially above it.</p>
<p>This is also the step where you can add things like highlighting and redaction using the ‘brush’ tool. The ‘multiply’ setting is good for highlighting because it will affect the white paper but not black print.</p>
<p><strong>Using Preexisting Documents</strong><br>
Some things like equipment manuals, safety posters, and non-BM technical papers I just looked up on the Internet. GIMP has a very useful feature that allows you to import one or more pages from a PDF as an image file. Those typically have white backgrounds, so I just run the color-to-alpha filter on them and put an appropriate background behind them.</p>
<p><strong>Using Hand-Drawn Figures</strong><br>
My preferred method of generating hand-drawn figures or doodles is to take them off of IRL sources. I work at a research university so there are tons of whiteboards and notebooks just lying around with random scientific scribblings for me to photograph; another good place to get materials like this is from YouTube where professors will often post videos of their lectures that you can take screenshots of; sometimes you can also find drawings of things just through Google Images but I’d recommend looking at YouTube first. I suppose you could just draw and annotate diagrams yourself and photograph them, but I’d worry that all of these documents supposedly by different people would come out all in the same style and all with the same handwriting.</p>
<p>Regardless of source, typically what you get is a photo of a whiteboard, chalkboard, or piece of paper with stuff drawn on it.<br>
<div class="lightbox-wrapper"><a class="lightbox" href="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/original/2X/3/3ce2070544c6c2873d112b9ebf41e75bf3565c10.jpeg" data-download-href="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/3ce2070544c6c2873d112b9ebf41e75bf3565c10" title="image"><img src="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/optimized/2X/3/3ce2070544c6c2873d112b9ebf41e75bf3565c10_2_690x440.jpeg" alt="image" data-base62-sha1="8GAUp4Qqs8pJ4TFkB4osMR1K0NO" width="690" height="440" srcset="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/optimized/2X/3/3ce2070544c6c2873d112b9ebf41e75bf3565c10_2_690x440.jpeg, https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/optimized/2X/3/3ce2070544c6c2873d112b9ebf41e75bf3565c10_2_1035x660.jpeg 1.5x, https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/original/2X/3/3ce2070544c6c2873d112b9ebf41e75bf3565c10.jpeg 2x" data-small-upload="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/optimized/2X/3/3ce2070544c6c2873d112b9ebf41e75bf3565c10_2_10x10.png"><div class="meta"><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-far-image svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#far-image"></use></svg><span class="filename">image</span><span class="informations">1135×725 235 KB</span><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-discourse-expand svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#discourse-expand"></use></svg></div></a></div><br>
You’ll want to begin by cropping out all of the surrounding material so that only the figure and the background are visible.<br>
<div class="lightbox-wrapper"><a class="lightbox" href="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/original/2X/d/d867c36f6d28ec4844dad16a542b0fd7527c681c.jpeg" data-download-href="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/d867c36f6d28ec4844dad16a542b0fd7527c681c" title="image"><img src="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/optimized/2X/d/d867c36f6d28ec4844dad16a542b0fd7527c681c_2_690x443.jpeg" alt="image" data-base62-sha1="uSprDkOgd4HdVxKTUfmQJ5TBPPe" width="690" height="443" srcset="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/optimized/2X/d/d867c36f6d28ec4844dad16a542b0fd7527c681c_2_690x443.jpeg, https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/optimized/2X/d/d867c36f6d28ec4844dad16a542b0fd7527c681c_2_1035x664.jpeg 1.5x, https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/original/2X/d/d867c36f6d28ec4844dad16a542b0fd7527c681c.jpeg 2x" data-small-upload="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/optimized/2X/d/d867c36f6d28ec4844dad16a542b0fd7527c681c_2_10x10.png"><div class="meta"><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-far-image svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#far-image"></use></svg><span class="filename">image</span><span class="informations">1127×725 170 KB</span><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-discourse-expand svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#discourse-expand"></use></svg></div></a></div><br>
We will want to use “color to alpha” again to extract the figure, but to do that we want the background to be perfectly white and not the mix of light grays it is at the start. This can be achieved by using the ‘Levels’ tool to shift the white threshold of the image but not the black. Sometimes you may need to make multiple passes to get rid of all color in the background without washing out the figure itself:<br>
<div class="lightbox-wrapper"><a class="lightbox" href="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/original/2X/8/83ce8d56350d394e14e7cab4216de6b6716e526f.jpeg" data-download-href="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/83ce8d56350d394e14e7cab4216de6b6716e526f" title="image"><img src="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/optimized/2X/8/83ce8d56350d394e14e7cab4216de6b6716e526f_2_690x445.jpeg" alt="image" data-base62-sha1="iO15eDZdrtQ6U4kdIOKx8vOiuMD" width="690" height="445" srcset="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/optimized/2X/8/83ce8d56350d394e14e7cab4216de6b6716e526f_2_690x445.jpeg, https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/optimized/2X/8/83ce8d56350d394e14e7cab4216de6b6716e526f_2_1035x667.jpeg 1.5x, https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/original/2X/8/83ce8d56350d394e14e7cab4216de6b6716e526f.jpeg 2x" data-small-upload="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/optimized/2X/8/83ce8d56350d394e14e7cab4216de6b6716e526f_2_10x10.png"><div class="meta"><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-far-image svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#far-image"></use></svg><span class="filename">image</span><span class="informations">1127×727 187 KB</span><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-discourse-expand svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#discourse-expand"></use></svg></div></a></div><br>
<div class="lightbox-wrapper"><a class="lightbox" href="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/original/2X/9/9b531b40fd74ed69a55c82565628a06c81972b08.jpeg" data-download-href="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/9b531b40fd74ed69a55c82565628a06c81972b08" title="image"><img src="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/optimized/2X/9/9b531b40fd74ed69a55c82565628a06c81972b08_2_690x427.jpeg" alt="image" data-base62-sha1="ma43SYKCx44Bo1ucs7MAVilU0uQ" width="690" height="427" srcset="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/optimized/2X/9/9b531b40fd74ed69a55c82565628a06c81972b08_2_690x427.jpeg, https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/optimized/2X/9/9b531b40fd74ed69a55c82565628a06c81972b08_2_1035x640.jpeg 1.5x, https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/original/2X/9/9b531b40fd74ed69a55c82565628a06c81972b08.jpeg 2x" data-small-upload="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/optimized/2X/9/9b531b40fd74ed69a55c82565628a06c81972b08_2_10x10.png"><div class="meta"><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-far-image svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#far-image"></use></svg><span class="filename">image</span><span class="informations">1187×735 262 KB</span><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-discourse-expand svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#discourse-expand"></use></svg></div></a></div><br>
<div class="lightbox-wrapper"><a class="lightbox" href="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/original/2X/5/5b6111fab27ed6d8424d02e1b8121cd345da358e.png" data-download-href="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/5b6111fab27ed6d8424d02e1b8121cd345da358e" title="image"><img src="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/optimized/2X/5/5b6111fab27ed6d8424d02e1b8121cd345da358e_2_690x423.png" alt="image" data-base62-sha1="d2nq9ucCF7TIlP7xKlFym24OERE" width="690" height="423" srcset="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/optimized/2X/5/5b6111fab27ed6d8424d02e1b8121cd345da358e_2_690x423.png, https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/optimized/2X/5/5b6111fab27ed6d8424d02e1b8121cd345da358e_2_1035x634.png 1.5x, https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/original/2X/5/5b6111fab27ed6d8424d02e1b8121cd345da358e.png 2x" data-small-upload="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/optimized/2X/5/5b6111fab27ed6d8424d02e1b8121cd345da358e_2_10x10.png"><div class="meta"><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-far-image svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#far-image"></use></svg><span class="filename">image</span><span class="informations">1189×729 113 KB</span><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-discourse-expand svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#discourse-expand"></use></svg></div></a></div><br>
After that, using color to alpha (and optionally converting to grayscale or colorizing all or part of the image) will produce a nice drawing:<br>
<div class="lightbox-wrapper"><a class="lightbox" href="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/original/2X/9/924069031042e3d53728263bbc7b4a2db61133fc.jpeg" data-download-href="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/924069031042e3d53728263bbc7b4a2db61133fc" title="image"><img src="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/optimized/2X/9/924069031042e3d53728263bbc7b4a2db61133fc_2_467x500.jpeg" alt="image" data-base62-sha1="kRNHX2S9o9CGFE4itRzDkF0dRhi" width="467" height="500" srcset="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/optimized/2X/9/924069031042e3d53728263bbc7b4a2db61133fc_2_467x500.jpeg, https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/optimized/2X/9/924069031042e3d53728263bbc7b4a2db61133fc_2_700x750.jpeg 1.5x, https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/optimized/2X/9/924069031042e3d53728263bbc7b4a2db61133fc_2_934x1000.jpeg 2x" data-small-upload="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/optimized/2X/9/924069031042e3d53728263bbc7b4a2db61133fc_2_10x10.png"><div class="meta"><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-far-image svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#far-image"></use></svg><span class="filename">image</span><span class="informations">963×1029 338 KB</span><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-discourse-expand svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#discourse-expand"></use></svg></div></a></div><br>
For drawings on chalkboards you may want to invert the colors to produce a dark drawing on a pale background.</p>
<p>Basic things like scribbles, underlines, or circles can generally be found on Google Images.</p>
<p><strong>Making Emails &amp; Other Computer Records</strong><br>
I typically start with a ‘blank’ version of a common program like Outlook or Word. These can be made pretty simply just by finding a screenshot of the program on an older version of Windows and whiting out the text fields. If you wanted to be fancy I suppose you could set up your computer with a retro Windows theme and take screenshots off of that. Either way, I typically just edit the ‘blank’ versions directly in GIMP to add my own text; for things like PowerPoint slides I copy stuff from Draw.<br>
<div class="lightbox-wrapper"><a class="lightbox" href="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/original/2X/d/d0c4ee78abf76d3d8887912d02ccaac256d4abb9.png" data-download-href="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/d0c4ee78abf76d3d8887912d02ccaac256d4abb9" title="image"><img src="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/original/2X/d/d0c4ee78abf76d3d8887912d02ccaac256d4abb9.png" alt="image" data-base62-sha1="tMReJKsUqppmxjYiQPZteipUo7n" width="690" height="405" data-small-upload="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/optimized/2X/d/d0c4ee78abf76d3d8887912d02ccaac256d4abb9_2_10x10.png"><div class="meta"><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-far-image svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#far-image"></use></svg><span class="filename">image</span><span class="informations">1059×623 27.8 KB</span><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-discourse-expand svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#discourse-expand"></use></svg></div></a></div><br>
I’ve found that 11-point Tahoma with anti-aliasing disabled very well approximates the system font on old versions of Windows.</p>
<p>There’s blank versions of each of the programs I’ve used in the relevant pre-disaster VPK files.</p>
<p><strong>The ‘Terminal’ Screen Effect</strong><br>
Sometimes for older displays or ones that aren’t a full computer monitor, I’ve added a striated glow effect. This works best on diagrams that are predominantly a black background with light-colored shapes- the ‘invert’ filter in GIMP can be very helpful in this regard.</p>
<p>The actual filter is a four-step process: first, I add the 'Distorts &gt; Video" filter to create the scan lines effect; then, I decompose the image into R, G, and B layers; then, <em>for each layer</em>, I run the ‘artistic &gt; softglow’ filter; and finally recompose the image. This is necessary because if the softglow filter is applied to a full RGB image it just makes the glow white and not the color of what is glowing.</p>
<p><strong>Final Preparation Of Document Textures</strong><br>
The first thing you will want to do once a document is concocted to your satisfaction is to adjust it so that no part of it is exactly 0-0-0 black. This is because the later Source visual effect will use an RGB value of 0 0 0 to decide <em>not</em> to render portions of the image- this will cause portions of your document which are exactly black to render as ‘holes’ through which the background can be seen. Setting the dark output level in the ‘levels’ tool to 5 is a good way to remove any actual black areas without visibly altering the image:<br>
<div class="lightbox-wrapper"><a class="lightbox" href="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/original/2X/d/d3f57255f0f74acb8decc0ac449632cfa0136018.png" data-download-href="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/d3f57255f0f74acb8decc0ac449632cfa0136018" title="image"><img src="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/original/2X/d/d3f57255f0f74acb8decc0ac449632cfa0136018.png" alt="image" data-base62-sha1="uf4C1g8JOwO1fmls09f0nlbfRJ6" width="320" height="500" data-small-upload="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/optimized/2X/d/d3f57255f0f74acb8decc0ac449632cfa0136018_2_10x10.png"><div class="meta"><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-far-image svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#far-image"></use></svg><span class="filename">image</span><span class="informations">373×581 13.8 KB</span><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-discourse-expand svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#discourse-expand"></use></svg></div></a></div></p>
<p>Next, make sure the image is scaled properly. Source Engine textures must be a power of 2 along each axis (although it needn’t be the <em>same</em> power of 2, i.e. the image can be a rectangle and not a square), but while it’s good practice to fill as much of the available space in the image as possible the actual document need not take up <em>all</em> of it. Since some images (like computer outputs) are supposed to be a specific pixel-for-pixel representation of something and even those that aren’t can lose resolution when resized, you may want to scale the <em>canvas</em> to a power of 2 without affecting the image.</p>
<p>Export the image to some sort of lossless format, import it into VTFEdit, and save it as a VTF file somewhere in your materials directory. Make a corresponding VMT with the following information:</p>
<blockquote>
<p>LightmappedGeneric<br>
{<br>
“$basetexture”	“path/to/vtf”<br>
$selfillum 1<br>
$selfillumtint “[.75 .75 .75]”<br>
}</p>
</blockquote>
<p>The $selfillumtint parameter determines how bright your document will look and is influenced by your tonemap settings. Generally you don’t want them looking dark gray, but at the same time you don’t want them to be at full brightness because then under most tonemap settings there will be heavy bloom that obscures the text.</p>
<p><strong>Displaying The Document In Hammer</strong><br>
The apparatus for displaying a document consists of three parts.</p>
<p>The first is the document itself, which is kept outside the main play area of the map with a point_camera pointed at it. I typically put mine all in a row in a single location, but they can really go anywhere.<br>
<div class="lightbox-wrapper"><a class="lightbox" href="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/original/2X/d/d8b5515e74673dfc39968fa92a58c6bc21c121d9.png" data-download-href="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/d8b5515e74673dfc39968fa92a58c6bc21c121d9" title="image"><img src="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/optimized/2X/d/d8b5515e74673dfc39968fa92a58c6bc21c121d9_2_690x373.png" alt="image" data-base62-sha1="uV5BwPcmlYfg41aWdoY4QOkHXWV" width="690" height="373" srcset="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/optimized/2X/d/d8b5515e74673dfc39968fa92a58c6bc21c121d9_2_690x373.png, https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/optimized/2X/d/d8b5515e74673dfc39968fa92a58c6bc21c121d9_2_1035x559.png 1.5x, https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/optimized/2X/d/d8b5515e74673dfc39968fa92a58c6bc21c121d9_2_1380x746.png 2x" data-small-upload="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/optimized/2X/d/d8b5515e74673dfc39968fa92a58c6bc21c121d9_2_10x10.png"><div class="meta"><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-far-image svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#far-image"></use></svg><span class="filename">image</span><span class="informations">1920×1038 290 KB</span><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-discourse-expand svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#discourse-expand"></use></svg></div></a></div><br>
The size of the document texture in Hammer doesn’t actually matter because Source maintains the original image resolution regardless of the texture scale- a texture will look just as crisp if it is on a large brush the player is far away from as it will on a small brush the player is close to. This is true for the camera entity as well. A document that takes up a little less than a 32-by-32 brush with the camera ~16 units away will typically be well-positioned to fill the screen. The brush behind the transparent document should be black. The camera doesn’t need any special properties other than a unique name.</p>
<p>The second component is a collection of player behavior and view-management entities. These include a logic_auto with the output</p>
<blockquote>
<p>OnMapSpawn &lt;NAME OF YOUR SCRIPT_INTRO&gt; SetBlendMode 5</p>
</blockquote>
<p>a game_ui ent with the output</p>
<blockquote>
<p>PlayerOff &lt;NAME OF THE FUNC_BUTTON BELOW&gt; PressOut</p>
</blockquote>
<p>and the ‘Freeze Player’, ‘Hide Weapon’, ‘+Use Deactivates’, and ‘Jump Deactivates’ flags all set, and a script_intro entity which can be named anything. You only need one of these sets per map.</p>
<p>Finally, each document you want to view needs a func_button entity with the “Use Activates”, “Toggle”, and “Don’t Move” flags set and the outputs</p>
<blockquote>
<p>OnIn &lt;NAME OF  YOUR SCRIPT_INTRO&gt; SetCameraViewEntity &lt;NAME OF THE CAMERA THAT SHOWS YOUR DOCUMENT&gt;<br>
OnIn &lt;NAME OF YOUR FUNC_UI&gt; Activate<br>
OnIn &lt;NAME OF YOUR SCRIPT_INTRO&gt; Activate 0.01<br>
OnOut &lt;NAME OF YOUR FUNC_UI&gt; Deactivate<br>
OnOut &lt;NAME OF YOUR SCRIPT_INTRO&gt; Deactivate</p>
</blockquote>
<p>It is most convenient for all of your buttons to have the same target name.<br>
I made a small custom sprite to make the buttons visible, but this has no effect on their logic. The sprite texture is called documents/docflag_sprite.vmt and is available in any Pre-Disaster VPK.</p>
            <p><small>3 posts - 2 participants</small></p>
            <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/document-generation-tutorial/61982">Read full topic</a></p>
          ]]></description>
          <link>https://leakfree.org/t/document-generation-tutorial/61982</link>
          <pubDate>Tue, 11 Dec 2018 02:17:29 +0000</pubDate>
          <discourse:topicPinned>No</discourse:topicPinned>
          <discourse:topicClosed>No</discourse:topicClosed>
          <discourse:topicArchived>No</discourse:topicArchived>
          <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-topic-61982</guid>
          <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/document-generation-tutorial/61982.rss">Document Generation Tutorial</source>
        </item>
        <item>
          <title>Opposing Force Style HECU</title>
          <dc:creator><![CDATA[Yukon]]></dc:creator>
          <category>Black Mesa</category>
          <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Hello there,</p>
<p>I am currently working on some HECU models in the style of Opposing Force, mostly for use in SFM but I’d like to bring them over into Black Mesa. But I have a question regarding how the bodygroups/skingroups work for this game and how to setup the .qc in a way that tells the game to use a variety of bodygroups and skingroups instead of the same ones over and over. If perhaps there are other qc lines required instead of just the $bodygroup ones. Gmod has a method using lua but I’m not sure how Black Mesa handles it. I apologize if this isn’t the right place to ask this.</p>
<p>Can anybody shed some light on this?</p>
            <p><small>4 posts - 2 participants</small></p>
            <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/opposing-force-style-hecu/61979">Read full topic</a></p>
          ]]></description>
          <link>https://leakfree.org/t/opposing-force-style-hecu/61979</link>
          <pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 18:37:21 +0000</pubDate>
          <discourse:topicPinned>No</discourse:topicPinned>
          <discourse:topicClosed>No</discourse:topicClosed>
          <discourse:topicArchived>No</discourse:topicArchived>
          <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-topic-61979</guid>
          <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/opposing-force-style-hecu/61979.rss">Opposing Force Style HECU</source>
        </item>
        <item>
          <title>A better look for this game</title>
          <dc:creator><![CDATA[24Seg]]></dc:creator>
          <category>Black Mesa</category>
          <description><![CDATA[
            <p>The intention of this post, is to give my opinion and ideas maybe already thought, about things that should have happened but they did not happen, this are changes that would make this title more enjoyable, i hope they can be heard someday, i would like you to say with constructive criticism.</p>
<ol>
<li>
<ul>
<li>if they can add (because it is possible) animations such as “Use” for (doors / buttons) animation like turn on/off the flashlight, inspect weapon, add “procedural bones” for the (fps look) that would improve the look (up / down) and the ( walk/run) add this without affect the current animations (sprint) and add a (fps body) which would add many layers of immersion to the game, not realism.</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ol>
<p>Side Note; these changes are things that can take from left 4 dead, such as (npc bloodpool) and (blood in hands and weapons).</p>
<ol start="2">
<li>
<ul>
<li>add some graphic effects, such as (d-light) when shooting, (smoke) when shooting, and sprites that are generated when walking in water, such as left 4 dead 1, also improve the particles from the beginning I never liked them, they are small and realistic “that was not necessary” it would be better if the bullet impact were something more exaggerated.</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ol>
<p>Side Note; I do not mean so exaggerated, i want to say more striking, shocking.</p>
<ol start="3">
<li>
<ul>
<li>The mapping is good, well optimized and well taken, the problem is in the lack of sense in many situations that I find, such as ghost doors, poorly made walls, and poor transition between sectors, as an example ( Sector C &amp; B ) what separates them is a door in a warehouse, “a disappointment for me” I expected the sectors to be independent from each other and what connected them were designated areas for that.</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ol>
<p>Side Note; This is good because it could add more content to the game without needing to manage things that do not fit.</p>
<ul>
<li>
<p>I imagined that each sector should be isolated from one of the others, that an example the sector to enter has to go through 2 (blastdoor) I assumed that to exit also by a (blastdoor) or similar that would connect with an area for the introduction of material or personnel that was not civil.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>The idea that had about these areas, should have the function (of point of control, point of supply, pumping, water and other elements, electricity, ventilation, insertion of non-civilian personnel, transport security guards, workers and etc), and their use of these would have certain restrictions according to the authorization levels across the sectors.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<ol start="4">
<li>
<ul>
<li>They should create or add a scatter system and recoil, for weapons, (not for realism purposes) only for good gameplay purposes, a system that has (recoil &amp; dispersion) based on the movements that we use, because in general the weapons feel strange, without a job behind, only simple weapons with damage and random, so they would also achieve a unique feeling (by weapon) and it does not have to be a system that impacts a lot, it is not needed so much because it is a game single-player</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ol>
<p>Side Note; just a little (scatter &amp; recoil) for weapons does not even have to be much, the most important thing is what is seen moves the aim based on the movement as in the csgo.</p>
<ol start="5">
<li>
<ul>
<li>They should rework the enemies in the game because it feels bad to play them, from the beginning I never liked the (bullsquid), (zombies), (vortigaunts), especially I never like the zombies in the series of Half Life, there are to give them a turn to make them more dangerous, I will tell them how I would have liked those enemies to be.</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ol>
<ul>
<li>
<p>Bullsquid, they are intelligent animals, they should lurk, but when you leave their field of vision “they are deactivated”, they should follow you, in addition to attacking body to body, spitting and make a charge.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Vortigaunt, they should be more defensive always hidding, because they are more intelligent, apart they should having a faster reaction for the attack time “they are very slow and weak”.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Zombies, i would have liked the (zombies) from the beginning, were dressed with all personal skins (guards, scientist, workers), and not have a recognizable head model, and also that followed the pattern of (poison zombies) that had many (headcrabs) in his body and In addition to throwing, also that throw things, and when more headcrabs have more stronger is, also can walk and run like (zombine).<br>
Side Note; not every single zombie have to be like that, but with this we have variety, (no only in models also in difficulty), and diversion of the game.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<ol start="6">
<li>
<ul>
<li>You must add the construction workers, machinists, electricians (they can create a model and change the tone of the suit to deduce in what zone it works, blue as an electrician) office employees, administrators (because each zone has to have a boss ), and people with a hazmat suit because there are areas where we go through machinery that contains radiation.</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>
<ul>
<li>Should return the variants of the (headcrabs) and the zombies of their respective classes, because they already existed in xen and are evolutions or subspecies of them, also should add the (antlions) to xen, even in inaccessible areas, just to have them of decoration would be a detail of the which you would be congratulated.</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ol>
<p>8.- the arsenal, all weapons should have a secondary trigger, with an alternative animation and all weapons (except the hornetgun, and throwables) should have an animation to recharge following the logic of weapons clear, also should remove the shared ammunition of weapons.<br>
Side Note; All those weapons changes that I propose are good ideas of how it should evolve in the future if you want, can add a difficulty that could be (classic that keeps things as they are).</p>
<p>Slot 1 - Crowbar, if the lever could be programmed to function as the melee weapons of (left 4 dead 2), in which sweep an area in front of the player, and not that point in the middle of the screen, also add a secondary attack, heavier.</p>
<p>Slot 2 - Pistol, it could be a glock model 20 - 10mm, 15 bullets, the secondary trigger causes it to fire a burst of 3 bullets.<br>
Side Note; the fire-rate would be the same in burst but you will be able to shoot 2 or 3 bullets per shoot.</p>
<p>Slot 2 - Magnum i no like the fact it is a python, el modelo que mas se parece es un S&amp;W m29 with 6 bullets, secondary trigger laser sight or who’s prefer a fast shoots.<br>
Side Note, for me, the iron sight is out of context, I prefer a new mechanic as a laser sight with better precision or on the secondary trigger shoot faster by hammering manually with the hand.</p>
<p>Slot 3 - Submachinegun, the mp5 that you developed is almost perfect, only lacks the animation of recharging the grenade launcher.<br>
Side Note; we should have the possibility to change it for an m4 with an m203 with its complete set of animations.</p>
<p>Slot 3 - Shotgun, the prefer model of SPAS-12C with a folding stock, and its secondary trigger should be switched to semi-automatic mode to semi-auto/pump-action.<br>
Side Note; this change will improve the way of play of the SPAS-12C, because you can select in the moments of accion, semi-auto, in the moments more slower can select to pump for no waste ammo.</p>
<p>Slot 3 - Crossbow - the crossbow is perfect, only that they should improve the optical sight in one way or another, or place an animated sprite, to optimize the performance impact it has.</p>
<p>Slot 4 - RPG, the problem with the (RPG) is that it feels weak and light, should not be so, also has a (fire-rate) very high, should be slower, cause more damage, and a larger radius of explosion, be more lethal.</p>
<p>Slot 4 - Gauss Gun; this weapon needs a total repair, it should be like a shotgun firing 5 times and then turning the cylinder (it will rotate the cylinder 3 times, 15 shots) then it runs out of ammunition, the secondary trigger turns the cylinder and you perform a concentrated shot while spending 5 shots in 1, and a recharge animation and one for the secondary trigger.</p>
<p>Slot 4 - Gluon Gun, i suggest that you should add it, a secondary trigger and a recharge animation, the secondary trigger would trigger a slightly wider wave of gluon that would be useful to fight against bosses.</p>
<p>Slot 4 - Hornet gun, remains intact.</p>
<p>Slot 5 - Granada, should create something similar to what did valve with its grenades of csgo, you can choose between medium, short and long throwing game with clicks, the rest of this weapon is well elaborated, except the animation what can be improved.</p>
<p>Slot 5 - Satchel, remains intact.</p>
<p>Slot 5 - Tripmine, remain intact.</p>
<p>Slot 5 - snark, the most significant change for this weapon would be that you could take the sack of snarks, and throw them when the sack hit the ground, they would jump from there 6 snark.</p>
<p><div class="lightbox-wrapper"><a class="lightbox" href="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/original/2X/0/0db6f8a397d171f2a7b8f647a1e0f2429bdb4cb9.jpeg" data-download-href="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/0db6f8a397d171f2a7b8f647a1e0f2429bdb4cb9" title="20180705175733_1.jpg"><img src="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/optimized/2X/0/0db6f8a397d171f2a7b8f647a1e0f2429bdb4cb9_2_690x500.jpeg" alt="20180705175733_1.jpg" data-base62-sha1="1XkdIiQXpC7exPmbMd0LnO0x7f3" width="690" height="500" srcset="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/optimized/2X/0/0db6f8a397d171f2a7b8f647a1e0f2429bdb4cb9_2_690x500.jpeg, https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/optimized/2X/0/0db6f8a397d171f2a7b8f647a1e0f2429bdb4cb9_2_1035x750.jpeg 1.5x, https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/optimized/2X/0/0db6f8a397d171f2a7b8f647a1e0f2429bdb4cb9_2_1380x1000.jpeg 2x" data-small-upload="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/optimized/2X/0/0db6f8a397d171f2a7b8f647a1e0f2429bdb4cb9_2_10x10.png"><div class="meta"><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-far-image svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#far-image"></use></svg><span class="filename">20180705175733_1.jpg</span><span class="informations">1920×1080 505 KB</span><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-discourse-expand svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#discourse-expand"></use></svg></div></a></div></p>
<p><div class="lightbox-wrapper"><a class="lightbox" href="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/original/2X/5/58c492624108313211dc2896fef316805583ec33.jpeg" data-download-href="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/58c492624108313211dc2896fef316805583ec33" title="20180705175719_1.jpg"><img src="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/optimized/2X/5/58c492624108313211dc2896fef316805583ec33_2_690x500.jpeg" alt="20180705175719_1.jpg" data-base62-sha1="cFhazE8pF11fZk1GEDmGfHzFWgz" width="690" height="500" srcset="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/optimized/2X/5/58c492624108313211dc2896fef316805583ec33_2_690x500.jpeg, https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/optimized/2X/5/58c492624108313211dc2896fef316805583ec33_2_1035x750.jpeg 1.5x, https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/optimized/2X/5/58c492624108313211dc2896fef316805583ec33_2_1380x1000.jpeg 2x" data-small-upload="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/optimized/2X/5/58c492624108313211dc2896fef316805583ec33_2_10x10.png"><div class="meta"><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-far-image svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#far-image"></use></svg><span class="filename">20180705175719_1.jpg</span><span class="informations">1920×1080 883 KB</span><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-discourse-expand svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#discourse-expand"></use></svg></div></a></div></p>
            <p><small>5 posts - 3 participants</small></p>
            <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/a-better-look-for-this-game/15422">Read full topic</a></p>
          ]]></description>
          <link>https://leakfree.org/t/a-better-look-for-this-game/15422</link>
          <pubDate>Tue, 20 Nov 2018 16:52:53 +0000</pubDate>
          <discourse:topicPinned>No</discourse:topicPinned>
          <discourse:topicClosed>No</discourse:topicClosed>
          <discourse:topicArchived>No</discourse:topicArchived>
          <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-topic-15422</guid>
          <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/a-better-look-for-this-game/15422.rss">A better look for this game</source>
        </item>
        <item>
          <title>Rev-Amp</title>
          <dc:creator><![CDATA[24Seg]]></dc:creator>
          <category>Source 1</category>
          <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Hello everybody, i want to create a project of Rev-Amp, but more of that! It’s give to BM improved and (sence) in some areas, cause the game itself, it’s too small and out of sence in some parts, and areas, so I’m looking for some help, and if the creators like it,<br>
what im proposing? Im not a expert on hammer, but i have very good ideas, and i have a couple of friends, whos are architects, and they are guide me how can i be the place, with differents conditions. soon illl make an exaple of what’s im saying, im just a fan and i wan’t to improve the game, cause the game, and the dev deserv  a little help.</p>
            <p><small>16 posts - 5 participants</small></p>
            <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/rev-amp/15408">Read full topic</a></p>
          ]]></description>
          <link>https://leakfree.org/t/rev-amp/15408</link>
          <pubDate>Wed, 26 Sep 2018 19:43:54 +0000</pubDate>
          <discourse:topicPinned>No</discourse:topicPinned>
          <discourse:topicClosed>No</discourse:topicClosed>
          <discourse:topicArchived>No</discourse:topicArchived>
          <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-topic-15408</guid>
          <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/rev-amp/15408.rss">Rev-Amp</source>
        </item>
        <item>
          <title>BMPD: Pre-Disaster Apprehension</title>
          <dc:creator><![CDATA[TJHL]]></dc:creator>
          <category>Source 1</category>
          <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I’ve had my eye on Apprehension for some time, mainly to learn the basics of hammer, as the rundown feel gave the impression that a pre-disaster version would very similar.  With Admiral Sakai working on a <a href="https://forums.blackmesasource.com/t/bmpd-pre-disaster-questionable-ethics/14839/47" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">pre-disaster QE transit station</a>, and that there’s actually a lot of inferred story within the maps, I’ve come to realize that apprehension is probably one of the most important chapters for the entire PD project. As Gordon is kidnapped by two marines, the distance between App. and RP could be theoretically as far as the size of black mesa, so an unofficial route has to be made, unless everyone is fine with two drunk barneys replacing the marines in the PD. (That’s called foreshadowing, kids!) Also, one of the biggest things throwing me off track is the doubt of state of repair. “Should this stay how it is, or should i fix it up?”</p>
            <p><small>40 posts - 9 participants</small></p>
            <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/bmpd-pre-disaster-apprehension/15406">Read full topic</a></p>
          ]]></description>
          <link>https://leakfree.org/t/bmpd-pre-disaster-apprehension/15406</link>
          <pubDate>Sat, 08 Sep 2018 18:18:07 +0000</pubDate>
          <discourse:topicPinned>No</discourse:topicPinned>
          <discourse:topicClosed>No</discourse:topicClosed>
          <discourse:topicArchived>No</discourse:topicArchived>
          <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-topic-15406</guid>
          <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/bmpd-pre-disaster-apprehension/15406.rss">BMPD: Pre-Disaster Apprehension</source>
        </item>
        <item>
          <title>BMPD: Pre-Disaster Anomalous Materials</title>
          <dc:creator><![CDATA[Admiral_Sakai]]></dc:creator>
          <category>Source 1</category>
          <description><![CDATA[
            <p>It seems an odd thing to add to the BMPD project given that Anomalous Materials is <span class="bbcode-i">already </span>pre-Disaster, but I was getting some interest in this when I mentioned it in other threads so I thought I’d make it official.</p>
<p>A while back I used Anomalous Materials as a base with which to demo some of my techniques for ambient interior lighting, and actually took a liking to the end result, to the point where I went ahead and did the entirety of bm_c1a0a in that style. In the process I also opened up some of the labs that the player cannot get to in the vanilla map version. A long time ago, SB776 (the guy who did the Lambda Complex PD) and I talked about making a version of AM with a working, non-Resonance-Cascade-causing anti-mass-spectrometer, so I decided to run with that and include it along with documents and connection to the pre-disaster transit system. Expect more to be filled out on the details of this project as I get it ready to show- most of the geometry of pd_c1a0a is actually already done, but there’s a good bit of logic still left to do and since this was originally his idea I was planning to see if SB776 was still around and if he had any suggestions.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">MEDIA</span></p>
<p>pd_c1a0a: <a href="https://forums.blackmesasource.com/index.php/Thread/45503-BMPD-Pre-Disaster-Anomalous-Materials/?postID=649620#post649620" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">LINK</a><br>
pd_c1a0b: <a href="https://forums.blackmesasource.com/index.php/Thread/45503-BMPD-Pre-Disaster-Anomalous-Materials/?postID=649953#post649953" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">LINK</a></p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">DEVELOPMENT NOTES</span></p>
<p>pd_c1a0a: <a href="https://forums.blackmesasource.com/index.php/Thread/45503-BMPD-Pre-Disaster-Anomalous-Materials/?postID=649596#post649596" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">LINK</a><br>
pd_c1a0b: Work In Progress</p>
            <p><small>50 posts - 14 participants</small></p>
            <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/bmpd-pre-disaster-anomalous-materials/15404">Read full topic</a></p>
          ]]></description>
          <link>https://leakfree.org/t/bmpd-pre-disaster-anomalous-materials/15404</link>
          <pubDate>Sat, 18 Aug 2018 20:59:51 +0000</pubDate>
          <discourse:topicPinned>No</discourse:topicPinned>
          <discourse:topicClosed>No</discourse:topicClosed>
          <discourse:topicArchived>No</discourse:topicArchived>
          <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-topic-15404</guid>
          <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/bmpd-pre-disaster-anomalous-materials/15404.rss">BMPD: Pre-Disaster Anomalous Materials</source>
        </item>
        <item>
          <title>&quot;Evacuation&quot; / &quot;Rescue&quot; Singleplayer Map Mode</title>
          <dc:creator><![CDATA[Admiral_Sakai]]></dc:creator>
          <category>Black Mesa</category>
          <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I’ve been tossing around for a little while now the idea of a type of singleplayer map where the objective is to hunt down as many friendly NPCs as possible in various locations throughout a map and bring them safely to an elevator, evac chopper, or other safe area. There’s levels somewhat like this in Half-Life and its expansions, but to my knowledge it has never been attempted in quite the same way:</p>
<ul>
<li>
<p>Office Complex in Half-Life/Black Mesa allows you to accumulate quite a number of friendly NPCs as you travel through the level, but they don’t really <span class="bbcode-i">do</span> anything once you get to the end.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Questionable Ethics requires the player to bring a scientist to the end of the level to open a door, but all the scientists are in one place.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Blue Shift’s Captive Freight has multiple scientists located throughout who then appear in later levels and evacuate the facility with you, but they automatically survive regardless of what the player does.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Decay has Domestic Violence where a security guard needs to be found and saved among many who are being threatened by enemies, but again only one is actually savable.<br>
A dedicated ‘evac’ map style would, I think, introduce a number of gameplay elements rarely found in standard HL/Black Mesa style levels:</p>
</li>
<li>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Multiple Degrees Of Success</span>: I am thinking it will be possible to technically ‘complete’ the level in the sense of getting to the end of it with all or nearly all of the NPCs dead, but the number the player saved will explicitly be tallied at the end and possibly result in additional items/dialogue/whatever. I am thinking that not all NPCs will be placed equally, with some being very easy to find/save and some being very difficult- think of it like a Metroidvania or Zelda style gamewith optional items where there’s a concept of a completion percentage and a 100% run.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">“Broad” Multi-Objective Gameplay</span>: While there are exceptions and a fair number of side areas to explore, typically HL/Black Mesa gameplay is fairly directional and linear. I am imagining that an evacuation map will have much less of a directional quality since NPCs can be found in many different places and recovered in different orders. At the same time, there is no reason <span class="bbcode-i">every</span> area has to be accessible from the start without completing some secondary objective elsewhere in the map.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Defense of Fixed Positions Or Non-Player Objectives</span>: Escort missions are generally derided for a number of pretty good reasons, but used in moderation I think protecting NPCs from enemy attacks could be a tense, interesting element of gameplay.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Time Pressure</span>: I don’t think having NPCs die at predetermined intervals while the player is doing something completely unrelated is necessarily <span class="bbcode-i">fair</span>, but once they are in sight of the player it would be fairly easy to create a variety of situations where said player has to think quickly to kill an enemy or de-activate an environmental hazard threatening them- from simple tasks on the order of a second or two to more complex tasks involving the environment which must be done within a relatively large number of minutes.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Secondary Objectives to Make Areas Navigable</span>: Once the player has FOUND an NPC that may not be the end of interaction with them; the way the player <span class="bbcode-i">got</span> to them might not be usable as a way out, requiring additional player effort to secure a safe evacuation route.<br>
The big obstacle I see to this sort of map is that just using their native AI the Black Mesa NPCs are not particularly adept at navigating dangerous areas or moving around in large groups, and while Black Mesa typically works around this by keeping their actions heavily scripted the scripts are not then in turn moddable.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<p>Is this something people would be interested in playing?</p>
            <p><small>10 posts - 4 participants</small></p>
            <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/evacuation-rescue-singleplayer-map-mode/15381">Read full topic</a></p>
          ]]></description>
          <link>https://leakfree.org/t/evacuation-rescue-singleplayer-map-mode/15381</link>
          <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jun 2018 19:25:35 +0000</pubDate>
          <discourse:topicPinned>No</discourse:topicPinned>
          <discourse:topicClosed>No</discourse:topicClosed>
          <discourse:topicArchived>No</discourse:topicArchived>
          <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-topic-15381</guid>
          <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/evacuation-rescue-singleplayer-map-mode/15381.rss">&quot;Evacuation&quot; / &quot;Rescue&quot; Singleplayer Map Mode</source>
        </item>
        <item>
          <title>Convex Collision Meshes In Blender</title>
          <dc:creator><![CDATA[Admiral_Sakai]]></dc:creator>
          <category>Source 1</category>
          <description><![CDATA[
            <p>So I’m making a modified version of a prop (a mirrored “table_l” desk) in Blender using Crowbar decompilations, and am having some problems with the collision model. I am for whatever reason not able to split it into convex parts properly, and the recompilation just produces a “shrink-wrap” collision which needless to say is effectively unusable for this highly concave prop. The ancient SDW tutorial describes a way to export multiple groups in one model file using a ‘set smooth’ tool, but this seems to have been removed from the new versions of Blender and all I can seem to do is export the collision mesh as multiple <span class="bbcode-i">files</span> which the compiler will not accept.</p>
<p>How to proceed?</p>
            <p><small>6 posts - 3 participants</small></p>
            <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/convex-collision-meshes-in-blender/15379">Read full topic</a></p>
          ]]></description>
          <link>https://leakfree.org/t/convex-collision-meshes-in-blender/15379</link>
          <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jun 2018 20:16:33 +0000</pubDate>
          <discourse:topicPinned>No</discourse:topicPinned>
          <discourse:topicClosed>No</discourse:topicClosed>
          <discourse:topicArchived>No</discourse:topicArchived>
          <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-topic-15379</guid>
          <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/convex-collision-meshes-in-blender/15379.rss">Convex Collision Meshes In Blender</source>
        </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
