<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Early Magnum</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/early-magnum/13857</link>
    <description>I noticed this when playing the mod pre steam and was always curious about the reasoning behind the design change of this weapons entry into the player&#39;s arsenal. Originally it was acquired after defeating the tentacles in Blast Pit, now it is acquired in We&#39;ve Got Hostiles where the player would normally acquire the shotgun. The player then gets the shotgun off of the marines shortly thereafter (or maybe it was in Blast Pit). I don&#39;t think anyone has reason to complain about having that extra bit of firepower going into the fights with the military but I am curious as to why the crowbar collective decided on this. It is a good decision, just curious about it.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 10 May 2015 23:35:49 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>The Cafeteria</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/early-magnum/13857.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Early Magnum</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Stairway_To_Sto_Vo_K]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I played through most of the mod version a couple months ago, and I first got the magnum after killing the zombie guard. I got the steam version a few days ago and I  first got the magnum by taking the alternate path through the ceiling in office complex, in the big room with partitioned workstations where multiple vortigaunts spawn. The magnum was by the dead guard in the hole where the 2nd ceiling sentry is. I forgot how i ended up at the place with the zombie guard, but I didn’t come across that area on the steam version. Just thought of it yesterday and was wondering where you DO go to reach that spot.</p>
<p>Also about the (steam version)shotgun, unless you’re literally arm-length away from enemies it seems to do pathetic damage. Not sure why.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/early-magnum/13857/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/early-magnum/13857/5</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 10 May 2015 23:35:49 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13857-5</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/early-magnum/13857.rss">Early Magnum</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Early Magnum</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Slendgy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I think it just had to do with the weapon rebalancing. The shotgun is more for bullet-sponges in this version, and almost a wast against normal enemies, as it tends to be overkill. It just made sense as there weren’t many high-HP enemies in office complex.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/early-magnum/13857/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/early-magnum/13857/4</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 10 May 2015 23:25:36 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13857-4</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/early-magnum/13857.rss">Early Magnum</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Early Magnum</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Lord_Arion]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Yeah, that is the spot where originally you’d get the shotgun. I’m just curious as to why they moved the magnum up so much in its entry into the player’s arsenal. The extra firepower is nice and I’m not complaining. As a game designer I am just curious to understand the design choice as I work through college and my own games. Its a good design choice, I’m just curious what brought about that change.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/early-magnum/13857/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/early-magnum/13857/3</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 07 May 2015 21:05:03 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13857-3</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/early-magnum/13857.rss">Early Magnum</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Early Magnum</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[FalkeXY]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Havent played the Steam Version but i’m pretty sure you can acquire the first Magnum in Office Complex. There is an optional path that you can take where a security guard wants you to ‘help’ his zombified buddy. If you kill the zombie, the guard lets you into a weapons room where you can find a magnum.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/early-magnum/13857/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/early-magnum/13857/2</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 07 May 2015 19:18:40 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13857-2</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/early-magnum/13857.rss">Early Magnum</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Early Magnum</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Lord_Arion]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I noticed this when playing the mod pre steam and was always curious about the reasoning behind the design change of this weapons entry into the player’s arsenal. Originally it was acquired after defeating the tentacles in Blast Pit, now it is acquired in We’ve Got Hostiles where the player would normally acquire the shotgun. The player then gets the shotgun off of the marines shortly thereafter (or maybe it was in Blast Pit). I don’t think anyone has reason to complain about having that extra bit of firepower going into the fights with the military but I am curious as to why the crowbar collective decided on this. It is a good decision, just curious about it.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/early-magnum/13857/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/early-magnum/13857/1</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 07 May 2015 03:44:33 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13857-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/early-magnum/13857.rss">Early Magnum</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
