<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Weird Performance Issue</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/weird-performance-issue/62951</link>
    <description>Just signed up to the forum to post bugs. I did post it on the Steam forum, but I figured it&#39;d be better seen on here.

I&#39;m currently on chapter 8 - On a Rail. I&#39;m at the part where you overhear two guards talking about Gordon outside. However, when going outside, the performance goes... weird. Despite my frame rate being well above 60fps, everything feels... janky. As though there&#39;s some erratic frame pacing issue when the frame rate changes. Even if I set the graphics settings to low, it&#39;s still the same. Likewise if I turn off G-Sync.

My spec:

Windows 10 Home
i7 4790K
MSI GTX 1080
16GB RAM
And I&#39;m running off an SSD.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 08 Mar 2020 23:04:30 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>In-game Issues</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/weird-performance-issue/62951.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Weird Performance Issue</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Gazzoid]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Just signed up to the forum to post bugs. I did post it on the Steam forum, but I figured it’d be better seen on here.</p>
<p>I’m currently on chapter 8 - On a Rail. I’m at the part where you overhear two guards talking about Gordon outside. However, when going outside, the performance goes… weird. Despite my frame rate being well above 60fps, everything feels… janky. As though there’s some erratic frame pacing issue when the frame rate changes. Even if I set the graphics settings to low, it’s still the same. Likewise if I turn off G-Sync.</p>
<p>My spec:</p>
<p>Windows 10 Home<br>
i7 4790K<br>
MSI GTX 1080<br>
16GB RAM<br>
And I’m running off an SSD.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/weird-performance-issue/62951/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/weird-performance-issue/62951/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 08 Mar 2020 23:04:30 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-62951-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/weird-performance-issue/62951.rss">Weird Performance Issue</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
