<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Source Multiplayer Games</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/source-multiplayer-games/7978</link>
    <description>Is it me or am I the only one who gets this crappy 1 hit death at any part on my body shot. On any source game I play it&#39;s the same, I unload half+ a clip on someone&#39;s upper torso or head and they one-bullet kill me with ANY gun at ANY part on my body, I recently discovered Day of Defeat: Source is probably one of my new favorite games (I never played the original.) and it&#39;s getting annoying when I play on GunGame or any other server and I randomly get 1 hit deaths.

Anyone else get this?</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 18 Oct 2011 21:02:28 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Technology and Gaming</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/source-multiplayer-games/7978.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Source Multiplayer Games</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[MDIGN]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Sorry, not all source games, just counter-strike and DoD atm. I know it isn’t headshots because it should say so on the kill log, there would also be some sort of blood on my character’s head were it from a headshot. multiple enemies shooting me is not too likely, but probable, as usually when i’m 1 shot killed i’m only around one person(enemy). I’m not the only person though as I have seen people get hit by the same thing, and heard about it from them too, also I have gotten one shot kills at random from 100% HP enemies.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/source-multiplayer-games/7978/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/source-multiplayer-games/7978/4</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 18 Oct 2011 21:02:28 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7978-4</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/source-multiplayer-games/7978.rss">Source Multiplayer Games</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Source Multiplayer Games</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[robot_deodorant]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>In DoD it is possible to die from one bullet. Not always, but possible. Usually the frustration of “unloading my entire clip into them!” comes from bad aim. DoD has recoil, once you’re really used to it you can adjust… one of the best ways is by crouching. It will reduce recoil and increase your accuracy.</p>
<p>GunGame can be harder to track who is killing you if the killcam isn’t on, but anyone with a decent rifle aimed at you can take you out if you are focused on one person atm.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/source-multiplayer-games/7978/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/source-multiplayer-games/7978/3</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 17 Oct 2011 23:38:45 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7978-3</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/source-multiplayer-games/7978.rss">Source Multiplayer Games</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Source Multiplayer Games</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Orpheon]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I think you’re going to have to be more specific than that. It’s not possible that you always get killed in 1 shot with any gun hitting you at any point in your body in any source game.</p>
<p>In Counter Strike, it has to be a headshot to be a 1-hit kill, unless you’re already low on health, in which case it’s not really a 1 hit kill. I think maybe an AWP could bodyshot you in 1 hit also, but most guns will take a number of hits to kill you.</p>
<p>In TF2, there are only a few things that can 1 hit you, such as a sniper headshot, a spy’s backstab, a sticky bomb trap, crit rockets, etc. Generally it’s easier to stay alive in TF2 than other FPS games.</p>
<p>Haven’t played DoD, so can’t comment on that. But it sounds to me that other people can just aim better and take you out with headshots before you can kill them with bodyshots. It’s also very likely, since you’re playing gungame, that several people are shooting you at once, so it just seems like you’re getting 1 hit killed with bodyshots, when you actually take a lot of damage from several sources at once.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/source-multiplayer-games/7978/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/source-multiplayer-games/7978/2</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 17 Oct 2011 23:08:49 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7978-2</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/source-multiplayer-games/7978.rss">Source Multiplayer Games</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Source Multiplayer Games</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[MDIGN]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Is it me or am I the only one who gets this crappy 1 hit death at any part on my body shot. On any source game I play it’s the same, I unload half+ a clip on someone’s upper torso or head and they one-bullet kill me with ANY gun at ANY part on my body, I recently discovered Day of Defeat: Source is probably one of my new favorite games (I never played the original.) and it’s getting annoying when I play on GunGame or any other server and I randomly get 1 hit deaths.</p>
<p>Anyone else get this?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/source-multiplayer-games/7978/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/source-multiplayer-games/7978/1</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 17 Oct 2011 20:38:15 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7978-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/source-multiplayer-games/7978.rss">Source Multiplayer Games</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
