<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>What to do about friend&#39;s suicide will</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/what-to-do-about-friends-suicide-will/11520</link>
    <description>I lost my best friend a couple days ago to suicide. I&#39;ve been dealing with it ok so far, but today I visited his parents and they showed me the note he left, in which he instructed that I receive some possessions of his. Here is where I&#39;m unsure of what to do or how to feel. I feel like it would be strange and painful to take and especially to use things that were his, like his computer. But should I take these things out of respect for his wishes? Should I hold on to them until I can better decide how I feel, or should I just get rid of them? Or let his parents keep them? If anyone has gone through this before, please share your thoughts and feelings. Maybe I will get some insight from your experiences.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Nov 2012 12:11:36 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Off Topic</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/what-to-do-about-friends-suicide-will/11520.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>What to do about friend&#39;s suicide will</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Eric_Fong]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>That’s helps alot, I am trying my best</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/what-to-do-about-friends-suicide-will/11520/45">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/what-to-do-about-friends-suicide-will/11520/45</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 03 Nov 2012 12:11:36 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11520-45</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/what-to-do-about-friends-suicide-will/11520.rss">What to do about friend&#39;s suicide will</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>What to do about friend&#39;s suicide will</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Orpheon]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I’m sorry to hear that. Friends can be a great support in hard times. They may not show it under normal circumstances, but most people who know us often care much deeper about us than we might expect or realize.</p>
<p>Try to remember too, that problems are often temporary, but death is always a permanent solution. If you keep hanging on and keep working at it, you can get past the dark spots and enjoy life again. Your friends and family are more than willing to help you. Please do not hesitate to ask, or to seek medical treatment if you need it. The suffering a loved one leaves behind after suicide is almost unbearable. There is nothing a real friend or family member would not do to avert that and help relieve your pain.</p>
<p>Also, I know work can be stressful, and your employers often want to make your work come first in your life, but <span class="bbcode-i">it’s still your life</span>. You choose your priorities. I can’t and don’t presume to know your circumstances, but work and money should not come above your well-being and happiness if at all possible. Everywhere is different, of course, and I hope that in some way you can regain some balance and peace in your life soon…</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/what-to-do-about-friends-suicide-will/11520/44">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/what-to-do-about-friends-suicide-will/11520/44</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Nov 2012 08:26:41 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11520-44</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/what-to-do-about-friends-suicide-will/11520.rss">What to do about friend&#39;s suicide will</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>What to do about friend&#39;s suicide will</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Eric_Fong]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Sorry for your lost, losing your best friend is very hard to get over.</p>
<p>Few month ago, I’ve struggled through the though of suicide and cut myself several times. Until one day mother saw the cut and she cried. I know she love me as her son and since then. I am trying to fix my depression and anxiety by hanging out with my friends as much as I can. Still, it is very hard to get the though of suicide out of my mind due to the stress of work.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/what-to-do-about-friends-suicide-will/11520/43">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/what-to-do-about-friends-suicide-will/11520/43</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Nov 2012 11:22:11 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11520-43</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/what-to-do-about-friends-suicide-will/11520.rss">What to do about friend&#39;s suicide will</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>What to do about friend&#39;s suicide will</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Mabilis]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>You have my condolences Orpheon, and I am glad you take the support from people here well.</p>
<p>I agree very much with Disturbulator. However, like the body, I believe the mind can heal; what doesn’t kill you makes you stronger as they say… even if it is as bad as trauma, WHEN someone gets healed with therapy, they will be a stronger person than someone who hasn’t gone through the experience.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/what-to-do-about-friends-suicide-will/11520/42">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/what-to-do-about-friends-suicide-will/11520/42</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 25 Oct 2012 10:05:58 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11520-42</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/what-to-do-about-friends-suicide-will/11520.rss">What to do about friend&#39;s suicide will</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>What to do about friend&#39;s suicide will</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Khaney]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>^well said</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/what-to-do-about-friends-suicide-will/11520/41">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/what-to-do-about-friends-suicide-will/11520/41</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 25 Oct 2012 09:44:12 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11520-41</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/what-to-do-about-friends-suicide-will/11520.rss">What to do about friend&#39;s suicide will</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>What to do about friend&#39;s suicide will</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Disturbulator]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Everyone has a tragic story to tell, some are severe, others not so much. The body may heal, but the mind is not so resilient.<br>
I’d share my story, but speaking objectively I doubt many people here bother reading into others’ tales.</p>
<p>Main point being, no one is ever truly alone, and people do care for your well being, even if they don’t show it openly.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/what-to-do-about-friends-suicide-will/11520/40">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/what-to-do-about-friends-suicide-will/11520/40</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 25 Oct 2012 06:14:12 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11520-40</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/what-to-do-about-friends-suicide-will/11520.rss">What to do about friend&#39;s suicide will</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>What to do about friend&#39;s suicide will</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Orpheon]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Sorry I haven’t checked back in for a while. I just wanted to say thanks again for everyone’s support and stories.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/what-to-do-about-friends-suicide-will/11520/39">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/what-to-do-about-friends-suicide-will/11520/39</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 25 Oct 2012 05:39:38 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11520-39</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/what-to-do-about-friends-suicide-will/11520.rss">What to do about friend&#39;s suicide will</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>What to do about friend&#39;s suicide will</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Khaney]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>am glad I had a great time both in school and collage, had a lot of friends back then, and I mean a lot!, never had any trouble with bullying =]</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/what-to-do-about-friends-suicide-will/11520/38">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/what-to-do-about-friends-suicide-will/11520/38</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 21 Oct 2012 13:46:15 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11520-38</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/what-to-do-about-friends-suicide-will/11520.rss">What to do about friend&#39;s suicide will</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>What to do about friend&#39;s suicide will</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[SarahDank]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Winged One">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Winged One:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>That’s the short and the end of it for me, too.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>id be in the same boat too.</p>
<p><a class="mention" href="/u/theegoatpig">@TheeGoatPig</a> -<br>
Those things… that fact that people do that kind of thing… I shit you not it makes my blood boil. If I saw that happen to anyone, Id be right there with a bat.<br>
Unfortunately… some people unluckily don’t make it to that part of their life when it all gets better.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/what-to-do-about-friends-suicide-will/11520/37">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/what-to-do-about-friends-suicide-will/11520/37</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 21 Oct 2012 12:46:38 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11520-37</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/what-to-do-about-friends-suicide-will/11520.rss">What to do about friend&#39;s suicide will</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>What to do about friend&#39;s suicide will</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[MDIGN]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Khaney">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/k/838e76/40.png" class="avatar"> Khaney:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>wow, didn’t know that we had members who considered suicide at some point of their life</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I have considered faking my death and making it appear real in way that they have nothing to bury(pretending to jump off of a cliff where someone sees me, but landing on some hidden ledge.) and then moving on and eventually come back to my family and friends after a few years. I find that most people really don’t want to die, they just want to get away from their current lives.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/what-to-do-about-friends-suicide-will/11520/36">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/what-to-do-about-friends-suicide-will/11520/36</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 21 Oct 2012 02:26:42 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11520-36</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/what-to-do-about-friends-suicide-will/11520.rss">What to do about friend&#39;s suicide will</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>What to do about friend&#39;s suicide will</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[JeffMOD]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Sorry for your loss, Orpheon. My first thought was already said by Strangelove, but that’s not necessarily the case, maybe he just wanted you to benefit from his rig, rather than having something hidden away for you on it.<br>
If it’s what he wanted, I personally think you should do it. (Which, looking back on the thread, you have already decided to)</p>
<p>I felt like an outcast for all of primary school, and the first year and a half or so of secondary/high school, because by then I was too withdrawn to seek out new friends (which I did find eventually) I attempted suicide twice <span class="bbcode-i">(both poorly thought out plans involving falling from heights when I was very young and not overly aware of just how high a fall you’d need to even sustain injuries more serious than bruises)</span> and I thought about it briefly quite a few other times over the years when things were going particularly poorly.</p>
<p>But then I realized that’s what they* want me to do. So fuck them.<br>
I wish more people would come to this train of thought rather than killing themselves.  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/frowning.png?v=9" title=":frowning:" class="emoji" alt=":frowning:"></p>
<p><span class="bbcode-i">*I have no idea who “they” are, or if they exist, but they are bad people and don’t deserve to have their way.</span></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/what-to-do-about-friends-suicide-will/11520/35">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/what-to-do-about-friends-suicide-will/11520/35</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 21 Oct 2012 01:30:24 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11520-35</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/what-to-do-about-friends-suicide-will/11520.rss">What to do about friend&#39;s suicide will</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>What to do about friend&#39;s suicide will</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[TheeGoatPig]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>It hampered my ability to stand up for myself. It hampered my ability to make friends. Derrick would have been a no good piece of shit either way, but if I hadn’t been stunted, I might have had a friend on my side, if not in grade school than in high school, maybe. The world will never know though.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/what-to-do-about-friends-suicide-will/11520/34">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/what-to-do-about-friends-suicide-will/11520/34</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 20 Oct 2012 20:08:14 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11520-34</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/what-to-do-about-friends-suicide-will/11520.rss">What to do about friend&#39;s suicide will</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>What to do about friend&#39;s suicide will</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Khaney]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>it’s not your fault, some people are just MEAN bastards who really are a waste of oxygen, but be glad since you said that you’re happy with your job and life now  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/wink.png?v=9" title=":wink:" class="emoji" alt=":wink:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/what-to-do-about-friends-suicide-will/11520/33">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/what-to-do-about-friends-suicide-will/11520/33</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 20 Oct 2012 20:06:38 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11520-33</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/what-to-do-about-friends-suicide-will/11520.rss">What to do about friend&#39;s suicide will</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>What to do about friend&#39;s suicide will</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[TheeGoatPig]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I almost slammed a pipe clamp into a kid’s head in wood shop one year. I am so surprised I didn’t. He would have been dead, and I would have died in jail (I wouldn’t have made it to prison).</p>
<p>I still want to punch Derrick Freedman in the gut a few times (the kind who punched my in elementary school). Yeah, I said his real name. I don’t give a shit right now.</p>
<p>also, you have to remember, I was epileptic as a child. I started taking medication for it in the 3rd grade, but it slowed me down socially for over a decade of my life. I still don’t think I have caught up…</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/what-to-do-about-friends-suicide-will/11520/32">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/what-to-do-about-friends-suicide-will/11520/32</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 20 Oct 2012 19:13:53 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11520-32</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/what-to-do-about-friends-suicide-will/11520.rss">What to do about friend&#39;s suicide will</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>What to do about friend&#39;s suicide will</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Khaney]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="TheeGoatPig">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/user_avatar/leakfree.org/theegoatpig/40/4495_2.png" class="avatar"> TheeGoatPig:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>For me, I felt like an outcast since my second day of kindergarten. I missed the actual second day of school when they assigned seats, sat in someone else’s seat not knowing, got scolded, and never recovered.</p>
<p>In first and second grade I got punched in the stomach every day after class on the way to the buses.</p>
<p>I have (still) never had a real friend. I didn’t even hang out with anyone in my school days. I asked a girl out in the 7th grade and got teased mercilessly by everyone int he class. Asked another girl out in 10th grade, she said yes and stood me up. Asked another girl out during summer vacation before junior year and got a fake number.</p>
<p>People were always trying to stick stuff on my back, or get gum in my long hair, or stomp on my book bag. I got randomly punched or tripped in the hallway by different people. I was always teased for being incredibly skinny with dry flaky skin and messed up teeth.</p>
<p>My grades were very good and I had no idea what I was going to do directly after high school (even though I was pretty sure of what I would be doing with my life, which is also what I am doing now as an architectural designer).</p>
<p>I just didn’t see things getting any better, ever. I was surprised at how much better they got after I graduated. I got a car, a job, and then a girlfriend, I got into a band, and everything just kept getting better and better.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>man, what a rough childhood you had there, if I was in the same situation as you, I would be long rotting in prison, because I really don’t have that cool temper, I would really killed someone if they kept harassing me like that not the other way around, umm suicide I mean</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/what-to-do-about-friends-suicide-will/11520/31">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/what-to-do-about-friends-suicide-will/11520/31</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 20 Oct 2012 19:10:04 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11520-31</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/what-to-do-about-friends-suicide-will/11520.rss">What to do about friend&#39;s suicide will</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>What to do about friend&#39;s suicide will</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Jack_Freeman]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I still feel like an outcast in my school, but I’ve learnt to live with it.</p>
<p>Also, I’m very sorry for your loss Orpheon.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/what-to-do-about-friends-suicide-will/11520/30">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/what-to-do-about-friends-suicide-will/11520/30</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 20 Oct 2012 18:56:20 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11520-30</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/what-to-do-about-friends-suicide-will/11520.rss">What to do about friend&#39;s suicide will</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>What to do about friend&#39;s suicide will</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[TheeGoatPig]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Khaney">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/k/838e76/40.png" class="avatar"> Khaney:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>damn, School is indeed a hell for lot of kids, mostly the victims of bullying, but what was it that made you wanting to kill yourself so bad ?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>For me, I felt like an outcast since my second day of kindergarten. I missed the actual second day of school when they assigned seats, sat in someone else’s seat not knowing, got scolded, and never recovered.</p>
<p>In first and second grade I got punched in the stomach every day after class on the way to the buses.</p>
<p>I have (still) never had a real friend. I didn’t even hang out with anyone in my school days. I asked a girl out in the 7th grade and got teased mercilessly by everyone int he class. Asked another girl out in 10th grade, she said yes and stood me up. Asked another girl out during summer vacation before junior year and got a fake number.</p>
<p>People were always trying to stick stuff on my back, or get gum in my long hair, or stomp on my book bag. I got randomly punched or tripped in the hallway by different people. I was always teased for being incredibly skinny with dry flaky skin and messed up teeth.</p>
<p>My grades were very good and I had no idea what I was going to do directly after high school (even though I was pretty sure of what I would be doing with my life, which is also what I am doing now as an architectural designer).</p>
<p>I just didn’t see things getting any better, ever. I was surprised at how much better they got after I graduated. I got a car, a job, and then a girlfriend, I got into a band, and everything just kept getting better and better.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/what-to-do-about-friends-suicide-will/11520/29">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/what-to-do-about-friends-suicide-will/11520/29</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 20 Oct 2012 18:43:45 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11520-29</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/what-to-do-about-friends-suicide-will/11520.rss">What to do about friend&#39;s suicide will</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>What to do about friend&#39;s suicide will</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Chickenprotector]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I’m sorry for your loss. I can empathize with your position. The honorable thing to do would be to take the stuff and set it up with what he wanted you to have.</p>
<p>I lost a dear friend of mine about 4 months ago and I didn’t find out about it till a few weeks ago. Drug overdose. It’s no where close to a similar situation mind you, but it’s similar destructive behavior.</p>
<p>I’ve not been in the boots of some of the other members, I never once considered taking my own life, I would say about 1/2 of the way down the road before I just realized there’s more shit in my life than just that and it was just a pointless waste of time. Different people have different coping mechanisms.</p>
<p>I prefer beating the crap out of someone or something through sparring if I’m that upset. Working out helps too. Hold in there, and I hope your friend finds peace in the afterlife.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/what-to-do-about-friends-suicide-will/11520/28">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/what-to-do-about-friends-suicide-will/11520/28</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 20 Oct 2012 17:01:24 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11520-28</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/what-to-do-about-friends-suicide-will/11520.rss">What to do about friend&#39;s suicide will</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>What to do about friend&#39;s suicide will</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[bur]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>For me, school has never had anything to do with it.<br>
The feeling of being stuck in my head is what causes it for me. I’ve felt like that for a long time and it doesn’t seem like it will ever stop.</p>
<p>What Karamazov and Winged One said goes for me too, actually.</p>
<p>So sorry for your loss, Orpheon  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/frowning.png?v=9" title=":frowning:" class="emoji" alt=":frowning:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/what-to-do-about-friends-suicide-will/11520/27">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/what-to-do-about-friends-suicide-will/11520/27</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 20 Oct 2012 15:33:51 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11520-27</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/what-to-do-about-friends-suicide-will/11520.rss">What to do about friend&#39;s suicide will</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>What to do about friend&#39;s suicide will</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Khaney]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>damn, School is indeed a hell for lot of kids, mostly the victims of bullying, but what was it that made you wanting to kill yourself so bad ?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/what-to-do-about-friends-suicide-will/11520/26">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/what-to-do-about-friends-suicide-will/11520/26</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 20 Oct 2012 15:21:11 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11520-26</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/what-to-do-about-friends-suicide-will/11520.rss">What to do about friend&#39;s suicide will</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>What to do about friend&#39;s suicide will</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[TheeGoatPig]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Cheerios4606">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Cheerios4606:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Perhaps cuz people keep hearing the VERY inaccurate saying “High school / College was the best years of my life”.  It may be for some, but for a lot of people, schooling was the all time low in their life.</p>
<p>To someone that is experiencing the worst of it during school years, hearing and believing everything is going to go downhill from there would be crushing.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I consider my life to have started after I graduated high school, got a car, and a job. Things got so much better for me I don’t even know where to start.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Khaney">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/k/838e76/40.png" class="avatar"> Khaney:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>wow, didn’t know that we had members who considered suicide at some point of their life</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I had a gun to my head around 20 years ago when I was 17. I was seriously considering pulling the trigger, and have no idea why I didn’t. Now, the thing that keeps me from ever doing it is that I want to see what happens next. I have become quite a curious fellow.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/what-to-do-about-friends-suicide-will/11520/25">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/what-to-do-about-friends-suicide-will/11520/25</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 20 Oct 2012 15:08:14 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11520-25</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/what-to-do-about-friends-suicide-will/11520.rss">What to do about friend&#39;s suicide will</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>What to do about friend&#39;s suicide will</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Winged_One]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Khaney">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/k/838e76/40.png" class="avatar"> Khaney:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>wow, didn’t know that we had members who considered suicide at some point of their life</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Still do on occasions.  I’ve learned to mostly deal with my emotion in productive ways over the course of <span class="bbcode-i">way too many years</span>, but every now and then i find myself seriously considering the best way to do it without upsetting my relations too much.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/what-to-do-about-friends-suicide-will/11520/24">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/what-to-do-about-friends-suicide-will/11520/24</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 20 Oct 2012 14:40:20 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11520-24</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/what-to-do-about-friends-suicide-will/11520.rss">What to do about friend&#39;s suicide will</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>What to do about friend&#39;s suicide will</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[TheOneAndOnly]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Would you believe? There may even be <span class="bbcode-i">women </span>in here, too! Unbelievable eh?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/what-to-do-about-friends-suicide-will/11520/23">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/what-to-do-about-friends-suicide-will/11520/23</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 20 Oct 2012 13:54:55 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11520-23</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/what-to-do-about-friends-suicide-will/11520.rss">What to do about friend&#39;s suicide will</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>What to do about friend&#39;s suicide will</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Khaney]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>wow, didn’t know that we had members who considered suicide at some point of their life</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/what-to-do-about-friends-suicide-will/11520/22">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/what-to-do-about-friends-suicide-will/11520/22</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 20 Oct 2012 13:24:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11520-22</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/what-to-do-about-friends-suicide-will/11520.rss">What to do about friend&#39;s suicide will</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>What to do about friend&#39;s suicide will</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Winged_One]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Dr. Karamazov">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Dr. Karamazov:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Suicide blows.  The one reason I couldn’t commit suicide (as tempted as I was in my younger more emo years) was because it would really fuck things up for people I knew.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>That’s the short and the end of it for me, too.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/what-to-do-about-friends-suicide-will/11520/21">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/what-to-do-about-friends-suicide-will/11520/21</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 20 Oct 2012 13:12:32 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11520-21</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/what-to-do-about-friends-suicide-will/11520.rss">What to do about friend&#39;s suicide will</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
