<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>No more room in hell (beta 1.06 is out!)</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/no-more-room-in-hell-beta-1-06-is-out/11720</link>
    <description>Hi! 

I&#39;ve just ckecked [url=&#39;https://www.nomoreroominhell.com/&#39;]nmrih.com[/url].
I&#39;ve waited it for a while and finally...

[b]beta 1.06 is out![/b][/SIZE]

[b]WTF is no more room in hell?[/b]
[QUOTE=Wikipedia Eng]
No More Room in Hell is a Source Engine mod. The beta was released on Halloween 2011, after nearly seven years in development. The game is inspired by the Living Dead movies of George Romero. The title is a quote from the movie Dawn of the Dead, &quot;When there&#39;s no more room in hell, the dead will walk the earth.&quot;The zombies in the game are computer-controlled. Up to eight players can play online as the survivors of the zombie apocalypse.[...]
The gameplay is based around survival horror. Firearms and ammunition are limited in availability. There are two gamemodes currently. In Objective mode, the survivors must complete a series of objectives that will allow them to be rescued.[5] Another game mode, survival, is a wave-based survival run with supply drops and safe zones to maintain.[5]
[/QUOTE]
If you want to install nmrih, the procedure is the same as Black mesa(yep! it uses the Source sdk 2007).

[b]
Greenlight news[/b]
[QUOTE=nmrih.com]
Where is Greenlight?!
 Many of you have been wondering when our game will be available on Steam. We are working closely with Valve on making this a reality. We should be ready to launch on Steam with our next patch! We plan on making 1.07 our biggest patch yet. As development happens, we will throw up some videos on our YouTube channel.

 Tired of Survival? Don&#39;t worry! nay0r, Lou Saffire, and thegregster are working on fresh objective maps. That doesn&#39;t mean we won&#39;t be giving you more Survival content though. Shirk is finalizing his map deemed Suburb Survival. In the next few weeks we will be showing you some screenshots and videos of those so keep a vigilant eye out. 

 As for the present, here is Beta 1.06 featuring two new weapons, a new blood tech, and saying goodbye to a lot of old Half-Life 2 content!
[/QUOTE]
You can download it here: [url=&#39;https://www.nomoreroominhell.com/&#39;]https://www.nomoreroominhell.com/[/url]

Let me know if you want to play it...
We can organize something.

Bye!</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 20 Nov 2012 13:10:46 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Half-Life Series</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/no-more-room-in-hell-beta-1-06-is-out/11720.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>No more room in hell (beta 1.06 is out!)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[elivance]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Hi!</p>
<p>I’ve just ckecked <a href="https://www.nomoreroominhell.com/" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">nmrih.com</a>.<br>
I’ve waited it for a while and finally…</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">beta 1.06 is out!</span>[/SIZE]</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">WTF is no more room in hell?</span></p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Wikipedia Eng">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Wikipedia Eng:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>No More Room in Hell is a Source Engine mod. The beta was released on Halloween 2011, after nearly seven years in development. The game is inspired by the Living Dead movies of George Romero. The title is a quote from the movie Dawn of the Dead, "When there’s no more room in hell, the dead will walk the earth."The zombies in the game are computer-controlled. Up to eight players can play online as the survivors of the zombie apocalypse.[…]<br>
The gameplay is based around survival horror. Firearms and ammunition are limited in availability. There are two gamemodes currently. In Objective mode, the survivors must complete a series of objectives that will allow them to be rescued.[5] Another game mode, survival, is a wave-based survival run with supply drops and safe zones to maintain.[5]</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>If you want to install nmrih, the procedure is the same as Black mesa(yep! it uses the Source sdk 2007).</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b"><br>
Greenlight news</span></p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="nmrih.com">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 nmrih.com:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Where is Greenlight?!<br>
Many of you have been wondering when our game will be available on Steam. We are working closely with Valve on making this a reality. We should be ready to launch on Steam with our next patch! We plan on making 1.07 our biggest patch yet. As development happens, we will throw up some videos on our YouTube channel.</p>
<p>Tired of Survival? Don’t worry! nay0r, Lou Saffire, and thegregster are working on fresh objective maps. That doesn’t mean we won’t be giving you more Survival content though. Shirk is finalizing his map deemed Suburb Survival. In the next few weeks we will be showing you some screenshots and videos of those so keep a vigilant eye out.</p>
<p>As for the present, here is Beta 1.06 featuring two new weapons, a new blood tech, and saying goodbye to a lot of old Half-Life 2 content!</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>You can download it here: <a href="https://www.nomoreroominhell.com/" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://www.nomoreroominhell.com/</a></p>
<p>Let me know if you want to play it…<br>
We can organize something.</p>
<p>Bye!</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/no-more-room-in-hell-beta-1-06-is-out/11720/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/no-more-room-in-hell-beta-1-06-is-out/11720/1</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 20 Nov 2012 13:10:46 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11720-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/no-more-room-in-hell-beta-1-06-is-out/11720.rss">No more room in hell (beta 1.06 is out!)</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
