<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Game Freezes on Manual Save</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/game-freezes-on-manual-save/9980</link>
    <description>I played up to the end of... I wanna say it was Blast Pit without a problem, but at seemingly random, whenever I tried to manually save, the game would freeze. This has become more common the further I&#39;ve progressed since then.

The game never exactly crashed though, so it never created a mdmp. What happens is I hit Esc &gt; Save Game, and the menu highlight sound would get stuck in a loop. The second time this happened, I let it sit for a minute or so. It didn&#39;t unfreeze, so I hit Ctrl+Alt+Delete, and the instant I hit it, it unfroze. This hasn&#39;t worked anytime since.

The game generally runs fine. I don&#39;t have the best computer in the world by far, but it runs most games acceptably. It&#39;s just the &#39;Save Freezing&#39; that is testing my patience. Other than that, the game is great, and I have REALLY been enjoying it. I can&#39;t thank you enough for making Black Mesa.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 20 Sep 2012 05:35:54 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>In-game Issues (Mod)</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/game-freezes-on-manual-save/9980.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Game Freezes on Manual Save</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Bud_Hempstead]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I had a problem where manually saving quit working, so I moved all but my first manual save, plus that last 20 or so saves and now it works fine.<br>
I think it may be a Source problem I did not see in other games, as I find I am saving more often than normal in Black Mesa.<br>
I hope this helps you.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/game-freezes-on-manual-save/9980/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/game-freezes-on-manual-save/9980/2</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 20 Sep 2012 05:35:54 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9980-2</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/game-freezes-on-manual-save/9980.rss">Game Freezes on Manual Save</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Game Freezes on Manual Save</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Setsugami]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I played up to the end of… I wanna say it was Blast Pit without a problem, but at seemingly random, whenever I tried to manually save, the game would freeze. This has become more common the further I’ve progressed since then.</p>
<p>The game never exactly crashed though, so it never created a mdmp. What happens is I hit Esc &gt; Save Game, and the menu highlight sound would get stuck in a loop. The second time this happened, I let it sit for a minute or so. It didn’t unfreeze, so I hit Ctrl+Alt+Delete, and the instant I hit it, it unfroze. This hasn’t worked anytime since.</p>
<p>The game generally runs fine. I don’t have the best computer in the world by far, but it runs most games acceptably. It’s just the ‘Save Freezing’ that is testing my patience. Other than that, the game is great, and I have REALLY been enjoying it. I can’t thank you enough for making Black Mesa.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/game-freezes-on-manual-save/9980/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/game-freezes-on-manual-save/9980/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 15 Sep 2012 19:39:07 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9980-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/game-freezes-on-manual-save/9980.rss">Game Freezes on Manual Save</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
