<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Freeman military story line suggestion</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/freeman-military-story-line-suggestion/11123</link>
    <description>Some thoughts I have about beefing up the story structure of the relationship between Freeman and the military.

Starting with &#39;Weve got Hostiles&#39; I&#39;d move that scripted conversation at the end of the chapter (where the HECU talk about killing scientist) to the very first encounter where the first scientist gets gunned down. Start that sequence a little earlier when you first enter that area and have two HECU there and have them do the conversation after killing that scientist, after which you proceed through the rest of &#39;Weve got Hostiles&#39; wasting all the HECU in that chapter. Then where that conversation used to be at the end have a new one where the HECU are interrogating a scientist who tells them who you are.

You are now setup for &#39;Power Up&#39; where you encounter the militarys first base camp and they know who you are. This area is already setup for that as it&#39;s the first time they start calling you by name. Only thing I would add to that is a radioset in their position that is broadcasting your information that they discovered at the end of &#39;Weve got Hostiles&#39;.

They figured out who you were in &#39;weve got hostiles&#39; then you over ran thier position in &#39;Power up&#39; so now they should be super pissed and really out to get you in &#39;On a Rail&#39; all setup to really ramp up their desire to get freeman. Start it out right after you lower and cross the bridge with some trip mines in the tunnel leading to the big elevator sentry gun trap. Have words painted on the walls by the trip mines &#39;die freeman!&#39; &#39;payback time freeman!&#39;

In the next section I&#39;d remove the single sentry gun and stick a couple HECUs patrolling that tunnel with a conversation along the line &#39;hey sounds like someone set off the sentry gun trap&#39; &#39;ya think its freeman?&#39; then you come around the corner on the tram. This leads into the first big base camp in &#39;On a Rail&#39; where the HECU should be using much more of the freeman sound bytes. I&#39;d also have the radioset in this area broadcasting to take out freeman.

Everything from there should play out pretty much the same. Some slight modifications, as you advance futhur and futher through &#39;On a Rail&#39; the HECUs chance of saying a freeman related line should increase. With the radiosets throughout &#39;On a Rail&#39; I&#39;d ramp up the get freeman conversation as you move on. Example in &#39;Power up&#39; radioset is just giving out your name. By the first radioset in &#39;On a Rail&#39; it should be telling them to get you, by the next radioset your a priority until you reach the last radioset just before exiting outside to the rocket where its saying at all costs stop freeman dont let him launch that rocket! I&#39;d also setup a trigger for the radiosets so when you get close to them they stop broadcasting the &#39;get freeman&#39; message and say something like &#39;alpha base come in,over&#39; then on the next radioset part of the message can be &#39;lost contact with base alpha, suspect freeman in the area, get him!&#39; ... heh on a side funny note, just an idea, as you take out thier positions and the radio changes from the &#39;freeman&#39; message to a &#39;hello is anybody there message&#39; I thought it would be funny if the person on the other end is getting more and more frustrated as you take out thier positions. Have the broacasts go from a calm &#39;alpha base come in, over&#39; to at the very last one hes super frustrated and is yelling &#39;FREEMAN!!!!&#39; ...also after you launch the rocket, a bunch of HECUs should come piling out of that area that opened up, and they all should be using freeman only lines.


I think these minor changes would really add a lot of emersion and the feeling of really being part of a story to Black Mesa. The additions made by the BM team in the first few chapters was very nicely done and I feel after that it just dropped right out of the game. What do you all think?</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 25 Sep 2012 20:21:20 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>The Cafeteria</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/freeman-military-story-line-suggestion/11123.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Freeman military story line suggestion</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Paz_Ortega_Andrade]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Solokiller">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/s/e56c9b/40.png" class="avatar"> Solokiller:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Most people would just shoot any soldiers they come across, friendly or not.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>It depends.<br>
Some people just kill all the officers of security and scientists they come across also…</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/freeman-military-story-line-suggestion/11123/12">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/freeman-military-story-line-suggestion/11123/12</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 25 Sep 2012 20:21:20 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11123-12</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/freeman-military-story-line-suggestion/11123.rss">Freeman military story line suggestion</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Freeman military story line suggestion</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Solokiller]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Most people would just shoot any soldiers they come across, friendly or not.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/freeman-military-story-line-suggestion/11123/11">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/freeman-military-story-line-suggestion/11123/11</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 25 Sep 2012 20:08:36 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11123-11</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/freeman-military-story-line-suggestion/11123.rss">Freeman military story line suggestion</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Freeman military story line suggestion</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Paz_Ortega_Andrade]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I like the idea of “neutral” or “friendly” soldados. It would make sense later on when the aliens are taking over. I don’t really think that all the soldiers have something against Gordon personally. When it comes to extreme situations like that an enemy of your enemy can become your friend. Especially if that’s a human that is not really interested in slaughtering everything that moves and dying later.</p>
<p>Making some soldiers go neutral or even friendly would, of course, help the story, it’ll seem more realistic from the emotional point of view, but I think that probability of this happening is very low.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/freeman-military-story-line-suggestion/11123/10">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/freeman-military-story-line-suggestion/11123/10</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 25 Sep 2012 19:57:38 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11123-10</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/freeman-military-story-line-suggestion/11123.rss">Freeman military story line suggestion</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Freeman military story line suggestion</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[YosemiteSam]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="RicheyEdwards">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/r/46a35a/40.png" class="avatar"> RicheyEdwards:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I think this sort of shoving exposition in your face would absolutely kill any semblance of the original Half-Life. The entire game is based on the premise that the story is in the background, there for you to make logical assumptions and piece things together if you so choose. It’s kept vague, yet still holds up immaculately.</p>
<p>The Military take control of the VOX and Black Mesa security systems in We’ve Got Hostiles, so from then on they’re watching a bloke running around ripping shit up in an H.E.V. suit (that has tracking devices built into it) on the monitors. It’s fairly obvious that they’d have access to information that could identify you as Gordon Freeman given those circumstances.</p>
<p>Any scenes involving “interrogating scientists” to gain this information, or mentioning Freeman <span class="bbcode-i">purely for the sake of mentioning him</span> would only serve to hurt the storytelling. Less is more, and there’s plenty already there to string things together.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Good point about the interrogation not being needed to indentify Freeman with all the security cameras around.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/freeman-military-story-line-suggestion/11123/9">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/freeman-military-story-line-suggestion/11123/9</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 25 Sep 2012 18:11:15 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11123-9</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/freeman-military-story-line-suggestion/11123.rss">Freeman military story line suggestion</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Freeman military story line suggestion</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Verdale]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="RicheyEdwards">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/r/46a35a/40.png" class="avatar"> RicheyEdwards:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I think this sort of shoving exposition in your face would absolutely kill any semblance of the original Half-Life. The entire game is based on the premise that the story is in the background, there for you to make logical assumptions and piece things together if you so choose. It’s kept vague, yet still holds up immaculately.</p>
<p>…</p>
<p>Less is more, and there’s plenty already there to string things together.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Less is more, perfect way of putting it. Although Episodes One and Two may have deviated a bit from this “show, don’t tell” narrative format, I’d rather the original stay the way that made it so popular.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/freeman-military-story-line-suggestion/11123/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/freeman-military-story-line-suggestion/11123/8</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 25 Sep 2012 17:53:24 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11123-8</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/freeman-military-story-line-suggestion/11123.rss">Freeman military story line suggestion</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Freeman military story line suggestion</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[RicheyEdwards]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I think this sort of shoving exposition in your face would absolutely kill any semblance of the original Half-Life. The entire game is based on the premise that the story is in the background, there for you to make logical assumptions and piece things together if you so choose. It’s kept vague, yet still holds up immaculately.</p>
<p>The Military take control of the VOX and Black Mesa security systems in We’ve Got Hostiles, so from then on they’re watching a bloke running around ripping shit up in an H.E.V. suit (that has tracking devices built into it) on the monitors. It’s fairly obvious that they’d have access to information that could identify you as Gordon Freeman given those circumstances.</p>
<p>Any scenes involving “interrogating scientists” to gain this information, or mentioning Freeman <span class="bbcode-i">purely for the sake of mentioning him</span> would only serve to hurt the storytelling. Less is more, and there’s plenty already there to string things together.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/freeman-military-story-line-suggestion/11123/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/freeman-military-story-line-suggestion/11123/7</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 25 Sep 2012 17:48:24 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11123-7</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/freeman-military-story-line-suggestion/11123.rss">Freeman military story line suggestion</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Freeman military story line suggestion</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Malidictus]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="YosemiteSam">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/y/7feea3/40.png" class="avatar"> YosemiteSam:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I agree and made a suggestion along that line in the ‘is the invasion FUBAR’ thread. I suggested the thought of the HECU wanting to join up with Freeman at the very end too, full 180 from where they are hunting you to wanting your help. Thought it would fit in nicely too considering at that point the military has abandoned them and left them to die, why wouldnt they want to hook up with the Freeman. I like your idea of making an achivement out of it too, be a nice touch.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Well, “the military” joining Freeman strays into fan fiction territory, but having stray Marines help him here and there might not be a bad idea. We already have sort of a precedent to show not all Marines are evil - Adrian Shepard is a good guy, and most of his platoon may be juvenile jackasses, but they’re ultimately good guys, as well. I could see having, say, one stray Marine down to his side-arm hiding behind crates, pinned down by Vorts. You save him and he goes: “Don’t shoot, Freeman! Look, things have gone to hell here, and a bunch of us got left behind. I’m the only one that made it out. I just wanna’ get out of here, so you just leave me alone and I leave you alone, OK?”</p>
<p>Or, hell, it doesn’t even have to have that much dialogue, just have one Marine pinned down who doesn’t shoot at Freeman backed into a corner and have him run away if Freeman leaves the room or basically turns his back on him. It would be an awesome way to show that not only are the military forces outmatched, their chain of command is breaking down and soldiers are are being abandoned to save themselves. You know, like in Opposing Force.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/freeman-military-story-line-suggestion/11123/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/freeman-military-story-line-suggestion/11123/6</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 25 Sep 2012 08:58:51 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11123-6</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/freeman-military-story-line-suggestion/11123.rss">Freeman military story line suggestion</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Freeman military story line suggestion</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[YosemiteSam]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Joe Freeman">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Joe Freeman:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>If you move that conversation of We’ve got hostiles to the beginning of the chapter, then you’ll know what’s happenning, and that sucks. That chapter is supposed to be a lot of confusion for Freeman since he doesn’t know what the hell are the marines doing. At least until the scientist tells him that is a clean up operation.</p>
<p>Also I don’t think the soldiers would try to stop Freeman from launching the rocket, that’s something they would like to do too(Since it’s supposed to close the portal and stop the invasion, saving even the lives of some soldiers). But they don’t know Freeman is going to do that. They just know they have to stop him.</p>
<p>But the rest of what you say is perfect. Unfortunately I don’t think it’ll be possible, it’s a lot of work for the voice actors.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>In the story the military stopped the launch on purpose, there is a conversation during the game that says so, remember at this point its still just a mop up operation… and as to the scientist conversation thats why I put that conversation there, thats the point you know the score as they mow down that scientist. Plus up to that point some scientists have been cut down by sentry guns (youre well into Weve got Hostiles before you see the HECU kill that first scientist) so you pretty much know the score at that point. Having it at the end doesnt quite fit IMO because youve been killing HECUs the whole chapter, the guys must know by then somebodys taking out thier buddys… I think it would fit better at the begining.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/freeman-military-story-line-suggestion/11123/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/freeman-military-story-line-suggestion/11123/5</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 25 Sep 2012 00:42:31 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11123-5</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/freeman-military-story-line-suggestion/11123.rss">Freeman military story line suggestion</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Freeman military story line suggestion</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[YosemiteSam]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="DirtyBlue929">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/d/a587f6/40.png" class="avatar"> DirtyBlue929:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Personally, I’d like to see more signs of the military actually having trouble with Freeman and the Aliens.</p>
<p>They’d be small at first- a soldier out of ammo cowering from the first Garg, for example.  Eventually, we’d see Soldiers screaming as they’re decimated by Alien Grunts.  Hell, maybe throw in an encounter where one of the last marines (Lambda Lab, etc) flat out surrenders to you.  There could even be achievements tied to them!  “Merciful: Spare all Surrendered Marines,” “Avenger: Execute all Surrendered Marines”</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I agree and made a suggestion along that line in the ‘is the invasion FUBAR’ thread. I suggested the thought of the HECU wanting to join up with Freeman at the very end too, full 180 from where they are hunting you to wanting your help. Thought it would fit in nicely too considering at that point the military has abandoned them and left them to die, why wouldnt they want to hook up with the Freeman. I like your idea of making an achivement out of it too, be a nice touch.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/freeman-military-story-line-suggestion/11123/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/freeman-military-story-line-suggestion/11123/4</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 25 Sep 2012 00:31:44 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11123-4</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/freeman-military-story-line-suggestion/11123.rss">Freeman military story line suggestion</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Freeman military story line suggestion</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Joe_Freeman]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>If you move that conversation of We’ve got hostiles to the beginning of the chapter, then you’ll know what’s happenning, and that sucks. That chapter is supposed to be a lot of confusion for Freeman since he doesn’t know what the hell are the marines doing. At least until the scientist tells him that is a clean up operation.</p>
<p>Also I don’t think the soldiers would try to stop Freeman from launching the rocket, that’s something they would like to do too(Since it’s supposed to close the portal and stop the invasion, saving even the lives of some soldiers). But they don’t know Freeman is going to do that. They just know they have to stop him.</p>
<p>But the rest of what you say is perfect. Unfortunately I don’t think it’ll be possible, it’s a lot of work for the voice actors.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/freeman-military-story-line-suggestion/11123/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/freeman-military-story-line-suggestion/11123/3</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 25 Sep 2012 00:28:29 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11123-3</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/freeman-military-story-line-suggestion/11123.rss">Freeman military story line suggestion</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Freeman military story line suggestion</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[DirtyBlue929]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Personally, I’d like to see more signs of the military actually having trouble with Freeman and the Aliens.</p>
<p>They’d be small at first- a soldier out of ammo cowering from the first Garg, for example.  Eventually, we’d see Soldiers screaming as they’re decimated by Alien Grunts.  Hell, maybe throw in an encounter where one of the last marines (Lambda Lab, etc) flat out surrenders to you.  There could even be achievements tied to them!  “Merciful: Spare all Surrendered Marines,” “Avenger: Execute all Surrendered Marines”</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/freeman-military-story-line-suggestion/11123/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/freeman-military-story-line-suggestion/11123/2</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 25 Sep 2012 00:16:34 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11123-2</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/freeman-military-story-line-suggestion/11123.rss">Freeman military story line suggestion</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Freeman military story line suggestion</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[YosemiteSam]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Some thoughts I have about beefing up the story structure of the relationship between Freeman and the military.</p>
<p>Starting with ‘Weve got Hostiles’ I’d move that scripted conversation at the end of the chapter (where the HECU talk about killing scientist) to the very first encounter where the first scientist gets gunned down. Start that sequence a little earlier when you first enter that area and have two HECU there and have them do the conversation after killing that scientist, after which you proceed through the rest of ‘Weve got Hostiles’ wasting all the HECU in that chapter. Then where that conversation used to be at the end have a new one where the HECU are interrogating a scientist who tells them who you are.</p>
<p>You are now setup for ‘Power Up’ where you encounter the militarys first base camp and they know who you are. This area is already setup for that as it’s the first time they start calling you by name. Only thing I would add to that is a radioset in their position that is broadcasting your information that they discovered at the end of ‘Weve got Hostiles’.</p>
<p>They figured out who you were in ‘weve got hostiles’ then you over ran thier position in ‘Power up’ so now they should be super pissed and really out to get you in ‘On a Rail’ all setup to really ramp up their desire to get freeman. Start it out right after you lower and cross the bridge with some trip mines in the tunnel leading to the big elevator sentry gun trap. Have words painted on the walls by the trip mines ‘die freeman!’ ‘payback time freeman!’</p>
<p>In the next section I’d remove the single sentry gun and stick a couple HECUs patrolling that tunnel with a conversation along the line ‘hey sounds like someone set off the sentry gun trap’ ‘ya think its freeman?’ then you come around the corner on the tram. This leads into the first big base camp in ‘On a Rail’ where the HECU should be using much more of the freeman sound bytes. I’d also have the radioset in this area broadcasting to take out freeman.</p>
<p>Everything from there should play out pretty much the same. Some slight modifications, as you advance futhur and futher through ‘On a Rail’ the HECUs chance of saying a freeman related line should increase. With the radiosets throughout ‘On a Rail’ I’d ramp up the get freeman conversation as you move on. Example in ‘Power up’ radioset is just giving out your name. By the first radioset in ‘On a Rail’ it should be telling them to get you, by the next radioset your a priority until you reach the last radioset just before exiting outside to the rocket where its saying at all costs stop freeman dont let him launch that rocket! I’d also setup a trigger for the radiosets so when you get close to them they stop broadcasting the ‘get freeman’ message and say something like ‘alpha base come in,over’ then on the next radioset part of the message can be ‘lost contact with base alpha, suspect freeman in the area, get him!’ … heh on a side funny note, just an idea, as you take out thier positions and the radio changes from the ‘freeman’ message to a ‘hello is anybody there message’ I thought it would be funny if the person on the other end is getting more and more frustrated as you take out thier positions. Have the broacasts go from a calm ‘alpha base come in, over’ to at the very last one hes super frustrated and is yelling ‘FREEMAN!!!’ …also after you launch the rocket, a bunch of HECUs should come piling out of that area that opened up, and they all should be using freeman only lines.</p>
<p>I think these minor changes would really add a lot of emersion and the feeling of really being part of a story to Black Mesa. The additions made by the BM team in the first few chapters was very nicely done and I feel after that it just dropped right out of the game. What do you all think?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/freeman-military-story-line-suggestion/11123/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/freeman-military-story-line-suggestion/11123/1</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 24 Sep 2012 22:53:31 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11123-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/freeman-military-story-line-suggestion/11123.rss">Freeman military story line suggestion</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
