<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Star Wars: The Old Republic</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/star-wars-the-old-republic/8151</link>
    <description>Since we&#39;re getting close to release and we have no threads on TOR, I figured I&#39;d make one. Also since beta testers can actually discuss the game now, there might be more to talk about. So...

Who&#39;s going to play? What are you going to roll? How do you think the game will do? 

I&#39;ve played a couple beta weekends already. The last one was better than the first in a lot of ways, and it&#39;s a pretty fun game, but I&#39;m still not 100% sure if I really want to plunk down the cash for it. Maybe it&#39;s me, or maybe it&#39;s the other games I&#39;ve been playing recently, but something about it just isn&#39;t drawing me in. I&#39;m thinking it might be because it feels like playing a single player Bioware game but in an MMO environment. Guess I&#39;m kind of used to just mindlessly questing and stuff in MMOs and not paying attention to the story. 

If I do play, I think I might go trooper. That was probably the most fun class I played, but tbh I didn&#39;t try many classes. Jedi Knight was fun but didn&#39;t seem to be as useful in group missions, as ranged classes would kill all the enemies before I could get to them.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 20 Jun 2012 17:25:48 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Technology and Gaming</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/star-wars-the-old-republic/8151.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Star Wars: The Old Republic</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[elevenbravo]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>^ Sounds like you only played about two hours of the beta.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/star-wars-the-old-republic/8151/34">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/star-wars-the-old-republic/8151/34</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jun 2012 17:25:48 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8151-34</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/star-wars-the-old-republic/8151.rss">Star Wars: The Old Republic</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Star Wars: The Old Republic</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[JohnDay]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I played this from day 1. I was looking for something to take me away from WoW. It did kind of succeed in that i gave it 3 months to convince me to keep playing. In all honesty the game did have great potential but it failed realy badly.</p>
<p>First thing that should be right above anything else in an MMO is the controls need to work. Which for most classes they didnt, huge lag delay and sometimes abilities not even activating at times, took them 2 1/2 months to sort that out.</p>
<p>Second the UI really needs certain things which werent there, UI scaling, Target of Target among other things. That took them atleast 4 - 5 months to bring into the game.</p>
<p>Third and the major part of an MMO is the endgame content. Not only were you fighting your UI and controls but buggy bosses aswell. Along with all that the PvP was always breaking in certain areas aswell as repeatable quests.</p>
<p>Unfortunatly the MMO community dont give developers that much time before they say, you had your chance but its just not good enough. Im not sure if thats because monthly subs are involved (that was certainly my reason) or some are just impatient.</p>
<p>My thoughts are the game could have been great and i would have played it for a long time i think. But it was released far too early. If EA had waited a little longer for certain things to have been corrected im pretty sure that quite a few more people would have stuck with it. Many of the points ive just mentioned and more were pointed out by the testers apparently but they pushed it out anyway.</p>
<p>Things need to work in an MMO to keep players going back to do the same bosses, but fighting bugs aswell as UI is just not acceptable.<br>
I understand things take time to get right but certain things need to be right from day 1, it felt like an alpha release never mind a beta or even release.</p>
<p>The game did have many good points though. The questing was fun, the PvP was actually quite entertaining and coming from me thats a good thing becuase i dont usualy like PvP. The story lines for each class were nice to go through aswell, really opened up the lore of the game to everyone and the backgrounds of where all the different classes started and why. Crafting and companions were nice in this game too.</p>
<p>I did go back to the game after a few months to check out what had and hadnt been sorted but unfortunatly everyone that i knew on that particular server had left to play something else, obviously my real life freinds i knew about but others id met in the game had moved on aswell. So i cant give an accurate description of what state the game is in other than the fixes mentioned.</p>
<p>To sum it up, if all is sorted with the game which i know some things are now, like UI scaling and the bad contact with the character controls. Maybe if they keep working on it properly to fix the endgame it should be a pretty good F2P. Of course that is aslong as it isnt play to win with silly restrictions in certain things that would annoy you from the beggining. Personaly i blame EA for pushing it too quickly, as it could have been a really fun game.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/star-wars-the-old-republic/8151/33">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/star-wars-the-old-republic/8151/33</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jun 2012 16:16:31 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8151-33</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/star-wars-the-old-republic/8151.rss">Star Wars: The Old Republic</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Star Wars: The Old Republic</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Orpheon]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Yes, if you like Star Wars and you like MMOs. I think it was worth it even paid. I did quit after only a few months, but I get burned out on MMOs quick. I had about 3 or 4 characters, got a couple to about 30 and one to 43 or so, so that tells you how much of the content I got through when you consider there’s 4 classes and 8 advanced classes for each side, plus there’s a number of things you can only do at 50.</p>
<p>Anyways, it’s got a great soundtrack, great voice work, and probably the best story lines of any MMO. The gameplay is good and solid, but at its heart it’s pretty much just a WoW clone in terms of combat and skills (according to a veteran WoW player), so that may be a positive or a negative depending on how you look at it. For the art style and graphics quality it is a surprisingly demanding game to run though, so unless they’ve managed to improve it since I played, you’ll need a pretty good PC to run it maxed out.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/star-wars-the-old-republic/8151/32">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/star-wars-the-old-republic/8151/32</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jun 2012 04:37:11 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8151-32</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/star-wars-the-old-republic/8151.rss">Star Wars: The Old Republic</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Star Wars: The Old Republic</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Medevilae]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>This going to be worth playing once it goes F2P?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/star-wars-the-old-republic/8151/31">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/star-wars-the-old-republic/8151/31</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jun 2012 03:26:56 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8151-31</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/star-wars-the-old-republic/8151.rss">Star Wars: The Old Republic</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Star Wars: The Old Republic</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[mechaelite]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>after playing KOTOR and KOTOR II I must say that this game looked promising for me when I saw it, I liked the idea of playing online. Then I noticed it was a MMORPG, looked at the website, saw I would have to pay a month suscription. The next thing I remember is a broken computer monitor and an axe in my hand.</p>
<p>Anyways. If I do buy it (thing that I doubt) I may play with bounty hunter, imperial agent or republic trooper. I just think that there have already been many “lol look I have force powers and a lightsaber that kills almost everyone who shoots me” Star wars games. Being able to have a Distance weaponry character Point of view (like SW Battlefront or Republic Commando) alongside the people who love having force powers and fight together in a battle where <span class="bbcode-u">everybody</span> counts to get a victory is something that I like.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/star-wars-the-old-republic/8151/30">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/star-wars-the-old-republic/8151/30</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 07 Dec 2011 15:19:24 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8151-30</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/star-wars-the-old-republic/8151.rss">Star Wars: The Old Republic</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Star Wars: The Old Republic</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[elevenbravo]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>After playing the beta, I absolutely love SWTOR. I pre-ordered the CE because I’m a total Star Wars nerd and I’ll actually get to play it for a while!</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/star-wars-the-old-republic/8151/29">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/star-wars-the-old-republic/8151/29</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 07 Dec 2011 08:45:12 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8151-29</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/star-wars-the-old-republic/8151.rss">Star Wars: The Old Republic</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Star Wars: The Old Republic</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Deimos]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="BaTz281">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/user_avatar/leakfree.org/batz281/40/4503_2.png" class="avatar"> BaTz281:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Haha nice, QFT.</p>
<p>True, plus expansions, and micro transactions, and dual-boxing, etc.</p>
<p>As a matter of principal, I don’t buy in (no pun intended) to subscription-based models.  I’m paying for a product, I want to be able to use it as long as I wish.  That’s why I really hate this shift towards cloud storage and “always online” models, especially for Diablo III (not to hijack the thread) - no single player campaign without an internet connection?  Bah!  I can pull out Rise of the Triad, throw it on DosBox and play to my heart’s content, no ISP required, no chance of a server being down or worse, a company out of business no longer operating the servers required to play it.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Then don’t buy or play Diablo 3, go play Rise Of The Triad, now everyones happy.</p>
<p>Meanwhile i’ll be playing Diablo 3 because not having an internet connection this day and age is just weird, Don’t get me wrong an offline and lan mode would be great but there’s not one and wont be one so it’s time to get over it. Also I don’t think we have to worry about Blizzard going out of business.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/star-wars-the-old-republic/8151/28">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/star-wars-the-old-republic/8151/28</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 06 Dec 2011 03:18:36 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8151-28</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/star-wars-the-old-republic/8151.rss">Star Wars: The Old Republic</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Star Wars: The Old Republic</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Fuskox]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>The subscriptions are there to cover server costs, make the company money of course, and also to pay for the development costs. MMOs are constantly changing and having new features developed and expanded rather than having the company who created the game focus solely on developing new games.</p>
<p>And yes, that situation isn’t always true, an average gamer would buy a game more often than every 4 months, and MMO gamers would sometimes buy other games, but nonetheless, people who play primarily MMOs and people who play all types of games will generally spend the same amount of money on gaming.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/star-wars-the-old-republic/8151/27">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/star-wars-the-old-republic/8151/27</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 06 Dec 2011 00:21:57 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8151-27</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/star-wars-the-old-republic/8151.rss">Star Wars: The Old Republic</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Star Wars: The Old Republic</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[BaTz281]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="geekofalltrades">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/g/c2a13f/40.png" class="avatar"> geekofalltrades:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>They spend all their money on their fucking subscriptions.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Haha nice, QFT.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Orpheon">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/o/6bbea6/40.png" class="avatar"> Orpheon:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>In reality though, there are a lot more situations than those two. However, assuming that all your assumptions are correct, your conclusion would be still wrong for cases like SWTOR, because you have to buy the game first. So for one year, it would go like this:</p>
<p>MMO-player: $50 game (includes 1 free month) + ($15 x 11 months) = $215<br>
Non-MMO-player: $60 game x (12 months/4 months) = $180</p>
<p>Perhaps in the long haul the MMO gamer would end up spending less, but have you known many people who only played one MMO continuously for years and years?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>True, plus expansions, and micro transactions, and dual-boxing, etc.</p>
<p>As a matter of principal, I don’t buy in (no pun intended) to subscription-based models.  I’m paying for a product, I want to be able to use it as long as I wish.  That’s why I really hate this shift towards cloud storage and “always online” models, especially for Diablo III (not to hijack the thread) - no single player campaign without an internet connection?  Bah!  I can pull out Rise of the Triad, throw it on DosBox and play to my heart’s content, no ISP required, no chance of a server being down or worse, a company out of business no longer operating the servers required to play it.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/star-wars-the-old-republic/8151/26">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/star-wars-the-old-republic/8151/26</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 06 Dec 2011 00:17:07 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8151-26</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/star-wars-the-old-republic/8151.rss">Star Wars: The Old Republic</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Star Wars: The Old Republic</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Dr_Karamazov]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I’m liking the big RPG story aspects.  With WoW I don’t even read the quests now, I just look at the marker on the map and go to it.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/star-wars-the-old-republic/8151/25">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/star-wars-the-old-republic/8151/25</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 05 Dec 2011 23:58:25 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8151-25</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/star-wars-the-old-republic/8151.rss">Star Wars: The Old Republic</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Star Wars: The Old Republic</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Orpheon]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Fuskox">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/f/ea666f/40.png" class="avatar"> Fuskox:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>MMO players generally play only 1 game, making it normally 15 $ a month. Lets say you buy a full price game every 4 months, which is quite reasonable, 60$. People who play just MMOs spend the same amount of money, or less, than the average gamer.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>In reality though, there are a lot more situations than those two. However, assuming that all your assumptions are correct, your conclusion would be still wrong for cases like SWTOR, because you have to buy the game first. So for one year, it would go like this:</p>
<p>MMO-player: $50 game (includes 1 free month) + ($15 x 11 months) = $215<br>
Non-MMO-player: $60 game x (12 months/4 months) = $180</p>
<p>Perhaps in the long haul the MMO gamer would end up spending less, but have you known many people who only played one MMO continuously for years and years?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/star-wars-the-old-republic/8151/24">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/star-wars-the-old-republic/8151/24</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 05 Dec 2011 23:42:17 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8151-24</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/star-wars-the-old-republic/8151.rss">Star Wars: The Old Republic</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Star Wars: The Old Republic</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Fuskox]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="geekofalltrades">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/g/c2a13f/40.png" class="avatar"> geekofalltrades:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>They spend all their money on their fucking subscriptions.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>MMO players generally play only 1 game, making it normally 15 $ a month. Lets say you buy a full price game every 4 months, which is quite reasonable, 60$. People who play just MMOs spend the same amount of money, or less, than the average gamer.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/star-wars-the-old-republic/8151/23">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/star-wars-the-old-republic/8151/23</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 05 Dec 2011 23:10:03 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8151-23</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/star-wars-the-old-republic/8151.rss">Star Wars: The Old Republic</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Star Wars: The Old Republic</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[K_amp_955_ON]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>From what I understand you won’t need Origin to play SWTOR, even if you originally preordered the game on Origin. The game itself runs through it’s own launcher, so you can bypass EAs platform all together. Even if you do get your Origin account banned, according to the SWTOR website you can still play.</p>
<p>Taken from the SWTOR FAQ:<br>
“<span class="bbcode-i">What will happen to my Star Wars: The Old Republic account if my Origin account is locked?</span><br>
If for any reason you are locked out of your Origin account, you will still be able to log in to the game using the same email and password that you used to create your SWTOR account.”</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/star-wars-the-old-republic/8151/22">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/star-wars-the-old-republic/8151/22</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 05 Dec 2011 22:31:45 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8151-22</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/star-wars-the-old-republic/8151.rss">Star Wars: The Old Republic</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Star Wars: The Old Republic</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[gibbelin]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I’ve decided I’m not picking this up until EA sorts out their clusterfuck of a banning policy. If I have a question to ask on the official forums, I don’t want to lose all my games because some retarded autoban didn’t like a post I was quoted in.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/star-wars-the-old-republic/8151/21">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/star-wars-the-old-republic/8151/21</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 05 Dec 2011 20:55:33 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8151-21</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/star-wars-the-old-republic/8151.rss">Star Wars: The Old Republic</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Star Wars: The Old Republic</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[geekofalltrades]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>They spend all their money on their fucking subscriptions.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/star-wars-the-old-republic/8151/20">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/star-wars-the-old-republic/8151/20</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 05 Dec 2011 20:16:23 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8151-20</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/star-wars-the-old-republic/8151.rss">Star Wars: The Old Republic</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Star Wars: The Old Republic</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Orpheon]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="mankyman6">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/m/8797f3/40.png" class="avatar"> mankyman6:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Maybe they knew that they couldn’t get the graphics to the realistic standards that people would normally expect, so they gave it a cartoon look instead.</p>
<p>Who knows, really. It’s just my guess.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>More likely to make it marketable to more people. Seems like a lot of MMO players can’t or don’t upgrade their computers or buy new ones very often.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/star-wars-the-old-republic/8151/19">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/star-wars-the-old-republic/8151/19</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 03 Dec 2011 04:33:43 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8151-19</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/star-wars-the-old-republic/8151.rss">Star Wars: The Old Republic</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Star Wars: The Old Republic</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[mankyman6]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="BahamutBBob">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/b/e9bcb4/40.png" class="avatar"> BahamutBBob:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I don’t like how the graphics are similar to The Clone Wars (with more realistic proportions) but they work well enough.  They could use some fancier effects for the scenery, but it’s okay without them.  It mainly bugs me that people are still using Wolfenstein and Doom’s 2D effects in detailed 3D worlds. (most commonly flat plants)</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Maybe they knew that they couldn’t get the graphics to the realistic standards that people would normally expect, so they gave it a cartoon look instead.</p>
<p>Who knows, really. It’s just my guess.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/star-wars-the-old-republic/8151/18">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/star-wars-the-old-republic/8151/18</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Dec 2011 23:11:41 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8151-18</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/star-wars-the-old-republic/8151.rss">Star Wars: The Old Republic</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Star Wars: The Old Republic</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[TheKeeper]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="OrderOfDagon">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/user_avatar/leakfree.org/orderofdagon/40/4963_2.png" class="avatar"> OrderOfDagon:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>[url]I’m easily one of the most knowledgeable Star Wars fans on this site. (Doesn’t make my opinion correct, just well informed.)</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="OrderOfDagon">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/user_avatar/leakfree.org/orderofdagon/40/4963_2.png" class="avatar"> OrderOfDagon:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I actually didn’t play Kotor that much – maybe that’s where the feeling is at. Oh well, it’s not for everyone…</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>wtf!? I don’t get it.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/star-wars-the-old-republic/8151/17">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/star-wars-the-old-republic/8151/17</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Dec 2011 22:08:22 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8151-17</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/star-wars-the-old-republic/8151.rss">Star Wars: The Old Republic</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Star Wars: The Old Republic</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[BahamutBBob]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>It’s supposed to be about 1000 years after KOTOR IIRC.</p>
<p>I don’t like how the graphics are similar to The Clone Wars (with more realistic proportions) but they work well enough.  They could use some fancier effects for the scenery, but it’s okay without them.  It mainly bugs me that people are still using Wolfenstein and Doom’s 2D effects in detailed 3D worlds. (most commonly flat plants)</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/star-wars-the-old-republic/8151/16">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/star-wars-the-old-republic/8151/16</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Dec 2011 19:34:07 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8151-16</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/star-wars-the-old-republic/8151.rss">Star Wars: The Old Republic</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Star Wars: The Old Republic</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Kaweebo]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Ah okay, I see where you’re coming from then. KOTOR has it’s own distinct Star Wars feel. To me at least, it feels like Star Wars, but from a different era obviously. (The game takes place 4000 years before the movies) This game is made by the same company who made the first one and it’s set around that same time frame.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/star-wars-the-old-republic/8151/15">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/star-wars-the-old-republic/8151/15</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Dec 2011 14:54:20 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8151-15</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/star-wars-the-old-republic/8151.rss">Star Wars: The Old Republic</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Star Wars: The Old Republic</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[OrderOfDagon]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I actually didn’t play Kotor that much – maybe that’s where the feeling is at. Oh well, it’s not for everyone…</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/star-wars-the-old-republic/8151/14">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/star-wars-the-old-republic/8151/14</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Dec 2011 00:23:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8151-14</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/star-wars-the-old-republic/8151.rss">Star Wars: The Old Republic</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Star Wars: The Old Republic</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Kaweebo]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="OrderOfDagon">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/user_avatar/leakfree.org/orderofdagon/40/4963_2.png" class="avatar"> OrderOfDagon:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>The game honestly looks terrible imo. It doesn’t look nor feel like Starwars.</p>
<p>It’s like Battle Star Galactica meets Mass Effect – they just added lightsabers.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Feels like KOTOR to me, which in turn feels like Star Wars imo.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/star-wars-the-old-republic/8151/13">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/star-wars-the-old-republic/8151/13</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2011 20:39:11 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8151-13</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/star-wars-the-old-republic/8151.rss">Star Wars: The Old Republic</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Star Wars: The Old Republic</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[StOnE]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="OrderOfDagon">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/user_avatar/leakfree.org/orderofdagon/40/4963_2.png" class="avatar"> OrderOfDagon:</div>
<blockquote>
<p><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=yz_rdXjtyt8" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=yz_rdXjtyt8</a></p>
<p>Looks like Fallout meets Second life.</p>
<p>I’m easily one of the most knowledgeable Star Wars fans on this site. (Doesn’t make my opinion correct, just well informed.)</p>
<p>Doesn’t feel right to me – I’m not hearing the music or any Starwars related dialogue. Seriously, I honestly can’t even tell if this is starwars. Not only does it look unrelated to Star Wars, but it looks boring as all hell.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>You’re basing this off of youtube videos. You need to acctually play the game. I guarantee it will feel Star-Warsy from the moment you load in.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Orpheon">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/o/6bbea6/40.png" class="avatar"> Orpheon:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I think it’s sufficiently Star Wars-y, but the art style can be off-putting for some. Gameplay wise it’s no worse than any other MMO. I think that the worst problem facing it is that, after how long it’s been in development hell, no matter if it’s good or even great, it won’t be able to live up to expectations.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>It was in development for about as long as World of Warcraft was, and that did pretty well. You’re right though, there is always going to be someone that nit-picks.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/star-wars-the-old-republic/8151/12">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/star-wars-the-old-republic/8151/12</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2011 19:15:03 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8151-12</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/star-wars-the-old-republic/8151.rss">Star Wars: The Old Republic</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Star Wars: The Old Republic</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Conlaen]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Going to play it with my girlfriend. She’ll be rolling up a Smuggler and I’m going to go Trooper to support her. Might also roll another character on the side, cause I tend to play a bit more then my girlfriend. Will probably make a Sith so I don’t get spoilered on the Republic quests lines. Not sure yet what class that will be.</p>
<p>I have to say that I didn’t think we’d be playing this. Up until the beta I thought the graphics were a bit disappointing and the combat seemed stiff and not very interesting. Well the graphics are still kind of lame, and the combat animations do look a bit stiff often, but the fights are still interesting enough. The big selling point however is the story lines. I played a couple of characters up to level 10 in the stress test beta and the stories are really quite nice to play through. Especially the Trooper quest line for the starting planet kept me interested.</p>
<p>I do think that as soon as I’ve played through all the story quests I’ll probably end up putting the game aside. I think I’ll mostly end up playing the game as a single player game (or in the case where I play it with my gf, a coop 2-player game).</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/star-wars-the-old-republic/8151/11">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/star-wars-the-old-republic/8151/11</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2011 16:28:21 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8151-11</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/star-wars-the-old-republic/8151.rss">Star Wars: The Old Republic</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Star Wars: The Old Republic</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Bolteh]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Played the beta (thanks Jokerine) and I’m pleasantly surprised by it, the game is very polished for a beta. It actualyl feels like a retail-viable game. Aoen, RIFT, AoC, WAR etc all felt like they were hardly ready to get out of alpha on launch.</p>
<p>ToR does feel a lot like WoW, though. Especially the combat system and the talent/skill tree. As a former WoW player I didn’t have to do some research on how to or where to find certain things, it felt very natural. All in all, it feels like a western MMO, not the Asian crapfest MMOs like Aeon or RIFT.</p>
<p>There’s quite a few things that ToR does better than WoW though. The way you quest and progress is amazingly well done. The fully-voiced questlines add a lot of atmosphere and immersion. Same goes with the class-based questing, where your class is the only one that can enter a specific zone and have its own unique quests.</p>
<p>Crew skills is an interesting concept, but I kind of enjoyed the engagement professions required in WoW. In ToR you just send an NPC to craft/gather things for you.</p>
<p>Anyway, ToR feels very much like Star Wars. The sounds, the voice acting, the music, the effects, the story… It simply oozes Star Wars.</p>
<p>Didn’t manage to get a lot of dungeons in (or “flashpoints” I believe they are called), nor do I know how the endgame will look like, but the beta has left a good impression on me).</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/star-wars-the-old-republic/8151/10">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/star-wars-the-old-republic/8151/10</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2011 12:47:36 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8151-10</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/star-wars-the-old-republic/8151.rss">Star Wars: The Old Republic</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
