<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Half-Life conversations</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/half-life-conversations/2991</link>
    <description>hello everyone. I didn&#39;t know where to open this theard and i choose this section. so could anyone give me txt files where is conversations with scientists and other characters in HL HLOF HLBS. i need them becouse i haven&#39;t heared a lot about whats happening and i want to know details which sometimes are important</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 09 Mar 2010 03:24:04 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Half-Life Series</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/half-life-conversations/2991.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Half-Life conversations</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[LazySunday]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>“So where are we taking this Freeman guy?”<br>
“Topside for questioning.”<br>
“But we got him, let’s kill him now!”<br>
“And if they find the body?”<br>
“Body? What body?”<br>
“MWAAAHAHAHAHA”<br>
“DURRHURRHURRDURR”</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/half-life-conversations/2991/68">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/half-life-conversations/2991/68</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 09 Mar 2010 03:24:04 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2991-68</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/half-life-conversations/2991.rss">Half-Life conversations</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Half-Life conversations</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[waqwarrior]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Gordon! You’re alive! What the hell are these things? And why are they wearing science team uniforms?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/half-life-conversations/2991/67">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/half-life-conversations/2991/67</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 25 Feb 2010 22:44:38 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2991-67</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/half-life-conversations/2991.rss">Half-Life conversations</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Half-Life conversations</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[sekoshiba]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="cloak">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/c/c68b51/40.png" class="avatar"> cloak:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>In the beginning of HL on your way to the test chamber you see G-Man and a scientist arguing about something in a room with a locked door.  If you go up to the door all you can hear is mumbles.  It would be nice to know what they’re saying. (also the briefcase he’s carrying has a BM logo on it… so i wonder if its actually G-man or just an ‘administrator’ that they were to lazy to make a different skin for)</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>no its the g-man, he makes the resonance cascade by giving eli and kliener a contaminated zen crystal.</p>
<p>…oh and a couple quotes:</p>
<p>*get away from the beam!!!</p>
<p>*i bet your glad i got my gun…huh?..huh?</p>
<p>*these “crabs” take over peoples bodies i wonder what the next stage of infection looks like…</p>
<p>ps. zombies turn into gonomes…</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/half-life-conversations/2991/66">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/half-life-conversations/2991/66</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 18 Feb 2010 08:06:10 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2991-66</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/half-life-conversations/2991.rss">Half-Life conversations</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Half-Life conversations</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Assassin]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>conversations from HL HLOF HLBS  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=9" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/half-life-conversations/2991/65">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/half-life-conversations/2991/65</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 16 Feb 2010 09:28:49 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2991-65</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/half-life-conversations/2991.rss">Half-Life conversations</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Half-Life conversations</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[LimitBreak]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="danielsangeo">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/user_avatar/leakfree.org/danielsangeo/40/4347_2.png" class="avatar"> danielsangeo:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Err, this is from Blue Shift.  Gordon’s tram spoke at 8:47 AM.  Are we counting mods?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Ah, yes.  Now that I examine it again, it is Blue Shift.</p>
<p>I’ll post the actual one then.<br>
<span class="bbcode-i"><br>
Good morning and welcome to the Black Mesa Transit System. This automated train is provided for the security and convenience of the Black Mesa Research Facility personnel. The time is 8:47 AM. Current topside temperature is 93 degrees with an estimated high of 105. The Black Mesa Compound is maintained at a pleasant 68 degrees at all times. This train is inbound from Level 3 Dormitories to Sector C Test Labs and Control Facilities. If your intended destination is a high-security area beyond Sector C, you will need to return to the central transit hub in Area 9 and board a high-security train. If you have not yet submitted your identity to the retinal clearance system, you must report to Black Mesa personnel for processing before you will be permitted into the high-security branch of the transit system. A reminder that the Black Mesa Hazard Course Decathlon will commence this evening at 1900 hours in the Level 3 facility. The semi-finals for high-security personnel will be announced in a separate, secure-access transmission. Remember: more lives than your own may depend on your fitness. A reminder to all Black Mesa personnel: regular radiation and biohazard screenings are a requirement of continued employment in the Black Mesa Research Facility. Missing a scheduled urinalysis or radiation checkup grounds for immediate termination. If you feel you have been exposed to radioactive or other hazardous materials in the course of your duties, contact your Radiation Safety Officer immediately! Work safe. Work smart. Your future depends on it. Due to the high toxicity of material routinely handled in the Black Mesa Compound, no smoking, eating or drinking are permitted within the Black Mesa transit system. Please keep your limbs inside the train at all times. Do not attempt to open the doors until the train has come to a complete halt at the station platform. In the event of an emergency, passengers are to remain seated and await further instruction. If it is necessary to exit the train, disabled personnel should be evacuated first. Please stay away from electrified rails and proceed to an emergency station until assistance arrives. Do you have a friend or relative who would make a valuable addition to the Black Mesa team? Immediate openings are available in the areas of Materials Handling and low-clearance security. Please contact Black Mesa personnel for further information. If you have an associate in the background of Theoretical Physics, Biotechnology or other high-tech disciplines, please contact our Civilian Recruitment Division. The Black Mesa Research Facility is an equal opportunity employer. Now arriving at Sector C Test Labs and Control Facilities. Please stand back from the automated door and wait for the security officer to verify your identity. Before exiting the train, be sure to check your area for personal belongings. Thank you and have a very safe and productive day.</span></p>
<p>These don’t seem to be in order.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/half-life-conversations/2991/64">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/half-life-conversations/2991/64</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 16 Feb 2010 03:23:10 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2991-64</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/half-life-conversations/2991.rss">Half-Life conversations</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Half-Life conversations</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[danielsangeo]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="LimitBreak">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/l/4bbf92/40.png" class="avatar"> LimitBreak:</div>
<blockquote>
<p><span class="bbcode-i">The time is 8:42 AM</span></p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Err, this is from Blue Shift.  Gordon’s tram spoke at 8:47 AM.  Are we counting mods?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/half-life-conversations/2991/63">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/half-life-conversations/2991/63</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 16 Feb 2010 03:18:39 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2991-63</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/half-life-conversations/2991.rss">Half-Life conversations</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Half-Life conversations</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[LimitBreak]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Jingles">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/j/46a35a/40.png" class="avatar"> Jingles:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>You actually typed all of that up!I lawl’d</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>It’s called copy and paste.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/half-life-conversations/2991/62">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/half-life-conversations/2991/62</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 16 Feb 2010 03:01:09 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2991-62</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/half-life-conversations/2991.rss">Half-Life conversations</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Half-Life conversations</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Jingles]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="LimitBreak">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/l/4bbf92/40.png" class="avatar"> LimitBreak:</div>
<blockquote>
<p><span class="bbcode-i">Good morning and welcome to the Black Mesa transit system. This automated train is provided for the comfort and convenience of Black Mesa residents and visitors to the Black Mesa Research Facility. The time is 8:42 AM. Current topside temperature is 91 degrees with an estimated high today of 105. The Black Mesa Compound is maintained at 68 degrees at all times. This train is inbound from the Area 8 Topside Dormitories to the Central Transit Hub in Area 9. Please keep your limbs inside the train at all times. Do not attempt to open the doors until the train has come to a complete halt at the station platform. In the event of an emergency, passengers are to remain seated and await further instruction. If it is necessary to exit the train, disabled passengers should be evacuated first. Please stay away from electrified rails and proceed to an emergency station until assistance arrives. If your intended destination is a high-security area beyond Sector C, you will need to board a high-security train in the Central Transit Hub. If you have not yet submitted your identity for the retinal clearance system, you must report to Black Mesa personnel for processing before you will be admitted to the high-security branch of the transit system. If you wish to transfer to the Sector B or C medium-security lines, you may do so before you reach the Central Transit Hub, at the Area 9 Security Checkpoint. Access to the medium-security branch of the transit system is for employees of the Black Mesa Research Facility and authorized visitors ONLY and requires that you wear your security badge at all times… This train is now transferring to the Sector C line of the transit system. This is a medium security area of the Black Mesa Facility. Be sure to wear your identification badge at all times. Now arriving at Area 3 Security Facilities. Please stand back from the automated door until it has fully opened. Before exiting the train, be sure to check your area for personal belongings. Thank you, and have a safe and productive day!</span></p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>You actually typed all of that up!I lawl’d</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/half-life-conversations/2991/61">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/half-life-conversations/2991/61</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 15 Feb 2010 10:12:29 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2991-61</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/half-life-conversations/2991.rss">Half-Life conversations</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Half-Life conversations</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Ballsopt]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>thanks a bunch…</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/half-life-conversations/2991/60">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/half-life-conversations/2991/60</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 15 Feb 2010 05:36:51 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2991-60</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/half-life-conversations/2991.rss">Half-Life conversations</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Half-Life conversations</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crikulus]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><span class="bbcode-b">Scientists:</span></p>
<p><span class="bbcode-i">-This is as far as I go!</span><br>
<span class="bbcode-i">-My god! What are you doing??</span><br>
<span class="bbcode-i">-A fellow scientist!</span><br>
<span class="bbcode-i">-I can’t take much more of this!</span><br>
<span class="bbcode-i">-I’d give my right hemisphere for a few hours of sleep.</span><br>
<span class="bbcode-i">-Did you hear something?</span><br>
<span class="bbcode-i">-That sound, what is it?</span><br>
<span class="bbcode-i">-Is anyone else… Getting hungry?</span><br>
<span class="bbcode-i">-Don’t you find this all… Rather fascinating?</span><br>
<span class="bbcode-i">-Are you thinking what I’m thinking?</span><br>
<span class="bbcode-i">-Wouldn’t it be fantastic to get some pure readings for a change?</span><br>
<span class="bbcode-i">-Stop asking that question!</span><br>
<span class="bbcode-i">-How interesting, just look at that!</span><br>
<span class="bbcode-i">-Why are you asking ME?</span><br>
<span class="bbcode-i">-Lead the way!</span><br>
<span class="bbcode-i">-I really don’t know.</span><br>
<span class="bbcode-i">-Absolutely not!</span><br>
<span class="bbcode-i">-You are completely wrong.</span><br>
<span class="bbcode-i">-I don’t think so.</span><br>
<span class="bbcode-i">-You can’t be serious!</span><br>
<span class="bbcode-i">-I’m not at all sure.</span><br>
<span class="bbcode-i">-Positively!</span><br>
<span class="bbcode-i">-I’m sure of it!</span><br>
<span class="bbcode-i">-Of course!</span><br>
<span class="bbcode-i">-I believe so.</span><br>
<span class="bbcode-i">-Absolutely.</span><br>
<span class="bbcode-i">-Do you smell something burning?</span><br>
<span class="bbcode-i">-hmmm, what a peculiar odor.</span><br>
<span class="bbcode-i">-I believe something smells quite fowl here.</span><br>
<span class="bbcode-i">-Do you smell what I smell?</span><br>
<span class="bbcode-i">-I hope that odor isn’t coming from you??</span><br>
<span class="bbcode-i">-STOP!</span><br>
<span class="bbcode-i">-WAH!</span><br>
<span class="bbcode-i">-ECK!</span><br>
<span class="bbcode-i">-WUH WA WAH!!</span><br>
<span class="bbcode-i">-Oh my god!! We’re doomed!!!</span><br>
<span class="bbcode-i">-No! Please!</span><br>
<span class="bbcode-i">-Are you insane?</span><br>
<span class="bbcode-i">-Have I been that much of a burden?</span><br>
<span class="bbcode-i">-Take me with you, I’m the one man who knows EVERYTHING!</span><br>
<span class="bbcode-i">-Put that down, it’s a prototype…</span><br>
<span class="bbcode-i">-It’s much too unpredictable, don’t let it overcharge!</span><br>
<span class="bbcode-i">-NO!</span><br>
<span class="bbcode-i">-Why do we all have to wear these ridiculous ties?</span><br>
<span class="bbcode-i">-Do you know who ate all the donuts?</span></p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Guards:</span></p>
<p><span class="bbcode-i">-Eat this, you outer-space octopus!</span><br>
<span class="bbcode-i">-Hey, catch me later - I’ll buy you a beer!</span><br>
<span class="bbcode-i">-C’mon, Gordon! You trying to get me into trouble?</span><br>
<span class="bbcode-i">-Roger that, let’s run like hell!</span><br>
<span class="bbcode-i">-Do you think there’s a cold beer for us at the end of all this?</span><br>
<span class="bbcode-i">-I’d like to get my hands on the guy responsible for this mess.</span><br>
<span class="bbcode-i">-What is this thing, some kinda weapon?</span><br>
<span class="bbcode-i">-Man! Why aren’t we using it?</span><br>
<span class="bbcode-i">-What d’ya mean, “overcharge”?</span></p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Soldier:</span></p>
<p><span class="bbcode-i">-I didn’t sign on for this shit.</span><br>
<span class="bbcode-i">-We’ve got hostiles!</span><br>
<span class="bbcode-i">-Come in, Cooper! Do you copy? Forget about Freeman, we’re abandoning the base. If you have any last bomb targets, mark them on the tactical map. Otherwise, get the hell out of there! Repeat, we are pulling out and commencing airstrikes, give us targets or get below!</span><br>
<span class="bbcode-i">-Forget about Freeman, we are cutting our losses and pulling out! Anybody left down there now is on his own, repeat, if you weren’t already, you are now!</span><br>
<span class="bbcode-i">-I killed twelve dumbass scientists and not one of 'em fought back. This sucks.</span></p>
<p>And MUCH MUCH MUCH more, but I’m getting tired of listing these. Check out the <a href="https://www.newgrounds.com/portal/view/391034" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Scientist Sound Board</a>, and use google, there’s tons of pages full of quotes.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/half-life-conversations/2991/59">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/half-life-conversations/2991/59</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 15 Feb 2010 05:31:10 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2991-59</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/half-life-conversations/2991.rss">Half-Life conversations</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Half-Life conversations</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Ballsopt]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><span class="bbcode-i">Did you see that thing…with the missing leg?</span></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/half-life-conversations/2991/58">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/half-life-conversations/2991/58</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 15 Feb 2010 04:05:39 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2991-58</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/half-life-conversations/2991.rss">Half-Life conversations</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Half-Life conversations</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[danielsangeo]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><span class="bbcode-i">Looks like you’re in the barrel today.</span></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/half-life-conversations/2991/57">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/half-life-conversations/2991/57</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 15 Feb 2010 03:05:39 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2991-57</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/half-life-conversations/2991.rss">Half-Life conversations</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Half-Life conversations</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Maxey]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><span class="bbcode-i">“It’s one of these days, I guess…”</span></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/half-life-conversations/2991/56">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/half-life-conversations/2991/56</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 15 Feb 2010 00:00:16 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2991-56</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/half-life-conversations/2991.rss">Half-Life conversations</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Half-Life conversations</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[King_Max]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><span class="bbcode-i">“Shutting down”<br>
It’s not-it’s not shutting down<br>
OH NAOW-</span></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/half-life-conversations/2991/55">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/half-life-conversations/2991/55</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 14 Feb 2010 23:50:55 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2991-55</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/half-life-conversations/2991.rss">Half-Life conversations</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Half-Life conversations</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Afroded]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><span class="bbcode-i">If you would be so good as to climb up and start the rotors, we can bring the antimasspectrometer to 100% and hold it there, until the carrier arrives.</span></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/half-life-conversations/2991/54">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/half-life-conversations/2991/54</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 14 Feb 2010 23:27:10 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2991-54</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/half-life-conversations/2991.rss">Half-Life conversations</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Half-Life conversations</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[lkariher]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><span class="bbcode-i">run’n a little late Gordon</span></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/half-life-conversations/2991/53">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/half-life-conversations/2991/53</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 14 Feb 2010 23:23:07 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2991-53</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/half-life-conversations/2991.rss">Half-Life conversations</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Half-Life conversations</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[King_Max]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><span class="bbcode-i">Stop attacking! He’s a friend!</span></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/half-life-conversations/2991/52">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/half-life-conversations/2991/52</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 14 Feb 2010 23:07:27 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2991-52</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/half-life-conversations/2991.rss">Half-Life conversations</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Half-Life conversations</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[LimitBreak]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><span class="bbcode-i">Well, there goes our grant money.</span></p>
<p><span class="bbcode-i">Who is responsible for this mess?</span></p>
<p>[i]You’re going to have to leave me here, Gordon.</p>
<p>I’m going to stay here, and wait for my colleagues.[/i]</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/half-life-conversations/2991/51">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/half-life-conversations/2991/51</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 14 Feb 2010 22:42:21 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2991-51</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/half-life-conversations/2991.rss">Half-Life conversations</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Half-Life conversations</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Maxey]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><span class="bbcode-i">“I’m afraid we’ll have to deviate from standard analysis procedures  today, Gordon.”</span><br>
<span class="bbcode-i">“Yes, but for good reason. This is a rare  opportunity for us. This is the purest sample we’ve seen yet.”</span><br>
<span class="bbcode-i">“Yes,  but potentially, the most unstable.”</span><br>
<span class="bbcode-i">“Now, now. If we follow  standard insertion procedures, everything will be fine.”</span><br>
<span class="bbcode-i">“What? I  don’t know how you can say that. Although I will admit, the possibility  of a resonance cascade scenario is extremely unlikely.”</span><br>
<span class="bbcode-i">“Gordon  doesn’t need to hear this, he’s a highly trained professional. We’ve  assured the Administrator that NOTHING WILL GO WRONG.”</span><br>
<span class="bbcode-i">Ah. Yes,  Gordon, we have complete faith in you."</span><br>
<span class="bbcode-i">Well, go ahead, let’s let  him in now."</span></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/half-life-conversations/2991/50">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/half-life-conversations/2991/50</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 14 Feb 2010 20:19:40 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2991-50</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/half-life-conversations/2991.rss">Half-Life conversations</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Half-Life conversations</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[LimitBreak]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><span class="bbcode-i">Good morning and welcome to the Black Mesa transit system. This automated train is provided for the comfort and convenience of Black Mesa residents and visitors to the Black Mesa Research Facility. The time is 8:42 AM. Current topside temperature is 91 degrees with an estimated high today of 105. The Black Mesa Compound is maintained at 68 degrees at all times. This train is inbound from the Area 8 Topside Dormitories to the Central Transit Hub in Area 9. Please keep your limbs inside the train at all times. Do not attempt to open the doors until the train has come to a complete halt at the station platform. In the event of an emergency, passengers are to remain seated and await further instruction. If it is necessary to exit the train, disabled passengers should be evacuated first. Please stay away from electrified rails and proceed to an emergency station until assistance arrives. If your intended destination is a high-security area beyond Sector C, you will need to board a high-security train in the Central Transit Hub. If you have not yet submitted your identity for the retinal clearance system, you must report to Black Mesa personnel for processing before you will be admitted to the high-security branch of the transit system. If you wish to transfer to the Sector B or C medium-security lines, you may do so before you reach the Central Transit Hub, at the Area 9 Security Checkpoint. Access to the medium-security branch of the transit system is for employees of the Black Mesa Research Facility and authorized visitors ONLY and requires that you wear your security badge at all times… This train is now transferring to the Sector C line of the transit system. This is a medium security area of the Black Mesa Facility. Be sure to wear your identification badge at all times. Now arriving at Area 3 Security Facilities. Please stand back from the automated door until it has fully opened. Before exiting the train, be sure to check your area for personal belongings. Thank you, and have a safe and productive day!</span></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/half-life-conversations/2991/49">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/half-life-conversations/2991/49</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 14 Feb 2010 17:36:52 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2991-49</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/half-life-conversations/2991.rss">Half-Life conversations</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Half-Life conversations</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Calebmcghee]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>The border-world, Xen, Is under our control, for the time being, thanks to you.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/half-life-conversations/2991/48">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/half-life-conversations/2991/48</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 14 Feb 2010 17:03:58 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2991-48</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/half-life-conversations/2991.rss">Half-Life conversations</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Half-Life conversations</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Android11x]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Can we be friends, Lord Grievous?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/half-life-conversations/2991/47">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/half-life-conversations/2991/47</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 14 Feb 2010 16:30:29 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2991-47</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/half-life-conversations/2991.rss">Half-Life conversations</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Half-Life conversations</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Lord_Grievous]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><em>Splat</em> (when you gib someone)</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/half-life-conversations/2991/46">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/half-life-conversations/2991/46</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 14 Feb 2010 16:15:46 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2991-46</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/half-life-conversations/2991.rss">Half-Life conversations</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Half-Life conversations</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Jingles]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><span class="bbcode-i">Catch me later and I’ll buy  you a beer!</span></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/half-life-conversations/2991/45">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/half-life-conversations/2991/45</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 14 Feb 2010 14:50:37 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2991-45</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/half-life-conversations/2991.rss">Half-Life conversations</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Half-Life conversations</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Assassin]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><span class="bbcode-i">Good Morning, Mr. Freeman!</span></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/half-life-conversations/2991/44">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/half-life-conversations/2991/44</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 14 Feb 2010 10:30:36 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2991-44</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/half-life-conversations/2991.rss">Half-Life conversations</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
