<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>[Audio] Rocket Launch Replays [Fixed]</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/audio-rocket-launch-replays-fixed/11219</link>
    <description>map: bm_c2a2c
pos: 1604.812500 -626.151428 320.031250

After the rocket launched, I watched it fly up for a few seconds, until the flare disappeared, turned around, and quicksaved. I ran around a bit, reloaded for whatever reason, and the last half of &quot;seven&quot; in the countdown played, with the rocket&#39;s audio (engines coming on, firing, etc.) continuing for the full duration after.

I have four saves in that area: one auto from when the rocket is pretty high in the air, one quick that I mentioned above, an auto after walking into the newly opened area with the electrified water, and one quick standing on the new tram. All four behave as described when I load them.

I hope that makes sense. I&#39;ll see if it&#39;s stuck to all future save games or if it&#39;s just this area/map.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 30 Sep 2012 05:02:47 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>In-game Issues (Mod)</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/audio-rocket-launch-replays-fixed/11219.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>[Audio] Rocket Launch Replays [Fixed]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[efeman]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>map: bm_c2a2c<br>
pos: 1604.812500 -626.151428 320.031250</p>
<p>After the rocket launched, I watched it fly up for a few seconds, until the flare disappeared, turned around, and quicksaved. I ran around a bit, reloaded for whatever reason, and the last half of “seven” in the countdown played, with the rocket’s audio (engines coming on, firing, etc.) continuing for the full duration after.</p>
<p>I have four saves in that area: one auto from when the rocket is pretty high in the air, one quick that I mentioned above, an auto after walking into the newly opened area with the electrified water, and one quick standing on the new tram. All four behave as described when I load them.</p>
<p>I hope that makes sense. I’ll see if it’s stuck to all future save games or if it’s just this area/map.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/audio-rocket-launch-replays-fixed/11219/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/audio-rocket-launch-replays-fixed/11219/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 30 Sep 2012 05:02:47 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11219-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/audio-rocket-launch-replays-fixed/11219.rss">[Audio] Rocket Launch Replays [Fixed]</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
