<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Atomic PC - BM Preview</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/atomic-pc-bm-preview/5329</link>
    <description>[url]https://www.atomicmpc.com.au/Feature/230583,is-black-mesa-the-ultimate-half-life-2-mod.aspx[/url]
[quote]
Black Mesa is an ambitious mod to recreate Half Life in the latest Source Engine - and it goes way beyond a mere mod...

Half Life is one of those rare games that&#39;s as much an historical event as a genre-defining moment in gaming. It&#39;s one of those things that many people can remember perfectly, including what they were doing when they first played, where they were - we were writing a preview for PC Authority when we received the first 20 per cent of the finished game from then unknown developer Valve.

And we finished it one massive, jawdropping session.

The part time devs behind the Black Mesa project get the importance of Half Life. You&#39;d certainly hope they do, given the epic scope of what they&#39;re trying to achieve - a full, ground-up re-interpretation of the original using the current Source engine. Get something like that wrong, and you&#39;ll know about it. Get it right, and like many great mods teams you&#39;ll likely find your project to be an important step into getting fulltime employment.

Black Mesa isn&#39;t even complete or released yet, and already a lot of team have found themselves offered jobs at some pretty major development houses. What these guys are doing is making even the Source engine&#39;s creators scratch their heads. Which is pretty fair, we&#39;ve played a goodly portion of Black Mesa now, and these guys are doing some amazing work.

Inside man
We&#39;re pretty lucky here at Atomic. One of the Black Mesa team&#39;s texture wranglers is no less than our very own comment troll Orcone. He brought in the latest build for us to play with yesterday, and play with it we have. The game&#39;s more or less complete - albeit with lots of tweaking to go - right up to the Xen levels. We could have jumped into any part of the game, but really, you have to start at the classic starter level, Inbound.

Wow. 

The combination of attention to original detail, and new material provided by the modern team is impressive. If you&#39;ve ever tried to go back to Half Life you&#39;ll know the old engine really isn&#39;t aging well; this, however, makes the game fresh and up to date.

It&#39;s also fiendishly self-referential - there&#39;s a newspaper on one of the chairs in your carriage called the Inbound Times... The Half Life sense of humour is very much intact and expanded upon. 

But apart from that, this is all new material - new textures, new animations, even new voice work. It&#39;s all lovingly based off the original, but with a few twists that keep the story in line with the now much more expanded universe that subsequent releases have given us.

Full use has also been made of the Source engine&#39;s implementation of Havok physics. Most items can be picked up and thrown around, and the explosive action is much more chaotic than ever before. But it&#39;s the simple things that amuse, it seems - we spent more time than is probably healthy stacking chairs, folders and magazines on the Anomalous Materials reception desk during our initial run through.

Much to Orcone&#39;s dismay.

This is an outstanding effort from an obviously dedicated and remarkably skilled team. We can&#39;t wait to see more of the game.
[/quote]</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 16 Sep 2010 19:29:42 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>The Cafeteria</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/atomic-pc-bm-preview/5329.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Atomic PC - BM Preview</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[RabidMonkey]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="angel123">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/a/d9b06d/40.png" class="avatar"> angel123:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>and than they dropped support in Hammer for 1.6</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Locked thread so I feel silly about replying. But…</p>
<p>Hammer still works just fine for 1.6 and has ever since the Source SDK was released in 2004. You can’t easily use the SOURCE SDK for CS 1.6, I think you can figure out why.</p>
<p>Just because something doesn’t work on your computer doesn’t mean they’ve stopped supporting it. People have and still are making Half-Life and CS maps, and the editor hasn’t been supported…ever? Find me a game developer who actively supports their software development tools (not a ‘use this at your own risk’ kind of deal) and I’ll give you a cookie!</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/atomic-pc-bm-preview/5329/428">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/atomic-pc-bm-preview/5329/428</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 16 Sep 2010 19:29:42 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-5329-428</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/atomic-pc-bm-preview/5329.rss">Atomic PC - BM Preview</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Atomic PC - BM Preview</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[CatzEyes93]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>This thread had a topic. Not anymore.    <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/frowning.png?v=9" title=":frowning:" class="emoji" alt=":frowning:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/atomic-pc-bm-preview/5329/427">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/atomic-pc-bm-preview/5329/427</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 16 Sep 2010 00:18:47 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-5329-427</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/atomic-pc-bm-preview/5329.rss">Atomic PC - BM Preview</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Atomic PC - BM Preview</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[McVeigh]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>“This message is hidden because <span class="bbcode-b">angel123</span> is on your <a href="https://forums.blackmesasource.com/profile.php?do=ignorelist" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">ignore list</a>.”</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/atomic-pc-bm-preview/5329/426">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/atomic-pc-bm-preview/5329/426</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 16 Sep 2010 00:16:16 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-5329-426</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/atomic-pc-bm-preview/5329.rss">Atomic PC - BM Preview</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Atomic PC - BM Preview</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Maxey]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Ok, I get it, it’s just that the way you output your opinion makes you look like a troll.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/atomic-pc-bm-preview/5329/425">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/atomic-pc-bm-preview/5329/425</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 16 Sep 2010 00:13:05 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-5329-425</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/atomic-pc-bm-preview/5329.rss">Atomic PC - BM Preview</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Atomic PC - BM Preview</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[angel123]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>It would be boring if all sad same things same things Valve is best company there is there is there is there is…</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/atomic-pc-bm-preview/5329/424">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/atomic-pc-bm-preview/5329/424</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 16 Sep 2010 00:07:54 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-5329-424</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/atomic-pc-bm-preview/5329.rss">Atomic PC - BM Preview</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Atomic PC - BM Preview</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Maxey]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>What you’re doing is saying that you don’t like the way Valve’s been doing things lately to a forum chokeful of Valve fans.</p>
<p>I know you’re entitled to your opinion and I’m all for it, but what I don’t understand is your motive behind it.</p>
<p>Or maybe you simply want to share your opinion?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/atomic-pc-bm-preview/5329/423">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/atomic-pc-bm-preview/5329/423</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 16 Sep 2010 00:01:49 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-5329-423</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/atomic-pc-bm-preview/5329.rss">Atomic PC - BM Preview</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Atomic PC - BM Preview</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[angel123]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I’m talking about Valve support that you are counting on and engine updates, while you and the rest of “fans” are trolling my every post…</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/atomic-pc-bm-preview/5329/422">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/atomic-pc-bm-preview/5329/422</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 15 Sep 2010 23:55:05 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-5329-422</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/atomic-pc-bm-preview/5329.rss">Atomic PC - BM Preview</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Atomic PC - BM Preview</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Maxey]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>So, what are you really doing in this forum?</p>
<p>Oh, wait, trolling, yeah.</p>
<p>Bye.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/atomic-pc-bm-preview/5329/421">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/atomic-pc-bm-preview/5329/421</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 15 Sep 2010 23:50:40 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-5329-421</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/atomic-pc-bm-preview/5329.rss">Atomic PC - BM Preview</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Atomic PC - BM Preview</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[angel123]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Not to mention constant spamming when I open Steam window, It’s almost like adware…</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/atomic-pc-bm-preview/5329/420">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/atomic-pc-bm-preview/5329/420</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 15 Sep 2010 23:49:54 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-5329-420</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/atomic-pc-bm-preview/5329.rss">Atomic PC - BM Preview</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Atomic PC - BM Preview</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[angel123]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Just look at it, whole game shifted from scientist vs aliens to “nazi” combine soldiers vs crysis mother*cker fighting behind the wheels…</p>
<p>One of the first things Valve changed in cs 1.6 is new CT shield so the whole game would be more noob friendly and sell better…<br>
It took them 10 years to fix the bugs but only one day to add new “features”, and than they dropped support in Hammer for 1.6 so they could sell more cs :s , that company is not my favorite any more…</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/atomic-pc-bm-preview/5329/419">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/atomic-pc-bm-preview/5329/419</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 15 Sep 2010 23:42:19 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-5329-419</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/atomic-pc-bm-preview/5329.rss">Atomic PC - BM Preview</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Atomic PC - BM Preview</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[CatzEyes93]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>both.</p>
<p>And nothing happened with Orcone. The team is good about getting past issues and not dwelling on mistakes, this incident was not an exception.</p>
<p>GO TEAM!  :cheerleader:</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/atomic-pc-bm-preview/5329/418">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/atomic-pc-bm-preview/5329/418</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 15 Sep 2010 23:29:15 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-5329-418</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/atomic-pc-bm-preview/5329.rss">Atomic PC - BM Preview</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Atomic PC - BM Preview</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Maxey]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>He’s either trolling or he simply has no idea of what he’s babbling about.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/atomic-pc-bm-preview/5329/417">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/atomic-pc-bm-preview/5329/417</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 15 Sep 2010 23:26:27 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-5329-417</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/atomic-pc-bm-preview/5329.rss">Atomic PC - BM Preview</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Atomic PC - BM Preview</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[johnyo]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Well, if Valve’s games don’t meet your standards, gaming’s simply not for you. What are you even doing here anyway?</p>
<p>[Edit] As expected, :ninja:'d</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/atomic-pc-bm-preview/5329/416">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/atomic-pc-bm-preview/5329/416</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 15 Sep 2010 23:19:10 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-5329-416</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/atomic-pc-bm-preview/5329.rss">Atomic PC - BM Preview</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Atomic PC - BM Preview</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Winged_One]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>So you just want them to rerelease the same game over and over?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/atomic-pc-bm-preview/5329/415">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/atomic-pc-bm-preview/5329/415</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 15 Sep 2010 23:16:52 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-5329-415</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/atomic-pc-bm-preview/5329.rss">Atomic PC - BM Preview</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Atomic PC - BM Preview</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[angel123]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Maxey">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/user_avatar/leakfree.org/maxey/40/4358_2.png" class="avatar"> Maxey:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>People want to play BM because they want a proper remake of HL1 in the Source engine. Good graphics may be important to the equation but they’re not the the only important selling point.</p>
<p>In fact, you’re missing the point if you think advanced graphics are what’s important here. Look at all of Valve’s single-player games. What are the most important aspects in all of them? The aspects Valve worked the most in all of them?</p>
<p>Gameplay mechanics and immersive storytelling.</p>
<p>Black Mesa, as a reinterpretation of Valve’s primordial game, is not only recreating HL1’s gameplay and plot but also improving and expanding on them. Good graphics come right after.</p>
<p>The BM team is creating this mod using the same mentality Valve uses in their games. Gameplay and immersion first of all, good graphics are just the cherry on top of the cake.</p>
<p>(No cake jokes please)</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>My point of view is that Valve is going sideways since HL2, I didn’t even play Episode Two for that reason.<br>
Portal was nice (I played demo), but didn’t go further than that since I felt Prey was satisfying enough…<br>
Decision was made something like this : shit I’m gonna go play chess instead of waiting to download Portal…</p>
<p>Maybe those were some good games that I missed, but Valve made some compromises to attract as many people as they could.<br>
That’s why there are so many gamers returning to CS 1.6 from CS;S, some things are lost while new things are added and not everyone is going to like it…<br>
Take the car in HL2 for example, who thought we would get to drive a car in  HL -nobody!<br>
In Episode 3 you can expect to drive 747 while fighting terrorists for what I know that shit might sell better than Modern Warfare but I’m not going to buy it!<br>
Gameplay mechanics is broken in cs;s and even more in HL2 and there are no excuses fore that nor number of sold games is proof of quality, if you watch things like that than any porn movie is better than the xyz title with a cult following…</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/atomic-pc-bm-preview/5329/414">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/atomic-pc-bm-preview/5329/414</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 15 Sep 2010 23:12:05 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-5329-414</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/atomic-pc-bm-preview/5329.rss">Atomic PC - BM Preview</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Atomic PC - BM Preview</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[McVeigh]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>He is no longer part of the team. The exact details of his departure have not been disclosed.</p>
<p><a href="https://wiki.blackmesasource.com/Past_Team_Members#Texture_Art" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://wiki.blackmesasource.com/Past_Team_Members#Texture_Art</a></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/atomic-pc-bm-preview/5329/413">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/atomic-pc-bm-preview/5329/413</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 15 Sep 2010 22:15:45 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-5329-413</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/atomic-pc-bm-preview/5329.rss">Atomic PC - BM Preview</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Atomic PC - BM Preview</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Winged_One]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Alright, my condolences for the leak, guys.  I really hope your morale bounces back from such an unfortunate event.</p>
<p>I’m not sure this was covered, what’s Orcone’s status now?  Has he been kicked out and/or reprimanded in some other way?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/atomic-pc-bm-preview/5329/412">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/atomic-pc-bm-preview/5329/412</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 15 Sep 2010 22:00:47 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-5329-412</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/atomic-pc-bm-preview/5329.rss">Atomic PC - BM Preview</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Atomic PC - BM Preview</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[jerry]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>found it<br>
<a href="https://www.moddb.com/mods/raindrop" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://www.moddb.com/mods/raindrop</a></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/atomic-pc-bm-preview/5329/411">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/atomic-pc-bm-preview/5329/411</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 15 Sep 2010 17:52:37 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-5329-411</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/atomic-pc-bm-preview/5329.rss">Atomic PC - BM Preview</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Atomic PC - BM Preview</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Kazioo]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>It WAS Raindrop. They changed engine ;(</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/atomic-pc-bm-preview/5329/410">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/atomic-pc-bm-preview/5329/410</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 15 Sep 2010 17:50:06 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-5329-410</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/atomic-pc-bm-preview/5329.rss">Atomic PC - BM Preview</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Atomic PC - BM Preview</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[_amp_955_dam]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Isn’t it Slums?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/atomic-pc-bm-preview/5329/409">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/atomic-pc-bm-preview/5329/409</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 15 Sep 2010 17:46:47 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-5329-409</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/atomic-pc-bm-preview/5329.rss">Atomic PC - BM Preview</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Atomic PC - BM Preview</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[jerry]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Medevilae">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/m/aca169/40.png" class="avatar"> Medevilae:</div>
<blockquote>
<p><img src="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/optimized/2X/3/3bd82be6bb12e640c4eb61dc2f0dd857ef29f7fb_2_690x431.jpeg" alt="" data-base62-sha1="8xpjAQmENIJtudfunWGm5eesfhx" width="690" height="431" srcset="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/optimized/2X/3/3bd82be6bb12e640c4eb61dc2f0dd857ef29f7fb_2_690x431.jpeg, https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/optimized/2X/3/3bd82be6bb12e640c4eb61dc2f0dd857ef29f7fb_2_1035x646.jpeg 1.5x, https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/optimized/2X/3/3bd82be6bb12e640c4eb61dc2f0dd857ef29f7fb_2_1380x862.jpeg 2x" data-small-upload="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/optimized/2X/3/3bd82be6bb12e640c4eb61dc2f0dd857ef29f7fb_2_10x10.png"></p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>:jizz:<br>
what mod is that?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/atomic-pc-bm-preview/5329/408">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/atomic-pc-bm-preview/5329/408</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 15 Sep 2010 17:33:07 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-5329-408</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/atomic-pc-bm-preview/5329.rss">Atomic PC - BM Preview</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Atomic PC - BM Preview</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[_amp_955_dam]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><span alt="" class="broken-image" title="This image is broken"><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-unlink svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#unlink"></use></svg></span></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/atomic-pc-bm-preview/5329/407">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/atomic-pc-bm-preview/5329/407</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 15 Sep 2010 16:53:33 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-5329-407</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/atomic-pc-bm-preview/5329.rss">Atomic PC - BM Preview</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Atomic PC - BM Preview</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Winged_One]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I just read through this thread.</p>
<p>Holy shit.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/atomic-pc-bm-preview/5329/406">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/atomic-pc-bm-preview/5329/406</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 15 Sep 2010 13:07:39 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-5329-406</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/atomic-pc-bm-preview/5329.rss">Atomic PC - BM Preview</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Atomic PC - BM Preview</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[DiePoente]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="213">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/2/aca169/40.png" class="avatar"> 213:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>the source engine only looks good in the dear esther mod remake.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>:hmph:</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/atomic-pc-bm-preview/5329/405">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/atomic-pc-bm-preview/5329/405</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 15 Sep 2010 12:18:52 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-5329-405</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/atomic-pc-bm-preview/5329.rss">Atomic PC - BM Preview</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Atomic PC - BM Preview</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Maxey]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Now, we have two, lol.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/atomic-pc-bm-preview/5329/404">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/atomic-pc-bm-preview/5329/404</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 15 Sep 2010 11:07:34 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-5329-404</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/atomic-pc-bm-preview/5329.rss">Atomic PC - BM Preview</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
