<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Faceposer Help</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/faceposer-help/7703</link>
    <description>I&#39;ve been testing the Valve SDK Faceposer tool, I&#39;ve managed to get it working fine, but whenever I attempt to run my animation in a Source game, I have a problem. The animation keeps repeating its-self, which is what I want, but, whenever it&#39;s just about to replay the animation, the actor will stand up and go back to his idle pose, before re-playing the animation. This is annoying when I want the NPC to sit down. The console commands I&#39;m using are:

ent_setname X
ent_fire setexpressionoverride scenes/X.vcd

X refers to either the name of the actor, or the name of the Faceposer animation. Thanks in advance for any help.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 17 Aug 2011 18:46:23 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Help and Support</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/faceposer-help/7703.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Faceposer Help</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Mr_Bozza]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I’ve been testing the Valve SDK Faceposer tool, I’ve managed to get it working fine, but whenever I attempt to run my animation in a Source game, I have a problem. The animation keeps repeating its-self, which is what I want, but, whenever it’s just about to replay the animation, the actor will stand up and go back to his idle pose, before re-playing the animation. This is annoying when I want the NPC to sit down. The console commands I’m using are:</p>
<p>ent_setname X<br>
ent_fire setexpressionoverride scenes/X.vcd</p>
<p>X refers to either the name of the actor, or the name of the Faceposer animation. Thanks in advance for any help.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/faceposer-help/7703/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/faceposer-help/7703/1</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 17 Aug 2011 18:46:23 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7703-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/faceposer-help/7703.rss">Faceposer Help</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
