<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Surface Tension glitches</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/surface-tension-glitches/10475</link>
    <description>I&#39;ve encountered some minor and some major glitches in Surface Tension.

setpos 1349.407227 7752.468750 1472.046875;setang 17.687998 167.327881 0.000000

status
hostname: Half-Life 2
version : 1.0.1.0/14 4104 insecure  
map     : bm_c2a5a at: 1349 x, 7752 y, 1472 z

I went through the beginning of Surface Tension up to the dam, then came under fire and almost ran out of health, so I went back through the level back to the tunnel, which was still open. I then went into the tunnel (to the previous map) and collected a medkit from the previous map. I then went to leave the tunnel, and the door had mysteriously closed again, when I approached the door to open it the next map (c2a5a) loaded, but the door magically appeared open again without the animation of it opening. This was a few hours ago, but I didn&#39;t record it so just now I reloaded the map to get pos and status for you. I tried to reproduce the problem but the door was closed when I tried to backtrack, perhaps as intended.

setpos -20.893488 -3246.466553 411.966003;setang 6.138010 11.177628 0.000000
] status
hostname: Half-Life 2
version : 1.0.1.0/14 4104 insecure  
map     : bm_c2a5f at: -20 x, -3246 y, 411 z

That was a minor glitch, the major glitch I encountered was later in surface tension when you have to blow up the helicopter that is dropping marines in the middle of map bm_c2a5f. The way I played the level was to kill the vortigaunts and the first wave of dropping marines, and then I ignored the helicopter and ran through to where the TOW cannon is. I kept trying to use the TOW cannon to blow up the tank, while the helicopter was still floating there. No more marines came out of the helicopter while I was fighting the tank, and after launching all TOW missiles and 5 RPGs at the tank, it wasn&#39;t taking damage and kept firing at me until I was dead. I then spent half an hour trying to destroy the helicopter with the TOW missiles, the tank with the TOW missiles, and onward, until I got fed up and searched the forums to learn that I&#39;m supposed to destroy the helicopter with RPGs before I ever reach the TOW gun. So after learning this I blew away the helicopter and after it exploded a single marine remained suspended mid-air where the helecopter used to be holding on to an imaginary rope. I then killed him, and blew up the tank.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 17 Sep 2012 03:50:47 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>In-game Issues (Mod)</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/surface-tension-glitches/10475.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Surface Tension glitches</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Insomniak]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I’ve encountered some minor and some major glitches in Surface Tension.</p>
<p>setpos 1349.407227 7752.468750 1472.046875;setang 17.687998 167.327881 0.000000</p>
<p>status<br>
hostname: Half-Life 2<br>
version : 1.0.1.0/14 4104 insecure<br>
map     : bm_c2a5a at: 1349 x, 7752 y, 1472 z</p>
<p>I went through the beginning of Surface Tension up to the dam, then came under fire and almost ran out of health, so I went back through the level back to the tunnel, which was still open. I then went into the tunnel (to the previous map) and collected a medkit from the previous map. I then went to leave the tunnel, and the door had mysteriously closed again, when I approached the door to open it the next map (c2a5a) loaded, but the door magically appeared open again without the animation of it opening. This was a few hours ago, but I didn’t record it so just now I reloaded the map to get pos and status for you. I tried to reproduce the problem but the door was closed when I tried to backtrack, perhaps as intended.</p>
<p>setpos -20.893488 -3246.466553 411.966003;setang 6.138010 11.177628 0.000000<br>
] status<br>
hostname: Half-Life 2<br>
version : 1.0.1.0/14 4104 insecure<br>
map     : bm_c2a5f at: -20 x, -3246 y, 411 z</p>
<p>That was a minor glitch, the major glitch I encountered was later in surface tension when you have to blow up the helicopter that is dropping marines in the middle of map bm_c2a5f. The way I played the level was to kill the vortigaunts and the first wave of dropping marines, and then I ignored the helicopter and ran through to where the TOW cannon is. I kept trying to use the TOW cannon to blow up the tank, while the helicopter was still floating there. No more marines came out of the helicopter while I was fighting the tank, and after launching all TOW missiles and 5 RPGs at the tank, it wasn’t taking damage and kept firing at me until I was dead. I then spent half an hour trying to destroy the helicopter with the TOW missiles, the tank with the TOW missiles, and onward, until I got fed up and searched the forums to learn that I’m supposed to destroy the helicopter with RPGs before I ever reach the TOW gun. So after learning this I blew away the helicopter and after it exploded a single marine remained suspended mid-air where the helecopter used to be holding on to an imaginary rope. I then killed him, and blew up the tank.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/surface-tension-glitches/10475/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/surface-tension-glitches/10475/1</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 17 Sep 2012 03:50:47 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-10475-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/surface-tension-glitches/10475.rss">Surface Tension glitches</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
