<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Weapon Changes (or lack of changes, mostly)</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/weapon-changes-or-lack-of-changes-mostly/115</link>
    <description>The purpose here is basically trying to reconstruct some of the more informative threads that I can think of that were lost when the site crashed. I did most of this from memory, but JamesKane was kind enough to fill in a lot of stuff that I had either forgotten, or that simply hadn&#39;t been confirmed before yet. One personal note I&#39;d like to make sure people remember that &quot;CONFIRMED&quot; does not mean &quot;SET IN STONE&quot; it&#39;s just that if the devs do change it, it&#39;s most likely only going to be for gameplay balancing reasons that will be done ENTIRELY at their own discretion. Anything in [COLOR=&#39;Red&#39;]red still hasn&#39;t been confirmed:

[b]Possible/Confirmed Changes from HL1 - [/b]

Glock
Primary fire can be shot as fast as button is clicked (with limits set so that binding primary fire to scroll wheel doesn&#39;t result in the ability to burn through a full clip all at once) Allowing autofire rates to be achieved simply by clicking that fast.
Secondary fire currently does nothing, but MIGHT be changed to implement a standard autofire rate when held.

RPG
(Rocket will follow laser site based on(but apparently NOT EXACTLY THE SAME AS) HL2&#39;s following pattern, instead of HL1. This might mean that the rocket can be turned completely around. I&#39;m guessing that it will have minute differences that a lot of people won&#39;t notice unless they specifically play around with the RPG launcher on HL1, HL2, and Black Mesa to compare, but otherwise will function effectively enough.
Secondary fire will still turn Laser site on/off as in HL1
New Rocket cannot be loaded until previously fired rocket is destroyed)
[COLOR=&#39;DarkRed&#39;][I have not managed to get a full confirmation on this particular detail yet, but neither has it been denied: I am assuming that the Rocket will still be able to be fired and travel underwater, as in HL1]

Gluon Gun
[COLOR=&#39;Red&#39;]Secondary Fire does nothing?
[COLOR=&#39;Red&#39;][Judging from the [url=&#39;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=CqXmXzLfdZ0&#39;]VIDEO[/url] that the devs released, it&#39;s fairly certain that the alt fire animation is included, but there&#39;s no way to be certain if it&#39;s triggered by the alt fire button or if it&#39;s just an idle animation as it was in HL: S]

Hornet Gun
number of hornets remains the same, primary fire still shoots homing hornets, secondary fires straight, rate of fire/restocking may be altered for gameplay balancing purposes. Homing script for hornets is new and apparently works well enough that hornets are capable of circling their target. Another point of interest is that they are &quot;physically simulated&quot; though what that means for gameplay I can only guess at.
[quote=&quot;JamesKane&quot;]
If you aim hornet gun at an entity then the hornets will follow that entity (The code knows you want to directly target that entity, so it sets the hornets to follow that entity).

Another reason for this design is to prevent you from accidentally killing friendlies unless of course you directly fire upon them.

edit: We also took extra measure like increasing damage, speed, and what not to ensure it is an effective weapon unlike how it was in HL.
[/quote]
Grenades
Will be implemented, but hasn&#39;t yet - Secondary Fire will work like HL2, to allow a grenade to be tossed a shorter distance, or while ducking, rolled across the ground
Is ALREADY implemented - Grenade &quot;Cooking&quot; = Primary Fire remains like HL1 where time to blast is counted from initial button press, and not from releasing the button to throw it. This would allow grenades to be timed to make less time for enemies to run, but would also allow the player to blow themselves up by holding on too long
HASN&#39;T been implemented - Grenades that have been thrown can be picked up with the &quot;use&quot; button and thrown as was possible in HL2. If this does get left out, I&#39;m betting it&#39;s due to the lack of gravity gun killing any of usefulness that this feature would have added. There&#39;s just not enough time to grab an enemy grenade and toss it far enough away to be worth not simply running away from it. The only other purpose it served was to allow you to throw it after it had been armed since HL2 didn&#39;t have grenade cooking, but since Black Mesa will implement this, it again becomes pointless.

Satchel Charges
Primary will always toss out a satchel
Secondary will always detonate any satchels that have been tossed out
Devs are &quot;Looking into&quot; implementing the feature that placed satchels can be picked up and moved, or picked back up into the inventory, by pressing the &quot;use&quot; button on them after they&#39;ve been initially thrown out. [COLOR=&#39;Red&#39;]Cross your fingers, folks, what I&#39;m hoping for is that they implement it [url=&#39;https://forums.blackmesasource.com/showpost.php?p=3754&amp;postcount=81&#39;]like this[/url]

[b]CONFIRMED No Changes from HL1 -[/b](NOTE: does not mean &quot;no changes from HL: S&quot;)

Crowbar
suggestions already killed - no using secondary for winding up for stronger swing, or for throwing

Python
Secondary fire, which activates zoom and laser site in deathmatch, WILL be available in deathmatch, but NOT through single player mode

MP5
Uses same ammo as Glock instead of having it&#39;s own ammo, as was done in HL2 with the Submachine Gun. A vmt. trick that apparntly let you strip the gun down to it&#39;s basic parts and not have the extra attachments show apparently works to some degree in Black Mesa as well, but through [url=&#39;https://forums.blackmesasource.com/showpost.php?p=4118&amp;postcount=97&#39;]different methods[/url]. 
(yes folks, seriously; in HL1 the MP5 uses the same reserve ammo as the glock does. I don&#39;t know if this the case for HL: S, but I have personally confirmed it to be true for HL1)

Assault Shotgun
Chambers 8 shots, not limited to HL2&#39;s 6 shots

Crossbow
suggestions already killed - will NOT be able to pin enemies to walls. Sure, it looks cool, but in HL1 they&#39;re SUPPOSED to be tranq darts. In HL2, those were superheated rebar being fired. I wanted it too, but lets be real about this; HL: S was a hastily slapped together port and the only reason it was the same as HL2 was because it was easier to just leave in the coding that came with the HL2 engine. That&#39;s not what the point of Black Mesa is.

Tau Cannon (this is also called the Gauss gun, people!)
The jumping abilities that are exclusive to deathmatch will remain exclusive, and not be carried over to single player, but recoil from secondary fire will still push player back just like in HL1

Trip Mines
suggestions already killed - no secondary fire to allow trip mines to be thrown or tossed out, they must be placed directly against a surface
[COLOR=&#39;Red&#39;][I have not confirmed if &#39;trip mine climbing&#39; is possible, nor if it is still possible to plant the tripmine directly on an NPC or player.At the very least i hope the latter is possible]

Snarks
suggestions already killed - no secondary fire to allow snarks to be captured if there is room free in the snark hive and snarks are chasing you</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 21 Mar 2010 21:51:17 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>The Cafeteria</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/weapon-changes-or-lack-of-changes-mostly/115.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Weapon Changes (or lack of changes, mostly)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[bur]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>That would already double the amount of detailed character models, though, which probably takes up a lot of space and memory.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/weapon-changes-or-lack-of-changes-mostly/115/197">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/weapon-changes-or-lack-of-changes-mostly/115/197</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 21 Mar 2010 21:51:17 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-115-197</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/weapon-changes-or-lack-of-changes-mostly/115.rss">Weapon Changes (or lack of changes, mostly)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Weapon Changes (or lack of changes, mostly)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Tom_caT]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="JeffMOD">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/user_avatar/leakfree.org/jeffmod/40/4333_2.png" class="avatar"> JeffMOD:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>It would require too many body submodels to be efficient and good looking.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Though I agree they shouldn’t take the time. It wouldn’t be too many models to make all the humanoid creatures have just a headless model. The HECU, guards, scientists, vorts, assassins, AGrunts and maybe Controllers. The rest can gib because, well, they don’t have noticable heads.</p>
<p>Just my 2 cents on the subject though.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/weapon-changes-or-lack-of-changes-mostly/115/196">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/weapon-changes-or-lack-of-changes-mostly/115/196</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 21 Mar 2010 20:36:17 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-115-196</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/weapon-changes-or-lack-of-changes-mostly/115.rss">Weapon Changes (or lack of changes, mostly)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Weapon Changes (or lack of changes, mostly)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[JeffMOD]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>It would be neat, but it would take too much time, effort, and diskspace.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/weapon-changes-or-lack-of-changes-mostly/115/195">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/weapon-changes-or-lack-of-changes-mostly/115/195</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 21 Mar 2010 17:01:23 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-115-195</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/weapon-changes-or-lack-of-changes-mostly/115.rss">Weapon Changes (or lack of changes, mostly)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Weapon Changes (or lack of changes, mostly)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Lord_Grievous]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I know, I know, I just said it would be neat.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/weapon-changes-or-lack-of-changes-mostly/115/194">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/weapon-changes-or-lack-of-changes-mostly/115/194</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 21 Mar 2010 14:03:09 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-115-194</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/weapon-changes-or-lack-of-changes-mostly/115.rss">Weapon Changes (or lack of changes, mostly)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Weapon Changes (or lack of changes, mostly)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[JeffMOD]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>It would require too many body submodels to be efficient and good looking.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/weapon-changes-or-lack-of-changes-mostly/115/193">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/weapon-changes-or-lack-of-changes-mostly/115/193</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 21 Mar 2010 12:43:53 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-115-193</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/weapon-changes-or-lack-of-changes-mostly/115.rss">Weapon Changes (or lack of changes, mostly)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Weapon Changes (or lack of changes, mostly)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Lord_Grievous]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>It would be pretty neat though  :rolleyes:</p>
<p><span alt="" class="broken-image" title="This image is broken"><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-unlink svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#unlink"></use></svg></span></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/weapon-changes-or-lack-of-changes-mostly/115/192">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/weapon-changes-or-lack-of-changes-mostly/115/192</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 21 Mar 2010 10:30:34 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-115-192</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/weapon-changes-or-lack-of-changes-mostly/115.rss">Weapon Changes (or lack of changes, mostly)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Weapon Changes (or lack of changes, mostly)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Mr_Someguy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I don’t think you can gib individual limbs like in L4D.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/weapon-changes-or-lack-of-changes-mostly/115/191">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/weapon-changes-or-lack-of-changes-mostly/115/191</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 21 Mar 2010 10:21:52 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-115-191</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/weapon-changes-or-lack-of-changes-mostly/115.rss">Weapon Changes (or lack of changes, mostly)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Weapon Changes (or lack of changes, mostly)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Ramirezoid]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Will the magnum be able to pop an enemy’s skull into a big watermelony mess of explosive death, or will headshots just result in ragdolls/decapitation?</p>
<p>(I’ve seen the gib test video)</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/weapon-changes-or-lack-of-changes-mostly/115/190">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/weapon-changes-or-lack-of-changes-mostly/115/190</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 21 Mar 2010 08:57:39 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-115-190</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/weapon-changes-or-lack-of-changes-mostly/115.rss">Weapon Changes (or lack of changes, mostly)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Weapon Changes (or lack of changes, mostly)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Mr_Someguy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I was thinking, what if the Crossbow (being a tranquilizer gun) actually did damage over time instead of instantly. The most you shot a target, the faster it took damage. Could be used to help drain the health of an opponent over time while you attack them with another weapon.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/weapon-changes-or-lack-of-changes-mostly/115/189">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/weapon-changes-or-lack-of-changes-mostly/115/189</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 21 Mar 2010 08:31:44 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-115-189</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/weapon-changes-or-lack-of-changes-mostly/115.rss">Weapon Changes (or lack of changes, mostly)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Weapon Changes (or lack of changes, mostly)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[rorriMAesU]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I guess there is nothing new to talk about lol</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/weapon-changes-or-lack-of-changes-mostly/115/188">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/weapon-changes-or-lack-of-changes-mostly/115/188</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 19 Mar 2010 22:33:22 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-115-188</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/weapon-changes-or-lack-of-changes-mostly/115.rss">Weapon Changes (or lack of changes, mostly)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Weapon Changes (or lack of changes, mostly)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[bur]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Yeah, it should just be a physics object, you don’t have the time to throw it back, so it would still flush you out.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/weapon-changes-or-lack-of-changes-mostly/115/187">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/weapon-changes-or-lack-of-changes-mostly/115/187</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 19 Mar 2010 22:04:44 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-115-187</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/weapon-changes-or-lack-of-changes-mostly/115.rss">Weapon Changes (or lack of changes, mostly)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Weapon Changes (or lack of changes, mostly)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Doop]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="rorriMAesU">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/r/bc79bd/40.png" class="avatar"> rorriMAesU:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Whatever, less programming for the devs.  I think its time for a new topic…</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I’m just pointing this out, in HL2 if you pressed e you could throw back the grenade because it was a physics object. So I doubt they would need to do any programming and just make it a physics object with a very low weight. But since you couldn’t throw grenades back in HL, I don’t want it in Black Mesa.<br>
And like what TheeGoatPig said, it does sound dumb to me also.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/weapon-changes-or-lack-of-changes-mostly/115/186">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/weapon-changes-or-lack-of-changes-mostly/115/186</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 19 Mar 2010 21:53:31 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-115-186</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/weapon-changes-or-lack-of-changes-mostly/115.rss">Weapon Changes (or lack of changes, mostly)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Weapon Changes (or lack of changes, mostly)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[TheeGoatPig]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I have been playing half Life since the year it came out. I played Half Life 2 since it came out as well. I have never tried to pick up thrown grenades, even after hearing everyone talk about how much they love doing it. It just sounds dumb to me.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/weapon-changes-or-lack-of-changes-mostly/115/185">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/weapon-changes-or-lack-of-changes-mostly/115/185</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 19 Mar 2010 20:36:28 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-115-185</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/weapon-changes-or-lack-of-changes-mostly/115.rss">Weapon Changes (or lack of changes, mostly)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Weapon Changes (or lack of changes, mostly)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[rorriMAesU]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Even though it has been confirmed that you cannot pick up grenades and throw them back, it would have been just dandy if they had included this ability.  Personally I do not care.  With a 2.5 second fuse it really isn’t worth the chance, but you know that having the ability is do so would have been cool and still within the guidelines of BM. (it would be cool to watch an occasional HECU recruit attempt to toss back a grenade rambo style…only to explode)</p>
<p>Whatever, less programming for the devs.  I think its time for a new topic…</p>
<p>So, we all love the random explosive barrels placed throughout all the Half-Lifes (even though I doubt I’m the only one who has ever found themselves asking, “who in their right mind would leave all these barrels laying around?”). I was thinking how it would be sweet to have liquid nitrogen barrels or something similar…some kind of frozen variant of the random explosive barrel, a random freezing barrel lol.  Or, around the areas in the facility that require extreme cooling, have liquid N storage tanks or exposed pipes running the walls which, when pierced with the magnum, can freeze the surrounding area/victims.</p>
<p>It’s like that scene from T2: shooting the frozen T1000, and watching him explode.  Imagine doing that in HL…exploding, frozen zombies lol.  Perhaps include the ability to freeze feet to floors, leaving the bodies unharmed but helpless and struggling.  Just a thought, but it seems like fun.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/weapon-changes-or-lack-of-changes-mostly/115/184">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/weapon-changes-or-lack-of-changes-mostly/115/184</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 18 Mar 2010 04:00:41 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-115-184</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/weapon-changes-or-lack-of-changes-mostly/115.rss">Weapon Changes (or lack of changes, mostly)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Weapon Changes (or lack of changes, mostly)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Mr_Someguy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>It has a 2.5 second fuse. by the time it reaches you, it’ll probably have burned off at least a second.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/weapon-changes-or-lack-of-changes-mostly/115/183">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/weapon-changes-or-lack-of-changes-mostly/115/183</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 18 Mar 2010 02:35:35 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-115-183</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/weapon-changes-or-lack-of-changes-mostly/115.rss">Weapon Changes (or lack of changes, mostly)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Weapon Changes (or lack of changes, mostly)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Floyd]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Raminator">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/r/6bbea6/40.png" class="avatar"> Raminator:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Why do you ask a question when you give the answer in the same breath? If you can throw a grenade back, it isn’t doing its job of flushing you out. It’s meant to make you start <span class="bbcode-i">acting</span> and stop <span class="bbcode-i">reacting</span>, and its not going to be very effective if you can remove it as a threat.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Because throwing them back is immensely fun - it creates a very unique sense of tension and fun, especially with the removal of the tick - should you risk throwing it back and having it kill the enemy or blowing you up, or simply run away? There are going to be occasions where you see the soldier throw the grenade and you know the <span class="bbcode-i">exact</span> amount of time you have to remove the threat, and there are also going to occasions where you only <span class="bbcode-i">just</span> see the grenade and you are forced to do whatever you can to get out of the way.</p>
<p>I haven’t played the game, so I don’t know what effect that having a 2.5 second fuse would have on it. I just think that, on the off chance that you see a soldier throwing a grenade, you should be able to throw it back regardless. As android said, the choice should be up to you on whether you want to survive. Perhaps there are some situations where a player <span class="bbcode-i">is</span> able to pick up a thrown grenade and safely toss it back, perhaps there aren’t. I was just curious.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/weapon-changes-or-lack-of-changes-mostly/115/182">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/weapon-changes-or-lack-of-changes-mostly/115/182</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 18 Mar 2010 01:18:02 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-115-182</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/weapon-changes-or-lack-of-changes-mostly/115.rss">Weapon Changes (or lack of changes, mostly)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Weapon Changes (or lack of changes, mostly)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[etb513]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="JamesKane">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/j/838e76/40.png" class="avatar"> JamesKane:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>As for the satchel, you can carry it around like a physics prop.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Muhahaha this is going to be fun.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/weapon-changes-or-lack-of-changes-mostly/115/181">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/weapon-changes-or-lack-of-changes-mostly/115/181</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 17 Mar 2010 21:40:07 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-115-181</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/weapon-changes-or-lack-of-changes-mostly/115.rss">Weapon Changes (or lack of changes, mostly)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Weapon Changes (or lack of changes, mostly)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Dillxn]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Ooooooh, that sounds nifty!  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/smiley.png?v=9" title=":smiley:" class="emoji" alt=":smiley:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/weapon-changes-or-lack-of-changes-mostly/115/180">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/weapon-changes-or-lack-of-changes-mostly/115/180</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 17 Mar 2010 21:32:21 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-115-180</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/weapon-changes-or-lack-of-changes-mostly/115.rss">Weapon Changes (or lack of changes, mostly)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Weapon Changes (or lack of changes, mostly)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[JamesKane]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I love how you guys are still debating if the player should be able to pick up armed hand grenades after two developers already confirmed it wont happen.</p>
<p>As for the satchel, you can carry it around like a physics prop.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/weapon-changes-or-lack-of-changes-mostly/115/179">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/weapon-changes-or-lack-of-changes-mostly/115/179</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 17 Mar 2010 20:58:47 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-115-179</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/weapon-changes-or-lack-of-changes-mostly/115.rss">Weapon Changes (or lack of changes, mostly)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Weapon Changes (or lack of changes, mostly)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[bur]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>But it should still be possible to pick them up, to avoid a jarring “WTF?” moment shortly before you’re blown to pieces.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/weapon-changes-or-lack-of-changes-mostly/115/178">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/weapon-changes-or-lack-of-changes-mostly/115/178</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 17 Mar 2010 19:49:08 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-115-178</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/weapon-changes-or-lack-of-changes-mostly/115.rss">Weapon Changes (or lack of changes, mostly)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Weapon Changes (or lack of changes, mostly)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[etb513]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Mr. Someguy">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Mr. Someguy:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Maybe I’m just slow, but I am never able to toss grenades back without them blowing up in my face, it’s a dozen times safer to just move away.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Exactly, and with the grenades in BM having just a 2.5 second timer <span class="bbcode-i">and</span> the fact that we don’t have a gravity gun this time around, it seems entirely impractical to attempt to throw grenades back.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/weapon-changes-or-lack-of-changes-mostly/115/177">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/weapon-changes-or-lack-of-changes-mostly/115/177</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 17 Mar 2010 18:16:11 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-115-177</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/weapon-changes-or-lack-of-changes-mostly/115.rss">Weapon Changes (or lack of changes, mostly)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Weapon Changes (or lack of changes, mostly)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Mr_Someguy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Maybe I’m just slow, but I am never able to toss grenades back without them blowing up in my face, it’s a dozen times safer to just move away.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/weapon-changes-or-lack-of-changes-mostly/115/176">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/weapon-changes-or-lack-of-changes-mostly/115/176</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 17 Mar 2010 01:12:20 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-115-176</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/weapon-changes-or-lack-of-changes-mostly/115.rss">Weapon Changes (or lack of changes, mostly)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Weapon Changes (or lack of changes, mostly)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Android11x]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Regardless of all this YOU MUST RUN FROM NADE, there WILL be instances where you WON’T be able to run. You are going to have to chuck that mutha bubbard. I say leave the ability. It should be your choice on how you want to survive (or die :fffuuu <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=9" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"> .</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/weapon-changes-or-lack-of-changes-mostly/115/175">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/weapon-changes-or-lack-of-changes-mostly/115/175</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 17 Mar 2010 00:34:43 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-115-175</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/weapon-changes-or-lack-of-changes-mostly/115.rss">Weapon Changes (or lack of changes, mostly)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Weapon Changes (or lack of changes, mostly)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Marb]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I was so used to grenade behavior in HL and other games, it was many months before I realized you could do <span class="bbcode-b">anything </span>with enemy grenades in HL2.  I had one tossed back at me in a DM game via gravity gun - was actually pretty cool, so I had to try it in SP.  I’m still not good at throwing them back - I’m more likely to be hurt if I try to do <span class="bbcode-i">anything </span>with them instead of just running away!</p>
<p>And I don’t see what the big argument over the Satchel is.  I don’t think thrown satchels should be able to be put back in inventory or change the number in your inventory until they are detonated or the map changes.  But I think it would be good if you could pick it up as an object - this way, it would offer slight improvement over HL without changing things too much and keeping things simple.  If you don’t pick it up, but want more (threw it over a cliff or something), you’ll have to detonate the one(s) you threw.  If you don’t detonate before level change, the thrown satchel(s) disappear from inventory (or like in HL, you press the button and nothing happens).</p>
<p>And as for DM, just keep it the same.  And if someone wants to carry around their own or someone else’s satchel as a physics object, why not?  This way, you won’t have to worry about “ownership” issues.  Obviously, if you’re carrying your own, any weapons in your hands are inoperable, so you’d have to make sure you actually picked up your own and not someone elses…</p>
<p>1st guy: Hey, why are you carrying my satchel?<br>
2nd guy: This is yours?  I thought it was mine.<br>
1st guy: IDK, but I guess you can keep it either way…<br>
2nd guy: Thank y- <span class="bbcode-b"><span class="bbcode-i">BOOOM!!!</span></span></p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Greenhorn">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/g/0ea827/40.png" class="avatar"> Greenhorn:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>In Svencoop 4 you currently have both: the MP 5 (without a Grenade Launcher) and the M4A1 with the M203. Both using different types of Bullets there. The grenade launcher uses secondary fire-mode but 1st push only reloads the launcher and the second push will fire it - this makes it more realistic.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Don’t get me wrong, I like SC and think what they did works well for <span class="bbcode-i">that </span>game (hated the M203 at first, but got used to it).  But I think the M203 manual reload was put in more to stop grenade-spamming; otherwise, they would have made it auto-reload like the rocket launcher.  Besides, “faithful recreation of HL” isn’t really a top priority with SC.  So I think what BM has so far will work just fine.  In other words:  no separate M16 and no reload for the grenade launcher!  If you want to spam grenades, fine!  I’m sure ammo for it won’t be as plentiful as in some SC maps (especially since XP servers had ammo-regen).</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/weapon-changes-or-lack-of-changes-mostly/115/174">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/weapon-changes-or-lack-of-changes-mostly/115/174</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 16 Mar 2010 23:33:03 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-115-174</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/weapon-changes-or-lack-of-changes-mostly/115.rss">Weapon Changes (or lack of changes, mostly)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Weapon Changes (or lack of changes, mostly)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Dillxn]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Because some people’s common sense would tell them to chuck that thing as far away from them as they can? I can throw a grenade faster than I can run away from it. [COLOR=’<span class="hashtag">#212121</span>’](I’ve tried)</p>
<p>I still support the idea of having the grenade automatically blow up whenever a player picks it up. Eventually they’ll get the idea to not pick it up anymore.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/weapon-changes-or-lack-of-changes-mostly/115/173">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/weapon-changes-or-lack-of-changes-mostly/115/173</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 16 Mar 2010 22:42:39 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-115-173</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/weapon-changes-or-lack-of-changes-mostly/115.rss">Weapon Changes (or lack of changes, mostly)</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
