<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Eli&#39;s Story/Arc Idea</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/elis-story-arc-idea/62008</link>
    <description>So I was thinking about when the game is fully completed and if the devs want to try a DLC-type of thing with a small added story, I think there should be a story with how Eli escapes Black Mesa with the infant Alyx and with Isaac (and maybe Lamar). I know it&#39;s added work but it would be a cool idea to learn a bit of backstory about Gordon Freeman&#39;s long time friend who we know little of in the series regarding how he got out. Again that&#39;s if the Dev&#39;s are willing/wanting to do that. I talked about this before in the Cafeteria and I will post it here: https://forums.blackmesasource.com/t/elis-story-adventure-idea/14904</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 18 Dec 2018 19:09:02 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Half-Life Series</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/elis-story-arc-idea/62008.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Eli&#39;s Story/Arc Idea</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Demolitionist1]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>So I was thinking about when the game is fully completed and if the devs want to try a DLC-type of thing with a small added story, I think there should be a story with how Eli escapes Black Mesa with the infant Alyx and with Isaac (and maybe Lamar). I know it’s added work but it would be a cool idea to learn a bit of backstory about Gordon Freeman’s long time friend who we know little of in the series regarding how he got out. Again that’s if the Dev’s are willing/wanting to do that. I talked about this before in the Cafeteria and I will post it here: <a href="https://forums.blackmesasource.com/t/elis-story-adventure-idea/14904" rel="nofollow noopener">https://forums.blackmesasource.com/t/elis-story-adventure-idea/14904</a></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/elis-story-arc-idea/62008/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/elis-story-arc-idea/62008/1</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 18 Dec 2018 19:09:02 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-62008-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/elis-story-arc-idea/62008.rss">Eli&#39;s Story/Arc Idea</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
