<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Game names and how their impact on you</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/game-names-and-how-their-impact-on-you/7456</link>
    <description>Hi, 

I&#39;m doing a little study on the Video games names, how do you feel about them, etc.

Here are a few questions :

- On a 0 to 10 squale, rate how much the game name is important
- How would you describe a &quot;Good&quot; game name
- Do you believe the game name must be very related to the game or stay pretty vague ?

Also, you are very welcome to bring exemples of games and your feeling about them.

Few exemples of my feelings :

Duke Nukem Forever : Obvious easy name.
Mass Effect : Pretty unrelated, vague.
Half-Life : Very vague, mysterious
Bioshock : Unrelated ?
Portal : Describe game concept, related

There are multiple ways of naming a Game : for example : 

Describe the game concept (obvious portal)
Name the main interresting concept (again, portal but others to)
Attract attention (FEAR)
Mystery (Half-Life) 
Name the Hero (Pretty much any tomb raider)

Which do you think is the most efficient ?

Thats all, ofc anything on the subject is welcome.
Sorry for my english.

Thanks for your help !</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 06 Jul 2011 14:07:36 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Technology and Gaming</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/game-names-and-how-their-impact-on-you/7456.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Game names and how their impact on you</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Scrue]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>If it had Space in the name or has anything to do with physics I’ll probably buy it.<br>
Otherwise I, usually, am more attracted to short names that are easy to remember such as Homeworld and Starcraft.</p>
<p>EDIT:</p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>Half-life, I knew this game was a sci-fi shooter from the cover, and the name, half life referring to half the time it takes for an atom to decade.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Half-life is the period of time it takes for an element to decay to half it’s original number of atoms of the same element. not half the time it takes for half an atom to ten years.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/game-names-and-how-their-impact-on-you/7456/27">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/game-names-and-how-their-impact-on-you/7456/27</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 06 Jul 2011 14:07:36 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7456-27</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/game-names-and-how-their-impact-on-you/7456.rss">Game names and how their impact on you</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Game names and how their impact on you</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Nerdguy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Call of Duty: A call of duty?<br>
-Modern Warfare: The period of warfare<br>
-World at War: The world at war (2 fronts: Europe, Pacific)<br>
-Black Ops: Secret Stuff</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/game-names-and-how-their-impact-on-you/7456/26">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/game-names-and-how-their-impact-on-you/7456/26</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 06 Jul 2011 11:52:29 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7456-26</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/game-names-and-how-their-impact-on-you/7456.rss">Game names and how their impact on you</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Game names and how their impact on you</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Kairouseki]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Shub-Niggurath" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Shub-Niggurath</a><br>
<img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=9" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji only-emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/game-names-and-how-their-impact-on-you/7456/25">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/game-names-and-how-their-impact-on-you/7456/25</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 05 Jul 2011 16:13:24 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7456-25</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/game-names-and-how-their-impact-on-you/7456.rss">Game names and how their impact on you</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Game names and how their impact on you</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[mankyman6]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="ac3d">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/a/22d042/40.png" class="avatar"> ac3d:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Does not refer to the constant destruction and mayhem that goes on throughout the whole game,<br>
but is actually the codename for Shub-Niggurath.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Niggerwrath?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/game-names-and-how-their-impact-on-you/7456/24">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/game-names-and-how-their-impact-on-you/7456/24</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 05 Jul 2011 16:11:02 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7456-24</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/game-names-and-how-their-impact-on-you/7456.rss">Game names and how their impact on you</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Game names and how their impact on you</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Aemony]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="dblkion">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/d/da6949/40.png" class="avatar"> dblkion:</div>
<blockquote>
<ul>
<li>On a 0 to 10 squale, rate how much the game name is important</li>
</ul>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Depends on the situation and whether or not I’ve played another game with the same title before.</p>
<p>If it’s a completely unknown game which I’ve never before heard about and I am only reading the title of the name then the answer is 6/10. The name isn’t really important but serves as a first filter for my potential interest. For example a hardcore FPS game isn’t titled as a kids game would be, allowing me to easily filter out the games not intended for me.</p>
<p>Beyond that point the name doesn’t really matter as the naming schemes used in the gaming industry is screwed up beyond belief already. I was often surprised before when a title I would connect to a certain genre proved to instead be a game of a different genre, so I just stopped assuming things based on a game’s title.</p>
<p>However! If we’re talking about a sequel or another game in an already defined series of games then the name has a lot more weight attached to it, hence more importance. In those cases the name is of utmost importance and therefor the answer in these situations is 10/10.</p>
<p>Example of bad naming is, for example:<br>
<span class="bbcode-b">F.E.A.R. 3</span> (stylised as F.3.A.R.) - Doesn’t share the same ‘feel’ as the previous games. This title is on the borderline to being wrong.<br>
<span class="bbcode-b">Dragon Age 2</span> - Wrong, wrong, wrong, wrong! WRONG! The ‘2’ signifies that it is a sequel of some sort, while the game itself is more of a reboot than a direct continuation of the previous game. The ‘2’ allows players to make natural comparisons between the two titles whereby a lot of flaws in the ‘second’ game is made apparent and intensified.<br>
<span class="bbcode-b">Crysis 2</span> - Has the similar flaws as the previous mentioned example. People whom enjoy the game will probably find no problem with the title but people whom disliked the changes to the formula in the new game will hate the title since it doesn’t do the game justice.<br>
<span class="bbcode-b">Dungeon Siege 3</span> - The main genre of the game is changed and the whole formula is different. DS1 and DS2 were mostly dungeon crawlers where the loot and character development was the focus whereas DS3 is a ‘consolified’ story-driven action RPG with merely a small bit of dungeon crawling.</p>
<p>This whole ordeal is obviously by a game-to-game basis where the previous games determine the overall formula that connects the games within the series and which the newer games must respect and follow. Players aren’t surprised to learn that a new Final Fantasy game, for example, differs in terms of lore, world and characters from the previous game since this is an already defined part of the series. However what they wouldn’t like is a game which differs greatly from the previous games (which explains the backlash against FFXIII a bit), or is downright different.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">To summarize, the importance of the title of a game differs greatly depending on the situation at hand.</span></p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="dblkion">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/d/da6949/40.png" class="avatar"> dblkion:</div>
<blockquote>
<ul>
<li>How would you describe a “Good” game name</li>
</ul>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>A “good” game title would be one which tells new potential players something about the game while also giving more understanding, or reference, to actual players of the game.</p>
<p>Examples:<br>
<span class="bbcode-b">Mass Effect</span> - This is a great title because not only does the title signify that the game has something with physics about it, which for most people signifies a Sci-Fi oriented game, but it also is the title of the key element of the game, which only actual players of the game would understand. This, however, gives the title more meaning to those more interested in the story of the game than the potential customers.<br>
<span class="bbcode-b">Dragon Age</span> - This is also a great title as it brings the thoughts to the medieval period for potential customers which the games are ‘quite’ similar to. But for those whom have actually played the game it is actually the title of the age which the games take place in, meaning something else than just the medieval stuff.<br>
<span class="bbcode-b">Halo</span> - Brings the thoughts to something angelic, something unnatural and ‘above us’. It is not only a good description of the importance of the Master Chief character and how he relates to his fellow humans and his enemies, but it is also the name of the space rings of mass-destruction within the game, which the whole story and conflict is about. A potential customer would probably correlate the title to the former while an actual player would correlate it to the latter.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">So, a good title would be one which fullfills these two parameters, or something similar, describing the game for interested players while also acting as a reference to something within the game for those already playing the game.</span></p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="dblkion">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/d/da6949/40.png" class="avatar"> dblkion:</div>
<blockquote>
<ul>
<li>Do you believe the game name must be very related to the game or stay pretty vague ?</li>
</ul>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Depends, as they are both possible at the same time. Mass Effect and Halo are pretty vauge names while still heavily related to the games. It all depends on what perspective we’re talking about. But I do however think that it’s important that the title is more related than vague. Why? Simply because it makes it easier for players to correlate the title to the game by having a well-defined and easily understood title.</p>
<p>Take the title Half-Life for example. This is a really interesting name as it can be analysed quite extensively without ever coming up to an actual answer to what it refers to without getting the answer directly from Valve, the creators. Does the name refer to the nature of the work that the workers at Black Mesa are doing? Does it refer to Gordon Freeman’s “half life” as he seems to be but a pawn of the mysterious Gman? Is it a reference to the events of the Black Mesa Incident? Or is it merely a vague reference to the genre of the game?</p>
<p>Interesting, but a vague title that means a lot of risk-taking on the creators part. A risk most developers and/or publishers aren’t willing to take as gaming is becoming ever more mainstream and the title of a name is of utmost importance for customers when they are looking through potential games to buy.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">TL;DR: There’s no easy answer to any of these questions.</span></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/game-names-and-how-their-impact-on-you/7456/23">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/game-names-and-how-their-impact-on-you/7456/23</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 05 Jul 2011 13:54:25 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7456-23</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/game-names-and-how-their-impact-on-you/7456.rss">Game names and how their impact on you</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Game names and how their impact on you</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[ac3d]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>You knew what it meant before you saw it as a title for a game? I honestly didn’t.<br>
When I read the title “Half-Life” I didn’t think anything, I was too busy staring at Gordon’s face and all the bright vibrant colors on the cover.</p>
<p>edit:<br>
<span alt="" class="broken-image" title="This image is broken"><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-unlink svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#unlink"></use></svg></span><br>
Does not refer to the constant destruction and mayhem that goes on throughout the whole game,<br>
but is actually the codename for Shub-Niggurath.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/game-names-and-how-their-impact-on-you/7456/22">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/game-names-and-how-their-impact-on-you/7456/22</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 05 Jul 2011 13:17:57 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7456-22</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/game-names-and-how-their-impact-on-you/7456.rss">Game names and how their impact on you</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Game names and how their impact on you</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[TheSuperNova]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Half-life, I knew this game was a sci-fi shooter from the cover, and the name, half life referring to half the time it takes for an atom to decade.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/game-names-and-how-their-impact-on-you/7456/21">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/game-names-and-how-their-impact-on-you/7456/21</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 05 Jul 2011 11:44:50 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7456-21</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/game-names-and-how-their-impact-on-you/7456.rss">Game names and how their impact on you</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Game names and how their impact on you</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[k3nny1550]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Right. “Tactical Espionage Action.” derp</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/game-names-and-how-their-impact-on-you/7456/20">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/game-names-and-how-their-impact-on-you/7456/20</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 05 Jul 2011 09:20:14 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7456-20</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/game-names-and-how-their-impact-on-you/7456.rss">Game names and how their impact on you</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Game names and how their impact on you</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Jethrosoup]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="k3nny1550">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/user_avatar/leakfree.org/k3nny1550/40/4952_2.png" class="avatar"> k3nny1550:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Would anyone really have guessed they were buying a stealth action game from the white cover and red logo text?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>If they actually read what it said on the cover they might have guessed.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/game-names-and-how-their-impact-on-you/7456/19">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/game-names-and-how-their-impact-on-you/7456/19</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 05 Jul 2011 06:37:37 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7456-19</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/game-names-and-how-their-impact-on-you/7456.rss">Game names and how their impact on you</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Game names and how their impact on you</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[k3nny1550]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>What about “Metal Gear Solid?”</p>
<p><img src="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/original/2X/c/cdb2ca111d39ae20eee3c0f217c70ed3ee0eacf2.png" alt="" data-base62-sha1="tlGW1dESpgzcaIHKKUsXl8FTnJo" width="340" height="293"></p>
<p>The actual relation to the game is in the titular Metal Gear, but Solid refers to the polygons used in the game engine to place it above the original MSX2 Metal Gear games. Would anyone really have guessed they were buying a stealth action game from the white cover and red logo text?</p>
<p>Compare to Tom Clancy’s Splinter Cell, a game in the same genre-</p>
<p><img src="https://img.listal.com/image/184213/936full-tom-clancy%27s-splinter-cell-cover.jpg" alt="" width="" height=""></p>
<p>Tom Clancy- famous author of contemporary techno-thrillers</p>
<p>Splinter Cell relates to the character’s job. He’s a Splinter Cell- a lone operative sent on solo infiltration missions with a support staff working with him from the NSA.</p>
<p>BEFORE ANYONE TROLLS ME- I happen to <span class="bbcode-i">like</span> both of these games.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/game-names-and-how-their-impact-on-you/7456/18">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/game-names-and-how-their-impact-on-you/7456/18</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 05 Jul 2011 05:40:48 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7456-18</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/game-names-and-how-their-impact-on-you/7456.rss">Game names and how their impact on you</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Game names and how their impact on you</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[dblkion]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>How is your feelings for a game name not an opinion ?</p>
<p>Also, I don’t give a shit if i’m right or wrong, I asked people how THEY felt about them when they first discovered them, If you can’t understand that, I don’t know what u post in here</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/game-names-and-how-their-impact-on-you/7456/17">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/game-names-and-how-their-impact-on-you/7456/17</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 04 Jul 2011 20:48:28 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7456-17</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/game-names-and-how-their-impact-on-you/7456.rss">Game names and how their impact on you</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Game names and how their impact on you</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[TheeGoatPig]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Whether a game name is related to the game or not is not opinion though. You are simply wrong about a couple of those titles.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/game-names-and-how-their-impact-on-you/7456/16">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/game-names-and-how-their-impact-on-you/7456/16</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 04 Jul 2011 15:07:41 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7456-16</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/game-names-and-how-their-impact-on-you/7456.rss">Game names and how their impact on you</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Game names and how their impact on you</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[dblkion]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Its my personnal feeling about them, you can have your own opinion  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=9" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/game-names-and-how-their-impact-on-you/7456/15">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/game-names-and-how-their-impact-on-you/7456/15</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 04 Jul 2011 14:55:38 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7456-15</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/game-names-and-how-their-impact-on-you/7456.rss">Game names and how their impact on you</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Game names and how their impact on you</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[ac3d]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="dblkion">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/d/da6949/40.png" class="avatar"> dblkion:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>squale</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p><img src="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/original/2X/4/47d4999084ce5452f91f32e8ce3f5e0ca552c494.jpeg" alt="" data-base62-sha1="afrooD5zOAmGREMaNQdbiBt245K" width="520" height="466"></p>
<ul>
<li>
</li></ul>
<p><img src="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/original/2X/f/f53b3ecfa6e769411db964f8588a28abae278a0c.jpeg" alt="" data-base62-sha1="yZpUAZGwF7mLvoqvgmBko5lVAHG" width="526" height="373"></p>
<p>=</p>
<p><div class="lightbox-wrapper"><a class="lightbox" href="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/original/2X/7/7d45bca9392922fcb4b07c44590b73c6e8bb421e.jpeg" data-download-href="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/7d45bca9392922fcb4b07c44590b73c6e8bb421e" title=""><img src="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/original/2X/7/7d45bca9392922fcb4b07c44590b73c6e8bb421e.jpeg" alt="" data-base62-sha1="hSd5Rrn5wRLcoaAz8fTr8Q3oEJE" width="671" height="500" data-small-upload="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/optimized/2X/7/7d45bca9392922fcb4b07c44590b73c6e8bb421e_2_10x10.png"><div class="meta"><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-far-image svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#far-image"></use></svg><span class="filename"></span><span class="informations">731×544 69.7 KB</span><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-discourse-expand svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#discourse-expand"></use></svg></div></a></div></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/game-names-and-how-their-impact-on-you/7456/14">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/game-names-and-how-their-impact-on-you/7456/14</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 04 Jul 2011 07:28:41 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7456-14</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/game-names-and-how-their-impact-on-you/7456.rss">Game names and how their impact on you</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Game names and how their impact on you</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Zsub]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Except maybe high-poly or even RL asses? =)</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/game-names-and-how-their-impact-on-you/7456/13">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/game-names-and-how-their-impact-on-you/7456/13</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 04 Jul 2011 06:48:33 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7456-13</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/game-names-and-how-their-impact-on-you/7456.rss">Game names and how their impact on you</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Game names and how their impact on you</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Jethrosoup]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>There’s nothing more beautiful in the world.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/game-names-and-how-their-impact-on-you/7456/12">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/game-names-and-how-their-impact-on-you/7456/12</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 04 Jul 2011 05:18:44 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7456-12</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/game-names-and-how-their-impact-on-you/7456.rss">Game names and how their impact on you</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Game names and how their impact on you</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Jeannotvb]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Low poly normal mapped asses with specular highlight?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/game-names-and-how-their-impact-on-you/7456/11">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/game-names-and-how-their-impact-on-you/7456/11</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 04 Jul 2011 05:13:06 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7456-11</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/game-names-and-how-their-impact-on-you/7456.rss">Game names and how their impact on you</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Game names and how their impact on you</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Jethrosoup]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I think you got what you paid for<br>
<img src="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/original/2X/9/998e957180ebdab8040f2f880009481acad07f51.png" alt="" data-base62-sha1="lUqxjjrM9j6tPIIpiAMW5dARIPf" width="635" height="357"><br>
<img src="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/original/2X/f/fa6c6e46311cec193755c81ad092a93df76c0947.png" alt="" data-base62-sha1="zJlG7LOX3s3Q6IMpO6QOvQcB2Pd" width="636" height="355"></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/game-names-and-how-their-impact-on-you/7456/10">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/game-names-and-how-their-impact-on-you/7456/10</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 04 Jul 2011 03:38:52 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7456-10</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/game-names-and-how-their-impact-on-you/7456.rss">Game names and how their impact on you</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Game names and how their impact on you</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Idi]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>thought i was buying ass effect. stupid place to put the sticker</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/game-names-and-how-their-impact-on-you/7456/9">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/game-names-and-how-their-impact-on-you/7456/9</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 04 Jul 2011 03:20:33 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7456-9</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/game-names-and-how-their-impact-on-you/7456.rss">Game names and how their impact on you</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Game names and how their impact on you</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[dky.tehkingd.u]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Fuskox">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/f/ea666f/40.png" class="avatar"> Fuskox:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>He’s saying that people who haven’t played the game don’t know what it means.</p>
<p>“Mass Effect” doesn’t exactly scream “Story-driven sci-fi shooter”</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Personally I would think an effect involving mass does scream “sci-fi”. I dunno, maybe it’s just me. <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/expressionless.png?v=9" title=":expressionless:" class="emoji" alt=":expressionless:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/game-names-and-how-their-impact-on-you/7456/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/game-names-and-how-their-impact-on-you/7456/8</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 04 Jul 2011 02:03:31 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7456-8</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/game-names-and-how-their-impact-on-you/7456.rss">Game names and how their impact on you</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Game names and how their impact on you</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Fuskox]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>He’s saying that people who haven’t played the game don’t know what it means.</p>
<p>“Mass Effect” doesn’t exactly scream “Story-driven sci-fi shooter”</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/game-names-and-how-their-impact-on-you/7456/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/game-names-and-how-their-impact-on-you/7456/7</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 04 Jul 2011 01:56:29 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7456-7</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/game-names-and-how-their-impact-on-you/7456.rss">Game names and how their impact on you</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Game names and how their impact on you</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[dky.tehkingd.u]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="dblkion">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/d/da6949/40.png" class="avatar"> dblkion:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Mass Effect : Pretty unrelated, vague.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Err, you do realize that the Element Zero Mass Effect is the core element of the entire game’s story, right? It powers pretty much every single piece of technology in the game’s universe. And since the game series itself is heavily story-oriented, I fail to see how the name is “Pretty unrelated, vague.”</p>
<p>Anyway, I feel that it doesn’t matter how related the name is to the game as long as it’s memorable and able to make the game or series unique. The name should make the game unique and easy to identify with. Ideally it should be related to the game itself in some way, either in story or game mechanic, but I don’t think it’s totally necessary.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/game-names-and-how-their-impact-on-you/7456/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/game-names-and-how-their-impact-on-you/7456/6</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 04 Jul 2011 01:55:09 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7456-6</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/game-names-and-how-their-impact-on-you/7456.rss">Game names and how their impact on you</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Game names and how their impact on you</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[King_Kaddo]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>the game<br>
<span alt="" class="broken-image" title="This image is broken"><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-unlink svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#unlink"></use></svg></span></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/game-names-and-how-their-impact-on-you/7456/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/game-names-and-how-their-impact-on-you/7456/5</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 04 Jul 2011 00:39:10 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7456-5</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/game-names-and-how-their-impact-on-you/7456.rss">Game names and how their impact on you</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Game names and how their impact on you</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Jethrosoup]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Search optimization: Narbacular Drop</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/game-names-and-how-their-impact-on-you/7456/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/game-names-and-how-their-impact-on-you/7456/4</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 04 Jul 2011 00:31:38 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7456-4</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/game-names-and-how-their-impact-on-you/7456.rss">Game names and how their impact on you</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Game names and how their impact on you</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Ramirezoid]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>“Mass Effect” is unrelated to the game? it’s like why the people in that game can do what they do. They explain it in the opening title card.</p>
<p>I like hip cool misnomers myself. No More Heroes, Quake, etc.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/game-names-and-how-their-impact-on-you/7456/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/game-names-and-how-their-impact-on-you/7456/3</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 04 Jul 2011 00:26:43 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7456-3</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/game-names-and-how-their-impact-on-you/7456.rss">Game names and how their impact on you</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
