<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Fortress Forever 2.42</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/fortress-forever-2-42/7232</link>
    <description>Fortress Forever 2.42 release is imminent......here&#39;s a preview:
[url]https://forums.fortress-forever.com/showthread.php?t=22646[/url]

And, for anyone who doesn&#39;t know what this is:
[url]https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=UAsxa0VqrF0&amp;feature=player_embedded[/url]

I&#39;ll be seeing anyone who dares come in :jizz:</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 05 Jun 2011 06:01:42 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Technology and Gaming</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/fortress-forever-2-42/7232.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Fortress Forever 2.42</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Khaos124]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Heres what i think about tfc compared to tf2:<br>
TF2 was better in the beginning, when there was no hat bs, no class changes, no need to pay for weapons, etc.<br>
TFC became more appealing to me the second the first hat update was applied, just because i knew it wouldnt be long before servers were hosting farming maps and every persons goal was to have hats, and same with achievements for class changes. TFC was so simple, +grenades. There is no dumb gimmicks in tfc, +grenades. +grenades. +grenades.<br>
EDIT: i didnt like TF2 cuz i had no grenades</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/fortress-forever-2-42/7232/53">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/fortress-forever-2-42/7232/53</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jun 2011 06:01:42 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7232-53</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/fortress-forever-2-42/7232.rss">Fortress Forever 2.42</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Fortress Forever 2.42</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[DenDrio]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Honestly, I love both. I used to play FF before I had TF2 and it was quite fun. Now I have TF2 and I stopped playing FF because TF2 had more people playing. I feel like FF takes more skill though, seeing as how you have bunny-hopping and grenades. TF2 is fun, and you can stray from the objectives and still have fun. You can’t do the same in FF though. It’s fun if you stick to the objectives and it gets kind of dull in FF if you just kill each other, it’s more competitive in FF.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/fortress-forever-2-42/7232/52">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/fortress-forever-2-42/7232/52</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jun 2011 04:21:23 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7232-52</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/fortress-forever-2-42/7232.rss">Fortress Forever 2.42</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Fortress Forever 2.42</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[DrasarSalman]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Just rub it all over my face…</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/fortress-forever-2-42/7232/51">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/fortress-forever-2-42/7232/51</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2011 15:13:30 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7232-51</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/fortress-forever-2-42/7232.rss">Fortress Forever 2.42</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Fortress Forever 2.42</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Fuskox]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Double pooooooost!</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/fortress-forever-2-42/7232/50">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/fortress-forever-2-42/7232/50</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2011 19:57:29 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7232-50</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/fortress-forever-2-42/7232.rss">Fortress Forever 2.42</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Fortress Forever 2.42</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[DrasarSalman]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="CaLeB-">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 CaLeB-:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Fortress Forever started off great, but it began to have a downfall after a few patches. They started taking bad advice and unnecessarily tweaked gameplay mechanics, which put balance on a roller coaster.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>So FF is on it’s way to end up like TF2? Does that mean that soon, there will be no good sequel to TFC?</p>
<div class="sepquote">
<span class="smallfont">Edit:</span>
<br>
<br>
<p>Forgot to Ctrl + C, hit the edit button on my already posted post and then press ctrl + V :facepalm:</p>
</div>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/fortress-forever-2-42/7232/49">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/fortress-forever-2-42/7232/49</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2011 19:39:23 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7232-49</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/fortress-forever-2-42/7232.rss">Fortress Forever 2.42</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Fortress Forever 2.42</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[DrasarSalman]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="SURPLUS_NiNjA">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 SURPLUS_NiNjA:</div>
<blockquote>
<p><span alt="" class="broken-image" title="This image is broken"><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-unlink svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#unlink"></use></svg></span></p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>That looks like a badass version of minecraft!</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/fortress-forever-2-42/7232/48">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/fortress-forever-2-42/7232/48</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2011 19:36:56 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7232-48</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/fortress-forever-2-42/7232.rss">Fortress Forever 2.42</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Fortress Forever 2.42</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Peon]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="CaLeB-">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 CaLeB-:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Unfortunately, the sequel slows everything down. I can’t stand to play anything else but a scout on TF2.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I’m not going to ask your permission to use this quote in the future…but thanks. <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=9" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="The Bad Guys">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 The Bad Guys:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Problem was that when both came out (bad idea for the FF team to release the mod in almost the exact same time period as TF2’s release; not a very wise choice indeed)</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>FF was released first, by close to a month, and servers were pretty packed at first…I don’t think it was TF2 that drew these players away…</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="The Bad Guys">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 The Bad Guys:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>as a whole I think TF2 is very much a worthy sequel.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>And as a first for sequels, they subtracted abilities and gameplay elements…if you think that’s better.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="The Bad Guys">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 The Bad Guys:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>They axe some minor stuff like teleporters (which is terrible for the really large maps, when there are enough people to play them)</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>If by this you mean that you’re having a hard time getting around large maps quickly, then you’re doing something wrong…or you’re new to TFC/FF.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="The Bad Guys">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 The Bad Guys:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>but still let shit like infinite spy cloaks, EMP grenades, and other totally annoying shit remain.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I’ve never seen any players in FF, or poasting in the forums, ever complain about these things…they’ve never even been brought up when they talk about anything that’s un-balanced. Even the trolls never bitch about those.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="The Bad Guys">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 The Bad Guys:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>FF feels shoddy and done with no thoughtful mechanics insight other than just give the old TF a face-lift.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Ok, now I know you haven’t played it…you’re going to lose in a list war if you continue this charade.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="The Bad Guys">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 The Bad Guys:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Not to mention the player base is pretty much composed of clannish assholes that while blasting the TF2 player base ironically emit from themselves a bad vibe of community envy. Because they are so clannish and anal-retentive they’ve come to isolate themselves from anyone interested in continuing to play with them and it’s part of the reason why nobody plays on any of their servers.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Says the guy talking a bunch of bullshit about a game he doesn’t play, and doesn’t know shit about…no wonder you feel excluded. It doesn’t seem like they, or I, would have much fun playing FF with you anyways…what’s your point here again?</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="bamboomon">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/b/d9b06d/40.png" class="avatar"> bamboomon:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>My expectations for FF was that it was going to be TFC with better graphics.  But it isnt. It is a completly different game.  With the changes to the classes, weapons and pace, TF2 is closter to TFC than FF ever was.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>This statement just brings me confusion…I think you’re trying to egg me on.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/fortress-forever-2-42/7232/47">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/fortress-forever-2-42/7232/47</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2011 03:29:40 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7232-47</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/fortress-forever-2-42/7232.rss">Fortress Forever 2.42</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Fortress Forever 2.42</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[bamboomon]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>My expectations for FF was that it was going to be TFC with better graphics.  But it isnt. It is a completly different game.  With the changes to the classes, weapons and pace, TF2 is closter to TFC than FF ever was. It is why I dont play it.  I would rather fire up my TFC than FF or TF2.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/fortress-forever-2-42/7232/46">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/fortress-forever-2-42/7232/46</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 31 May 2011 16:12:16 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7232-46</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/fortress-forever-2-42/7232.rss">Fortress Forever 2.42</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Fortress Forever 2.42</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Shinobi]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Medevilae">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/m/aca169/40.png" class="avatar"> Medevilae:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Well, the sad part in this circumstance is most people make that opinion on the sole basis of having an opinion different than that of others.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>^ Golden, going into my sig.</p>
<p>As for TF2, I really love this game. I find it to be one of the more balanced games out there, as is evidenced by the fact that everyone really has their own favorite class; you don’t see an overuse of any one class (except for snipers on 2fort, but that’s why everyone hates that map). There are a massive number of weapons to choose from for each class, each with their own advantages and disadvantages. This is just like any other FPS out there, and is a good thing, unlike what some people were saying above. What the game doesn’t have is really overpowered weapons that you have to use to do well like the noob tube. Any weapon in the game is deadly in the hands of an experienced player especially the vanilla ones. If you watch competitive matches, pros only use vanilla weapons. The maps are balanced for the most part, community variations like Saxton Hale and zombie mode are well done and fun, the characters themselves are well developed, the developers don’t charge for DLC and updates, the microtransaction stuff is optional, and hey if you don’t like hats don’t wear em. As for the art style, well that’s just up to your taste, I personally enjoy it.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/fortress-forever-2-42/7232/45">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/fortress-forever-2-42/7232/45</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 30 May 2011 15:37:27 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7232-45</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/fortress-forever-2-42/7232.rss">Fortress Forever 2.42</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Fortress Forever 2.42</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Surplus]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>For the unknowing it should be noted that the initial TFC was actually a departure from TF’s original stylized look.</p>
<p><span alt="" class="broken-image" title="This image is broken"><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-unlink svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#unlink"></use></svg></span></p>
<p>So its actually much more like TF2 was a return to roots than it was a departure from the norm.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/fortress-forever-2-42/7232/44">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/fortress-forever-2-42/7232/44</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 30 May 2011 05:08:28 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7232-44</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/fortress-forever-2-42/7232.rss">Fortress Forever 2.42</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Fortress Forever 2.42</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[The_Bad_Guys]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I actually liked the idea of Fortress Forever when I first heard about the cartoonish direction the actual TF2 was headed in before it came out. I was all like, “Aw well, at least someone’s making a mod that keeps the original TF’s gameplay and more realistic aesthetic.”</p>
<p>Problem was that when both came out (bad idea for the FF team to release the mod in almost the exact same time period as TF2’s release; not a very wise choice indeed) and I played around with TF2, I was kind of won over not so much by the aesthetic, but by the mechanics, gameplay, and general class edits and re-balancing. While I may always have a gripe with the art style and some minor changes, as a whole I think TF2 is very much a worthy sequel. They made changes with thought and insight and made it a genuinely (except for servers full of tards) fun experience.</p>
<p>FF however, I found to be a poorly-done graphics tweak. Granted, I miss stuff like bunnyhopping, grenades, and faster movement of the older game play, but a lot of it really is better left behind. Bunnyhopping breaks balance, grenade spam ruins gameplay in general, and a lot of the classes they can’t seem to balance correctly or define it’s purpose coherently enough. They axe some minor stuff like teleporters (which is terrible for the really large maps, when there are enough people to play them) but still let shit like infinite spy cloaks, EMP grenades, and other totally annoying shit remain.</p>
<p>FF feels shoddy and done with no thoughtful mechanics insight other than just give the old TF a face-lift. Not to mention the player base is pretty much composed of clannish assholes that while blasting the TF2 player base ironically emit from themselves a bad vibe of community envy. Because they are so clannish and anal-retentive they’ve come to isolate themselves from anyone interested in continuing to play with them and it’s part of the reason why nobody plays on any of their servers.</p>
<p>Part of my rant against FF is not so much any kind of superiority complex or game-bias, but instead of my disappointment in what FF became, all because of the dev’s refusal to evolve and keep the whithered and vestigial remains of FPS stagnation while being as anti-social as you can be while trying to recruit for players.</p>
<p>I was really hoping it would be good. I am disappoint</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/fortress-forever-2-42/7232/43">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/fortress-forever-2-42/7232/43</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 30 May 2011 00:40:07 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7232-43</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/fortress-forever-2-42/7232.rss">Fortress Forever 2.42</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Fortress Forever 2.42</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Chickenprotector]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>^ Yes and no. The dev team that works on it now is what threw it out of whack. They don’t really listen to community suggestions terribly well. I don’t like half the changes they’re doing this patch, but what can you do.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/fortress-forever-2-42/7232/42">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/fortress-forever-2-42/7232/42</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 29 May 2011 19:43:29 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7232-42</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/fortress-forever-2-42/7232.rss">Fortress Forever 2.42</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Fortress Forever 2.42</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[CaLeB]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Fortress Forever started off great, but it began to have a downfall after a few patches. They started taking bad advice and unnecessarily tweaked gameplay mechanics, which put balance on a roller coaster. Then, it got to the point where you can simply hold down a button to bunnyhop. Need I say more?</p>
<p>As for this whole TFC/TF2 debate, I liked both the atmosphere/look and gameplay more in TFC. Classic obviously has a faster pace to it, which makes it more intense. Unfortunately, the sequel slows everything down. I can’t stand to play anything else but a scout on TF2. It also looks cartoony, but the new gamemodes are certainly a plus. I would still have to choose TFC over TF2.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/fortress-forever-2-42/7232/41">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/fortress-forever-2-42/7232/41</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 29 May 2011 19:36:56 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7232-41</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/fortress-forever-2-42/7232.rss">Fortress Forever 2.42</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Fortress Forever 2.42</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[DrasarSalman]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I don’t know, we’ll see…</p>
<p>Also: I have been a little disappointed because CS:S was almost the same as the mod, but TF2 wasn’t even close to TFC! Valve even stopped the making of the nail gun. That is why I am happy for mods like this and Black Mesa.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/fortress-forever-2-42/7232/40">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/fortress-forever-2-42/7232/40</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 29 May 2011 14:08:01 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7232-40</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/fortress-forever-2-42/7232.rss">Fortress Forever 2.42</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Fortress Forever 2.42</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[bamboomon]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I wonder if this is what the BM dev team is going to face a few years after they release BM.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/fortress-forever-2-42/7232/39">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/fortress-forever-2-42/7232/39</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 29 May 2011 13:41:20 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7232-39</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/fortress-forever-2-42/7232.rss">Fortress Forever 2.42</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Fortress Forever 2.42</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Chickenprotector]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="DrasarSalman">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/d/839c29/40.png" class="avatar"> DrasarSalman:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Fortress Forever is like TFC:S after what I’ve seen…</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Yes and no… there are quite a few changes over TFC, one of them is much faster gameplay, it takes about twice the time to get across the map in TFC than as it does in FF.</p>
<p>With 2.42 being released you can expect it to practically become its own fortress game as it will implement quite a few changes.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Peon">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/p/43a26b/40.png" class="avatar"> Peon:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>ROFLMAO!!! Whoooo man…the comedy here lately has been golden.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I think he meant TF2 before it became the overrated butt fuck it is now. (no offense meant)</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Idi">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/i/bcef8e/40.png" class="avatar"> Idi:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Pro-Tip: Eat a big ass turd motherfucker.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Pro-Tip: If you’re going to rage, do it with proper grammar, you drunken man-child.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/fortress-forever-2-42/7232/38">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/fortress-forever-2-42/7232/38</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 29 May 2011 02:57:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7232-38</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/fortress-forever-2-42/7232.rss">Fortress Forever 2.42</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Fortress Forever 2.42</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Surplus]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Ramirezoid">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/r/ba9def/40.png" class="avatar"> Ramirezoid:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>You’re an idiot, I happen to have the ability to create a unique opinion instead of stealing one from some fucking weenie with a higher postcount than me</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Saying something just because it is against the fold isn’t any better than hoping on the bandwagon. If you honestly are serious in all your game related posts than well that’s sad.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/fortress-forever-2-42/7232/37">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/fortress-forever-2-42/7232/37</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 29 May 2011 00:51:23 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7232-37</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/fortress-forever-2-42/7232.rss">Fortress Forever 2.42</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Fortress Forever 2.42</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Bloodshot]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Honestly, I never really enjoyed TF2 or TFC. The only one I ever found myself interested in was QWTF</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/fortress-forever-2-42/7232/36">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/fortress-forever-2-42/7232/36</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 29 May 2011 00:07:56 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7232-36</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/fortress-forever-2-42/7232.rss">Fortress Forever 2.42</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Fortress Forever 2.42</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Idi]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Protip: eat a bigass turd motherfucker</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/fortress-forever-2-42/7232/35">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/fortress-forever-2-42/7232/35</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 May 2011 23:58:45 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7232-35</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/fortress-forever-2-42/7232.rss">Fortress Forever 2.42</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Fortress Forever 2.42</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[DrasarSalman]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="T-1000">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/t/c2a13f/40.png" class="avatar"> T-1000:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Too bad Team Fortress 2 was never released.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Maybe the TFC team got “hired” by Valve? I doesn’t make much sense considering how TF2 ended up as. Now it is just an experiment, a test of what the “community” has to offer.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/fortress-forever-2-42/7232/34">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/fortress-forever-2-42/7232/34</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 May 2011 23:35:10 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7232-34</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/fortress-forever-2-42/7232.rss">Fortress Forever 2.42</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Fortress Forever 2.42</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Peon]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="T-1000">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/t/c2a13f/40.png" class="avatar"> T-1000:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Too bad Team Fortress 2 was never released.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>ROFLMAO!!! Whoooo man…the comedy here lately has been golden.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/fortress-forever-2-42/7232/33">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/fortress-forever-2-42/7232/33</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 May 2011 23:26:37 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7232-33</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/fortress-forever-2-42/7232.rss">Fortress Forever 2.42</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Fortress Forever 2.42</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[DrasarSalman]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Fortress Forever is like TFC:S after what I’ve seen…</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/fortress-forever-2-42/7232/32">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/fortress-forever-2-42/7232/32</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 May 2011 23:24:41 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7232-32</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/fortress-forever-2-42/7232.rss">Fortress Forever 2.42</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Fortress Forever 2.42</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Chickenprotector]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Pro-tip: You have horrible comprehension skills too, and the typing skills of a drunken baby. <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/expressionless.png?v=9" title=":expressionless:" class="emoji" alt=":expressionless:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/fortress-forever-2-42/7232/31">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/fortress-forever-2-42/7232/31</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 May 2011 22:23:22 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7232-31</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/fortress-forever-2-42/7232.rss">Fortress Forever 2.42</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Fortress Forever 2.42</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Idi]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>hey protip guy. protip: u a bitch w. poor cmprehension</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/fortress-forever-2-42/7232/30">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/fortress-forever-2-42/7232/30</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 May 2011 20:13:59 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7232-30</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/fortress-forever-2-42/7232.rss">Fortress Forever 2.42</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Fortress Forever 2.42</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Deimos]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I loved TF2 during its beta and it’s initial release, but yes these days it’s a fucking joke.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/fortress-forever-2-42/7232/29">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/fortress-forever-2-42/7232/29</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 May 2011 16:18:38 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-7232-29</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/fortress-forever-2-42/7232.rss">Fortress Forever 2.42</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
