<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Gonarch Bug with Satchel Bombs</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/gonarch-bug-with-satchel-bombs/63204</link>
    <description>In Gonarch&#39;s Lair, I came up with the clever idea to spread out a series of satchel bombs in hopes of chain- detonating them later after Gonarch made his appearance.  

Pleased with my idea, I planted one satchel without detonating it.  I planted another.  I planted a third.  I attempted to plant a fourth but the game froze completely.  I had to do a hard kill of the game (Ctrl-Alt-Delete) and restart the game.  I repeated the strategy and got another hard freeze.  This happened 3 times in different places of Gonarch&#39;s Lair.  I have never had any problems up until this point

I have given up on this strategy but I wanted to report the bug.  The game is otherwise  terrific.

I have a PC gaming machine, MSI Ace motherboard, 2080 Super game card, 32 gigs ram, AMD Ryzen 3900x.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 22 Apr 2020 11:41:59 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>In-game Issues</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/gonarch-bug-with-satchel-bombs/63204.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Gonarch Bug with Satchel Bombs</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Catsmack]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>In Gonarch’s Lair, I came up with the clever idea to spread out a series of satchel bombs in hopes of chain- detonating them later after Gonarch made his appearance.</p>
<p>Pleased with my idea, I planted one satchel without detonating it.  I planted another.  I planted a third.  I attempted to plant a fourth but the game froze completely.  I had to do a hard kill of the game (Ctrl-Alt-Delete) and restart the game.  I repeated the strategy and got another hard freeze.  This happened 3 times in different places of Gonarch’s Lair.  I have never had any problems up until this point</p>
<p>I have given up on this strategy but I wanted to report the bug.  The game is otherwise  terrific.</p>
<p>I have a PC gaming machine, MSI Ace motherboard, 2080 Super game card, 32 gigs ram, AMD Ryzen 3900x.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/gonarch-bug-with-satchel-bombs/63204/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/gonarch-bug-with-satchel-bombs/63204/1</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 22 Apr 2020 11:41:59 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-63204-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/gonarch-bug-with-satchel-bombs/63204.rss">Gonarch Bug with Satchel Bombs</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
