<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Good songs for closing a movie</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/good-songs-for-closing-a-movie/12442</link>
    <description>I&#39;m making a short film. It ends with a bus driving a through a desert road and disappearing in the horizon. The song shouldn&#39;t be slow nor sad, but rather cheerful. So, give me some songs that could fit with this scene.

I thought this one would be good, so it can be an example of what I&#39;m looking for:
Supertramp - Goodbye Stranger
[url]https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=YstSV2ydMk8[/url]</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2013 17:06:55 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Off Topic</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/good-songs-for-closing-a-movie/12442.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Good songs for closing a movie</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Mango_Assassin]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Nice one rot, nice.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/good-songs-for-closing-a-movie/12442/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/good-songs-for-closing-a-movie/12442/8</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2013 17:06:55 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12442-8</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/good-songs-for-closing-a-movie/12442.rss">Good songs for closing a movie</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Good songs for closing a movie</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[_rot_fodder]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=3mSaQ0jtaWo" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=3mSaQ0jtaWo</a></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/good-songs-for-closing-a-movie/12442/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/good-songs-for-closing-a-movie/12442/7</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2013 04:28:40 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12442-7</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/good-songs-for-closing-a-movie/12442.rss">Good songs for closing a movie</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Good songs for closing a movie</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Joe_Freeman]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="CPU">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/user_avatar/leakfree.org/cpu/40/4349_2.png" class="avatar"> CPU:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>What he said plus<br>
Is it a bus full of people, kids, parents and kids or just one guy/girl?<br>
Did someone overcome something and succeed?<br>
Is it a comedy?<br>
etc etc etc<br>
Need more of a story line ending to make sure the music fits.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>It is a comedy drama, so here is the plot:</p>
<p>Alan is a man who lives in the outskirts of a tiny city in north-west Argentina. He’s very poor, and survives on welfare. His shack is located in an usurpated land, and he lives with his obese girlfriend Jessica. They enjoy spending their days eating and watching TV, particularly one freak TV show called “Hechos y Protagonistas” One day he arrives to his house and finds out that his girlfriend passed away, suffocated by food. Eventhough his family and friends support him, he finds this very humilliating, so he starts heavy drinking. He drinks too much and ends in jail, where he meets an alcoholic Falklands war veteran, called Roberto. When they’re out of jail, he takes Alan with him, and they start living in an abandoned warehouse with other alcoholics. When comes back to his house, he realises it has been demolished, as it was occupying a public site. Homeless, he meets a man called Dario who he had previously seen in the abandoned warehouse. Dario offers Alan a house and food, but he must work for him in return, to which Alan agrees. Dario is a drug dealer, and Alan makes his way into the drug business in order to make a living. After several months of working together, Dario’s gang affiliates with a motel owner called Santillan, whose motel is also a brothel. Alan usually visits the brothel, and befriends one of the girls working there, called Jessica, just as his deceased girlfriend. But one day, Alan sees an advertisement in TV, with the picture of Jessica(the prostitute), telling that she’s disappeared and there is a reward for finding him. When Alan questions Jessica about this, she burst into tears and tells him that she was abducted several years ago and is forced to work as a prostitue. Infuriated, Alan comfronts Dario and Santillan, telling them he won’t work with people that is capable of commiting such atrocities. He is beaten by Dario’s henchmen and thrown in the middle of nowhere. He is found by Roberto, the Falkland’s veteran he met before. He tells him his story, which makes Roberto really sick. They decide to go to the brothel and free Jessica and the other girls that have been kidnapped. For this Roberto goes back to his house, which he hasn’t been in for months and takes a gun he had hidden there. His wife sees them and calls the police, but they take Roberto’s car and drive to the brothel, where they start a gunfight against Dario and Santillan. Santillan and Roberto die in the shootout, and Dario is severely injured. Alan is unharmed. However, he realises the police has followed them, and they are waiting outside. Dario, who is in his agony, tells Alan that the police are actually aware of the kidnapped girls, but they have been bribed, so they will just enter and kill Alan, and make as if nothing had happened. Alan takes all the money from the cash register and escapes through the woods before the police storms the brothel.</p>
<p>Two months after these events, Dario is shown living in a tiny house in the mountains. He writes his story about what happened to him during the last months, and sends it to major newspaper and television networks around the country. But he receives no answer, until one day a letter arrives to his home. It’s from the freak show that he used to watch with his girlfriend, “Hechos y Protagonistas”; telling him that they would like to interview him. He buys a bus ticket to Buenos Aires, and the movie ends with him looking the landscape from the window of the bus, that is almost empty with the exception of one old lady that is sitting aside to him. Then the image of the bus fading in the horizon, and the desert. At this moment the music starts playing and the film ends.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/good-songs-for-closing-a-movie/12442/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/good-songs-for-closing-a-movie/12442/6</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2013 02:27:41 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12442-6</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/good-songs-for-closing-a-movie/12442.rss">Good songs for closing a movie</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Good songs for closing a movie</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Dragunov2]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=huOQWNApKmA" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=huOQWNApKmA</a></p>
<p><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=vTEtjNoA-_U" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=vTEtjNoA-_U</a></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/good-songs-for-closing-a-movie/12442/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/good-songs-for-closing-a-movie/12442/5</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2013 01:51:28 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12442-5</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/good-songs-for-closing-a-movie/12442.rss">Good songs for closing a movie</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Good songs for closing a movie</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[CPU]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="danielsangeo">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/user_avatar/leakfree.org/danielsangeo/40/4347_2.png" class="avatar"> danielsangeo:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>…<br>
what other kind of feeling are you looking for?<br>
How does the movie end?<br>
A reunion?<br>
A person going to start a new era in their life?<br>
Finally taking that road trip they wanted to take all their life?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>What he said plus<br>
Is it a bus full of people, kids, parents and kids or just one guy/girl?<br>
Did someone overcome something and succeed?<br>
Is it a comedy?<br>
etc etc etc<br>
Need more of a story line ending to make sure the music fits.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/good-songs-for-closing-a-movie/12442/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/good-songs-for-closing-a-movie/12442/4</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2013 01:36:35 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12442-4</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/good-songs-for-closing-a-movie/12442.rss">Good songs for closing a movie</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Good songs for closing a movie</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[danielsangeo]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Beyond “cheerful” and “bus driving through a desert road and disappearing in the horizon”, what other kind of feeling are you looking for?  How does the movie end?  A reunion? A person going to start a new era in their life?  Finally taking that road trip they wanted to take all their life?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/good-songs-for-closing-a-movie/12442/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/good-songs-for-closing-a-movie/12442/3</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2013 01:18:19 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12442-3</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/good-songs-for-closing-a-movie/12442.rss">Good songs for closing a movie</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Good songs for closing a movie</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Idi]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>use that one shitty smash mouth song that was in every single film that came out for a while liek ten or so years ago</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/good-songs-for-closing-a-movie/12442/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/good-songs-for-closing-a-movie/12442/2</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2013 21:26:42 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12442-2</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/good-songs-for-closing-a-movie/12442.rss">Good songs for closing a movie</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Good songs for closing a movie</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Joe_Freeman]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I’m making a short film. It ends with a bus driving a through a desert road and disappearing in the horizon. The song shouldn’t be slow nor sad, but rather cheerful. So, give me some songs that could fit with this scene.</p>
<p>I thought this one would be good, so it can be an example of what I’m looking for:<br>
Supertramp - Goodbye Stranger<br>
<a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=YstSV2ydMk8" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=YstSV2ydMk8</a></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/good-songs-for-closing-a-movie/12442/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/good-songs-for-closing-a-movie/12442/1</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2013 21:20:12 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12442-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/good-songs-for-closing-a-movie/12442.rss">Good songs for closing a movie</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
