<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Half-Life Story vs. Mass Effect</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/half-life-story-vs-mass-effect/8655</link>
    <description>[align=center][COLOR=&#39;DarkOrange&#39;][FONT=&#39;Arial Black&#39;]Half-Life VS. Mass Effect[/FONT][/SIZE][/align]
[quote]
&quot;Over time, gameplay may fade but the stories and characters within these games lives on forever. Now, 32 of the most popular video game stories are trading blows in our Videogame Deathmatch for The Greatest Story Ever Told. Vote now and vote often to make sure your voice is heard so that your favorite game story can be crowned #1.&quot;
[/quote]
_________________________________________________

[COLOR=&#39;Silver&#39;]Commander Shepard, the first human Spectre, has been sent to Eden Prime to recover a Prothean beacon. Shepard is attacked by Saren, a rogue Specter, looking to unleash the power of Reapers, the same species that wiped out the Protheans 50,000 years prior.
_______________________

[COLOR=&#39;DarkOrange&#39;]Gordon Freeman awakes from stasis to learn Earth has been invaded by the Combine. Humanity&#39;s fate is in your hands, well humanity&#39;s fate is in your left hand, your right hand is holding a crowbar.
_______________________


Pretty shit description of Half-Life if you ask me, but this is definitely a debatable match up.

[b][url=&#39;https://www.g4tv.com/vgdm/best-video-game-story-2012/battleresult/214/MassEffect%20vs%20HalfLife2/BB3A2D08EF45435eB4F9796BCADB6DEC/&#39;]VOTE HERE![/url][/SIZE][/b]

Also up is [url=&#39;https://www.g4tv.com/vgdm/best-video-game-story-2012/battleresult/217/Portal2%20vs%20FinalFantasy7/A57207872D554740BD64E14799A70F4F/&#39;]Portal 2 vs. FF7.[/url]

Keep in mind this is ME1 vs. HL2</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 15 Apr 2012 14:24:02 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Technology and Gaming</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/half-life-story-vs-mass-effect/8655.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Half-Life Story vs. Mass Effect</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[k3nny1550]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I think the chief strength of Half Life is it’s mise en scene. The many things it implies throughout the game can translate to virtually any definition the player applies to it. I highly doubt Dragon’s theory was actually postulated by the writers, but who cares? I think it’s an interesting theory.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/half-life-story-vs-mass-effect/8655/39">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/half-life-story-vs-mass-effect/8655/39</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 15 Apr 2012 14:24:02 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8655-39</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/half-life-story-vs-mass-effect/8655.rss">Half-Life Story vs. Mass Effect</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Half-Life Story vs. Mass Effect</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Mont_Blanc]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Fun Fact : While Marc Laidlaw is the lead writer of HL2 story, Mike Laidlaw is one of the writers of Mass Effect.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/half-life-story-vs-mass-effect/8655/38">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/half-life-story-vs-mass-effect/8655/38</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 15 Apr 2012 01:27:04 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8655-38</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/half-life-story-vs-mass-effect/8655.rss">Half-Life Story vs. Mass Effect</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Half-Life Story vs. Mass Effect</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[dblkion]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><a class="mention" href="/u/orderofdagon">@OrderOfDagon</a></p>
<p>I respect your vision of the game, actually I find it pretty pleasing to know people put that much efforts trying to understand deeply what they play.</p>
<p>I’ve read your big post, and I have a little advice for you. Never ever say when you want to show your point : “The modern and overly-uneducated mind” after that point, no matter how good what you wrote was people won’t take you seriously.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/half-life-story-vs-mass-effect/8655/37">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/half-life-story-vs-mass-effect/8655/37</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 15 Apr 2012 01:14:15 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8655-37</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/half-life-story-vs-mass-effect/8655.rss">Half-Life Story vs. Mass Effect</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Half-Life Story vs. Mass Effect</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[OrderOfDagon]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Marc Laidlaw had more to do with the Story of Half Life 2 than either of them, I think.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/half-life-story-vs-mass-effect/8655/36">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/half-life-story-vs-mass-effect/8655/36</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 14 Apr 2012 16:49:30 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8655-36</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/half-life-story-vs-mass-effect/8655.rss">Half-Life Story vs. Mass Effect</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Half-Life Story vs. Mass Effect</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Surplus]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Do keep in mind I am not just assuming that the writers didn’t think about this.  But based on an interview with the writers on portal 2 where they were asked a lot of questions that looked at the story like that and they only ever responded “we didn’t mean to do that” I came to the conclusion that they aren’t that deep.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/half-life-story-vs-mass-effect/8655/35">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/half-life-story-vs-mass-effect/8655/35</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 14 Apr 2012 16:30:53 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8655-35</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/half-life-story-vs-mass-effect/8655.rss">Half-Life Story vs. Mass Effect</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Half-Life Story vs. Mass Effect</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[OrderOfDagon]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I used to think the writers didn’t mean anything by their plot either, but then I started listening in depth to the Breen casts and sorta felt that there was more to the game. I could still be over-analyzing it, but I’m so used to playing the game with this in mind. Moreover, I find that having the protagonist’s name be the “Free-man” blatantly ironic in light of the way I perceive the game.</p>
<p>I don’t know, I can see why people go for Mass Effect, regardless of their idea of what a story is, but I can’t help but remember the feeling I got when I stood staring at the Citadel at the beginning of “Our Benefactors.”</p>
<p>The story was just so pessimistic and unsmiling that I nearly felt grave fear for my own view of subjective-reality. Whether the game’s story is how I said it was, that is the game I played. And I’m sorry, but in my opinion, a fantasy Star-Trek style adventure game with sex and unnecessary social-choices doesn’t really scrape the surface of a Nuremberg Rally ambiance with <span class="bbcode-b">real</span> philosophical and scientific allegations against the entire human species.</p>
<p>But whatever, I’m done.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/half-life-story-vs-mass-effect/8655/34">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/half-life-story-vs-mass-effect/8655/34</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 14 Apr 2012 15:47:57 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8655-34</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/half-life-story-vs-mass-effect/8655.rss">Half-Life Story vs. Mass Effect</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Half-Life Story vs. Mass Effect</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Surplus]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="JeffMOD">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/user_avatar/leakfree.org/jeffmod/40/4333_2.png" class="avatar"> JeffMOD:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>So he’s taking the ‘English class’ approach?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Yes, exactly.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/half-life-story-vs-mass-effect/8655/33">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/half-life-story-vs-mass-effect/8655/33</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 14 Apr 2012 15:00:53 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8655-33</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/half-life-story-vs-mass-effect/8655.rss">Half-Life Story vs. Mass Effect</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Half-Life Story vs. Mass Effect</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[dblkion]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="SURPLUS_NiNjA">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 SURPLUS_NiNjA:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>To be honest I think with half-life you’re reading too much into stuff and I doubt the writers thought of that stuff.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>True, half life story was always free for fans to speculate on it, on the other hand, Mass effect’s story was set in stone, allowing fans to bash it every little mistake the writters did.</p>
<p>Anyway, mass effect is way more deserving to win.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/half-life-story-vs-mass-effect/8655/32">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/half-life-story-vs-mass-effect/8655/32</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 14 Apr 2012 12:30:19 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8655-32</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/half-life-story-vs-mass-effect/8655.rss">Half-Life Story vs. Mass Effect</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Half-Life Story vs. Mass Effect</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[JeffMOD]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>So he’s taking the ‘English class’ approach?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/half-life-story-vs-mass-effect/8655/31">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/half-life-story-vs-mass-effect/8655/31</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 14 Apr 2012 11:50:15 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8655-31</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/half-life-story-vs-mass-effect/8655.rss">Half-Life Story vs. Mass Effect</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Half-Life Story vs. Mass Effect</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Surplus]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="OrderOfDagon">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/user_avatar/leakfree.org/orderofdagon/40/4963_2.png" class="avatar"> OrderOfDagon:</div>
<blockquote>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Half Life</span> has a much more mature story based around real philosophy, ranging from Friedrich Nietzsche to Ayn Rand. The story that Half Life and its sequels pursue is a drastic interpretation of a philosophical stand-point -coined by Nietzsche- known as the, “Will to Power.”</p>
<p>You’ll often hear Dr. Breen reference Neurological Imperatives and broad-spectrum prospects, like <span class="bbcode-i">purpose</span>. Gordon Freeman, as a character, represents the slave-mentality of the average life-form. He is given tremendous power and seeks nothing but survival and the continuity of his species. His constant sabotage of fixed-Combine bases and the entire alliance of Xen is a clear reference to <span class="bbcode-i">territoriality</span>, which would make Gordon represent the more modern sense of morality and ways of thinking (or the Slave Mentality, as dictated by Nietzsche), where the Combine and their goals represent inevitability and conflicting purpose in both appearance and nature. It can also be symbolically interpreted as cultural tradition dissolving scientific and philosophical pragmatism. The territoriality is also used to contrast the advancement of the Combine and how our (humans) understanding and frequencies are primitive.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Mass Effect</span>, in my opinion, is a contrived and cluttered cleche driven merely by character development in the same stylistic fashion that most pieces of modern pop-culture try to pawn off as a story. With “Advanced Story” labeled as Mass Effect’s signature quality, I’m willing to bet it will win.</p>
<p>The modern and overly-uneducated mind too often mistakes drama as a more important aspect than concept and other key-elements in story writing. I’m certain that the cleche drama that Bioware pawns off as “Mature Story-telling” will fool most people. The problem with drama, is that it ends when the presentation is over. Concept and originality can change a person for the right reasons, where drama affects our emotions – something we have no control over and requires no real thinking on our part.</p>
<p>Most importantly, Half Life’s story isn’t as contrived and <span class="bbcode-i">in-your-face</span> as Mass Effect’s; Half Life’s story is told realistically and behind-the-scenes. Half Life’s story can be completely ignored and the game itself can be subjectively pursued as a strict action game, fore the game almost never halts the constant action. This is why Half Life is a true marvel in the eyes of someone who doesn’t struggle with mature and philosophical, if not scientific, concepts. The game itself disguises you as the common protagonist-hero attempting to liberate your brethren. The story -though incognito- is anything but. Anyone familiar with the basic quandaries of philosophy is instantly slapped with an impasse of personal belief. The line that divides common-place moral certainties and advanced-philosophical views is immediately drawn at the start of Half Life 2. Most players don’t even consider that you can personally choose to side with the Combine, or with the pragmatism that it presents. Half Life’s story isn’t over when the game if finished, nor did it begin back when Valve dished it out. The story of Half Life has been plaguing and frustrating the intellectual mind since Aristotle. It isn’t just a game, it’s a visual representation of a conflicting argument that puts you in the seat of the average man.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-i">"Look, Gordon! Look at what you are throwing away! "<br>
“Would we model ourselves on the Trilobite?!”<br>
“The Combine have thrown a switch and exorcised our demons in a single stroke. They have given us the strength we never could have summoned to overcome this compulsion; they have given us purpose. They have turned our eyes toward the stars.”<br>
</span></p>
<p>Anyone who has ever played the popular Half Life 2 mod, “The Stanely Parable” knows of these conflicting sides. Lets just say that anyone who turned the mod off before it was finished should never oppose the Combine – or Friedrich Nietzsche.</p>
<p>Half Life is fucking <span class="bbcode-b">clearly</span> superior than Mass Effect in story.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>To be honest I think with half-life you’re reading too much into stuff and I doubt the writers thought of that stuff.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/half-life-story-vs-mass-effect/8655/30">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/half-life-story-vs-mass-effect/8655/30</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 14 Apr 2012 01:59:50 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8655-30</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/half-life-story-vs-mass-effect/8655.rss">Half-Life Story vs. Mass Effect</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Half-Life Story vs. Mass Effect</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[OldDirtyBastard]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Evod">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/e/aeb1de/40.png" class="avatar"> Evod:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>If you don’t like discussion you don’t have to read it, no one is forcing you.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>didn’t even read lol</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/half-life-story-vs-mass-effect/8655/29">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/half-life-story-vs-mass-effect/8655/29</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 14 Apr 2012 01:22:41 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8655-29</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/half-life-story-vs-mass-effect/8655.rss">Half-Life Story vs. Mass Effect</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Half-Life Story vs. Mass Effect</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Evod]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="OldDirtyBastard">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/o/dec6dc/40.png" class="avatar"> OldDirtyBastard:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>this is balkc meas forums, not turnitin</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>If you don’t like discussion you don’t have to read it, no one is forcing you.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/half-life-story-vs-mass-effect/8655/28">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/half-life-story-vs-mass-effect/8655/28</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 14 Apr 2012 00:58:19 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8655-28</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/half-life-story-vs-mass-effect/8655.rss">Half-Life Story vs. Mass Effect</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Half-Life Story vs. Mass Effect</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[OldDirtyBastard]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="OrderOfDagon">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/user_avatar/leakfree.org/orderofdagon/40/4963_2.png" class="avatar"> OrderOfDagon:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>wtf is this comment</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>this is balkc meas forums, not turnitin</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/half-life-story-vs-mass-effect/8655/27">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/half-life-story-vs-mass-effect/8655/27</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 14 Apr 2012 00:12:15 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8655-27</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/half-life-story-vs-mass-effect/8655.rss">Half-Life Story vs. Mass Effect</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Half-Life Story vs. Mass Effect</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[OrderOfDagon]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="OldDirtyBastard">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/o/dec6dc/40.png" class="avatar"> OldDirtyBastard:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>wtf is this essay</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>wtf is this comment</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Evod">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/e/aeb1de/40.png" class="avatar"> Evod:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Going back to your analogy of the ants, you say that the ants serve no purpose until we humans give it to them. Yet you say we are purposeless compared to the combine. Can something that is purposeless (humans) give purpose to something that is also purposeless(ants)? I might argue that the combine are purposeless themselves. Does the seemingly desire for control the combine have make them guilty of the same instinct that holds us back? Are not the combine motivated by their own instinct? You make seem that nature/instinct is the chain that holds us down and that to evolve is to liberate us from those chains. However, I wonder if this “liberation” merely exchanges these chains for another</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>You know, it was a bad example. Nietzsche describes the characteristic of life itself as slavery; he believes that controlling our Neurological Imperatives is the next step in Evolution. Not necessarily freeing us, but giving us more freedom than we had. Basically, just because we are slaves -according to Friedrich- doesn’t mean we have to adopt the mentality of one.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/half-life-story-vs-mass-effect/8655/26">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/half-life-story-vs-mass-effect/8655/26</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 13 Apr 2012 23:17:16 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8655-26</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/half-life-story-vs-mass-effect/8655.rss">Half-Life Story vs. Mass Effect</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Half-Life Story vs. Mass Effect</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[OldDirtyBastard]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="OrderOfDagon">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/user_avatar/leakfree.org/orderofdagon/40/4963_2.png" class="avatar"> OrderOfDagon:</div>
<blockquote>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Half Life</span> has a much more mature story based around real philosophy, ranging from Friedrich Nietzsche to Ayn Rand. The story that Half Life and its sequels pursue is a drastic interpretation of a philosophical stand-point -coined by Nietzsche- known as the, “Will to Power.”</p>
<p>You’ll often hear Dr. Breen reference Neurological Imperatives and broad-spectrum prospects, like <span class="bbcode-i">purpose</span>. Gordon Freeman, as a character, represents the slave-mentality of the average life-form. He is given tremendous power and seeks nothing but survival and the continuity of his species. His constant sabotage of fixed-Combine bases and the entire alliance of Xen is a clear reference to <span class="bbcode-i">territoriality</span>, which would make Gordon represent the more modern sense of morality and ways of thinking (or the Slave Mentality, as dictated by Nietzsche), where the Combine and their goals represent inevitability and conflicting purpose in both appearance and nature. It can also be symbolically interpreted as cultural tradition dissolving scientific and philosophical pragmatism. The territoriality is also used to contrast the advancement of the Combine and how our (humans) understanding and frequencies are primitive.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Mass Effect</span>, in my opinion, is a contrived and cluttered cleche driven merely by character development in the same stylistic fashion that most pieces of modern pop-culture try to pawn off as a story. With “Advanced Story” labeled as Mass Effect’s signature quality, I’m willing to bet it will win.</p>
<p>The modern and overly-uneducated mind too often mistakes drama as a more important aspect than concept and other key-elements in story writing. I’m certain that the cleche drama that Bioware pawns off as “Mature Story-telling” will fool most people. The problem with drama, is that it ends when the presentation is over. Concept and originality can change a person for the right reasons, where drama affects our emotions – something we have no control over and requires no real thinking on our part.</p>
<p>Most importantly, Half Life’s story isn’t as contrived and <span class="bbcode-i">in-your-face</span> as Mass Effect’s; Half Life’s story is told realistically and behind-the-scenes. Half Life’s story can be completely ignored and the game itself can be subjectively pursued as a strict action game, fore the game almost never halts the constant action. This is why Half Life is a true marvel in the eyes of someone who doesn’t struggle with mature and philosophical, if not scientific, concepts. The game itself disguises you as the common protagonist-hero attempting to liberate your brethren. The story -though incognito- is anything but. Anyone familiar with the basic quandaries of philosophy is instantly slapped with an impasse of personal belief. The line that divides common-place moral certainties and advanced-philosophical views is immediately drawn at the start of Half Life 2. Most players don’t even consider that you can personally choose to side with the Combine, or with the pragmatism that it presents. Half Life’s story isn’t over when the game if finished, nor did it begin back when Valve dished it out. The story of Half Life has been plaguing and frustrating the intellectual mind since Aristotle. It isn’t just a game, it’s a visual representation of a conflicting argument that puts you in the seat of the average man.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-i">"Look, Gordon! Look at what you are throwing away! "<br>
“Would we model ourselves on the Trilobite?!”<br>
“The Combine have thrown a switch and exorcised our demons in a single stroke. They have given us the strength we never could have summoned to overcome this compulsion; they have given us purpose. They have turned our eyes toward the stars.”<br>
</span></p>
<p>Anyone who has ever played the popular Half Life 2 mod, “The Stanely Parable” knows of these conflicting sides. Lets just say that anyone who turned the mod off before it was finished should never oppose the Combine – or Friedrich Nietzsche.</p>
<p>Half Life is fucking <span class="bbcode-b">clearly</span> superior than Mass Effect in story.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>wtf is this essay</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/half-life-story-vs-mass-effect/8655/25">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/half-life-story-vs-mass-effect/8655/25</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 13 Apr 2012 11:30:56 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8655-25</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/half-life-story-vs-mass-effect/8655.rss">Half-Life Story vs. Mass Effect</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Half-Life Story vs. Mass Effect</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Evod]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>‘Double post’</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/half-life-story-vs-mass-effect/8655/24">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/half-life-story-vs-mass-effect/8655/24</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 13 Apr 2012 03:21:14 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8655-24</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/half-life-story-vs-mass-effect/8655.rss">Half-Life Story vs. Mass Effect</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Half-Life Story vs. Mass Effect</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Evod]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="OrderOfDagon">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/user_avatar/leakfree.org/orderofdagon/40/4963_2.png" class="avatar"> OrderOfDagon:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Pragmatism doesn’t mean quality for human life. Try and understand, humans go around hunting animals and endangering species to extinction simply because we are at the top of the food chain. Imagine pragmatism from something eons ahead of us in the food chain; i.e. The Combine. Humans are, essentially, purposeless sacks of water that go around appeasing their neurological requisites without thinking beyond their nature. The Combine gave them freedom from some of these impulses and -if you paid attention to Breen’s Announcements about immortality- were planning on giving freedom from physiological imperatives aswell. Even though the standard of living for humans wasn’t so great, it was necessary.</p>
<p>It’s like humans and ants. Lets say that we’re some modern-military tribe, and that ants were infecting our crops for whatever reason. Those crops fed our soldiers and kept us alive – what’s a solution? The tribe would probably try and contain the ants in a small but easily accessible space, like ant farms. Sure, the ants are more enclosed and uncomfortable, but who cares, right? So now lets say that we decide to set those ants on our enemies’ crops, making them weaker. Is the ant not incredibly more significant in purpose? They now have real gods (humans) where they initially had none; they have real comprehendable purpose; they are part of something bigger. Would you rather continue the monotonous life of an ant, or would you become apart of something great?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Going back to your analogy of the ants, you say that the ants serve no purpose until we humans give it to them. Yet you say we are purposeless compared to the combine. Can something that is purposeless (humans) give purpose to something that is also purposeless(ants)? I might argue that the combine are purposeless themselves. Does the seemingly desire for control the combine have make them guilty of the same instinct that holds us back? Are not the combine motivated by their own instinct? You make seem that nature/instinct is the chain that holds us down and that to evolve is to liberate us from those chains. However, I wonder if this “liberation” merely exchanges these chains for another</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/half-life-story-vs-mass-effect/8655/23">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/half-life-story-vs-mass-effect/8655/23</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 13 Apr 2012 03:14:07 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8655-23</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/half-life-story-vs-mass-effect/8655.rss">Half-Life Story vs. Mass Effect</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Half-Life Story vs. Mass Effect</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[OrderOfDagon]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I disagree objectively, but I respect your opinion – you have a very common opinion, so don’t feel like you’re deserving of any kind of “Scatthing rebuttals.”</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/half-life-story-vs-mass-effect/8655/22">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/half-life-story-vs-mass-effect/8655/22</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 13 Apr 2012 02:26:48 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8655-22</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/half-life-story-vs-mass-effect/8655.rss">Half-Life Story vs. Mass Effect</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Half-Life Story vs. Mass Effect</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[JeffMOD]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I’d just like to add my two cents to the current conversation.<br>
*Humans are mortal for a reason. Living forever would just get boring after a few hundred years.</p>
<p>*Breen’s broadcasted programming, while well worded, is propaganda for the Combine. Kind of like how Hitler was a very charismatic speaker. Doesn’t mean he had the right message.</p>
<p>*Along with our sexual urges (Part of being human, or rather of being an animal, rather than a plant) the combine took our freedom. With that, our ability to create. Our ability to decide what we want to do with our limited existence. There is nothing pragmatic about being slaves, just as there is nothing pragmatic about just sitting down and dying. If we cannot do anything but follow orders to wage war, (Which is what the remains of the human race are slowly being retrofitted to do) then we have no usefulness. There is no use in destroying. Only in creating. We have thumbs for a reason: So we can create and use tools, which in turn are used to create other things; shelters to live in, fires to warm ourselves, tools used for hunting food. And we mustn’t forget art, in it’s many forms; While it seemingly serves no direct purpose to some observers, it keeps us happy, keeps us sane, so we can continue to build and progress.</p>
<p>Anyway, that’s my opinion. Feel free to give scathing rebuttals.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/half-life-story-vs-mass-effect/8655/21">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/half-life-story-vs-mass-effect/8655/21</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 13 Apr 2012 01:27:23 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8655-21</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/half-life-story-vs-mass-effect/8655.rss">Half-Life Story vs. Mass Effect</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Half-Life Story vs. Mass Effect</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[OrderOfDagon]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Simontheb">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/s/ed655f/40.png" class="avatar"> Simontheb:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Okay I’m starting to get it. But if “being happy” is not satisfying one’s biological impulses, then what is it? What is hapinness for someone who disregard any biological impulse?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Happiness is just a signal of pleasure that is set-off to approve of your behavior or action. It can be stimulated by itself, but humans can’t access it without first making an action that triggers it. I think you may be mistaking satisfaction -which is essentially the removal of something that upsets us- and pleasure, which is what we get when we are simply happy.</p>
<p>This has been tested with rats and such. A rat with an impulse controller in his brain would sit in one spot and bite the pleasure button over and over again until it starved to death instead of eating food; this happens every time without fail.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Simontheb">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/s/ed655f/40.png" class="avatar"> Simontheb:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Just for curiosity’s sake, are you sure of that?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>It has to be true; traits and such don’t just pop into existence. They either expanded from smaller traits, or adapted to create new traits. We evolved to see color - it wasn’t always there clearly.</p>
<p>An example that might better one’s understand relates to the human appetite. Humans were once carnivorousness, but have recently become herbivorous in Evolution. The appendix was once a holder for the bacteria in raw meat, but now that it’s gone unused by our species for so long, it doesn’t work.</p>
<p>Many people will tell you that we are Omnivorousness – this is false. I’m not going to elaborate on that, but here is a <a href="https://www.stevepavlina.com/blog/2005/09/are-humans-carnivores-or-herbivores-2/" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">list</a> that will explain why.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Simontheb">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/s/ed655f/40.png" class="avatar"> Simontheb:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>But there is a difference between making an irrational decision under the influence of an impulse/feeling and making a rational decision meant to maximize the future amount of pleasure and minimize the future amount of pain for everyone involved.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Technically, Nietzsche describes someone who doesn’t seek happiness, or any emotion.<br>
I don’t actually know what Nietzsche thinks people will do without a desire. The desire to learn in itself is a Neurological Compulsion; maybe Nietzsche wants us to set our desire on learning or any trait that is deemed pragmatic and not-outdated – I don’t know.<br>
Maybe he was just trying to invoke the wrath of whatever created us.</p>
<p>No, I’m not a theist and neither is Nietzsche.</p>
<p>But Nietzsche often played with the idea that humans were designed to Evolve to become the best species on any planet they form on (I personally disagree with this theory of his and take a more Ayn Rand route). He believes in some huge ancient species that forced us to evolve in the same way that you force water to boil by heating it – a species that can see the entire universe in a microscope. He believes that perhaps the reason we are driven to follow our Neurological Influences is because by being active we power something, thus, The Will to Power. While he never makes a direct reference to some super-species, it is hinted that he believes such things are possible – it’s what he was getting at, so-to-speak.</p>
<p>Whether or not we are powering something, no one knows. But we do indeed have the urge to power as if we were, regardless of its consequence.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/half-life-story-vs-mass-effect/8655/20">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/half-life-story-vs-mass-effect/8655/20</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 12 Apr 2012 18:45:22 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8655-20</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/half-life-story-vs-mass-effect/8655.rss">Half-Life Story vs. Mass Effect</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Half-Life Story vs. Mass Effect</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Simontheb]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="OrderOfDagon">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/user_avatar/leakfree.org/orderofdagon/40/4963_2.png" class="avatar"> OrderOfDagon:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>You’re very intelligent Simontheb</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Uh… Thanks?</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="OrderOfDagon">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/user_avatar/leakfree.org/orderofdagon/40/4963_2.png" class="avatar"> OrderOfDagon:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Essentially, most human thought and drive is based around the object of goal – based around the pleasure that the goal will supposedly bring. An average person experiences random urges to achieve something that they have witnessed. This means that in any environment, a human person can be conditioned to desire.</p>
<p>Thing is, the only things that human’s desire is something that has been permitted by their Neurological Impulse. No matter how obscure, it can always be linked to either a Survival Instinct, Reproduction Instinct, and/or a Social Instinct (which inherently links to Reproduction anyway).</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Sounds pretty legit indeed.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="OrderOfDagon">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/user_avatar/leakfree.org/orderofdagon/40/4963_2.png" class="avatar"> OrderOfDagon:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Basically, humans never had a say in their own design. Pleasure itself is a tool in which nature coaxes you into doing what your species has evolved to, and displeasure or pain is a way of punishing you for not following. Based on Evolution, we made ourselves this way by our behavior and traditional-reaction to our environment.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Hum, “tool” and “punishment” make it sound like nature is some sort of intelligent entity. I guess that’s not what you mean, right? I’d rather say that pleasure and pain are signals, that say “good (in term of survival) for you/your specie” and “bad (in term of survival) for you/your specie”.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="OrderOfDagon">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/user_avatar/leakfree.org/orderofdagon/40/4963_2.png" class="avatar"> OrderOfDagon:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Examples: The reason that fruit is colorful is because humans, as a species, have become incredibly keen at perceiving food that was often searched for in our long history.</p>
<p>The reason that men are statistically more funny is because the more humorous males in our species got mates much faster than those who weren’t, making humorous men thrive in the ladder of Evolution.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Just for curiosity’s sake, are you sure of that?</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="OrderOfDagon">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/user_avatar/leakfree.org/orderofdagon/40/4963_2.png" class="avatar"> OrderOfDagon:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Friedrich Nietzsche spoke of a man who would awake one day and reject his control; a man who would decide on his own when to be happy; a man who would take control of his impulses and set a new course for the world. He calls these men, “Ubermensch.”</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Okay I’m starting to get it. But if “being happy” is not satisfying one’s biological impulses, then what is it?</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="OrderOfDagon">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/user_avatar/leakfree.org/orderofdagon/40/4963_2.png" class="avatar"> OrderOfDagon:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>You see, the problem with Neurological Impulses is that its evolution is an extremely slow process, and is more likely to devastate the human species than it is to lead us to any kind of salvation. Neurological Impulse is why we do everything we do, but what we do isn’t pragmatic.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I agree with that if you’re talking about impulses leading to pain/suffering.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="OrderOfDagon">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/user_avatar/leakfree.org/orderofdagon/40/4963_2.png" class="avatar"> OrderOfDagon:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Hatred is no longer necessary for it is a defensive emotion that is designed to dominate and defend - a very basic biological impulse. But the world is no longer a hostile place of wild beasts and mystery. We have science and laws, and hatred gets in the way of that.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I guess that’s right.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="OrderOfDagon">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/user_avatar/leakfree.org/orderofdagon/40/4963_2.png" class="avatar"> OrderOfDagon:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Love, though pleasurable, can lead to crimes all over the place.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Well, I think there can be love without jealousy, which is an impulse leading to suffering, therefore it must be fought.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="OrderOfDagon">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/user_avatar/leakfree.org/orderofdagon/40/4963_2.png" class="avatar"> OrderOfDagon:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Love is purely a way to push us toward reproduction, and since the world can become overpopulated very quickly, it isn’t necessary.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>But if we prevent sexuality from causing reproduction (like we do with birth control), we manage to take the “reward” of pleasure while ditching the negative consequence (that is to say, reproduction). It does the trick, don’t you think?</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="OrderOfDagon">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/user_avatar/leakfree.org/orderofdagon/40/4963_2.png" class="avatar"> OrderOfDagon:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>It is possible to condition a person to think differently and to naturally reject these impulses. The brain doesn’t finish growing until the age of 7 1/2[/SIZE], which means the synapses between the brain are still relatively easy to move through. If you explain and convince a child through intelligent and well-executed education that he has control over himself and should never make decision based on feelings, than he potentially can overcome his lesser half.</p>
<p>This, to Nietzsche’s mind, is the next step in Evolution.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>But there is a difference between making an irrational decision under the influence of an impulse/feeling and making a rational decision meant to maximize the future amount of pleasure and minimize the future amount of pain for everyone involved.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="OrderOfDagon">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/user_avatar/leakfree.org/orderofdagon/40/4963_2.png" class="avatar"> OrderOfDagon:</div>
<blockquote>
<p><span class="bbcode-i">“Imagine the day when happiness is a decision, not a goal.”</span></p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Then again, what is hapinness for someone who disregard any biological impulse?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/half-life-story-vs-mass-effect/8655/19">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/half-life-story-vs-mass-effect/8655/19</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 12 Apr 2012 15:10:22 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8655-19</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/half-life-story-vs-mass-effect/8655.rss">Half-Life Story vs. Mass Effect</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Half-Life Story vs. Mass Effect</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[OrderOfDagon]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>You’re very intelligent Simontheb – I’ll try and answers some of your question to the best of my ability.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Simontheb">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/s/ed655f/40.png" class="avatar"> Simontheb:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>What do you mean?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Essentially, most human thought and drive is based around the object of goal – based around the pleasure that the goal will supposedly bring. An average person experiences random urges to achieve something that they have witnessed. This means that in any environment, a human person can be conditioned to desire.</p>
<p>Thing is, the only things that human’s desire is something that has been permitted by their Neurological Impulse. No matter how obscure, it can always be linked to either a Survival Instinct, Reproduction Instinct, and/or a Social Instinct (which inherently links to Reproduction anyway). Basically, humans never had a say in their own design. Pleasure itself is a tool in which nature coaxes you into doing what your species has evolved to, and displeasure or pain is a way of punishing you for not following. Based on Evolution, we made ourselves this way by our behavior and traditional-reaction to our environment.</p>
<p>Examples: The reason that fruit is colorful is because humans, as a species, have become incredibly keen at perceiving food that was often searched for in our long history.</p>
<p>The reason that men are statistically more funny is because the more humorous males in our species got mates much faster than those who weren’t, making humorous men thrive in the ladder of Evolution.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Simontheb">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/s/ed655f/40.png" class="avatar"> Simontheb:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I don’t get it. What’s the point of having a god? What’s the point of being a pawn? What’s the point of having a purpose? And how taking part in a god’s war is “something great”?</p>
<p>See, I am a materialist. Of course you don’t have to agree with me here, but I think that we are nothing more than a bunch of particles interacting according to the laws of physics. Which implies there is no meaning of life. We are just here for a limited amount of time, until we die and that’s it. So, the best we can do during our lifetime if to maximize the amount of pleasure (wether physical, emotional or intellectual) and minimize the amount of suffering (wether physical, emotional or intellectual) we get, because we like taking pleasure and we don’t like suffering. And of course, that’s true for every lifeform with a nervous system, not just humans. So, for me being part of “something great” or even becoming immortal serves no useful purpose if it doesn’t bring pleasure. And in particular, being invaded by the Combine brought a whole lot of suffering and little to no pleasure. So, bad.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Friedrich Nietzsche spoke of a man who would awake one day and reject his control; a man who would decide on his own when to be happy; a man who would take control of his impulses and set a new course for the world. He calls these men, “Ubermensch.”</p>
<p>You see, the problem with Neurological Impulses is that its evolution is an extremely slow process, and is more likely to devastate the human species than it is to lead us to any kind of salvation. Neurological Impulse is why we do everything we do, but what we do isn’t pragmatic. Hatred is no longer necessary for it is a defensive emotion that is designed to dominate and defend - a very basic biological impulse. But the world is no longer a hostile place of wild beasts and mystery. We have science and laws, and hatred gets in the way of that. Love, though pleasurable, can lead to crimes all over the place. Love is purely a way to push us toward reproduction, and since the world can become overpopulated very quickly, it isn’t necessary.</p>
<p>It is possible to condition a person to think differently and to naturally reject these impulses. The brain doesn’t finish growing until the age of 7 1/2[/SIZE], which means the synapses between the brain are still relatively easy to move through. If you explain and convince a child through intelligent and well-executed education that he has control over himself and should never make decision based on feelings, than he potentially can overcome his lesser half.</p>
<p>This, to Nietzsche’s mind, is the next step in Evolution.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-i">“Imagine the day when happiness is a decision, not a goal.”</span></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/half-life-story-vs-mass-effect/8655/18">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/half-life-story-vs-mass-effect/8655/18</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 11 Apr 2012 22:42:43 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8655-18</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/half-life-story-vs-mass-effect/8655.rss">Half-Life Story vs. Mass Effect</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Half-Life Story vs. Mass Effect</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[TheSuperNova]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>For me, it’s a no brainer, Half-life 2 has the better stroryline, although mass effect’s story is awesome.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/half-life-story-vs-mass-effect/8655/17">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/half-life-story-vs-mass-effect/8655/17</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 11 Apr 2012 22:23:09 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8655-17</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/half-life-story-vs-mass-effect/8655.rss">Half-Life Story vs. Mass Effect</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Half-Life Story vs. Mass Effect</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Simontheb]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I’m seriously getting off-topic, sorry for that, but this is too interesting.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="OrderOfDagon">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/user_avatar/leakfree.org/orderofdagon/40/4963_2.png" class="avatar"> OrderOfDagon:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Pragmatism doesn’t mean quality for human life.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>For me it does. I think we don’t have the same vision of pragmatism.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="OrderOfDagon">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/user_avatar/leakfree.org/orderofdagon/40/4963_2.png" class="avatar"> OrderOfDagon:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Try and understand, humans go around hunting animals and endangering species to extinction simply because we are at the top of the food chain.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>That’s factually true, as far as I can tell (maybe a biologist wouldn’t agree with the “top of the food chain” part, I don’t know).</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="OrderOfDagon">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/user_avatar/leakfree.org/orderofdagon/40/4963_2.png" class="avatar"> OrderOfDagon:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Humans are, essentially, purposeless sacks of water that go around appeasing their neurological requisites…</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I totally agree, but you make it sound bad. I wouldn’t.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="OrderOfDagon">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/user_avatar/leakfree.org/orderofdagon/40/4963_2.png" class="avatar"> OrderOfDagon:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>without thinking beyond their nature.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>What do you mean?</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="OrderOfDagon">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/user_avatar/leakfree.org/orderofdagon/40/4963_2.png" class="avatar"> OrderOfDagon:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>The Combine gave them freedom from some of these impulses…</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>You mean, the impulse of sexuality? I don’t see why anyone could want to be “freed” from sexuality. It’s a very efficient mean to get pleasure.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="OrderOfDagon">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/user_avatar/leakfree.org/orderofdagon/40/4963_2.png" class="avatar"> OrderOfDagon:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>…and -if you paid attention to Breen’s Announcements about immortality- were planning on giving freedom from physiological imperatives aswell.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Now that you put it that way, it is possible indeed that striders and hunters are immortal. But immortality is pointless if it can’t be enjoyed, don’t you think?</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="OrderOfDagon">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/user_avatar/leakfree.org/orderofdagon/40/4963_2.png" class="avatar"> OrderOfDagon:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Even though the standard of living for humans wasn’t so great, it was necessary.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I don’t see why. The combine just chose to be brutal for it was easier to control humanity that way.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="OrderOfDagon">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/user_avatar/leakfree.org/orderofdagon/40/4963_2.png" class="avatar"> OrderOfDagon:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>It’s like humans and ants. Lets say that were some modern-military tribe, and that ants were infecting our crops for whatever reason. Those crops fed our soldiers and kept us alive – what’s a solution? The tribe would probably try and contain the ants in a small but easily accessible space, like ant farms. Sure, the ants are more enclosed and uncomfortable, but who cares, right?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I don’t think your analogy is valid. The combine were the one who invaded, not us. We were simply hanging on our planet minding our own business. Well, except the xen trip of course.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="OrderOfDagon">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/user_avatar/leakfree.org/orderofdagon/40/4963_2.png" class="avatar"> OrderOfDagon:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>So now lets say that we decide to set those ants on our enemies’ crops, making them weaker. Is the ant not incredibly more significant in purpose? They now have real gods (humans) where they initially had none; they have real comprehendable purpose; they are part of something bigger. Would you rather continue the monotonous life of an ant, or would you become apart of something great?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I don’t get it. What’s the point of having a god? What’s the point of being a pawn? What’s the point of having a purpose? And how taking part in a god’s war is “something great”?</p>
<p>See, I am a materialist. Of course you don’t have to agree with me here, but I think that we are nothing more than a bunch of particles interacting according to the laws of physics. Which implies there is no meaning of life. We are just here for a limited amount of time, until we die and that’s it. So, the best we can do during our lifetime if to maximize the amount of pleasure (wether physical, emotional or intellectual) and minimize the amount of suffering (wether physical, emotional or intellectual) we get, because we like taking pleasure and we don’t like suffering. And of course, that’s true for every lifeform with a nervous system, not just humans. So, for me being part of “something great” or even becoming immortal serves no useful purpose if it doesn’t bring pleasure. And in particular, being invaded by the Combine brought a whole lot of suffering and little to no pleasure. So, bad.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/half-life-story-vs-mass-effect/8655/16">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/half-life-story-vs-mass-effect/8655/16</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 11 Apr 2012 22:08:38 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8655-16</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/half-life-story-vs-mass-effect/8655.rss">Half-Life Story vs. Mass Effect</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Half-Life Story vs. Mass Effect</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[gibbelin]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Edit: actually, never mind. I just realized I don’t actually care about this conversation.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/half-life-story-vs-mass-effect/8655/15">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/half-life-story-vs-mass-effect/8655/15</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 11 Apr 2012 20:16:49 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8655-15</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/half-life-story-vs-mass-effect/8655.rss">Half-Life Story vs. Mass Effect</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
