<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Constant crashes, later on in &quot;Surface Tension&quot;</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/constant-crashes-later-on-in-surface-tension/11447</link>
    <description>I&#39;ve been having problems in &quot;Surface Tension&quot; - in the tunnel after the battle in the foyer, once you&#39;ve managed to get outside, Black Mesa keeps experiencing CTDs when I try to open the door with the keypad.  I&#39;ve tried everything I can think of - turning in the opposite direction to the loading area (which worked for me before), dropping the settings down as much as possible, restarting from earlier saves... but nothing&#39;s worked.

The .mdmp file from the latest of MANY crashes in this area is attached below.

EDIT: And, of course, as soon as I posted this, I tried again... and it WORKED.  GAH!

EDIT 2: And, a few minutes later, it crashed, and all &quot;Surface Tension&quot; saves I had won&#39;t load.  Why the hell...?
&lt;a class=&#39;attachment&#39; href=&#39;/uploads/default/original/2X/f/fa8722590c7bb1ca1a4b626adc66f6bb4f34478c.mdmp&#39;&gt;hl2_4104_crash_2012_10_11T9_17_52C0.mdmp&lt;/a&gt; (97.5 KB)</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 11 Oct 2012 09:22:58 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>In-game Issues (Mod)</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/constant-crashes-later-on-in-surface-tension/11447.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Constant crashes, later on in &quot;Surface Tension&quot;</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Sinndogg]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I’ve been having problems in “Surface Tension” - in the tunnel after the battle in the foyer, once you’ve managed to get outside, Black Mesa keeps experiencing CTDs when I try to open the door with the keypad.  I’ve tried everything I can think of - turning in the opposite direction to the loading area (which worked for me before), dropping the settings down as much as possible, restarting from earlier saves… but nothing’s worked.</p>
<p>The .mdmp file from the latest of MANY crashes in this area is attached below.</p>
<p>EDIT: And, of course, as soon as I posted this, I tried again… and it WORKED.  GAH!</p>
<p>EDIT 2: And, a few minutes later, it crashed, and all “Surface Tension” saves I had won’t load.  Why the hell…?<br>
<a class="attachment" href="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/original/2X/f/fa8722590c7bb1ca1a4b626adc66f6bb4f34478c.mdmp">hl2_4104_crash_2012_10_11T9_17_52C0.mdmp</a> (97.5 KB)</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/constant-crashes-later-on-in-surface-tension/11447/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/constant-crashes-later-on-in-surface-tension/11447/1</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 11 Oct 2012 09:22:58 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11447-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/constant-crashes-later-on-in-surface-tension/11447.rss">Constant crashes, later on in &quot;Surface Tension&quot;</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
