<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>&quot;Scum Save&quot; Achievements</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/scum-save-achievements/14863</link>
    <description>It is entirely possible to &quot;Scum Save&quot; the majority [s]all[/s] of the Steam achievement counters. I don&#39;t know if this kind of thing is common (Steam or otherwise), and i dont know if they are &quot;Steam&quot; achievements or &quot;Black Mesa&quot; achievements, or if theres a difference (and dont care). I&#39;ve never had much interest in achievement hunting, and still don&#39;t (this game being the only exception.

Quick save and quick load to...
Lure the same head crab into the same barnacle 10 times, same shotgun blast, same vending machine, same automated turret...you get the idea.

I don’t know if you can actually do anything about it, (e.g. If it’s in Steam&#39;s control, not yours) I just thought you should know (if you don&#39;t already).

[b]If there’s nothing that can be done, perhaps delete this thread...lol[/b]  :wink:</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 11 Jul 2016 19:27:09 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>In-game Issues</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/scum-save-achievements/14863.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>&quot;Scum Save&quot; Achievements</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Stigmund]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>It is entirely possible to “Scum Save” the majority <span class="bbcode-s">all</span> of the Steam achievement counters. I don’t know if this kind of thing is common (Steam or otherwise), and i dont know if they are “Steam” achievements or “Black Mesa” achievements, or if theres a difference (and dont care). I’ve never had much interest in achievement hunting, and still don’t (this game being the only exception.</p>
<p>Quick save and quick load to…<br>
Lure the same head crab into the same barnacle 10 times, same shotgun blast, same vending machine, same automated turret…you get the idea.</p>
<p>I don’t know if you can actually do anything about it, (e.g. If it’s in Steam’s control, not yours) I just thought you should know (if you don’t already).</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">If there’s nothing that can be done, perhaps delete this thread…lol</span>  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/wink.png?v=9" title=":wink:" class="emoji" alt=":wink:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/scum-save-achievements/14863/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/scum-save-achievements/14863/1</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jul 2016 19:27:09 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14863-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/scum-save-achievements/14863.rss">&quot;Scum Save&quot; Achievements</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
