<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>The Massdebating Handbook</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/the-massdebating-handbook/2579</link>
    <description>These are the rules:

1. [b]&#39;Ask a...&#39; Threads:[/b] If these aren&#39;t serious, you&#39;ll get an infraction. If the threads descend into petty name-calling and trolling, they&#39;re closed and the members responsible get an infraction.

2. [b]Be Civil:[/b] For the most part (apart from the above stipulation) I&#39;m going to try and be as un-moderating on this board as possible. Don&#39;t take this as a licence to be an idiot or else you&#39;ll be taking a holiday.

3. [b]Serious Threads:[/b] Religion, Politics, Popular Culture et al is fine. But don&#39;t make a debate thread for the hell of it.

4. [b]Reporting:[/b] Seeing as though the Massdebating Hall doesn&#39;t contribute to your post count, only report posts that are either deliberately derailing the thread or offensive.

5. [b]Re-Opening Threads:[/b] Once a thread is closed, it will no longer be re-opened.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 11 Jan 2010 23:52:31 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Off Topic</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/the-massdebating-handbook/2579.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>The Massdebating Handbook</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Garcian_Smith]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>These are the rules:</p>
<ol>
<li>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">‘Ask a…’ Threads:</span> If these aren’t serious, you’ll get an infraction. If the threads descend into petty name-calling and trolling, they’re closed and the members responsible get an infraction.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Be Civil:</span> For the most part (apart from the above stipulation) I’m going to try and be as un-moderating on this board as possible. Don’t take this as a licence to be an idiot or else you’ll be taking a holiday.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Serious Threads:</span> Religion, Politics, Popular Culture et al is fine. But don’t make a debate thread for the hell of it.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Reporting:</span> Seeing as though the Massdebating Hall doesn’t contribute to your post count, only report posts that are either deliberately derailing the thread or offensive.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Re-Opening Threads:</span> Once a thread is closed, it will no longer be re-opened.</p>
</li>
</ol>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/the-massdebating-handbook/2579/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/the-massdebating-handbook/2579/1</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jan 2010 23:52:31 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2579-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/the-massdebating-handbook/2579.rss">The Massdebating Handbook</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
