<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Help on creating biweekly email newsletter</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/help-on-creating-biweekly-email-newsletter/12742</link>
    <description>Howdy-do, folks!  It&#39;s me again.  I was hoping to get some assistance as my Google fu skills have failed me and I&#39;m getting a headache trying to figure this all out.

Basically, here&#39;s what I want to do:

I run a website for an annual get-together and I&#39;d like to send out a biweekly email containing information about the get-together to two different email lists.  I have permission to send out these biweekly emails. I want to compose the &#39;newsletter&#39; as a text document and then have some sort of program or whatever place that text document as plain text into the body of an email and send it out every two weeks.

However, that information may change including suggested activities, list of attendees and other such things, so whenever that information changes, I can just go into the text file and update the information and then have the program or whatever, read that new information and send out an updated email.

I know about the email capabilities of Windows 7&#39;s Task Scheduler, but you have to compose your email from inside the Task Scheduler.  Why don&#39;t I just do this?  It&#39;s a pain to go into that every time something changes.  I&#39;d rather have a text file I can quickly open from my desktop to update the information.

Is something like this even possible?

OS: Windows 7
Email Client: Thunderbird (24.1.0)
Email Server: Gmail

Thanks!  :retard:</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2013 07:10:01 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Help and Support</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/help-on-creating-biweekly-email-newsletter/12742.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Help on creating biweekly email newsletter</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Orpheon]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Don’t know if you’ve found a solution already, but creating a VB script is usually the first thing I turn to when I want to automate something. However, that might take more time and effort than it’s worth for this task. I’ve heard that there are some issues integrating with Task Scheduler anyway. Have you looked into something like <a href="https://www.boomeranggmail.com/" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Boomerang for Gmail</a>? I’ve used it before simply to send out time-delayed emails, but it looks like it can do more than that.  Although I’m not familiar with all of its features, it might be helpful for what you need. Or maybe there’s another gmail plugin that provides the functionality you need.</p>
<p>EDIT: Also found this on the Chrome Web Store: <a href="https://chrome.google.com/webstore/detail/newsletter-creator-for-gm/cihaednhfbocfdiflmpccekcmjepcnmb?hl=en" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Newsletter Creator for Gmail</a>. Don’t know if that’ll help either, but I’d say a third-party solution would probably be the simplest and fastest way to get this taken care of, rather than trying to whip up something yourself.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/help-on-creating-biweekly-email-newsletter/12742/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/help-on-creating-biweekly-email-newsletter/12742/2</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2013 07:10:01 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12742-2</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/help-on-creating-biweekly-email-newsletter/12742.rss">Help on creating biweekly email newsletter</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Help on creating biweekly email newsletter</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[danielsangeo]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Howdy-do, folks!  It’s me again.  I was hoping to get some assistance as my Google fu skills have failed me and I’m getting a headache trying to figure this all out.</p>
<p>Basically, here’s what I want to do:</p>
<p>I run a website for an annual get-together and I’d like to send out a biweekly email containing information about the get-together to two different email lists.  I have permission to send out these biweekly emails. I want to compose the ‘newsletter’ as a text document and then have some sort of program or whatever place that text document as plain text into the body of an email and send it out every two weeks.</p>
<p>However, that information may change including suggested activities, list of attendees and other such things, so whenever that information changes, I can just go into the text file and update the information and then have the program or whatever, read that new information and send out an updated email.</p>
<p>I know about the email capabilities of Windows 7’s Task Scheduler, but you have to compose your email from inside the Task Scheduler.  Why don’t I just do this?  It’s a pain to go into that every time something changes.  I’d rather have a text file I can quickly open from my desktop to update the information.</p>
<p>Is something like this even possible?</p>
<p>OS: Windows 7<br>
Email Client: Thunderbird (24.1.0)<br>
Email Server: Gmail</p>
<p>Thanks!  :retard:</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/help-on-creating-biweekly-email-newsletter/12742/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/help-on-creating-biweekly-email-newsletter/12742/1</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2013 02:41:32 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12742-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/help-on-creating-biweekly-email-newsletter/12742.rss">Help on creating biweekly email newsletter</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
