<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Question about the ATI 5750</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/question-about-the-ati-5750/2711</link>
    <description>Okay, before I begin, keep in mind that I live in South America, and here, hardware (and pretty much any other thing related to technology) is ridiculously overpriced. Due to our importing taxes and a few other factors, it&#39;s quite common for such things to cost 3 or 4 times their original price in North America/Europe. Therefore, it&#39;s pretty much impossible to go for high-end specs as I&#39;d prefer, and you just have to deal with using mid or even low-tier stuff  :frowning: .

It used to be like that for games as well, but since Steam came around, I&#39;ve been able to buy pretty much any game I like legitimately for their original price, only having to deal with the different currency, ending up in some very reasonable prices (1US$ is about 1.78 Brazilian R$), which is the reason I haven&#39;t torrented a single game in about 6 or 7 years  :smiley: . Thing is, having great games with a shitty computer doesn&#39;t add up too good, and I end up having to play most of my games with crappy fps, so lately I&#39;ve been saving to do an upgrade.

For the overall specs, I&#39;ve pretty much decided at these specs:

Processor: Intel Core 2 Duo E7500
RAM: 2x2GB DDR2 800Mhz Kingston
HDD: 1TB Seagate 7200 RPM
Mobo: I&#39;m keeping my current P5KPL-AM, because even though it&#39;s pretty crappy it should handle everything I&#39;m looking for.
PSU: Also keeping mine (550W)

The thing is, I can&#39;t decide on a GPU. I was originally going to save more until I had enough for a GTX 260/275, which cost a whole bunch around here, since they&#39;ve seemed to be cards that would allow me to play pretty much every game I own and still give me an edge for upcoming titles. But I&#39;ve found a very reasonable deal on a 5750 (which believe it or not is 479R$ or 267US$), and I&#39;m really inclined to go for it since it seems to be a good card (roughly the same as a GTS250) and has good power consumption, DirectX 11 support and all.

I&#39;ve never bought from ATI before and I&#39;ve heard they have issues with 64-bit drivers. Besides, I don&#39;t know exactly at which point I&#39;d be able to run recent titles. Since I like to multiplayer a lot (and when I&#39;m doing it I don&#39;t really care much about graphics), and also enjoy some single player (when I do care about graphics). My main doubts about a setup with a 5750 are:

- Would I be able to run multiplayer titles such as TF2/CSS and whatnot with [b]decent[/b] graphics, at a [b]very good[/b] frame rate (above 80 fps even during heavy gunfights and all)?

- Would I be able to run the most recent single player titles such as Crysis/Bioshock 2 at a [b]playable[/b] frame rate (40~60 fps)?

- Would such setup, due to having DirectX 11 support and all, provide me with [b]some[/b] future-proof for being able to run upcoming titles at a still reasonable frame rate (not necessarily at maximum graphics), or should I wait for the new generation cards from NVidia or ATI to come out and see if the prices drop?

Keep in mind what I&#39;ve stated in the first paragraph, since I really have no option to buy high-end specs unless I finally travel to the US or Europe (on which occasion I&#39;m gonna buy loads of other shit :3).

Hope someone more experienced can shed some light here, and sorry for the gigantic wall of text (feel free to go tl;dr  :stuck_out_tongue: ) :/.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 21 Jan 2010 15:07:01 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Help and Support</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/question-about-the-ati-5750/2711.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Question about the ATI 5750</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Mith]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Benjamin">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/b/3d9bf3/40.png" class="avatar"> Benjamin:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>EDIT: That was with Amazon. Apparently NewEgg doesn’t do international orders.  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/frowning.png?v=9" title=":frowning:" class="emoji" alt=":frowning:"></p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Yep. And even so, pretty much any site that ships internationally can only ship DVD’s/Books directly to Brazil. Any other product, from toothpaste to plasma TV’s, has to go through customs and gets charged for importing taxes (which are like 300% of the product’s price). It sucks big time  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/frowning.png?v=9" title=":frowning:" class="emoji" alt=":frowning:"> .</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/question-about-the-ati-5750/2711/11">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/question-about-the-ati-5750/2711/11</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jan 2010 15:07:01 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2711-11</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/question-about-the-ati-5750/2711.rss">Question about the ATI 5750</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Question about the ATI 5750</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Benjamin]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="eternalness">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/e/dc4da7/40.png" class="avatar"> eternalness:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I wuz talking about the moderators sending it.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>EDIT: That was with Amazon. Apparently NewEgg doesn’t do international orders.  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/frowning.png?v=9" title=":frowning:" class="emoji" alt=":frowning:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/question-about-the-ati-5750/2711/10">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/question-about-the-ati-5750/2711/10</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jan 2010 07:47:13 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2711-10</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/question-about-the-ati-5750/2711.rss">Question about the ATI 5750</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Question about the ATI 5750</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[eternalness]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I wuz talking about the moderators sending it.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/question-about-the-ati-5750/2711/9">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/question-about-the-ati-5750/2711/9</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jan 2010 07:02:49 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2711-9</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/question-about-the-ati-5750/2711.rss">Question about the ATI 5750</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Question about the ATI 5750</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Benjamin]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="eternalness">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/e/dc4da7/40.png" class="avatar"> eternalness:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I doubt they would do that.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>And why not? Hell, I got a tablet shipped to a remote corner of Canada pretty cheaply without much trouble, and the damn thing is way heavier and bigger than a video card.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/question-about-the-ati-5750/2711/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/question-about-the-ati-5750/2711/8</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jan 2010 06:47:06 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2711-8</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/question-about-the-ati-5750/2711.rss">Question about the ATI 5750</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Question about the ATI 5750</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[eternalness]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I doubt they would do that.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/question-about-the-ati-5750/2711/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/question-about-the-ati-5750/2711/7</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jan 2010 06:01:02 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2711-7</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/question-about-the-ati-5750/2711.rss">Question about the ATI 5750</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Question about the ATI 5750</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Benjamin]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Here’s my thoughts - how much is postage to the areas where you live? You might be able to get something shipped from NewEgg directly to you if you pay a little bit of extra postage, and if that doesn’t work you could find someone you trust within the USA (potentially one of the moderators here) and get them to purchase a card and send it to you.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/question-about-the-ati-5750/2711/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/question-about-the-ati-5750/2711/6</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jan 2010 05:59:51 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2711-6</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/question-about-the-ati-5750/2711.rss">Question about the ATI 5750</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Question about the ATI 5750</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Sitten_duck]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Considering I can can run all source games on high with really good results and crysis on medium with decent frame rates (until I hit the final boss then they take a huge dive) on my Radeon HD 4650, I think you’ll have no problem going with that card on Crysis or anyother game.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/question-about-the-ati-5750/2711/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/question-about-the-ati-5750/2711/5</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jan 2010 05:30:01 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2711-5</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/question-about-the-ati-5750/2711.rss">Question about the ATI 5750</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Question about the ATI 5750</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[eternalness]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Im running windows 7 Ultimate 64bit and I haven’t run into any problems with their drivers, and to please siggs I shant post my specs.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/question-about-the-ati-5750/2711/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/question-about-the-ati-5750/2711/4</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jan 2010 03:23:07 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2711-4</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/question-about-the-ati-5750/2711.rss">Question about the ATI 5750</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Question about the ATI 5750</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Mith]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Yeah I really wish I could fit one of those in my budget  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/frowning.png?v=9" title=":frowning:" class="emoji" alt=":frowning:"> , but the price is just out of consideration.</p>
<p>Just a few prices for comparison (and keep in mind these are the ABSOLUTELY LOWEST prices you can find around here, the average price in common stores is much higher):</p>
<p>5770: R$599,99 - US$335,00 (pretty much almost $100 higher)</p>
<p>5850: R$1299,99 - US$726,50 (YAY FOR DOUBLE PRICE!)</p>
<p>5870: R$1499,99 - US$838,00</p>
<p>5970: R$2153,00 - US$1204,00 (yay for the price of a full gaming setup in the US!)</p>
<p>It’s pretty sad when you take the time to compare it  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/frowning.png?v=9" title=":frowning:" class="emoji" alt=":frowning:"> .</p>
<p>Anyways, good to know those things you stated, guess it should fulfill my needs for the next couple of years. Hopefully by then I’ll be already working overseas  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/smiley.png?v=9" title=":smiley:" class="emoji" alt=":smiley:"> .</p>
<p>Also is it true that ATI has horrible issues with driver support for 64-bit OS’s? 'Cause if I’m going to buy a DirectX 11 GPU, then I’ll most likely use Windows 7, and the version I own of it is 64-bit (and let’s face it there’s really no reason to use 32-bit, even more so when you have 4GB or above of RAM), and it’d suck to spend that amount of money to find out the driver support sucks :/.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/question-about-the-ati-5750/2711/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/question-about-the-ati-5750/2711/3</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jan 2010 03:14:52 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2711-3</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/question-about-the-ati-5750/2711.rss">Question about the ATI 5750</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Question about the ATI 5750</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[eternalness]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>The 5750 should run any source engine game without a hitch. It will be able to crysis on high at playable framerates for the majority of the game with a few brief slowdowns here and there. Bioshock 2 should run so u shouldn’t worry about that. If u can fit it in ur budget, try to get a 5770 or 5850, they’ll give u much better future proofing and should handle any game out right now fine. If u want all out performance and future proofing, get a 5970, but thats expensive even in the states  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=9" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"> . ATi is a very respectable brand and their cards are very good.</p>
<p>5750: $144USD</p>
<p>5770: $160USD</p>
<p>5850: $300USD</p>
<p>5870: $400USD</p>
<p>5970: $700USD</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/question-about-the-ati-5750/2711/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/question-about-the-ati-5750/2711/2</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jan 2010 02:24:07 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2711-2</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/question-about-the-ati-5750/2711.rss">Question about the ATI 5750</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Question about the ATI 5750</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Mith]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Okay, before I begin, keep in mind that I live in South America, and here, hardware (and pretty much any other thing related to technology) is ridiculously overpriced. Due to our importing taxes and a few other factors, it’s quite common for such things to cost 3 or 4 times their original price in North America/Europe. Therefore, it’s pretty much impossible to go for high-end specs as I’d prefer, and you just have to deal with using mid or even low-tier stuff  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/frowning.png?v=9" title=":frowning:" class="emoji" alt=":frowning:"> .</p>
<p>It used to be like that for games as well, but since Steam came around, I’ve been able to buy pretty much any game I like legitimately for their original price, only having to deal with the different currency, ending up in some very reasonable prices (1US$ is about 1.78 Brazilian R$), which is the reason I haven’t torrented a single game in about 6 or 7 years  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/smiley.png?v=9" title=":smiley:" class="emoji" alt=":smiley:"> . Thing is, having great games with a shitty computer doesn’t add up too good, and I end up having to play most of my games with crappy fps, so lately I’ve been saving to do an upgrade.</p>
<p>For the overall specs, I’ve pretty much decided at these specs:</p>
<p>Processor: Intel Core 2 Duo E7500<br>
RAM: 2x2GB DDR2 800Mhz Kingston<br>
HDD: 1TB Seagate 7200 RPM<br>
Mobo: I’m keeping my current P5KPL-AM, because even though it’s pretty crappy it should handle everything I’m looking for.<br>
PSU: Also keeping mine (550W)</p>
<p>The thing is, I can’t decide on a GPU. I was originally going to save more until I had enough for a GTX 260/275, which cost a whole bunch around here, since they’ve seemed to be cards that would allow me to play pretty much every game I own and still give me an edge for upcoming titles. But I’ve found a very reasonable deal on a 5750 (which believe it or not is 479R$ or 267US$), and I’m really inclined to go for it since it seems to be a good card (roughly the same as a GTS250) and has good power consumption, DirectX 11 support and all.</p>
<p>I’ve never bought from ATI before and I’ve heard they have issues with 64-bit drivers. Besides, I don’t know exactly at which point I’d be able to run recent titles. Since I like to multiplayer a lot (and when I’m doing it I don’t really care much about graphics), and also enjoy some single player (when I do care about graphics). My main doubts about a setup with a 5750 are:</p>
<ul>
<li>
<p>Would I be able to run multiplayer titles such as TF2/CSS and whatnot with <span class="bbcode-b">decent</span> graphics, at a <span class="bbcode-b">very good</span> frame rate (above 80 fps even during heavy gunfights and all)?</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Would I be able to run the most recent single player titles such as Crysis/Bioshock 2 at a <span class="bbcode-b">playable</span> frame rate (40~60 fps)?</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Would such setup, due to having DirectX 11 support and all, provide me with <span class="bbcode-b">some</span> future-proof for being able to run upcoming titles at a still reasonable frame rate (not necessarily at maximum graphics), or should I wait for the new generation cards from NVidia or ATI to come out and see if the prices drop?</p>
</li>
</ul>
<p>Keep in mind what I’ve stated in the first paragraph, since I really have no option to buy high-end specs unless I finally travel to the US or Europe (on which occasion I’m gonna buy loads of other shit :3).</p>
<p>Hope someone more experienced can shed some light here, and sorry for the gigantic wall of text (feel free to go tl;dr  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=9" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"> ) :/.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/question-about-the-ati-5750/2711/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/question-about-the-ati-5750/2711/1</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jan 2010 01:03:02 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-2711-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/question-about-the-ati-5750/2711.rss">Question about the ATI 5750</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
