<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Need some critism</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/need-some-critism/6674</link>
    <description>Knowing how critical you guys are I thought I would share a piece of writing I&#39;m working on. It&#39;s far from done, and I need a lot of advice. Here are a few things I need help on:

1. How should I start this?
2. What should I get ride of/remove?
3. What should I add?
4. What sounds good, and what doesn&#39;t? 
5. How can I find a writing style that truly fits me (as I&#39;m borrowing from many different authors)? 

Please try to stay constructive... I don&#39;t need people telling me it sucks, but rather what you don&#39;t like about it. It&#39;s not a project or anything, I just enjoy writing. Here&#39;s what I have so far:

Long passed in the former world, before the gray brick lighthouse was precariously suspended on the rock-strewn peninsula, followed by this then erected into port and township. Long before the first man set foot onto the sandy beaches, and set in motion establishment. True, it had been long sense the island called out in its mysterious lore, sending bright its audible token straight into the airwaves, meeting with the cool air, and emitting for the world to behold a demonstration of likely magnificence. For it called, and the black rocks listened, it called, and the trees sang, it called, and the wind whistled. But, by and by, year after year, the rocks stopped listening and forgot how to hear, the trees stopped singing and forgot even the simplest note, and the wind stopped whistling, and forgot how to squeeze but a blow from cheek. Never the less, not a year had gone – nor had the subtle silhouette of hollowed trees eroded in the gut of beetle distorted in position from former passing by the cosmic alignment - with the intention that of the beacon not transmitting its ancient sign. It sent out, like a torch shining brightly beside the tide. And year after year, the dirt trails had forgotten the passerby’s of creature. The wooden oak, with routs long plunged into the plot amidst the Hebrides had sense, befitting their worn old age, began to mold, reduce, and decay into only that which would be suitable of smaller and less minded beings. The signal called; however, there was none from this consign to rejoin its arid message but the forlorn, dry airstream drifting, by and by, amidst the cliffs and black rocks littering the zone.  Even the lifeless, flaccid, and elderly foliage long sense forgotten about the white noise. A sad omniscient tone bounced from the moldy wreck amidst the coast, through the innards of the hermit, and gull.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 03 Mar 2011 04:57:01 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Help and Support</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/need-some-critism/6674.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Need some critism</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Spooboy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Knowing how critical you guys are I thought I would share a piece of writing I’m working on. It’s far from done, and I need a lot of advice. Here are a few things I need help on:</p>
<ol>
<li>How should I start this?</li>
<li>What should I get ride of/remove?</li>
<li>What should I add?</li>
<li>What sounds good, and what doesn’t?</li>
<li>How can I find a writing style that truly fits me (as I’m borrowing from many different authors)?</li>
</ol>
<p>Please try to stay constructive… I don’t need people telling me it sucks, but rather what you don’t like about it. It’s not a project or anything, I just enjoy writing. Here’s what I have so far:</p>
<p>Long passed in the former world, before the gray brick lighthouse was precariously suspended on the rock-strewn peninsula, followed by this then erected into port and township. Long before the first man set foot onto the sandy beaches, and set in motion establishment. True, it had been long sense the island called out in its mysterious lore, sending bright its audible token straight into the airwaves, meeting with the cool air, and emitting for the world to behold a demonstration of likely magnificence. For it called, and the black rocks listened, it called, and the trees sang, it called, and the wind whistled. But, by and by, year after year, the rocks stopped listening and forgot how to hear, the trees stopped singing and forgot even the simplest note, and the wind stopped whistling, and forgot how to squeeze but a blow from cheek. Never the less, not a year had gone – nor had the subtle silhouette of hollowed trees eroded in the gut of beetle distorted in position from former passing by the cosmic alignment - with the intention that of the beacon not transmitting its ancient sign. It sent out, like a torch shining brightly beside the tide. And year after year, the dirt trails had forgotten the passerby’s of creature. The wooden oak, with routs long plunged into the plot amidst the Hebrides had sense, befitting their worn old age, began to mold, reduce, and decay into only that which would be suitable of smaller and less minded beings. The signal called; however, there was none from this consign to rejoin its arid message but the forlorn, dry airstream drifting, by and by, amidst the cliffs and black rocks littering the zone.  Even the lifeless, flaccid, and elderly foliage long sense forgotten about the white noise. A sad omniscient tone bounced from the moldy wreck amidst the coast, through the innards of the hermit, and gull.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/need-some-critism/6674/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/need-some-critism/6674/1</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 03 Mar 2011 04:57:01 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-6674-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/need-some-critism/6674.rss">Need some critism</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
