<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Sound problem</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/sound-problem/13279</link>
    <description>Hello there,

There is a problem with sound mechanics with my BMS installation. When I start the game, after the train sequence all I hear is ambience music. I can&#39;t hear any dialogues, I can&#39;t even hear my footsteps or doors opening/closing before me. I think some very serious problems with speaker settings is in order but I have tried everything, I have 5.1 speakers but I have even set it to 2 speakers to see if it worked differently but it didn&#39;t. I googled about the problem but found no solution. Any help?</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2014 18:04:27 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Help!</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/sound-problem/13279.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Sound problem</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[CatzEyes93]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>In my totally uneducated opinion, if this were me, I would download the installation files again (possibly from a different source) and I would re install the game.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/sound-problem/13279/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/sound-problem/13279/2</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2014 18:04:27 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13279-2</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/sound-problem/13279.rss">Sound problem</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Sound problem</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[vorph]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Hello there,</p>
<p>There is a problem with sound mechanics with my BMS installation. When I start the game, after the train sequence all I hear is ambience music. I can’t hear any dialogues, I can’t even hear my footsteps or doors opening/closing before me. I think some very serious problems with speaker settings is in order but I have tried everything, I have 5.1 speakers but I have even set it to 2 speakers to see if it worked differently but it didn’t. I googled about the problem but found no solution. Any help?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/sound-problem/13279/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/sound-problem/13279/1</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2014 06:38:29 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13279-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/sound-problem/13279.rss">Sound problem</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
