<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Funny little glitch with elevator</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/funny-little-glitch-with-elevator/12249</link>
    <description>Ok, I didn&#39;t see this posted anywhere yet, so I decided I&#39;d put it up. It&#39;s just kind of funny, it doesn&#39;t affect the game in any way.

In Unforeseen Consequences, at the part where you come to the elevator where you are supposed to push the call button and send the three scientists plummeting to their deaths so that the crash busts the door open, it is possible to do a little sequence breaking sort of thing. If you find a physics object and throw it through the glass, you can advance without making the elevator crash and kill its occupants. The next loading point is right on the other side of the door, and the game evidently assumes you had to have crashed the elevator, because it suddenly appears in pieces at the bottom of the shaft. It doesn&#39;t assume that the scientists died, however, so you can go down there and have a chat with them, where they&#39;ll tell you things like &quot;It&#39;s about time!&quot; and &quot;Let me know if you see a bathroom.&quot;  :smiley: 

[img]https://cloud-2.steampowered.com/ugc/558719383366874196/B3DA602F8059548855B7E6E345E8418117C672B3/[/img]

Well, I thought it was funny anyway.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2013 05:54:02 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>In-game Issues (Mod)</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/funny-little-glitch-with-elevator/12249.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Funny little glitch with elevator</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Orpheon]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Ok, I didn’t see this posted anywhere yet, so I decided I’d put it up. It’s just kind of funny, it doesn’t affect the game in any way.</p>
<p>In Unforeseen Consequences, at the part where you come to the elevator where you are supposed to push the call button and send the three scientists plummeting to their deaths so that the crash busts the door open, it is possible to do a little sequence breaking sort of thing. If you find a physics object and throw it through the glass, you can advance without making the elevator crash and kill its occupants. The next loading point is right on the other side of the door, and the game evidently assumes you had to have crashed the elevator, because it suddenly appears in pieces at the bottom of the shaft. It doesn’t assume that the scientists died, however, so you can go down there and have a chat with them, where they’ll tell you things like “It’s about time!” and “Let me know if you see a bathroom.”  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/smiley.png?v=9" title=":smiley:" class="emoji" alt=":smiley:"></p>
<p><span alt="" class="broken-image" title="This image is broken"><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-unlink svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#unlink"></use></svg></span></p>
<p>Well, I thought it was funny anyway.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/funny-little-glitch-with-elevator/12249/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/funny-little-glitch-with-elevator/12249/1</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2013 05:54:02 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12249-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/funny-little-glitch-with-elevator/12249.rss">Funny little glitch with elevator</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
