<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Good mods let down by certain things</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/good-mods-let-down-by-certain-things/1075</link>
    <description>A while back I downloaded Portal :stuck_out_tongue: relude since people had been saying it was a good mod. I agreed that the level design and story was pretty good, but the one problem I had with this mod was the fact that they didn&#39;t even bother to put in voice-acting, they just used text-to-speech like Microsoft Sam. It just would have been so much better if they&#39;d used real people instead of some crappy program. 

So anyone else feel the same about this mod or have any other mods where it was let down by one thing?</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 24 Sep 2009 20:22:04 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Technology and Gaming</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/good-mods-let-down-by-certain-things/1075.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Good mods let down by certain things</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Grey_Acumen]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I’m resurrecting this thread to put Strider Mountain into this list. The game is great, very challenging, an interesting plot, seems fairly long(some 17 chapters?), and some very interesting cutscenes, yet despite this, I find that a lot of the game I feel I’m grinding. The enemies are ridiculously accurate for a HL2 game, and it feels like they never stop coming and it doesn’t make it feel action packed, just tedious. On top of that, even though the cut scenes feel extremely polished, the 3rd person perspective keeps breaking immersion and pulls me out of the character. Did they learn nothing from HL and HL2?<br>
Even worse than the cutscenes are the way that the path ahead is opened up to you. Where in HL1 and HL2, if your path ahead was blocked, you were almost always the one who unblocked it. In Strider mountain, 90% of the time, your path will be blocked by a simple locked door that will only be opened by the combine coming through to try to kill you. BUT this is only triggered when you try to go through a completely DIFFERENT locked door. It’s like playing a Zelda game where the door of a dungeon wont unlock until you’ve killed every enemy in that room except that its done in EVERY ROOM and the rooms are BORING.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/good-mods-let-down-by-certain-things/1075/61">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/good-mods-let-down-by-certain-things/1075/61</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 24 Sep 2009 20:22:04 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-1075-61</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/good-mods-let-down-by-certain-things/1075.rss">Good mods let down by certain things</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Good mods let down by certain things</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Grey_Acumen]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Unknowncode">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/u/edb3f5/40.png" class="avatar"> Unknowncode:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>To be honest, the only thing that people seem to complain about Radiotor:HwC is the gay relationship part. Honestly if people are that petty that they won’t play a game just because you’re supposed to be in a gay relationship, then that’s just childish. And this whole thing bowt “Oh I can’t empathise with it” is rubbish. You can empathise with Gordon Freeman can’t you? After all, he’s a 27 year old physicist who fights aliens and can bring down an oppresive society just by himself. So why are people unable to empathise with the characters in HwC? I really don’t understand how you can let prejudices get in the way of gameplay.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Empathizing? Who said anything about that shit? I said IMMERSION; the act of being able to get INTO the role.<br>
Gordon Freeman is a completely hollow shell. There is NOTHING to empathize WITH. The object is to be able to INSERT yourself into that role. You don’t become Gordon Freeman, HE becomes YOU. This is very important for FPS since the gameplay style thrusts you into that role automatically.<br>
In Radiator, a very major life decision of the main character is strictly defined from the very beginning. That can be prohibitive to immersion no matter what the particular life decision is.<br>
When the game mechanics and story elements are working at cross purposes, that means something is wrong, either with the story being told, or the game mechanics.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Patonki">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/p/e79b87/40.png" class="avatar"> Patonki:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Well, I took it as there is no clear “winning” in the game. You can intrepet the endings as you please. There is no emphasis on the repressed memories ending being the “correct” ending.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I actually clarified my point better on the <a href="https://forums.blackmesasource.com/showthread.php?t=1168&amp;page=5" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Radiator Thread</a> but I’ll quote the excerpt from my post that addresses your issue.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Grey Acumen">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Grey Acumen:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Now here, it’s pointed out that part of the object of the game IS to actually question whether or not the relationship even SHOULD survive. That’s great and all, except that there isn’t any question about it now. As I pointed out already, if a relationship requires repressing memories instead of talking them out, it’s not a relationship. The game has now shot itself in the foot as the method to REALLY winning is to NOT PLAY. For an art piece, this is a brilliant concept, but even the most novice game developer should be able to recognize the fatal flaw in designing a game that encourages you to NOT play it.</p>
<p>The fundamental underlying problem is shown pretty well right here. The developer focused too much on keeping the ending reward/consequence from being “trite” and forgot one of the fundamental principles of game design is for effort of the player to be REWARDED and lack of effort or skill to be met with CONSEQUENCES. If he really wanted to show that divorce could actually be considered the “good ending” then getting that ending should have required skill and effort as well or instead.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/good-mods-let-down-by-certain-things/1075/60">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/good-mods-let-down-by-certain-things/1075/60</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 06 Sep 2009 06:14:18 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-1075-60</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/good-mods-let-down-by-certain-things/1075.rss">Good mods let down by certain things</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Good mods let down by certain things</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Patonki]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Grey Acumen">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Grey Acumen:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>BLAH BLAH BLAH<br>
That is only a minor issue compared to the flawed foundation on which the entire HwC section is based. In order to “win” you have to BLAH BLAH BLAh</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Well, I took it as there is no clear “winning” in the game. You can intrepet the endings as you please. There is no emphasis on the repressed memories ending being the “correct” ending.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/good-mods-let-down-by-certain-things/1075/59">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/good-mods-let-down-by-certain-things/1075/59</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 05 Sep 2009 11:34:02 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-1075-59</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/good-mods-let-down-by-certain-things/1075.rss">Good mods let down by certain things</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Good mods let down by certain things</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Unknowncode]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>To be honest, the only thing that people seem to complain about Radiotor:HwC is the gay relationship part. Honestly if people are that petty that they won’t play a game just because you’re supposed to be in a gay relationship, then that’s just childish. And this whole thing bowt “Oh I can’t empathise with it” is rubbish. You can empathise with Gordon Freeman can’t you? After all, he’s a 27 year old physicist who fights aliens and can bring down an oppresive society just by himself. So why are people unable to empathise with the characters in HwC? I really don’t understand how you can let prejudices get in the way of gameplay.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/good-mods-let-down-by-certain-things/1075/58">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/good-mods-let-down-by-certain-things/1075/58</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 05 Sep 2009 10:33:36 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-1075-58</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/good-mods-let-down-by-certain-things/1075.rss">Good mods let down by certain things</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Good mods let down by certain things</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Grey_Acumen]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Oh, this looks like a good place to bitch about one of my favorite mods to hate.</p>
<p>Radiator 1-2: Polaris and Handle with Care</p>
<p>This game was perhaps the freshest takes I’ve seen on an FPS. Polaris was excellent, though slightly marred by the fact that I felt absolutely no connection to any of the characters, yet I was given the impression that the section was supposed to have some sort of emotional impact.</p>
<p>The Handle with Care section is the part that bugs me the most though, but I’m going to have to go into spoilers to explain it:[COLOR=‘Black’]<br>
The fundamental premise of HwC seems to be that you are tasked with repressing troubled memories inside your head during a marriage counseling session in order for your relationship with your gay lover to survive.<br>
The first issue I had was that a male specific name was used for the main character. There are a number of gender neutral names (like Lee/Leigh, Casey, Kim, Parker, Alex/Alyx, etc) that would have allowed the gender to be interpreted by the player; either playing as a girl in a straight relationship or as a guy in a gay relationship. I have nothing against any person for being homosexual, but at the same time I have no interest in supporting homosexuality as a lifestyle. As a result, this issue made it pretty much impossible to immerse myself in the character I was supposed to be playing as.<br>
That is only a minor issue compared to the flawed foundation on which the entire HwC section is based. In order to “win” you have to repress memories by moving boxes to shelves where they are sealed off. If you break any of these boxes, it results in an outburst during the counseling session, and if repeated often enough, results in the relationship ending.<br>
There is no possible way that a person could have a healthy relationship that requires repressing memories. A healthy relationship is based on communication, and only a complete quack in the field of relation counseling would think otherwise, yet throughout the entire game you are praised by the counselor for repression and chastised for any outbursts. I was left doubting and rejecting the entire premise of both the game setting and game play involved.<br>
Ultimately Radiator:Handle with Care shows itself as being highly polished with unique and well implemented metaphorical gameplay mechanics that could have been truly thought provoking , but since the metaphor upon which the gameplay is based is erroneous, the gameplay goes from being intuitive to counter intuitive.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/good-mods-let-down-by-certain-things/1075/57">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/good-mods-let-down-by-certain-things/1075/57</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 29 Aug 2009 08:49:27 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-1075-57</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/good-mods-let-down-by-certain-things/1075.rss">Good mods let down by certain things</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Good mods let down by certain things</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[raw_bean]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Dias">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/d/4491bb/40.png" class="avatar"> Dias:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>You’re saying his writing is good before Minerva, are you agreeing with me or what?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I said I’d <span class="bbcode-i">always </span>found his writing good, before and including Minerva.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/good-mods-let-down-by-certain-things/1075/56">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/good-mods-let-down-by-certain-things/1075/56</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 29 Aug 2009 01:53:14 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-1075-56</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/good-mods-let-down-by-certain-things/1075.rss">Good mods let down by certain things</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Good mods let down by certain things</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Fungus]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>In a comment in one of the pics near the botton he says that the lighting &amp; skybox is placeholder. I hope that turns out alright, I liked the first version of it.<br>
BTT: Mistake of Pythagoras (MoP), was a cool mod, but didnt actualy put anything ‘new’ in. Everything was stock HL2 and from what I can tell, the big block enemies are just brushes. But I could be wrong.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/good-mods-let-down-by-certain-things/1075/55">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/good-mods-let-down-by-certain-things/1075/55</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 21 Aug 2009 16:44:24 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-1075-55</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/good-mods-let-down-by-certain-things/1075.rss">Good mods let down by certain things</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Good mods let down by certain things</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Dias]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>While the maps may be higher poly, the texturing and lighting is where the real improvements need to be in order to make it easier to follow.</p>
<p>Aside from that, I don’t really see why the mod needs to be remade at all. But I’m not complaining.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/good-mods-let-down-by-certain-things/1075/54">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/good-mods-let-down-by-certain-things/1075/54</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 21 Aug 2009 06:16:44 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-1075-54</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/good-mods-let-down-by-certain-things/1075.rss">Good mods let down by certain things</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Good mods let down by certain things</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Repzik]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Dias">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/d/4491bb/40.png" class="avatar"> Dias:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>My biggest problem with Dear Esther is that I couldn’t figure out where to go. I got lost and wandered around for sometime before getting bored and noclipping. There were a few neat sights, but there wasn’t any contrast between one rocky wall formation and another leaving me with no idea where to go.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Hope you’ve seen <a href="https://www.littlelostpoly.co.uk/devblog/" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">this</a>.</p>
<p>Dear Esther’s maps are being completely remade by a Robert Briscoe (who I believe worked on Mirror’s Edge or something). So that won’t be a problem for much longer.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/good-mods-let-down-by-certain-things/1075/53">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/good-mods-let-down-by-certain-things/1075/53</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 21 Aug 2009 06:08:35 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-1075-53</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/good-mods-let-down-by-certain-things/1075.rss">Good mods let down by certain things</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Good mods let down by certain things</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Dias]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>There aren’t that many then, and there isn’t now. Dystopia is overrated, and under lit.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/good-mods-let-down-by-certain-things/1075/52">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/good-mods-let-down-by-certain-things/1075/52</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 21 Aug 2009 05:33:32 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-1075-52</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/good-mods-let-down-by-certain-things/1075.rss">Good mods let down by certain things</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Good mods let down by certain things</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Right4Dead]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I played Dystopia and it just wasn’t my thing. I loved going into the internet tron style but in the end I just sucked to much and there weren’t any servers back then.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/good-mods-let-down-by-certain-things/1075/51">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/good-mods-let-down-by-certain-things/1075/51</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 20 Aug 2009 13:25:55 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-1075-51</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/good-mods-let-down-by-certain-things/1075.rss">Good mods let down by certain things</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Good mods let down by certain things</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Dias]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="raw_bean">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/r/439d5e/40.png" class="avatar"> raw_bean:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I disagree, I thought Adam Foster’s writing (going back before Minerva to Someplace Else) was always worth reading.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>You’re saying his writing is good before Minerva, are you agreeing with me or what?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/good-mods-let-down-by-certain-things/1075/50">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/good-mods-let-down-by-certain-things/1075/50</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 20 Aug 2009 08:17:46 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-1075-50</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/good-mods-let-down-by-certain-things/1075.rss">Good mods let down by certain things</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Good mods let down by certain things</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Master_Chef]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Of course, Tamerain might think it’s shit, but Tam- erm, Hollow-WTF will think it’s the best mod ever.</p>
<p>I mean, he is that desperate for acceptance from people he’ll never meet.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/good-mods-let-down-by-certain-things/1075/49">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/good-mods-let-down-by-certain-things/1075/49</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 19 Aug 2009 04:06:37 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-1075-49</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/good-mods-let-down-by-certain-things/1075.rss">Good mods let down by certain things</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Good mods let down by certain things</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Collision]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Tamerain">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/t/47e85d/40.png" class="avatar"> Tamerain:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>overrated piece of shit.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>You may think it’s overrated, but the 10’s of thousands of us who played it think it’s a great mod.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/good-mods-let-down-by-certain-things/1075/48">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/good-mods-let-down-by-certain-things/1075/48</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 19 Aug 2009 01:29:17 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-1075-48</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/good-mods-let-down-by-certain-things/1075.rss">Good mods let down by certain things</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Good mods let down by certain things</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[raw_bean]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I disagree, I thought Adam Foster’s writing (going back before Minerva to Someplace Else) was always worth reading.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/good-mods-let-down-by-certain-things/1075/47">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/good-mods-let-down-by-certain-things/1075/47</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 18 Aug 2009 14:38:52 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-1075-47</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/good-mods-let-down-by-certain-things/1075.rss">Good mods let down by certain things</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Good mods let down by certain things</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Dias]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>He does have a point that you shouldn’t be forced to choose between breaking the flow of the game just to get the plot. If you’re able to go back and read it again, then it’s a bit more excusable, but Minerva didn’t. Not that the plot was worth reading to begin with.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/good-mods-let-down-by-certain-things/1075/46">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/good-mods-let-down-by-certain-things/1075/46</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 15 Aug 2009 08:12:42 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-1075-46</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/good-mods-let-down-by-certain-things/1075.rss">Good mods let down by certain things</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Good mods let down by certain things</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Aze]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="JohnKiller118">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 JohnKiller118:</div>
<blockquote>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">MINERVA-</span>…um… well, it would be nice if there was like a datalog for all the AI Bitch’s <span class="bbcode-i">(that’s what I call her)</span> messages. It’s annoying when I’m in a gun fight and suddenly I get a two paragraph long message that’s only up there for 5 seconds.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Uhm mate…have u ever heard about the “Pause” button? It’s on your keyboard and it works at the 90% of the games  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/wink.png?v=9" title=":wink:" class="emoji" alt=":wink:">  just like in minerva…I know cause I used it!</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/good-mods-let-down-by-certain-things/1075/45">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/good-mods-let-down-by-certain-things/1075/45</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 14 Aug 2009 21:12:35 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-1075-45</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/good-mods-let-down-by-certain-things/1075.rss">Good mods let down by certain things</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Good mods let down by certain things</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[OldDirtyBastard]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="mattemuse">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/m/dc4da7/40.png" class="avatar"> mattemuse:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Neotokyo, while an impressive effort, was somewhat let down by its lack of user-friendliness. Taking down your forums for a week starting the day the game was made available has to be one of the stupidest release decisions I’ve ever heard of. And now that the forums are back  up, there is still virtually no useful information for new players or anyone else available - a good mod let down by its community (including the developers) it seems to me. They’ve probably driven away the majority of their user base already.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Yeah, it’s like starting to live in another country, where locals speak in a language you don’t know.<br>
Sad to say, I was very positive towards it from the very beginning.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/good-mods-let-down-by-certain-things/1075/44">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/good-mods-let-down-by-certain-things/1075/44</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 14 Aug 2009 20:37:23 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-1075-44</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/good-mods-let-down-by-certain-things/1075.rss">Good mods let down by certain things</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Good mods let down by certain things</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Dias]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>My biggest problem with Dear Esther is that I couldn’t figure out where to go. I got lost and wandered around for sometime before getting bored and noclipping. There were a few neat sights, but there wasn’t any contrast between one rocky wall formation and another leaving me with no idea where to go.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/good-mods-let-down-by-certain-things/1075/43">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/good-mods-let-down-by-certain-things/1075/43</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 13 Aug 2009 04:52:27 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-1075-43</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/good-mods-let-down-by-certain-things/1075.rss">Good mods let down by certain things</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Good mods let down by certain things</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[DinoThrasher]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Dr. Perky">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Dr. Perky:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Does a game need guns or heavy violence to be good, and how in any way is it like Oblivion? Dear Esther was great because it was a change of pace from every other mod out there the concept is great, the setting is eerie and the voice acting was perfect. Don’t bad mouth a mod just because you found it boring because you can’t spend two minutes without shooting something in a game.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Agreed, Dear Esther was great because while it didn’t have heavy fighting, it had exploration, great narrated story, and atmosphere, which is something few games now a days do well I feel. Sure it wasn’t heavy on the gameplay, but it was relaxing, creative, original, different, and, as I said, had a lot of atmosphere which, in my opinion, allows the boring, cliche, and repetitive gameplay perfect reason to go take a vacation.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/good-mods-let-down-by-certain-things/1075/42">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/good-mods-let-down-by-certain-things/1075/42</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 13 Aug 2009 03:07:25 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-1075-42</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/good-mods-let-down-by-certain-things/1075.rss">Good mods let down by certain things</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Good mods let down by certain things</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Someonerandm]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Dr. Perky">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Dr. Perky:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>no the translation was fine its the presentation it was done entirely with a text-to-speech program so it sounds horrid.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>No I mean the creator couldn’t speak english very well (Listen to the audio commentary). He can write and understand it fine.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/good-mods-let-down-by-certain-things/1075/41">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/good-mods-let-down-by-certain-things/1075/41</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 12 Aug 2009 22:45:26 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-1075-41</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/good-mods-let-down-by-certain-things/1075.rss">Good mods let down by certain things</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Good mods let down by certain things</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Dr_Perky]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>no the translation was fine its the presentation it was done entirely with a text-to-speech program so it sounds horrid.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/good-mods-let-down-by-certain-things/1075/40">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/good-mods-let-down-by-certain-things/1075/40</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 12 Aug 2009 20:04:54 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-1075-40</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/good-mods-let-down-by-certain-things/1075.rss">Good mods let down by certain things</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Good mods let down by certain things</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Someonerandm]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>The reason portal prelude has sucky voice acting was because the creator was French I think and has bad english.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/good-mods-let-down-by-certain-things/1075/39">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/good-mods-let-down-by-certain-things/1075/39</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 12 Aug 2009 19:48:54 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-1075-39</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/good-mods-let-down-by-certain-things/1075.rss">Good mods let down by certain things</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Good mods let down by certain things</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[geekofalltrades]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Coolm4n">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/c/b2d939/40.png" class="avatar"> Coolm4n:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Most of the mods I’ve played so far were let down by a bad voice acting. “Ravenholm” was the most shocking one. I wonder what they were thinking when they recorded their audio files. :retard:</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Haha, I agree.  The one that stands out for me is “Awakening.”  And to think that their ModDB profile at one time claimed they had “professional voice acting…”</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/good-mods-let-down-by-certain-things/1075/38">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/good-mods-let-down-by-certain-things/1075/38</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 12 Aug 2009 19:09:58 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-1075-38</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/good-mods-let-down-by-certain-things/1075.rss">Good mods let down by certain things</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Good mods let down by certain things</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Dr_Perky]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="bob">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/b/ea666f/40.png" class="avatar"> bob:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>The only mod I can consider to be not that much fun is Dear Esther. There are no guns in the mod, only a voice talking to you and exploration to be done. It’s like Oblivion. On the other hand, there are good mods like Minerva (which is my favorite one so far), Riot Act, Awakening, and Rock 24. I know that Black Mesa will be up there with Minerva.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Does a game need guns or heavy violence to be good, and how in any way is it like Oblivion? Dear Esther was great because it was a change of pace from every other mod out there the concept is great, the setting is eerie and the voice acting was perfect. Don’t bad mouth a mod just because you found it boring because you can’t spend two minutes without shooting something in a game.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/good-mods-let-down-by-certain-things/1075/37">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/good-mods-let-down-by-certain-things/1075/37</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 12 Aug 2009 18:39:06 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-1075-37</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/good-mods-let-down-by-certain-things/1075.rss">Good mods let down by certain things</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
