<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>suggestion: HL:DM stile co-op for MP</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/suggestion-hl-dm-stile-co-op-for-mp/15282</link>
    <description>Ok this is highly likely to be in the wrong section but here is a suggestion for a co-op mode that would be pretty easy to do.


BM: co-op
info: co-op based maps for the multiplayer mode joined by anyone but with a single team each map would have an over arching objective.




FIRst map concept


the barracks
discription: defend the surface guard barracks from all hell breaking loose.

team: BMFS (security guards)
objective: survive 20 waves of hell defending an armory on the surface while trying to break into a motor pool to escape.


map info this map would be hybrid of the armory map and the car park map from surface tension with players spawning in the armory with shotguns unlocked at the start. players must defend a few NPC scientists that re in the armory (Can not be harmed by the players for anti greifing), while also helping an NPC guard secure floors of the car park every few waves once they make it to the top a working vehicle is found and you can escape.

map layout: players spawn in a 2 story barracks. on the top floor is an armory, bed area (door access to armory and stairs, spawn room), bath rooms, and roof access. the first floor has an office area, restrooms and 4 entry points. out side there is a small &quot;yard area&quot; and one other buildign with large walls all the way around, a north and south road access via double gates which you can not use. the second building is an office building which you can not access at the start. to the east is the car park which you also can not access at the start do to a 30 foot concrete wall.



waves and gameplay:

wave one: spawn wave, this wave starts 30 seconds after the map is loaded the first wave is simply headcrabs and hound eyes teleporting in, from this point on waves will spawn 2 minutes from each other with exceptions of the 10th, 15th, and 20th.
wave two: doors are broken down from a building next to the barracks allowing access from it spawns zombies and headcrabs random teleportation continues.

wave three: more spawns from teh building though they are mostly zombies jumping from the second story (players can not access do to a barricade)

wave four: houndeyes come in from a gate on the main road (similar ot level gates they players must use in campaign)

wave five:  armory access unlocked vorts start random teleportation more zombies from the nearby building. (armory is unlocked in parts when first opened only the shotgun spawn is &quot;unlocked&quot; with all others being blocked by a keypad which a scientist is trying to brute force do to the head of the guard being dead or something. to to explain why things are delayed)

wave six: wave five with more vorts and less headcrabs/zombies.

wave seven: right side of map gets a hole blown in it this is the access point to the car parks entry, from this spews zombies, a dead soldier with a grenade spawn is found on the road. (East side)

wave eight: more randomly teleporting vorts.

wave nine: zombies from the car park tunnel, hound eyes from the road entry, grenades unlocked in armory.

wave ten: wave is started by a player activating a radio in the barracks as soldiers are calling for survivor locations. wave starts with a group of hostile soldiers from the road entry, followed by some random teleport vorts and then ending with more soldiers.

wave eleven: soldiers repelling in, and comming from the car park, first level of the car park is activated has a few mp5 spawns.

wave twelve: satchel charges unlocked in armory, IFV attacks from main road.

wave thirteen: mortar strike and random teleportation.

wave fourteen: first alien grunts teleport in on the roof next to the barracks. vorts random teleport into the yard around the buildings.

wave fifteen: players are told to head to the car park and clear out the second floor, main hostiles are soldiers. RPG spawn in car park activated.

wave sixteen: mortar strike blows a few holes in the barracks opening it up, and breaking open a crossbow spawn in the armory but also destroying the shotgun spawn. two tanks spawn on this wave with support infantry from both road entry points.

wave seventeen: soldiers spawn in mass and siege from the road part way through the wave manta&#39;s strafe the road killing anything on it, another will strafe the office building allowing access to the second floor and destroying part of its roof.

wave eighteen: xen military attack lots of alien grunts and vorts. a manta will act as a teleport in vehicle taking it down will stop the hostile spawns (only part that would require things outside of scripting, mapping, and voice work).

wave nineteen: top level of the car park is opened a few soldiers are their but the are not hostile with a radio broadcast coming in asking for help, main hostiles of this wave are zecu and a few xen soldiers is the easiest wave sense wave nine, soldiers state they are abandoning their post and will evacuate you guys if you help defend their osprey as it fuels on the roof.

wave twenty: the last wave the scientists from the armory flee to the landed osprey found on the last wave. trigger a fuel pump to defend them, simply prevent xen forces from blowing the pump to win. on this wave a helicopter will spawn near the end but will not be hostile. radio chatter from the osprey reveals that the operation has fallen apart everyone is on their own, and the copter is giving cover fire to anyone that they can. (Copter only stays in the area for 30 seconds).

this wave is brutal with the players having to guard a point that is away from most ammo spawns, and with large numbers of xen forces. your only hint on the osprey and fuel trucks health will be if they are on fire or not. and well this map does have a bad ending with the fuel and osprey exploding taking the hole roof with them (implied all players on the roof die and the map ends) but if the players make it through their reward is a &quot;Evacuation&quot; via osprey for everyone that &quot;enters it&quot; (E to use camera set to its door get to watch it take off before screen goes black with [sector A security team: status safe... for now])


armory unlock tally

shotguns: wave, 5 with armroy access (destroyed wave sixteen along with ammo spawns)

grenades: tunnels wave  seven, armory wave ten

satchel charges: armory wave twelve

mp5: soldiers spawns all waves with soldiers (no armory access) has a few spawns in car park.

revolver: armory wave twelve

RPG: wave 15 car park in the back of a truck with infinite ammo crates. armory wave sixteen when a crate with them is blown open.(metal crate)

crossbow: access blown open wave 16.

snarks: hidden in a vent access as early as wave 15

mp5 grenades: infinite crate on roof with osprey, near it is a few 9mm ammo spawns.






note: teh bases of this idea is to be a single map that is co-op focused, I based this on one of the more complex ones I have seen in HL2 :smiley: M before the servers that hosted it died.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 08 Oct 2017 06:45:28 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>The Cafeteria</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/suggestion-hl-dm-stile-co-op-for-mp/15282.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>suggestion: HL:DM stile co-op for MP</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[darkone]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>WAVE FIFTEENTH: minor setback. wave starts with a military commander talking over a radio,</p>
<p>commander: (unit name) what is going on down there.<br>
soldier A(from the group with you):<em>rushes to a radio in teh room you are in</em> we where ambushed sir just as we rescued these civilians the damn aliens or what ever these things are ambushed us.<br>
Commander: understood: arlight, search for survivors and hold that point.(another unit) will be on the way shortly hold out for them and we will get you guys out of there.</p>
<p>wave enemies: during this wave, your main enemies are a few headcrabs, straggler vorts and a single A-grunt.</p>
<p>WAVE SIXTEEN: underseige, none stop teleportation, this time it isn’t as random coming from the tram station, break room, and shooting range areas. this wave is the hardest xen wave in teh set.</p>
<p>WAVE SEVENTEEN: military tango, soldiers arive via tram at the train station, they instantly start evacuating the other soldiers but do not allow the players to evacuate (invisible wall + soldier on tram with .50 call that will open fire if the players get to close).<br>
SOLDIER: we only have room for our wounded at the moment so stay back we will be back for you.</p>
<p>wave starts after the soldiers leave, it is a slightly weaker xen seige with a few more A-grunts.</p>
<p>WAVE EIGHTEEN: powereded down, the power goes out again, killing the turrets if you had any active (killing not just deactivating power surge and a big one, guess the cause will give a hint its freeman blowing of a garge) with the power out several security locks to doors you could not activate go down causing the doors to open unleashing a large amount of zombies on the players these zombies are mostly ZECU and the rooms they come from look like medical stations where they where locked into in hopes that they could be saved later.</p>
<p>wave NINETEEN: SEIGE PART TWO, another xen seige this time more powerful then the last do to the lack of defense or allied soldiers. this is the last true wave and it will kick your asses with everything from vorts teleporting in on the .50 call nest to A-grunts breaking holes into walls reducing your cover in choke points. this wave is a siege and even has oen big new feature A-grunts throwing snark nests that explode on contact with the ground dealing impact damage and spawning 2-3 snarks.</p>
<p>WAVE TWENTY: safe at last, this actually is not a true wave accruing 3/4s the way through the siege wave. This wave has the soldiers arive on their armored tram. (its really jsut a two care BMS tram with metal plates covering the windows, and 3 .50 calls one mounted facing the trams arival point, one on the front and one on the back. their are 5 soldiers on it, 2 exit the tram and start calling for the players saying the following.</p>
<p>SOLDIER: YO CIVILIANS IF ANY OF YOU ARE ALIVE MAKE YOUR WAY TO THE TRAM YOUR CHARIOT AWAITS!</p>
<p>the game ends when all players either get on the tram or die (respawns are disabled on wave 19) this map has 2 endings both of which are of the tram pulling away with different dialog.</p>
<p>the ending depends on how many soldiers survived to be evacuated on wave 17, if none escaped you get the death ending. (if none escaped you get dialog on that wave with the soldiers asking for HECU survivors when they get none tehy state they are not offerised to pick you up yet and leave, if they get survivors they do what I mentioned)</p>
<p>SURVIVAL ENDING</p>
<p>scientist: thanks for saving us back there we though that we where doomed.</p>
<p>soldier: don’t thank us yet.</p>
<p>scientist: why not?</p>
<p>soldier: orders are to detain survivors for questioning, that said after what you guys have been through I am sure they will let you go.</p>
<p>DEATH ENDING</p>
<p><em>gun fire on tram</em></p>
<p>soldier: This is ECHO-3 Juliet to command, civilian contacts have been silenced moving to next objective.</p>
<p>Command: understood Echo-3 Juliet, your orders are to head to the airfield and help logistics, apparently they are haven some problems with the uglys out there.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/suggestion-hl-dm-stile-co-op-for-mp/15282/12">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/suggestion-hl-dm-stile-co-op-for-mp/15282/12</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 08 Oct 2017 06:45:28 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-15282-12</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/suggestion-hl-dm-stile-co-op-for-mp/15282.rss">suggestion: HL:DM stile co-op for MP</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>suggestion: HL:DM stile co-op for MP</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[darkone]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I’m bored so here is one last map idea. I can’t figure out hammer to save my life so these will all remain text for likely ever.</p>
<p>MAP IDEA THREE: HORDE (this maybe a multi map item)<br>
map info: as a small group of scientists survive wave after wave of zombies and xen wildlife until the military arrives.<br>
note: hecu are friendly on this map.</p>
<p>map layout: players do not have full run of the map but every few waves zombies will break down a door or a wall. players start with access to only a hallway and a security check point that has a crowbar spawn and glock spawn inside. (you do not spawn armed, so waiting for the gun and melee to re spawn is key to surviving in fact by the end of wave 1 the crowbar will have respawned upto 8 times and the pistol 4 on average) (30 second respawn for pistol, 15 for crowbar, pistol ammo spawns near pistol) sorry for that ramble. the map is an office section with most of it locked down or baricading will say what can be accessed with what wave.</p>
<p>map special: no suit on players. you can not gain armor and your health is capped at 50. so the suit chargers and batteries are usless for you but the batteries do have a use at wave 10 when the main security station is opened.</p>
<p>MAP START: over radio.</p>
<p>game time set: we got hostiles.<br>
SOLDIER: Alright we here you guys loud and clear just stick tight and do not leave the office complex we have orders to shoot on sight for anyone outside of evacuation points so keep your heads down and stay in that office block. our ETA is 45 miks.</p>
<p>WAVE ONE: starts with zombies busting 3 double doors on the hall players spawn with access to, wave has a good number of headcrab zombies and headcrabs but most are weakened or wounded to cominsate for most of the players being unarmed.<br>
access open: main hallway, office block A, and food court hallway.<br>
weapon access opens: pistol ammo spawns in office block A, a battery spawn in office block A, dead secuirty guard with revolver ammo in main hallway.(ammo is useful at wave 5)</p>
<p>wave two: foodcourt bust, zombies break down door leading to food court large horde compaired to other early game waves.<br>
access open: food court, kitchen, freezer.<br>
spawns active: 2 battery spawns in freezer, 2 pistol ammo spawns on a dead guard sitting in the food court, one grenade spawn in the kitchen bellow the sink.</p>
<p>wave three: first random teleportation wave mostly hound eyes and headcrabs. no section of the map is safe.</p>
<p>WAVE FOUR: MAIN OFFICE BREAK: an explosion accourse at a barricade that was blocking access to teh main office area, barricade is broken with gibs of a security guard found more headcrab zombies though not as many as from teh food court stage. the main offices are a large open floor area with cubicles all over as these are the destroyible prop ones this area can end up looking completely different after teh wave.<br>
access open: maintence vents, main office (duh), tram access point (extremely useful later)</p>
<p>WAVE FIVE: second floor access is opened with a secuirty guard and scientist enter from the food court area, they are followed by a bullsquid. during this wave mroe random teleportation more vorts then anything now.<br>
access: second floor of food court, second floor office hallway, elevator shafts (one has a lift in it, the other is open with the burning wreck of a lift just out of sight bellow.<br>
spawn points: revolver spawn point. (secuirty guard will set down their revolver in the secuirty office you started in, while the scientist they where with tends to them, neither can be killed).</p>
<p>WAVE SIX: more zombies, they bust from the second floor office hallway and arrive via a tram from the tram entry point. (not much of a threat.)</p>
<p>WAVE SEVEN: more random teleportation, this time it is all vorts, while they do not teleport into teh secuirty office they tend to aim for the high ground like a balcony around the main offices (second floor access) and the food court.</p>
<p>WAVE EIGHT: full second floor access: zombies bust down the last barricade which was blocking access to the rest of the second floor. the hole second floor has a large horde of headcrab zombies. including a nice little joke where a group of headcrab zombies are eating a dead bullsquid.<br>
access: main security office, top floor offices, top floor restrooms, top floor balcony above main office, top floor vent access.<br>
spawn access: shotgun spawn (security office), grenades (2 near a dead guard in top floor mens restroom)<br>
special: main security office, in this office is a place you can put suit batteries placing batteries in these slots does one of 4 things depending on the slot.<br>
slot one: activates ceiling turrets in main office. (lasts 2 minutes, do not fire on players, scientists or soldiers)<br>
slot two: activates ceiling turrets in food court. (lasts 2 minutes, do not fire on players scientists or soldiers)<br>
slot three: turns on teh one working elevator allowing access to a small area above the offices, hostile military equipment is there but so is the only 40mm spawn and MP5 spawn. (you can not destroy the military sentries in the area.)<br>
slot four: opens access to the armory in the security station. (where the shotguns, shotgun ammo, and more revolvers spawn)</p>
<p>slot one and two are temporary while slot three and 4 are perminate. so far there are only 3 batteries on the map and they do not respawn.</p>
<p>WAVE NINE: HOLE IN THE WALL: an explosion happens blowing a hole in the wall to the east of the map. this hole is in the wall of the foodcourt and its top floor. from this comes more zombies, half way through the wave vorts also spwan in at random locations.<br>
access opened:  storage room, maintenance hallway, office D, (office D can be seen through most of the map but the hallway to it has collapsed on both floors)</p>
<p>WAVE TEN: RESCUED AT LAST, OH WAIT. military soldiers arive at the tram station just 4 soldiers one being a medic. (I should mention their is only two healing points and both are in the security stations). they are not hostile but the moment they arrive random teleportation happen including a bullsquid falling onto the tram causing it to partially come off the rails. the soldiers will fortify the tram entry point which is a bottle neck. giving the players a good cover point. (as they have mp5’s with grenade launchers and the players only have shotguns, unless they activated the challenge then maybe one or 2 has the mp5 with a few 40s)</p>
<p>note: during this wave the NPC scientist and guard in the smaller secuirty office are killed by a hound eye this can not be stopped as the players spawn moved to the main security office on wave eight.</p>
<p>WAVE ELEVEN: change of plans<br>
opening: VOX: ALL SECTORY A, PERSONEL, REPORT TO, MAIN SECURITY CHECKPOINT CHARLEY<br>
soldiers move in and blow open a door: you guys better follow us unless you want to be shot.</p>
<p>wave starts after that, first mobile wave players follow the soldiers through a hallway to security section main hostiles are zombies, vorts and a few houndeyes.</p>
<p>WAVE TWELVE: the group arives at another tram stop and the players are tasked with finding away to power it for the tram to be activated. this wave has two parts part one is going back over the area you just ran through to grab 3 suit batteries to power an emergency generator at the tram station and part two is protecting the soldiers against zombies that are comming from a section of teh office you can not access (barricade ramp zombies walking and falling over something that you can not cross. easy defense but readies for later)</p>
<p>WAVE THIRTEEN: into the tram, a two car tram arives at the station allowing players to board it. the soldiers split with the medic getting into teh back one and the other three into the front they then proceed to shoot out the front and rear windows on the tramp. this wave is mobile with players having to survive in the tram as they move to the main security checkpoint. the main hostile are vorts, bull squids and 2 alien grunts.</p>
<p>WAVE FOURTEEN: arival(map change?) players arive at the check point which has a large number of soldier protecting it they order the players into “safe” room, once all players are there the power goes out and gun fire is heard as random teleportation starts, once the power comes on most the soldiers are dead and the players task is changed from being safe to surviving the now overun military check point.</p>
<p>area note: teh main secuirty check point is a large area with a tram access point, a small office, shooting range… just imagine a larger version of the security area from blue shift, with military equipement.<br>
spawn notes: after the wave starts by the soldiers getting their asses kicked. (the 4 you where with where pretty bad ass and in fact are still alive as they where with you during the attack) several MP5 and shotgun spawns are placed around the area generally near a dead soldier, but there is also an armory with shotgun shells, revolver rounds, grenades, and trip mines.</p>
<p>security station note: there is another security station with battery ports, in this case their are 3 of them all three activate ceiling turrets  with out a timer do to them being a toggle battery, but you only have 1 HEV battery unless you saved a few from earlier (you can have all three guns activated just note they can die)<br>
security station note two: there is a .50 cal aimed at the tram station. remember this.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/suggestion-hl-dm-stile-co-op-for-mp/15282/11">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/suggestion-hl-dm-stile-co-op-for-mp/15282/11</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 08 Oct 2017 06:44:55 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-15282-11</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/suggestion-hl-dm-stile-co-op-for-mp/15282.rss">suggestion: HL:DM stile co-op for MP</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>suggestion: HL:DM stile co-op for MP</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[darkone]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Ok I got bored here is the second co-op map idea.</p>
<p>TRAPPED (based on a map I played once in synergy may be to long for BM)<br>
description: a small group of hecu soldiers fight for their lives in a collapsed tunnel can you escape?</p>
<p>team: HECU<br>
objective: protect mastiff-8 while fighting off waves of rouge BM personel and teh xen military.</p>
<p>map start: players start backed against a collapsed tunnel with a tank that is at half health and across the way a dead garge (unique model left arm blown off big hole in head, took to shots from the tank).</p>
<p>starting gear: MP5 with grenade rounds (full ammo, cause guess what ammo is rare on this map), glock, 2 grenades per player. no melee.</p>
<p>map layout: the map consists of 3 sectors</p>
<p>sector one: the start tunnel, this part the players are only in for 3 of the waves it is a short tunnel with the only way out a secuirty check point which is locked down. after wave three mastiff-8’s gunner comes over the radio and tells your team to hold your fire as they ram the gate breaking a hole in it but taking out their last MG.</p>
<p>sector two: this is an intersection with the path the the right blocked to the tanks movement by a burning fuel tanker and destroyed IFV. the path to the right has a draw bridge of sorts that is retracted for tram movement 2 of the inbound tram cars are on one side of it one hanging off of a sparking wire. during this part the players must protect the tank against waves of xen miltiary and BMRF security while an emergency generator is powered up to activate the bridge.</p>
<p>sector three: outside: after going across the bridge and protecting the tank for a bit more of tunnel movement the players will exit the tunnels and arrive at an external secuirty check point this area is open and the players must hold out through more then a few waves of hostile xen forces for an osprey to arrive.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">waves and game flow. (this map doesn’t really have waves more events that happen as the tank moves)</span></p>
<p>wave one: locked in<br>
starts: wave starts 10 seconds after map start with mastiff-8’s commander talking over the radio.<br>
dialog: well there goes any chances we had to turn back, hold these guys off while I find us another path.<br>
hostiles: the wave’s hostiles are a few vorts that teleport in.</p>
<p>wave two: wave two starts shortly after wave one is over, just a simple second wave includes 2 A-grunts.<br>
dialog from mastiff-8: got it, alright evac point zulu is just up ahead hold on while I get the door.</p>
<p>wave three: starts as mastiff three starts moving more A-grunts and vorts nothing to hard do to the MG fire from the tank.</p>
<p>event: mastiff-8 rams the door infront of you blowing a hole in it similar to the IFV scene in surface tensions uncut area. (ramming the wall disables its MG, if possible)</p>
<p>wave four: starts the moment mastiff-8 breaks through, several BMRF personel are on the other side with a few glock and revolver armed guards firing upon the players (set to ignore the tank)</p>
<p>event flow: the tank keeps moving a long the road a few zombies break out of a door on the side and out comes a horde the tank will fire a single shell into the horde. once the horde is clear dialog will happen</p>
<p>mastiff-8: damn looks like teh bridge  is down and we can’t brute force this one, take a look around and try and find a way to cross that gap.</p>
<p>wave five: spawns after dialog random teleporting xen military tank will aim at A-grunts and ignore vorts.</p>
<p>area flow: palyers must search the side areas for a set of 3 metal fuel tanks to bring to an emergency generator in maintenance area bellow a security room. once the generator is started up they must protect it and the tank from more xen creatures.</p>
<p>wave six: zombie horde breaks down a double door in the maintence area, secuirty guards come out of the booth above armed with revolvers and one with an RPG.</p>
<p>wave seven: bridge is almost back up, A-grunts teleport in on the other side and vorts all over the place around the players location. (random spawns)</p>
<p>event flow: tank starts moving across the bridge as it does more xenians teleport in. though its mostly vorts and none of them are a threat to the tank.</p>
<p>wave eight: players hit the air lock between tehm and the outside security guards come from its check point once again one is armed with an RPG while some of the others have MP5’s. inside the checkpoint stolen hecu equipement can be found.</p>
<p>event flow: players must press a button and protect their tank from more xen military, with a few A-grunts trying to ram it. (can destroy the tank). once the tank is in the airlock press the button again to close it and open the outside door.</p>
<p>out side: tank moves out along with the players to find a small open cortyard with a landing pad and make shift medical area, said medical area has several BMRF scientists using it some of which are armed and a few security guards. (hostile). from here dialog starts again.<br>
mastiff-8: here we are evac point zulu, hold the line while I call us in a bird, lets hope that some one friendly is still in these skies.</p>
<p>from this point players must survive 5 waves of xen military and on the 5th wave a garge teleports in, releasing its flames in anger. mastiff-8 will fire three shells at it with it being killed by the third one. upon its death a dialog will be heard.<br>
mastiff-8: good news and bad news guys, good news a birds on her way ETA 3 miks the bad news that was our last shell, so if anything big comes in we are royally screwed.</p>
<p>at this point a countdown timer starts with 3 minutes during this timer xenians will spawn in at random, and secuirty guards will come in from the tunnels. players must survive this constant bombardment during which 2 HECU soldiers will leave their tank turning it from an NPC to a prop. (they may die, at this point you do not need to protect them). once the timer is up an osprey with helecopter support will arive on map and land, with players having to make it to the copter to win. bonus points for saving the tank crew which is only armed with pistols.</p>
<p>weapon flow:</p>
<p>start: mp5’s max ammo for primary and secondary, also glocks.</p>
<p>access as map goes.</p>
<p>revolvers: first security guard encounter<br>
grenades: first security guard encounter.</p>
<p>RPG: second security guard encounter (only one)</p>
<p>RPG spawn: tunnel on third section entry.<br>
9mm ammo: gained from dead guards, and tunnel on third section entry.</p>
<p>infinite 9mm ammo: medical area in third section.</p>
<p>yeah not much weapon wise on this map its to make you feel like you are geared for a mission at the start but as their are not many spawns players have to make their shots count and rely on drops from the BMRF security personnel.</p>
<p>base idea: this is meant to be harder then the wave based one as you have to protect a single target during most of the map. or else the map fails.</p>
<p>NPC NOTES:</p>
<p>allied hecu NPCS.</p>
<p>medic: start area you will have a medic that is armed only with a pistol.</p>
<p>tank crew: two hecu soldiers that spawn at the start of the 3 minute countdown at hte back of the tank, neither has a helmet and both are only armed with glocks.</p>
<p>the copter at the end: it lays down alot of fire to make the last bit easier incase of enemy build up, missiles will take care of a lot.</p>
<p>note: this idea may be weaker then the wave based survival one, as you are not only playing the bad guys but you are mobile through out most of the map.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/suggestion-hl-dm-stile-co-op-for-mp/15282/10">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/suggestion-hl-dm-stile-co-op-for-mp/15282/10</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 04 Oct 2017 14:01:03 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-15282-10</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/suggestion-hl-dm-stile-co-op-for-mp/15282.rss">suggestion: HL:DM stile co-op for MP</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>suggestion: HL:DM stile co-op for MP</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Kenley]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Right after the original mod release, one of the devs shared a <a href="https://forums.blackmesasource.com/index.php/Thread/15597-BMS-Tower-Defense/?postID=526388" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">prototype map</a> that was essentially what you describe. The intention was to see whether it could be a viable co-op mode. It was cool and fun even as a single player “tower defense,” but I suspect any work that would have gone towards it got redirected to the Steam release and then Xen. Maybe someday, after Xen, it could be implemented. If you want, you can still <a href="https://www.mediafire.com/?pbr1o7iwtk2rgeq" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">download the map</a>, but it will only be compatible with the classic mod.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/suggestion-hl-dm-stile-co-op-for-mp/15282/9">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/suggestion-hl-dm-stile-co-op-for-mp/15282/9</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 02 Oct 2017 22:33:29 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-15282-9</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/suggestion-hl-dm-stile-co-op-for-mp/15282.rss">suggestion: HL:DM stile co-op for MP</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>suggestion: HL:DM stile co-op for MP</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[darkone]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>hence why this is in the general and not another topic, this would have to be something officially made to even work.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/suggestion-hl-dm-stile-co-op-for-mp/15282/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/suggestion-hl-dm-stile-co-op-for-mp/15282/8</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 02 Oct 2017 15:56:45 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-15282-8</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/suggestion-hl-dm-stile-co-op-for-mp/15282.rss">suggestion: HL:DM stile co-op for MP</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>suggestion: HL:DM stile co-op for MP</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[ESToomere]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Okay, so agrunts are out and the barneys and hgrunts get shotguns.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/suggestion-hl-dm-stile-co-op-for-mp/15282/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/suggestion-hl-dm-stile-co-op-for-mp/15282/7</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 02 Oct 2017 14:43:25 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-15282-7</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/suggestion-hl-dm-stile-co-op-for-mp/15282.rss">suggestion: HL:DM stile co-op for MP</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>suggestion: HL:DM stile co-op for MP</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[LordDz]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Before you guys go too crazy with ideas, you should know that certain weapons that the npcs have do crash in multiplayer.<br>
So while someone could “easily” do a map like this, it’s currently impossible due to the game crashing the instant those weapons are fired.</p>
<p>Weapons that crash the game currently:<br>
Pistol, 357, mp5, grunt hivehand.</p>
<p>So poke at the devs and try to get their attention.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/suggestion-hl-dm-stile-co-op-for-mp/15282/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/suggestion-hl-dm-stile-co-op-for-mp/15282/6</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 02 Oct 2017 14:37:30 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-15282-6</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/suggestion-hl-dm-stile-co-op-for-mp/15282.rss">suggestion: HL:DM stile co-op for MP</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>suggestion: HL:DM stile co-op for MP</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[darkone]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>it is possible to add to their health, a lot of co-op maps in HL2 <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/smiley.png?v=9" title=":smiley:" class="emoji" alt=":smiley:"> M did that, nothing was more annoying then a combine gunship on one of them that could take 50 hits from RPGs.</p>
<p>And the health power thing isn’t much of a problem first their will be scientists which can heal (I think, never really got that to happen so not sure if that is still a feature). and secondly that is just another way to up the challenge of player counts go up. sure you may have 12 or14 players but their is only 1 rpg spawn and it has a slow respawn timer. that and having hidden spawn points can help a lot.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/suggestion-hl-dm-stile-co-op-for-mp/15282/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/suggestion-hl-dm-stile-co-op-for-mp/15282/5</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 02 Oct 2017 12:01:10 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-15282-5</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/suggestion-hl-dm-stile-co-op-for-mp/15282.rss">suggestion: HL:DM stile co-op for MP</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>suggestion: HL:DM stile co-op for MP</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[ESToomere]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I suppose it’s possible hurt entities based on players present, but I don’t think it’s possible to add onto health. Yeah, that could work to balance it out a bit.</p>
<p>Another thing I was thinking about was health/power. The number of pick-ups remains the same but depending on the amount of players they’ll run out faster.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/suggestion-hl-dm-stile-co-op-for-mp/15282/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/suggestion-hl-dm-stile-co-op-for-mp/15282/4</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 02 Oct 2017 11:57:01 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-15282-4</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/suggestion-hl-dm-stile-co-op-for-mp/15282.rss">suggestion: HL:DM stile co-op for MP</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>suggestion: HL:DM stile co-op for MP</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[darkone]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>sort of the point the idea is this would have a player based spawn numbers, the more players the harder the map is.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b"> example the two tanks on wave sixteen</span></p>
<p>1-2 players: only one spawns at a time, the second one starts damaged.</p>
<p>3-4 players: only one spawns at a time.</p>
<p>5-6 players: both come in at the same time, one focuses on players the other fires at the barracks (func targets on windows.)</p>
<p>7-10 players: both come in at same time, both focus on players.</p>
<p>11+ players: support infantry have grenade launcher rounds and more medics.</p>
<p>I have actually seen a few co-op maps do this though it is rare do to requiring a good amount of on map triggers and scripts. it would only be worth it for some of the harder waves cause nomater 1 or 12 players some waves do not need a threat change.more examples of the idea</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">wave twelve:</span> IFV support and health<br>
note: base IFV health increased to take 6 satchel charges or ~20 grenades (if possible to vary it that way)</p>
<p>1-4 players: base, IFV doesn’t fire until it pulls off the main road. (idea is the vehicle comes in and pulls off the main road near the barracks giving it a good line of sight on two of the players exits and giving players on the roof a good angle to lob grenades at it)</p>
<p>5-8 players: IFV  fires as it enters and has support infantry.</p>
<p>9+ players: more support infantry, IFV has a TOW. (would require a model with a TOW. the TOW would be fired randomly between bursts though not able to fire twice in a row, it will one hit palyers on direct hits and deal 75 damage in splash. to un armed players.)</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">wave nineteen</span> (soldiers at start, all can die the osprey pilot will give the low down if they all die)</p>
<p>1-2 players: 6 surviving allied soldiers, one is a medic will heal players all have full health.</p>
<p>3-4 players: 4 surviving allied soldiers, one is a medic will heal players all have full health.</p>
<p>5-6 players: 3 surviving allied soldiers, all have 3/4s health.</p>
<p>7+ players: 3 surviving allied soldiers, one has 3/4s health the others are 1 or 2 hits from death.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">wave twenty: helicopter support</span></p>
<p>1-2 players: copter comes in near the start fires missiles at harder targets.</p>
<p>3-4 players: copter comes in near the start, does not fire missiles.</p>
<p>5-6 players: copter comes in about half way through, does not fire missiles</p>
<p>7-10 players: copter comes in near the end does not fire missiles.</p>
<p>11+ players: copter comes in fires only a few burst and leaves do to being out of ammo.</p>
<p>these are just the ones I know can be done easily. and the idea is to use a system like this for the map.</p>
<p>OH a note, I do have one other map idea that is hecu based will likely post that later today.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/suggestion-hl-dm-stile-co-op-for-mp/15282/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/suggestion-hl-dm-stile-co-op-for-mp/15282/3</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 02 Oct 2017 11:27:44 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-15282-3</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/suggestion-hl-dm-stile-co-op-for-mp/15282.rss">suggestion: HL:DM stile co-op for MP</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>suggestion: HL:DM stile co-op for MP</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[ESToomere]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>That IS pretty simple to do, however it would be pretty difficult to balance. It’ll be too easy for a good team of 3-4 players and too hard for 1 player to enjoy. I know that’s the point of co-op but the MP is pretty dead.</p>
<p>However, it would also be interesting (from personal testing) to have a three-sided team deathmatch: both teams have mirrored objectives AGAINST each other but it’ll get increasingly difficult as more difficult Xen aliens start randomly teleporting into the map.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/suggestion-hl-dm-stile-co-op-for-mp/15282/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/suggestion-hl-dm-stile-co-op-for-mp/15282/2</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 02 Oct 2017 10:37:20 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-15282-2</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/suggestion-hl-dm-stile-co-op-for-mp/15282.rss">suggestion: HL:DM stile co-op for MP</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>suggestion: HL:DM stile co-op for MP</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[darkone]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Ok this is highly likely to be in the wrong section but here is a suggestion for a co-op mode that would be pretty easy to do.</p>
<p>BM: co-op<br>
info: co-op based maps for the multiplayer mode joined by anyone but with a single team each map would have an over arching objective.</p>
<p>FIRst map concept</p>
<p>the barracks<br>
discription: defend the surface guard barracks from all hell breaking loose.</p>
<p>team: BMFS (security guards)<br>
objective: survive 20 waves of hell defending an armory on the surface while trying to break into a motor pool to escape.</p>
<p>map info this map would be hybrid of the armory map and the car park map from surface tension with players spawning in the armory with shotguns unlocked at the start. players must defend a few NPC scientists that re in the armory (Can not be harmed by the players for anti greifing), while also helping an NPC guard secure floors of the car park every few waves once they make it to the top a working vehicle is found and you can escape.</p>
<p>map layout: players spawn in a 2 story barracks. on the top floor is an armory, bed area (door access to armory and stairs, spawn room), bath rooms, and roof access. the first floor has an office area, restrooms and 4 entry points. out side there is a small “yard area” and one other buildign with large walls all the way around, a north and south road access via double gates which you can not use. the second building is an office building which you can not access at the start. to the east is the car park which you also can not access at the start do to a 30 foot concrete wall.</p>
<p>waves and gameplay:</p>
<p>wave one: spawn wave, this wave starts 30 seconds after the map is loaded the first wave is simply headcrabs and hound eyes teleporting in, from this point on waves will spawn 2 minutes from each other with exceptions of the 10th, 15th, and 20th.<br>
wave two: doors are broken down from a building next to the barracks allowing access from it spawns zombies and headcrabs random teleportation continues.</p>
<p>wave three: more spawns from teh building though they are mostly zombies jumping from the second story (players can not access do to a barricade)</p>
<p>wave four: houndeyes come in from a gate on the main road (similar ot level gates they players must use in campaign)</p>
<p>wave five:  armory access unlocked vorts start random teleportation more zombies from the nearby building. (armory is unlocked in parts when first opened only the shotgun spawn is “unlocked” with all others being blocked by a keypad which a scientist is trying to brute force do to the head of the guard being dead or something. to to explain why things are delayed)</p>
<p>wave six: wave five with more vorts and less headcrabs/zombies.</p>
<p>wave seven: right side of map gets a hole blown in it this is the access point to the car parks entry, from this spews zombies, a dead soldier with a grenade spawn is found on the road. (East side)</p>
<p>wave eight: more randomly teleporting vorts.</p>
<p>wave nine: zombies from the car park tunnel, hound eyes from the road entry, grenades unlocked in armory.</p>
<p>wave ten: wave is started by a player activating a radio in the barracks as soldiers are calling for survivor locations. wave starts with a group of hostile soldiers from the road entry, followed by some random teleport vorts and then ending with more soldiers.</p>
<p>wave eleven: soldiers repelling in, and comming from the car park, first level of the car park is activated has a few mp5 spawns.</p>
<p>wave twelve: satchel charges unlocked in armory, IFV attacks from main road.</p>
<p>wave thirteen: mortar strike and random teleportation.</p>
<p>wave fourteen: first alien grunts teleport in on the roof next to the barracks. vorts random teleport into the yard around the buildings.</p>
<p>wave fifteen: players are told to head to the car park and clear out the second floor, main hostiles are soldiers. RPG spawn in car park activated.</p>
<p>wave sixteen: mortar strike blows a few holes in the barracks opening it up, and breaking open a crossbow spawn in the armory but also destroying the shotgun spawn. two tanks spawn on this wave with support infantry from both road entry points.</p>
<p>wave seventeen: soldiers spawn in mass and siege from the road part way through the wave manta’s strafe the road killing anything on it, another will strafe the office building allowing access to the second floor and destroying part of its roof.</p>
<p>wave eighteen: xen military attack lots of alien grunts and vorts. a manta will act as a teleport in vehicle taking it down will stop the hostile spawns (only part that would require things outside of scripting, mapping, and voice work).</p>
<p>wave nineteen: top level of the car park is opened a few soldiers are their but the are not hostile with a radio broadcast coming in asking for help, main hostiles of this wave are zecu and a few xen soldiers is the easiest wave sense wave nine, soldiers state they are abandoning their post and will evacuate you guys if you help defend their osprey as it fuels on the roof.</p>
<p>wave twenty: the last wave the scientists from the armory flee to the landed osprey found on the last wave. trigger a fuel pump to defend them, simply prevent xen forces from blowing the pump to win. on this wave a helicopter will spawn near the end but will not be hostile. radio chatter from the osprey reveals that the operation has fallen apart everyone is on their own, and the copter is giving cover fire to anyone that they can. (Copter only stays in the area for 30 seconds).</p>
<p>this wave is brutal with the players having to guard a point that is away from most ammo spawns, and with large numbers of xen forces. your only hint on the osprey and fuel trucks health will be if they are on fire or not. and well this map does have a bad ending with the fuel and osprey exploding taking the hole roof with them (implied all players on the roof die and the map ends) but if the players make it through their reward is a “Evacuation” via osprey for everyone that “enters it” (E to use camera set to its door get to watch it take off before screen goes black with [sector A security team: status safe… for now])</p>
<p>armory unlock tally</p>
<p>shotguns: wave, 5 with armroy access (destroyed wave sixteen along with ammo spawns)</p>
<p>grenades: tunnels wave  seven, armory wave ten</p>
<p>satchel charges: armory wave twelve</p>
<p>mp5: soldiers spawns all waves with soldiers (no armory access) has a few spawns in car park.</p>
<p>revolver: armory wave twelve</p>
<p>RPG: wave 15 car park in the back of a truck with infinite ammo crates. armory wave sixteen when a crate with them is blown open.(metal crate)</p>
<p>crossbow: access blown open wave 16.</p>
<p>snarks: hidden in a vent access as early as wave 15</p>
<p>mp5 grenades: infinite crate on roof with osprey, near it is a few 9mm ammo spawns.</p>
<p>note: teh bases of this idea is to be a single map that is co-op focused, I based this on one of the more complex ones I have seen in HL2 <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/smiley.png?v=9" title=":smiley:" class="emoji" alt=":smiley:"> M before the servers that hosted it died.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/suggestion-hl-dm-stile-co-op-for-mp/15282/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/suggestion-hl-dm-stile-co-op-for-mp/15282/1</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 02 Oct 2017 10:09:56 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-15282-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/suggestion-hl-dm-stile-co-op-for-mp/15282.rss">suggestion: HL:DM stile co-op for MP</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
