<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Huge FPS drop at the end of Apprehension</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/huge-fps-drop-at-the-end-of-apprehension/9616</link>
    <description>Just droping this by cause I&#39;m still playing.  :slight_smile: 

In last Apprehension level (the one where we fight Black Ops), right after I killed everyone, switched the lever to open the door, and quick saved the game, the fps dropped down very weirdly. I have quite descent PC, and had no problems through my gameplay with performance whatsoever (I don&#39;t see the fps count but it runs very smoothly). Right after that quick save, frames dropped to - I don&#39;t know, like - 5 to 10? When I turn around and face the &#39;rest&#39; of the level (the side where the knockout sequence happen), everything runs normal again. But looking around at the whole chopper hangar causes mentioned problem.

I will see if this happens on my second playthrough. Just wanted you guys to know.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 16 Sep 2012 14:38:25 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>In-game Issues (Mod)</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/huge-fps-drop-at-the-end-of-apprehension/9616.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Huge FPS drop at the end of Apprehension</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Lewk]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I too am having huge fps drops in apprehension. As soon as the elevator reaches the top where the security guard gets shot by an assassin, my fps drops from 120 to 27. Then when I enter the large room looking at the helipads and the sky it drops down to 8 fps. When I walk into the room behind it goes back up to 120.</p>
<p>Reloading the level doesn’t help. Starting from the previous level where I have a savegame and working back into the area doesn’t fix it either. I’m stuck, because it’s unplayable at 8 fps and I can’t kill the assassins. I don’t have enough health to get into the back room and have the assassins follow me and kill them.</p>
<p>My rig is: i7, 8 gig ram, gtx480 (with latest 306.23 drivers)</p>
<p>EDIT: I fixed it by restarting Apprehension via the New Game Chapter select screen. Had to do the whole chapter again, but at least it fixed the fps drop.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/huge-fps-drop-at-the-end-of-apprehension/9616/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/huge-fps-drop-at-the-end-of-apprehension/9616/5</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 16 Sep 2012 14:38:25 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9616-5</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/huge-fps-drop-at-the-end-of-apprehension/9616.rss">Huge FPS drop at the end of Apprehension</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Huge FPS drop at the end of Apprehension</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Mr_Freeman]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Okay, I was able to easily replicate it again. Killed an assassin, ran up to the lever, switched it, quick saved, quick loaded. Then bam, massive framerate drop.</p>
<p><a href="https://i.imgur.com/HC7v7.jpg" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Here is a screenshot with the showbudget panel.</a></p>
<p>Note: After that quick load, it mostly fluctuates between 6-10 fps. I took that within milliseconds of quick loading so it was even worse.</p>
<p>EDIT: <a href="https://www.sendspace.com/file/yumq8t" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Here is the quick save</a>, if that helps at all. Every time I load that quick save, the framerate drop is still present. Not sure if it will be for others.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/huge-fps-drop-at-the-end-of-apprehension/9616/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/huge-fps-drop-at-the-end-of-apprehension/9616/4</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 15 Sep 2012 19:57:48 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9616-4</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/huge-fps-drop-at-the-end-of-apprehension/9616.rss">Huge FPS drop at the end of Apprehension</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Huge FPS drop at the end of Apprehension</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Sashi420]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I wish the graphics would be the original half life 2 graphics no lie the graphics in BMS is Phenomenal but wow i remember one part i got 20fps and i have a 8gb ram computer and can run battle field 3 with max settings and still have 80fps</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/huge-fps-drop-at-the-end-of-apprehension/9616/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/huge-fps-drop-at-the-end-of-apprehension/9616/3</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 15 Sep 2012 11:03:12 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9616-3</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/huge-fps-drop-at-the-end-of-apprehension/9616.rss">Huge FPS drop at the end of Apprehension</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Huge FPS drop at the end of Apprehension</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Mr_Freeman]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Pretty much the same thing happened to me, although I still had two assassins left. I quick saved after I switched the lever; either that triggered the FPS drop, or the quick load I made like 10 seconds after that did. I’ll try to test again later.</p>
<p>Specs:<br>
OS: Windows 7 64-bit<br>
CPU: AMD Phenom II X2 555<br>
RAM: 4 GB<br>
GPU: Radeon HD 5770</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/huge-fps-drop-at-the-end-of-apprehension/9616/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/huge-fps-drop-at-the-end-of-apprehension/9616/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 15 Sep 2012 01:06:20 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9616-2</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/huge-fps-drop-at-the-end-of-apprehension/9616.rss">Huge FPS drop at the end of Apprehension</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Huge FPS drop at the end of Apprehension</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Vibez]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Just droping this by cause I’m still playing.  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=9" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
<p>In last Apprehension level (the one where we fight Black Ops), right after I killed everyone, switched the lever to open the door, and quick saved the game, the fps dropped down very weirdly. I have quite descent PC, and had no problems through my gameplay with performance whatsoever (I don’t see the fps count but it runs very smoothly). Right after that quick save, frames dropped to - I don’t know, like - 5 to 10? When I turn around and face the ‘rest’ of the level (the side where the knockout sequence happen), everything runs normal again. But looking around at the whole chopper hangar causes mentioned problem.</p>
<p>I will see if this happens on my second playthrough. Just wanted you guys to know.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/huge-fps-drop-at-the-end-of-apprehension/9616/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/huge-fps-drop-at-the-end-of-apprehension/9616/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 15 Sep 2012 00:04:07 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9616-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/huge-fps-drop-at-the-end-of-apprehension/9616.rss">Huge FPS drop at the end of Apprehension</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
