<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>A great Game not just a mod</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/a-great-game-not-just-a-mod/10382</link>
    <description>Hi,

I must first excuse for my poor english before i write ahead.

I just finished black mesa. As i am a true Half life fan from the begging, i was patinetly waiting for this mod, as one day i find the clock that is counting towards the release. I waited, and then on the day spent hourse getting a server or mirror to download. But when i begin to played it atleast for me it was worth the wait. I experianced a full game with absolutle no bugs or gliches. It was black mesa but not just redone but remasterd, like the sprint, and the flare gameplay, it was just fun. The conversesions were better, fun, gameplay, all was better. i played the mod, but it soon begun to feel like a stand alone game, as it was more than a mod, it was a game true to it&#39;s predassesory Half life 1. I must also give a big plus to the soundtrack, the fights with the cool music were awsome, like the questionable etichs, when the marines rappel down as they set the trap for you, and the music begins, it is just awsome. the grapichs are amazing, and so is the gameplay, i was a little disapointed in the weapon model for the mp5, and the crowbar animations, but all the others looked great. I must also congratulate on the awsome scene with the hive hand, when you stick your hand in it. Great game, please continue the work, make a great level of xen, and then in the future consider Opposing force, and blue shift, you would make masterpieces.

Thanks from a true Half life fan!


P.S. Barney&#39;s and ther talking is awsome and funny!</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 16 Sep 2012 21:04:26 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>The Cafeteria</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/a-great-game-not-just-a-mod/10382.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>A great Game not just a mod</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[_amp_amp_RB_amp_amp]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>There are a few mod teams doing a redux of Blue Shift and OP4 on the Source engine on <a href="http://MODDB.com" rel="nofollow noopener">MODDB.com</a>. But glad to see you love it as well!</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/a-great-game-not-just-a-mod/10382/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/a-great-game-not-just-a-mod/10382/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 16 Sep 2012 21:04:26 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-10382-2</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/a-great-game-not-just-a-mod/10382.rss">A great Game not just a mod</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>A great Game not just a mod</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Kent_Slak]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Hi,</p>
<p>I must first excuse for my poor english before i write ahead.</p>
<p>I just finished black mesa. As i am a true Half life fan from the begging, i was patinetly waiting for this mod, as one day i find the clock that is counting towards the release. I waited, and then on the day spent hourse getting a server or mirror to download. But when i begin to played it atleast for me it was worth the wait. I experianced a full game with absolutle no bugs or gliches. It was black mesa but not just redone but remasterd, like the sprint, and the flare gameplay, it was just fun. The conversesions were better, fun, gameplay, all was better. i played the mod, but it soon begun to feel like a stand alone game, as it was more than a mod, it was a game true to it’s predassesory Half life 1. I must also give a big plus to the soundtrack, the fights with the cool music were awsome, like the questionable etichs, when the marines rappel down as they set the trap for you, and the music begins, it is just awsome. the grapichs are amazing, and so is the gameplay, i was a little disapointed in the weapon model for the mp5, and the crowbar animations, but all the others looked great. I must also congratulate on the awsome scene with the hive hand, when you stick your hand in it. Great game, please continue the work, make a great level of xen, and then in the future consider Opposing force, and blue shift, you would make masterpieces.</p>
<p>Thanks from a true Half life fan!</p>
<p>P.S. Barney’s and ther talking is awsome and funny!</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/a-great-game-not-just-a-mod/10382/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/a-great-game-not-just-a-mod/10382/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 16 Sep 2012 20:59:45 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-10382-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/a-great-game-not-just-a-mod/10382.rss">A great Game not just a mod</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
