<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Importing BM props and textures into SDK (everything has pink frosting)</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/importing-bm-props-and-textures-into-sdk-everything-has-pink-frosting/11330</link>
    <description>I was able to set up BM in SDK 2007 with the handy guide on this forum, but now I&#39;m trying to import models (mainly props) and textures from BM into SDK 2009. I&#39;ve tried to do this before with L4D vehicle models, with similar results. I placed the models into the ep2/hl/models folder, and in both cases (with the L4d models and now with BM) the models do appear in the model browser, but without textures, so they are checkered with pink and black squares. I have no idea if this is simply due to misplacing the model textures (I&#39;ve tried putting them in several different folders, with no change) or something to do with the model textures themselves.

Likewise I experimented with placing the BM concrete textures folder into the EP2 materials folder. Again they do show up in the browser and a handful work properly, but most, when placed, appear with a veneer of pink over them, and some of the original SDK textures were tinted as well, so I had to remove the folder.

Thus far I haven&#39;t been able to find much by way of information, especially for this specific scenario (importing models and textures from other steam games). Does the fact that BM is in SDK 2007 a major barrier? If anyone can help me with these issues, it would be appreciated.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 06 Oct 2012 22:20:24 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Help!</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/importing-bm-props-and-textures-into-sdk-everything-has-pink-frosting/11330.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Importing BM props and textures into SDK (everything has pink frosting)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Animyr]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Anyone?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/importing-bm-props-and-textures-into-sdk-everything-has-pink-frosting/11330/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/importing-bm-props-and-textures-into-sdk-everything-has-pink-frosting/11330/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 06 Oct 2012 22:20:24 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11330-2</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/importing-bm-props-and-textures-into-sdk-everything-has-pink-frosting/11330.rss">Importing BM props and textures into SDK (everything has pink frosting)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Importing BM props and textures into SDK (everything has pink frosting)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Animyr]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I was able to set up BM in SDK 2007 with the handy guide on this forum, but now I’m trying to import models (mainly props) and textures from BM into SDK 2009. I’ve tried to do this before with L4D vehicle models, with similar results. I placed the models into the ep2/hl/models folder, and in both cases (with the L4d models and now with BM) the models do appear in the model browser, but without textures, so they are checkered with pink and black squares. I have no idea if this is simply due to misplacing the model textures (I’ve tried putting them in several different folders, with no change) or something to do with the model textures themselves.</p>
<p>Likewise I experimented with placing the BM concrete textures folder into the EP2 materials folder. Again they do show up in the browser and a handful work properly, but most, when placed, appear with a veneer of pink over them, and some of the original SDK textures were tinted as well, so I had to remove the folder.</p>
<p>Thus far I haven’t been able to find much by way of information, especially for this specific scenario (importing models and textures from other steam games). Does the fact that BM is in SDK 2007 a major barrier? If anyone can help me with these issues, it would be appreciated.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/importing-bm-props-and-textures-into-sdk-everything-has-pink-frosting/11330/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/importing-bm-props-and-textures-into-sdk-everything-has-pink-frosting/11330/1</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2012 05:54:42 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11330-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/importing-bm-props-and-textures-into-sdk-everything-has-pink-frosting/11330.rss">Importing BM props and textures into SDK (everything has pink frosting)</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
