<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Dr. Wallace Breen</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/dr-wallace-breen/11339</link>
    <description>We have a G-man thread, but in my opinion, this guy is as mysterious in some regards.
I don&#39;t think this has ever been explained, but how come did he survive the BM explosion?
What are the relations between the two men?

The only explanation that comes to my mind is that the G-man did save him (just as with Alyx) this would suggest that once they were friendly and working with/for each other.

In my opinion, &quot;my employers&quot; are none other than Aperture Science staff that have time-traveled into a/the future, and... dunno 0_o

/discuss, if unneeded for this to have it&#39;s own thread, then I&#39;m not against a merger.

Maybe &quot;Resonance Cascade&quot; was an attempt of AS to destroy BM, but it had some &quot;unforeseen consequences&quot; known as Combine invasion.

The man that they have tried to fu* with, ironically &quot;allied&quot; himself with the common enemy, Combine, thus they became responsible for the humanity&#39;s downfall.
And that&#39;s why the G-man has employed our hero Gordon.

Also a spoiler: [COLOR=&#39;Black&#39;]our mysterious guy is in fact none other than a leftover superior specimen of &quot;Mantismen&quot; jk lol, or not? 0_o</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 08 Oct 2012 16:05:26 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Half-Life Series</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/dr-wallace-breen/11339.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Dr. Wallace Breen</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Pettifogg]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Mented">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/m/9de0a6/40.png" class="avatar"> Mented:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>On the contrary, I’m fully convinced the Combine knew very well of the resistance in the city, and in fact Breen moved his main operations here directly BECAUSE of that.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>They most likely knew there was something going on in the general area, yes, but not the extent or specific locations, e.g. the underground railway. One of the Overwatch announcements during the canals says “Local unrest structure detected”, implying it had only recently been uncovered. Also, what Breen knew and what the Combine knew aren’t necessarily the same thing. He may well have kept some information from the advisors until he had enough to show his hand. Anyway, point is, the Combine do have some history of not being that observant, so I wouldn’t put it past them to miss some folk from Aperture until Gordon’s actions got their attention. After all, it’s like the US military not noticing an ant colony under their base.</p>
<p>Regarding the other things, those are pretty good alternate explanations, and like I said there are other (probably more sensible) theories, I just think it’s interesting how there does seem to be something of a link between Aperture and the Combine. Especially when you consider the Borealis and how that holds such a major significance to them.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/dr-wallace-breen/11339/24">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/dr-wallace-breen/11339/24</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 08 Oct 2012 16:05:26 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11339-24</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/dr-wallace-breen/11339.rss">Dr. Wallace Breen</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Dr. Wallace Breen</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Mented]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Dotard">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/d/d26b3c/40.png" class="avatar"> Dotard:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>sounds legit, it’s a videogame we are talking about</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>No it doesn’t sound legit at all, it’s a retarded theory based on a developers joke. It’s a video game, but it’s not a completely fucking retarded one. As I’ve already said, Portal is the comedy relief of the series, DO NOT start intertwining it’s comedy into the regular Half-Life universe. It becomes boring, tedious and annoying.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Pettifrog">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Pettifrog:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>You’d think so, but the Combine don’t seem to be that observant. They didn’t really notice a whole underground resistance movement in their primary city until Gordon led them right into it. Like Alyx said “The Combine can be slow to wake, but once they’re up you don’t want to get in their way”.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>On the contrary, I’m fully convinced the Combine knew very well of the resistance in the city, and in fact Breen moved his main operations here directly BECAUSE of that.</p>
<p>You see if the Combine are after the last of the scientists who know of teleport technology, they’ll know full well they’d rather kill themselves than give it up to the Combine. Hence a full frontal assault, ripping through every building finding them would be far too dangerous in regards to their end goal.<br>
When Freeman arrives however all of this changes.</p>
<p>The only real secret kept from the Combine, and kept well, is the direct location of the labs and White Forest.</p>
<p>In regards to Aperture, I’m unconvinced the technology is a sign of Combine contact. Obviously it was much easier for Valve to reuse assets from HL-2, and I doubt they wanted the tech to so closely resemble Combine tech aesthetically, So I try and come up with alternate theories to explain it.<br>
Personally I simply see it as extremely archaic versions of Combine tech naturally developed by the science staff. Thinking about it, similar Combine tech is eons ahead of anything at Aperture at seemingly much less cost.</p>
<p>The Health charger I was actually unaware of until you pointed it out. I’d say though that it seems more plausible to me that AS tech was simply used by the Combine for their new human forces, slightly upgraded, it being the best for the job. It is literally the only one ever seen pre-invasion, and thus could of been developed at another AS R+D center, state of the art at the time.</p>
<p>As for the Borealis, I think you’ve got it the wrong way around. The reason we see this video is because the Combine have captured it whilst tracking Mossman ( perhaps she was bugged without knowing it ). Eli had not heard from her since her departure.</p>
<p>Thus the Combine attached this and the location files to the packet they were sending with the portal codes for their reinforcements.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/dr-wallace-breen/11339/23">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/dr-wallace-breen/11339/23</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 07 Oct 2012 15:37:16 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11339-23</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/dr-wallace-breen/11339.rss">Dr. Wallace Breen</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Dr. Wallace Breen</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Dotard]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Pyro">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/p/71e660/40.png" class="avatar"> Pyro:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I hate how people latch on to throwaway jokes from Portal 2 and insist they’re proof that G-Man is really a time-traveling mantis man with peanut water for blood.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>sounds legit, it’s a videogame we are talking about</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/dr-wallace-breen/11339/22">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/dr-wallace-breen/11339/22</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 07 Oct 2012 14:22:39 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11339-22</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/dr-wallace-breen/11339.rss">Dr. Wallace Breen</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Dr. Wallace Breen</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Pyroclase]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I hate how people latch on to throwaway jokes from Portal 2 and insist they’re proof that G-Man is really a time-traveling mantis man with peanut water for blood.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/dr-wallace-breen/11339/21">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/dr-wallace-breen/11339/21</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 07 Oct 2012 05:24:15 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11339-21</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/dr-wallace-breen/11339.rss">Dr. Wallace Breen</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Dr. Wallace Breen</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Jack_Freeman]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Breen saw Gordon in the start of Half-Life 2, when the portal to Black Mesa East failed, he got to the top of the Citadel, Breen looked at him and asked “What is this? Who are you?”.<br>
Then he teleported up there again and Breen was talking with an advisor; “I am absolutely sure that was… <em>Turns head to Gordon</em> Gordon Freeman.”</p>
<p>So I don’t think the advisors told him or anything.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/dr-wallace-breen/11339/20">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/dr-wallace-breen/11339/20</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 07 Oct 2012 05:12:31 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11339-20</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/dr-wallace-breen/11339.rss">Dr. Wallace Breen</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Dr. Wallace Breen</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Pettifogg]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Mented">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/m/9de0a6/40.png" class="avatar"> Mented:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Interesting but I wouldn’t imagine so. If AS had been to any Combine world they’d of drawn attention, and thus an invasion would of happened much sooner. I’m not even sure how the portal gun works, and whether it even uses Xen at all ( although I assume it must to an extent ) or if AS knew about it, perhaps nodding to why the Borealis went so disastrously wrong.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>You’d think so, but the Combine don’t seem to be that observant. They didn’t really notice a whole underground resistance movement in their primary city until Gordon led them right into it. Like Alyx said “The Combine can be slow to wake, but once they’re up you don’t want to get in their way”.</p>
<p>There’s also some evidence to support this theory, what with Mossman’s transmission about the Borealis containing contact codes for the Combine Overworld, the suspiciously similar tech Aperture has to the Combine (High Energy Pellets, Hard Light Bridges and Excursion Funnels reek of their influence), and the <a href="https://imageshack.us/photo/my-images/857/p13edit.jpg/" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">fact that they have a Combine health charger</a>. These can be explained away, and I have my doubts that Valve would go in that direction, but when you put them all together it does seem to indicate something.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="heldro">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/h/7993a0/40.png" class="avatar"> heldro:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>In what way Wallace Breen and Gman are related to eachother? I still dont understand the meaning of this scene.</p>
<p><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=UvOgv6HpByw" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=UvOgv6HpByw</a></p>
<p>at 2: 35 he’s offering Gordon to work by his side so he can controll the rebels.<br>
“How about it Dr Freeman? Did you realise your contract was open to the highest bidder?”</p>
<p>Did Gman release Gordon into City17 because Wallace Breen payed for his contract?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I don’t think the G-Man is payed for by any human. He makes contact with them to further his goals, but his motivations are his own as far as anyone on Earth can tell. Either he mentioned Gordon to Breen, or Breen learnt of his involvement from the Advisors. Presumably they have some means of taking Gordon back from him, a la the Vorts.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/dr-wallace-breen/11339/19">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/dr-wallace-breen/11339/19</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 06 Oct 2012 19:11:53 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11339-19</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/dr-wallace-breen/11339.rss">Dr. Wallace Breen</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Dr. Wallace Breen</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[yrr]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Hm… still some mysteries about Breen… I guess it could be how you mentioned it but I think Breen hasn’t payed but WILL pay (he can bargain with the Combine, now that he has Gordon and Eli, two of the resistance leaders), so it wasn’t the Motivation for GMan to release Gordon because Breen didn’t pay before hand. If so, he wouldn’t be so surprised to actually see Gordon when the teleport went wrong.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/dr-wallace-breen/11339/18">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/dr-wallace-breen/11339/18</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 06 Oct 2012 11:17:48 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11339-18</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/dr-wallace-breen/11339.rss">Dr. Wallace Breen</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Dr. Wallace Breen</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[heldro]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>In what way Wallace Breen and Gman are related to eachother? I still dont understand the meaning of this scene.</p>
<p><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=UvOgv6HpByw" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=UvOgv6HpByw</a></p>
<p>at 2: 35 he’s offering Gordon to work by his side so he can controll the rebels.<br>
“How about it Dr Freeman? Did you realise your contract was open to the highest bidder?”</p>
<p>Did Gman release Gordon into City17 because Wallace Breen payed for his contract?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/dr-wallace-breen/11339/17">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/dr-wallace-breen/11339/17</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 06 Oct 2012 11:02:47 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11339-17</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/dr-wallace-breen/11339.rss">Dr. Wallace Breen</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Dr. Wallace Breen</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Problematic_A-hole]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>lol</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/dr-wallace-breen/11339/16">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/dr-wallace-breen/11339/16</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 06 Oct 2012 03:19:01 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11339-16</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/dr-wallace-breen/11339.rss">Dr. Wallace Breen</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Dr. Wallace Breen</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Mented]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>LALALA</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/dr-wallace-breen/11339/15">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/dr-wallace-breen/11339/15</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 06 Oct 2012 01:08:25 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11339-15</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/dr-wallace-breen/11339.rss">Dr. Wallace Breen</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Dr. Wallace Breen</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Problematic_A-hole]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>too much bat-shit crazy theories<br>
AP isn’t really that clever to pull something like that off, really</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/dr-wallace-breen/11339/14">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/dr-wallace-breen/11339/14</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2012 23:30:58 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11339-14</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/dr-wallace-breen/11339.rss">Dr. Wallace Breen</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Dr. Wallace Breen</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Dr_Maxwell]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>My pet theory is that Aperture was like G-Man’s first draft of Black Mesa.  They proved too insane to be useful, so he moved on.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/dr-wallace-breen/11339/13">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/dr-wallace-breen/11339/13</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2012 23:24:13 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11339-13</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/dr-wallace-breen/11339.rss">Dr. Wallace Breen</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Dr. Wallace Breen</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Jack_Freeman]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I don’t think Aperture would travel to the Combine Overworld since it needs a tremendous amount of power, much more than a portal to Xen.<br>
But Aperture can make their whole facility run on only 1.1 volts so /shrug.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/dr-wallace-breen/11339/12">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/dr-wallace-breen/11339/12</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2012 20:31:19 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11339-12</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/dr-wallace-breen/11339.rss">Dr. Wallace Breen</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Dr. Wallace Breen</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Mented]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Dotard">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/d/d26b3c/40.png" class="avatar"> Dotard:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Well, they fought constantly in an effort to surpass each other. BM was “the winner” so maybe Cave Johnson came up with a plan to travel into a future where BlackMesa no longer exists or wasn’t even created. But that in turn caused the Combine Invasion and in their reality there was no Gordon, and that’s why the G-man later employed him in the past</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I wouldn’t put to much thought into AS or Cave Johnson. You’ve gotta think of AS as the comedy relief of the Half-Life universe. Other than the actual business itself there won’t be a crossover into the half-life side, it simply WOULDN’T work.</p>
<p>How could there be no gordon in the combine invasion reality? What? Have you PLAYED the original game? How does that make sense? Where do you get that from?</p>
<p>Also, it would seem Cave Johnson died well before teleportation existed on earth. It would seem whoever took over AS decided to take the company in a much more ‘sane’ direction, hence the borealis.<br>
( Unless of course the Borealis is extremely old, evidenced by black and white pictures, and has only just come back recently. I however am not convinced of this. )</p>
<p>Also, being able to travel forward in time because your using a slow teleport doesn’t mean at all you can travel back. There is literally nothing within the HL series that shows us you can do such a thing. If there was it’d probably of been hinted at, like being able to travel forward ( in a sense ). So what Cave Johnson could hope to achieve is beyond me. I just don’t get your logic tbh, I think you’ve got far too hung up on Portal and its sequel.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>I do have a pet theory that Aperture was sending survey teams to the Combine Overworld like Black Mesa was with Xen, but I don’t know how realistic that is.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Interesting but I wouldn’t imagine so. If AS had been to any Combine world they’d of drawn attention, and thus an invasion would of happened much sooner. I’m not even sure how the portal gun works, and whether it even uses Xen at all ( although I assume it must to an extent ) or if AS knew about it, perhaps nodding to why the Borealis went so disastrously wrong.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/dr-wallace-breen/11339/11">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/dr-wallace-breen/11339/11</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2012 20:26:26 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11339-11</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/dr-wallace-breen/11339.rss">Dr. Wallace Breen</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Dr. Wallace Breen</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Pettifogg]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Mented">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/m/9de0a6/40.png" class="avatar"> Mented:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Breen probably got out with the marines in HL once they stormed the facility. He’d be wanted alive like the few other high priority targets. In fact he probably got out WITH Alyx, the marines would go far, but shooting kids? Doubt it. A perfect ‘cover’ whilst you let them know who you are.</p>
<p>[snip]</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Yeah, this seems the most plausible explanation.</p>
<p>If the G-Man had anything to do with Aperture Science, he wasn’t working with them any more than he was with Breen - he used them for his own ends, nothing more. I do have a pet theory that Aperture was sending survey teams to the Combine Overworld like Black Mesa was with Xen, but I don’t know how realistic that is.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/dr-wallace-breen/11339/10">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/dr-wallace-breen/11339/10</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2012 19:14:08 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11339-10</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/dr-wallace-breen/11339.rss">Dr. Wallace Breen</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Dr. Wallace Breen</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Dotard]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Mented">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/m/9de0a6/40.png" class="avatar"> Mented:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Didn’t he come up in the G-man thread?</p>
<p>Breen probably got out with the marines in HL once they stormed the facility. He’d be wanted alive like the few other high priority targets. In fact he probably got out WITH Alyx, the marines would go far, but shooting kids? Doubt it. A perfect ‘cover’ whilst you let them know who you are.</p>
<p>Breen was duped by the G-man into going ahead with the test under specific circumstances, probably in exchange for power or recognition ( Ha, G-man and his irony ). Once the excrement hit the fan he’d realized he’d been duped and during the Combine invasion realized how far.</p>
<p>The G-man isn’t friendly with anyone, he doesn’t work WITH anyone, at least nothing that isn’t the same as his own kind if there ARE anymore of his kind.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Also, your theories on AP and BM sabotage seem extremely thin, your theories on AP staff time traveling and the G-man being one of them laughable.</span></p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Well, they fought constantly in an effort to surpass each other. BM was “the winner” so maybe Cave Johnson came up with a plan to travel into a future where BlackMesa no longer exists or wasn’t even created. But that in turn caused the Combine Invasion and in their reality there was no Gordon, and that’s why the G-man later employed him in the past</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/dr-wallace-breen/11339/9">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/dr-wallace-breen/11339/9</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2012 19:12:28 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11339-9</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/dr-wallace-breen/11339.rss">Dr. Wallace Breen</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Dr. Wallace Breen</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[yrr]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Jack Freeman">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Jack Freeman:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I hope you’re joking with this because the Borealis is about teleportation and not time traveling.</p>
<p>And if the G-Man <span class="bbcode-i">is</span> human, could you care to explain to me where he have gotten those extra-terrestrial powers of his?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>1st: Hm… I wouldn’t essentially set those two apart… remember that teleport in HL 2  where Alyx and Gordon only teleported for seconds and were missed a week in which the uprising began ? That’s not exactly time travel but something like slowed down/delayed time. Also, if you teleport from point a on earth to point b in universe X when you would otherwise need thousands of years, isn’t that some kind of time travel ?</p>
<p>2nd. I also think that G-Man is some extraterrestrial entity which cloaks itself as human or uses the human form to be able to communicate with Gordon, Eli, etc. I think it’s a bit too far fetched that he has something to do with the Aperture Science labs… but hey… maybe it’s the reincarnation of Cave Johnson ?!?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/dr-wallace-breen/11339/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/dr-wallace-breen/11339/8</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2012 19:05:30 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11339-8</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/dr-wallace-breen/11339.rss">Dr. Wallace Breen</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Dr. Wallace Breen</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Mented]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Didn’t he come up in the G-man thread?</p>
<p>Breen probably got out with the marines in HL once they stormed the facility. He’d be wanted alive like the few other high priority targets. In fact he probably got out WITH Alyx, the marines would go far, but shooting kids? Doubt it. A perfect ‘cover’ whilst you let them know who you are.</p>
<p>Breen was duped by the G-man into going ahead with the test under specific circumstances, probably in exchange for power or recognition ( Ha, G-man and his irony ). Once the excrement hit the fan he’d realized he’d been duped and during the Combine invasion realized how far.</p>
<p>The G-man isn’t friendly with anyone, he doesn’t work WITH anyone, at least nothing that isn’t the same as his own kind if there ARE anymore of his kind.</p>
<p>Also, your theories on AP and BM sabotage seem extremely thin, your theories on AP staff time traveling and the G-man being one of them laughable.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/dr-wallace-breen/11339/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/dr-wallace-breen/11339/7</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2012 19:04:58 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11339-7</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/dr-wallace-breen/11339.rss">Dr. Wallace Breen</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Dr. Wallace Breen</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Dotard]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="yrr">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/y/2bfe46/40.png" class="avatar"> yrr:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Hm… kinda interesting Idea, although I would stick to Jack Freemans Intimations.</p>
<p>Have you ever considered to write Marc Laidlaw about information for that Character ?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>And to give them an extra reason not to release HL3? better not to  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/smiley.png?v=9" title=":smiley:" class="emoji" alt=":smiley:"><br>
I think these things should be revealed in a sequel, so we better let them surprise us.<br>
EDIT: <a class="mention" href="/u/freeman">@Freeman</a>, play Portal 2<br>
EDIT2: maybe he has a device of some sorts, or it’s simply a trick of mind</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/dr-wallace-breen/11339/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/dr-wallace-breen/11339/6</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2012 19:01:02 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11339-6</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/dr-wallace-breen/11339.rss">Dr. Wallace Breen</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Dr. Wallace Breen</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Jack_Freeman]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Dotard">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/d/d26b3c/40.png" class="avatar"> Dotard:</div>
<blockquote>
<ol>
<li>“Borealis”</li>
</ol>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I hope you’re joking with this because the Borealis is about teleportation and not time traveling.</p>
<p>And if the G-Man <span class="bbcode-i">is</span> human, could you care to explain to me where he have gotten those extra-terrestrial powers of his?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/dr-wallace-breen/11339/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/dr-wallace-breen/11339/5</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2012 19:00:19 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11339-5</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/dr-wallace-breen/11339.rss">Dr. Wallace Breen</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Dr. Wallace Breen</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[yrr]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Hm… kinda interesting Idea, although I would stick to Jack Freemans Intimations.</p>
<p>Have you ever considered to write Marc Laidlaw about information for that Character ?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/dr-wallace-breen/11339/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/dr-wallace-breen/11339/4</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2012 18:46:26 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11339-4</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/dr-wallace-breen/11339.rss">Dr. Wallace Breen</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Dr. Wallace Breen</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Dotard]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Jack Freeman">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Jack Freeman:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Have you ever thought that Breen maybe did escape BM on a legit way rather than getting teleported?</p>
<p>And about Aperture:</p>
<ol>
<li>They work with portals, not time traveling.</li>
<li>They’re humans while the G-Man has extra-terrestrial powers.</li>
</ol>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>It’s possible, something like Barney’s Blue Shift escape, but it’s canonicity is more than questionable.<br>
Not to mention I don’t see why Alyx had to be teleported, it doesn’t appear like there was much time left to escape and the only ones aware of the bomb were the HECU, Black Ops and G-man.<br>
One way or another, unexplained for now.</p>
<p>also:</p>
<ol>
<li>“Borealis”</li>
<li>That still doesn’t suggest him not being a human</li>
</ol>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/dr-wallace-breen/11339/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/dr-wallace-breen/11339/3</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2012 18:27:47 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11339-3</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/dr-wallace-breen/11339.rss">Dr. Wallace Breen</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Dr. Wallace Breen</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Jack_Freeman]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Have you ever thought that Breen maybe did escape BM on a legit way rather than getting teleported?</p>
<p>And about Aperture:</p>
<ol>
<li>They work with portals, not time traveling.</li>
<li>They’re humans while the G-Man has extra-terrestrial powers.</li>
</ol>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/dr-wallace-breen/11339/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/dr-wallace-breen/11339/2</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2012 18:17:38 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11339-2</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/dr-wallace-breen/11339.rss">Dr. Wallace Breen</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Dr. Wallace Breen</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Dotard]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>We have a G-man thread, but in my opinion, this guy is as mysterious in some regards.<br>
I don’t think this has ever been explained, but how come did he survive the BM explosion?<br>
What are the relations between the two men?</p>
<p>The only explanation that comes to my mind is that the G-man did save him (just as with Alyx) this would suggest that once they were friendly and working with/for each other.</p>
<p>In my opinion, “my employers” are none other than Aperture Science staff that have time-traveled into a/the future, and… dunno 0_o</p>
<p>/discuss, if unneeded for this to have it’s own thread, then I’m not against a merger.</p>
<p>Maybe “Resonance Cascade” was an attempt of AS to destroy BM, but it had some “unforeseen consequences” known as Combine invasion.</p>
<p>The man that they have tried to fu* with, ironically “allied” himself with the common enemy, Combine, thus they became responsible for the humanity’s downfall.<br>
And that’s why the G-man has employed our hero Gordon.</p>
<p>Also a spoiler: [COLOR=‘Black’]our mysterious guy is in fact none other than a leftover superior specimen of “Mantismen” jk lol, or not? 0_o</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/dr-wallace-breen/11339/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/dr-wallace-breen/11339/1</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2012 17:51:57 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-11339-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/dr-wallace-breen/11339.rss">Dr. Wallace Breen</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
