<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Improvements /Community Feedback for Black Mesa</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/improvements-community-feedback-for-black-mesa/13792</link>
    <description>First of all, congratulations for getting the Early Access out on steam !
After 10 years, it&#39;s finally here and personally, I&#39;m glad I can &quot;pay &quot; you back with a little money.


The implementation of Steam Workshop, the community hub as well as many other things will certainly add to improve the (already spectacular) quality of this game. 
So that brings me to a few questions and/or claims towards the DEV&#39;s:

* Over what platform will you (for the main part) communicate updates / improvements or announcements regarding Black Mesa ?
* Especially us Translation people now long for the scripts to provide our fellow countryman that are not able or not willing to play BM in English can also experience it. I realize that it may not be finished in regards to Xen being still missing or other issues. Still, it would be nice to get an update or some kind of answer on this part.
* Will there be some kind of tournament for the multiplayer part ? Where to deliver our feedback to maps, mechanics and , most important to me ,(future) the new game modes  (You could even communicate some Xen features if you think it won&#39;t spoil anything and ask the community what they think of it, for example.) ?


These kind of questions may seem redundant or irrational because you already communicate (a lot) over FB, Steam or the forums with the community, and things like the workshop already give the opportunity for many things. I&#39;m more asking for a more &quot;bundled&quot; information stream or access if you will. 


Thanks in advance !</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 05 May 2015 16:16:26 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>The Cafeteria</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/improvements-community-feedback-for-black-mesa/13792.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Improvements /Community Feedback for Black Mesa</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[yrr]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>First of all, congratulations for getting the Early Access out on steam !<br>
After 10 years, it’s finally here and personally, I’m glad I can "pay " you back with a little money.</p>
<p>The implementation of Steam Workshop, the community hub as well as many other things will certainly add to improve the (already spectacular) quality of this game.<br>
So that brings me to a few questions and/or claims towards the DEV’s:</p>
<ul>
<li>Over what platform will you (for the main part) communicate updates / improvements or announcements regarding Black Mesa ?</li>
<li>Especially us Translation people now long for the scripts to provide our fellow countryman that are not able or not willing to play BM in English can also experience it. I realize that it may not be finished in regards to Xen being still missing or other issues. Still, it would be nice to get an update or some kind of answer on this part.</li>
<li>Will there be some kind of tournament for the multiplayer part ? Where to deliver our feedback to maps, mechanics and , most important to me ,(future) the new game modes  (You could even communicate some Xen features if you think it won’t spoil anything and ask the community what they think of it, for example.) ?</li>
</ul>
<p>These kind of questions may seem redundant or irrational because you already communicate (a lot) over FB, Steam or the forums with the community, and things like the workshop already give the opportunity for many things. I’m more asking for a more “bundled” information stream or access if you will.</p>
<p>Thanks in advance !</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/improvements-community-feedback-for-black-mesa/13792/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/improvements-community-feedback-for-black-mesa/13792/1</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 05 May 2015 16:16:26 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13792-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/improvements-community-feedback-for-black-mesa/13792.rss">Improvements /Community Feedback for Black Mesa</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
