<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Post Your Name Definitions</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/post-your-name-definitions/4232</link>
    <description>Search your name in [url=&#39;https://www.urbandictionary.com/&#39;]Urban Dictionary[/url] and post the funny stuff that comes up. Variations of your name are allowed. To start off...
Sam:
[quote]
A ninja who has a stuffed squirrel and likes lemurs and lucky enough to know a munchlax, loves to eat pie, does not mind his girl friend driving his car, and is addicted to Monster. 
[/quote]

[quote]
Sexually Active Mongoose 
an ethiopian squirrel peasent derived from a family of birds that prey on young malasian prostitutes for their gypsy magic and unrelentless wisdom 
another definition for sam is short as in small or not tall
[/quote]

[quote]
One of the great Viking Lords of the 9th century, a very gay man. A revolutionary in the world of the gay, he was known to pass out lube and erotic gay paintings at every port he passed through. A drunkard, who smelled of rotting cats and mustard, that often destroyed villages with a swing of the genitalia and was renknowned for eating small children. He was married 16 times; 6 wives, 4 husbands, and 6 unknown creatures that were most likely eaten after the marriage. These marriages gave him 37 beautiful children, 13 of whom were fed to Sam fifer in order to calm him.
[/quote]

[quote]
noun- A huge turd floating in the Detroit sewer system usually resulting from eating nachos at another Lions loss. Sometimes Sams can travel great distances and have been known to pop up as far away from Detroit as Vermont or North Carolina. 
[/quote]
Samuel:
[quote]
An obese man who lives in the sewer and wears expensive clothing. He battles oversized alligators and eats them. He is a legend in his own mind. He has bright orange skin and looks like John Madden.
[/quote]
And the only one for my real name.
Samuli:
[quote]
Absolutely bangable male. When a guy is called Samuli, he&#39;s so georgeous that all ladies want to bang him simultaneously.
[/quote]
 :rolleyes:</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 28 May 2010 00:42:50 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Off Topic</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/post-your-name-definitions/4232.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Post Your Name Definitions</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[OldDirtyBastard]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Victor and Victoria are the best names you could ever have, haha.<br>
Victory = win.<br>
I love those. totally me.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Victor:</span></p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>Common name of a playa who’ll leave you without saying a word. Also known as “hustla”, this individual is particularly good in bed and has vast experience he’ll never admit he does, which is why all of his xs still chase him. Hard to catch, impossible to keep, the biggest mistake you can make is introducing him to your best friend, who of course, is going to wanna nail him. This name can also translate to “Winner, triumphant, <span class="hashtag">#1</span>” in various languages.<br>
“dam nigz, u is a Victor”</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>A highly intelligent, smooth talking, mysterious, player, who appears rough on the exterior, but has a heart, you just won’t know it…Use CAUTION when in the vicinity of said male species; as they can suck you in and bend you to their will; stripping you of all your values and moral beliefs. Also highly contagious…most men wanna be him and all females wanna have him. Has the ability to turn you into a wimpering ball of flesh with one comment, leaving victim to question their validity for life.<br>
<span class="hashtag">#1:</span> dude what’s the matter with you? Why you sucking your thumb?</p>
<p><span class="hashtag">#2:</span> I got victorized!</p>
<p><span class="hashtag">#1:</span> Wanna blankey now?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>An amazing guy. Except that only one girl will hold his heart, He is a very difficult guy and a player, but a great smooth talker and very persuasive, never fake though. Eyes that will swoon you in and a smile that could light up the darkest of tunnels. Easy to fall for but if your a tough cookie it’s hard for you to admit it. Usually of the hispanic race, very big nice family and an even bigger heart. One girl will win his heart and by ages 16 she probably already has, This guy is most compatible with virgos the two personalitys click. Although with his loved one age may be a problem seeing he is probably older. Usually nick names are Vick or Vic doesn’t really obtain the full name unless it’s a serious matter. Pretty well known guy and definitely a hearthrob but if watch out. He definitely has experience but like’s a challenge. His ex’s always chase him but he always goes to the same girl although she’s not an ex and has never gave it up to him, Wants her but not just for her sex but for herself. This guy has got a temper so try not to set it off.<br>
Well i guess that’s definitely a Victor</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>A chill person whos funny an gets along with evryone. He’s open to all kinds of friends even if they are mentally disabled or handicapped it doesnt matter to him. If your lesbian he’ll still accept you ([COLOR=‘Red’]well who the fuck wouldn’t). His heart belongs 2 one girl and she might not know it, but they are meant to be together. He will give his heart. to that girl and she’ll always have it.He looks for love and not sex. He has an alcohol addiction because the girl and cuts himself for her.</p>
<p>-Hey did you see Victors wrists as he drank?<br>
-Yeah he did it 4 his love<br>
-Woah harsh, they should date already=<br>
-Hey did you see Victors wrists as he drank?<br>
-Yeah he did it 4 his love<br>
-Woah harsh, they should date already=</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Viktor:</span></p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<ol>
<li>awesome <span class="bbcode-b">2. a ninja</span>
</li>
</ol>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>And ahahahha @ these:</p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>Clueless gypsy with incestuous temptations towards his mom.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>The name Victor comes from the ancient Latin word No-lifus! Victors have a tendency to be No-lifes and often look like Shrek. They spend there days in front screens and when there finnished playing gay games like “Online Football Manager” which makes them lamer than they naturaly are!</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>dirty mexican</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Totally not jealous.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/post-your-name-definitions/4232/45">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/post-your-name-definitions/4232/45</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 May 2010 00:42:50 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-4232-45</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/post-your-name-definitions/4232.rss">Post Your Name Definitions</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Post Your Name Definitions</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Surplus]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>Leeland</p>
<ol>
<li>One whom might find themselves thoroughly baked and shooting a harpoon gun in a massive crowd on a daily basis.<br>
2)The act of pinching a friends ball sack from behind.</li>
</ol>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>The second one makes me disappoint  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/frowning.png?v=9" title=":frowning:" class="emoji" alt=":frowning:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/post-your-name-definitions/4232/44">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/post-your-name-definitions/4232/44</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 May 2010 00:42:10 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-4232-44</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/post-your-name-definitions/4232.rss">Post Your Name Definitions</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Post Your Name Definitions</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Theevilpplz]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Ok. I’m upset…</p>
<p>Dayle:</p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>A girl with a lot of potential in everything she does. Very beautiful and has a big heart for her friends. Has love problems because she tends to go back to old boyfriends that she liked that didn’t work out when she knows she has a close friend that she talks to very frequently that she can take interest in.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I’m a guy :[</p>
<p>That ruined my day.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/post-your-name-definitions/4232/43">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/post-your-name-definitions/4232/43</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 May 2010 00:38:21 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-4232-43</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/post-your-name-definitions/4232.rss">Post Your Name Definitions</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Post Your Name Definitions</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Mr.Shadow]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>The one that contains the most truth:</p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>Joshua is a sexy, masculine individual exuding the most desirable of traits. Although Joshua may be timid at first, his genuine and compassionate charm shine through above all things. He can be trusted with any secret and will always pull through even when the going gets tough. His understanding and supportive nature can put anyone at ease as he is never judgmental but rather always willing to listen with an open mind. He is the epitome of a true man.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>The least true one:</p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>A boyfriend who cooks, cleans, pays, and drives. A Joshua.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>And the one that describes how I was when I was a teenager:</p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>A super hot computer nerd who is funny, sarcastic, and a bit of a bad ass.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/post-your-name-definitions/4232/42">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/post-your-name-definitions/4232/42</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 27 May 2010 11:56:45 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-4232-42</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/post-your-name-definitions/4232.rss">Post Your Name Definitions</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Post Your Name Definitions</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[noonem]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>noonem isn’t defined <span class="bbcode-u">yet</span>.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p><img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/frowning.png?v=9" title=":frowning:" class="emoji" alt=":frowning:">  :’(</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/post-your-name-definitions/4232/41">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/post-your-name-definitions/4232/41</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 27 May 2010 11:45:30 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-4232-41</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/post-your-name-definitions/4232.rss">Post Your Name Definitions</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Post Your Name Definitions</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Jingles]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>From Ioseph, the Latin form of Greek Ιωσηφ (Ioseph), which was from the Hebrew name יוֹסֵף (Yosef) meaning “he will add”. In the Old Testament Joseph was the eleventh son of Jacob. Because he was the favourite of his father, his older brothers sent him to Egypt and told their father that he had died. In Egypt, Joseph became an advisor to the pharaoh, and was eventually reconciled with his brothers when they came to Egypt during a famine. This name also occurs in the New Testament, belonging to Saint Joseph the husband of Mary and Joseph of Arimathea.<br>
In the Middle Ages, Joseph was a common Jewish name, being less frequent among Christians. In the late Middle Ages Saint Joseph became more highly revered, and the name became popular in Spain and Italy. In England it became common after the Protestant Reformation. This name was borne by rulers of the Holy Roman Empire and Portugal. Other notable bearers include Polish-British author Joseph Conrad (1857-1924) and the Soviet dictator Joseph Stalin (1878-1953).</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/post-your-name-definitions/4232/40">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/post-your-name-definitions/4232/40</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 25 May 2010 19:04:50 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-4232-40</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/post-your-name-definitions/4232.rss">Post Your Name Definitions</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Post Your Name Definitions</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[CatzEyes93]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>My day cannot get more perfect than right now at this moment.  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=9" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>In Ireland, this is a name givin to someone that makes you laugh alot.<br>
<span class="bbcode-i">I was laughing all day because of a Victoria i know.</span></p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>Really nice, makes you laugh, beautiful, has a lot of passion, great friend to have<br>
[i]Guy1: Did you see Victoria?</p>
<p>Guy2: Yeah I wish she wasn’t taken</p>
<p>Girl1: She’s not that great</p>
<p>Guy1: Shut up Girl1 you’re just jealous![/i]</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>Italian name meaning “Victorious” or “Victory” given to a girl that embodies the highest level of beauty. The best Victoria’s are found in Franklin Square, LI.<br>
<span class="bbcode-i">I was on the LIRR, and suddenly I saw a girl and I knew her name must be Victoria because she was soooo hot!</span></p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>A name given to the most ridiculously amazing, beautiful, sweet, gorgeous, incredible, cute, all around perfect girl in the whole Universe. She is just stunning, she can light up the darkest rooms with her smile, and bring up anyones day with her voice, there is nothing wrong with her at all, she just never ceases to amaze anyone, her beauty is hypnotic and her eyes are mesmerizing, she herself is so magnetic, on a scale of 1 to 10 she is an Eleventy Fortyfour,she may seem like a good girl but have a night with her and you’ll discover her total bad girl side, she is into pink fuzzy handcuffs and leather,but you still cant help but remain in love with her,even though she is incredibly kinky.<br>
<span class="bbcode-i">Gosh! When I saw Victoria pass by my zipper broke!</span></p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>Beautiful, hot, loves to party<br>
[i]Boringgirl: Hey you wanna stay in and starve and look like a skeleton?</p>
<p>Coolperson: Uh… no I’m going out tonight with Victoria and you’re not invited[/i]</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>A true friend, or a BFFL. A victoria is a sexy bitch. Sometimes is a mexican.<br>
<span class="bbcode-i">Victoria is my best friend, and you should be jealous.</span></p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>Capital City of British Columbia, Canada.<br>
population: 300,000<br>
Like the stoned younger brother of Vancouver, Victoria is the kind of place for people who aren’t into the go-go lifestyle of big city life.<br>
<span class="bbcode-i">Victoria is sooo much nicer than Vancouver</span></p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/post-your-name-definitions/4232/39">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/post-your-name-definitions/4232/39</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 25 May 2010 18:51:40 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-4232-39</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/post-your-name-definitions/4232.rss">Post Your Name Definitions</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Post Your Name Definitions</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Coolm4n]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>Jeremie<br>
<span class="bbcode-b">A gay way to spell Jeremy</span>. Usually given to children who are born with birth <span class="bbcode-b">defects</span> and have a feeling of being good at intellectual games, because of spending large amounts of time studying them, but in practice is beaten by people with only a basic understanding of the game repeatedly and still has an overwhelming sense of being good, causing him to lose large amounts of money.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>:retard:</p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>Jeremie is the sweetest, nicest guy you could ever hope to meet! He is the guy you take home to meet your parents-he is the guy you hope to marry and have children with. If you meet a “Jeremie” he’s a keeper! People with this name tend to be balanced, and receptive to cooperation. They are the ideal partner and seek peace. Origin: Hebrew Meaning: God will raise up; God will set free</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p><img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=9" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji only-emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/post-your-name-definitions/4232/38">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/post-your-name-definitions/4232/38</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 25 May 2010 18:31:53 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-4232-38</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/post-your-name-definitions/4232.rss">Post Your Name Definitions</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Post Your Name Definitions</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[X_Mastershot_X]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Ryan:A noble ganster who shoots unstabel niggers</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/post-your-name-definitions/4232/37">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/post-your-name-definitions/4232/37</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 25 May 2010 18:29:51 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-4232-37</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/post-your-name-definitions/4232.rss">Post Your Name Definitions</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Post Your Name Definitions</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[samzala]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Ooh I forgot that one.<br>
oh lol<br>
Joona:</p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<ol>
<li>a Korean name that symbolizes mystery. A great legend says of a warrior name Joona who saved the Princess Mi Cha from the all powerful “TigerLord” using unknown martial arts known only by the greatest of Heroes 2)A person with this name is very popular among all types of people. 3) a MothaFukka 4) a Korean nickname for men with the name Byeong Joon</li>
</ol>
</blockquote>
</aside>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/post-your-name-definitions/4232/36">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/post-your-name-definitions/4232/36</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 25 May 2010 18:25:43 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-4232-36</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/post-your-name-definitions/4232.rss">Post Your Name Definitions</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Post Your Name Definitions</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Doop]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Im lazy so heres the link: <a href="https://www.urbandictionary.com/define.php?term=Ryan" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://www.urbandictionary.com/define.php?term=Ryan</a></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/post-your-name-definitions/4232/35">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/post-your-name-definitions/4232/35</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 25 May 2010 18:24:04 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-4232-35</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/post-your-name-definitions/4232.rss">Post Your Name Definitions</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Post Your Name Definitions</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Lolipopman]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I tried my middle name…:</p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>slang for a person who is often called a terrorist and a person with a huge nose</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/post-your-name-definitions/4232/34">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/post-your-name-definitions/4232/34</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 25 May 2010 18:11:13 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-4232-34</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/post-your-name-definitions/4232.rss">Post Your Name Definitions</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Post Your Name Definitions</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[FireTime]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Nick:</p>
<ol>
<li>the most amazing person alive with a huge penis</li>
</ol>
<p>2.the hottest, sexiest man you will ever meet. usually has a very large penis, makes a really good boyfriend and is alwyas condfident about himself. can kick almost anyones ass and is quite a gentleman. always get with a nick, you will alwyas be pleased.</p>
<p>ha, Well I feel content.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/post-your-name-definitions/4232/33">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/post-your-name-definitions/4232/33</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 25 May 2010 18:08:13 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-4232-33</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/post-your-name-definitions/4232.rss">Post Your Name Definitions</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Post Your Name Definitions</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[gugamilare]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Someonerandm">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/s/d78d45/40.png" class="avatar"> Someonerandm:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Fun Fact: 99.3548% of positive definitions were crated by a guy with that name.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>And the other 0.6452% were made by their girlfriends.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/post-your-name-definitions/4232/32">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/post-your-name-definitions/4232/32</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 25 May 2010 17:54:40 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-4232-32</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/post-your-name-definitions/4232.rss">Post Your Name Definitions</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Post Your Name Definitions</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Lolipopman]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Christopher:</p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>Maybe when you first meet a Christopher they’ll seem like a jerk, and hurt you emotionally multiple times, or possible make the lamest jokes but one day he’ll make up for it all, the best he can. Christophers will eventually realize the love that they’ve stored in a safe place for you. Christophers usually have the most gorgeous smile out there, and the most seductive voice. They’re someone you wouldn’t mind spending the rest of your entire life with. They have a tendancy to spend more time thinking of what to do for someone else than themselves. Christophers love adventure, new things, something to get their blood rushing and heart pounding. I love my Christopher, forever and always. That soldier, he keeps me sane. (=</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>A man with furth unyealing, and heroics past the point of normal comprehension. Often associated with being of the upmost heterosexuality. One who’s prowess in pleasing women is only surpassed by his large member.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I CAN’T HEAR YOU.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/post-your-name-definitions/4232/31">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/post-your-name-definitions/4232/31</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 25 May 2010 17:22:54 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-4232-31</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/post-your-name-definitions/4232.rss">Post Your Name Definitions</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Post Your Name Definitions</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Someonerandm]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Fun Fact: 99.3548% of positive definitions were crated by a guy with that name.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/post-your-name-definitions/4232/30">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/post-your-name-definitions/4232/30</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 25 May 2010 17:04:58 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-4232-30</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/post-your-name-definitions/4232.rss">Post Your Name Definitions</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Post Your Name Definitions</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[X_Mastershot_X]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Samuel:</p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>The name of a guy who is amazing at life, basketball, golf, and everything else. He is fun the hang out with, he’s super good-looking, has a great sense of humor, very smart, loving, generous, gentleman, and more. You can’t go wrong having him as your best friend, or boyfriend. There is never a dull moment with him. You can trust him with anything, and he’s the best advice giver in the world. He has great taste in clothes, even though he’s perfectly straight, and will do anything to make his girlfriend happy. He was raised by some awesome people, and will be the best husband and father.</p>
<ol>
<li>“Samuel, I love you.”</li>
<li>“Samuel! Be good!”</li>
<li>“Buh-bye.”</li>
<li>“I hahrt you.”</li>
</ol>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p><span alt="" class="broken-image" title="This image is broken"><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-unlink svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#unlink"></use></svg></span></p>
<p>Deniz:</p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>A disgusting ugly, cold-hearted, selfish, conceited, stubborn, hateful pig; most likely the re-incarnation of Jack the Ripper and Hirohito (The Shōwa Emperor). If in the presence of this evil being one must be cautious and keep it happy, as soon as it is angered there will be no mercy.<br>
Deniz (daily thought): Who will I destroy today?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>:what:</p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>A synonym for “superawesome”. This word is actually the first word to be used publicly by a Greek God. The God was Zeus, and he said he was sure feeling like Deniz today.<br>
Man, that party was DENIZ!</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p><span alt="" class="broken-image" title="This image is broken"><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-unlink svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#unlink"></use></svg></span></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/post-your-name-definitions/4232/29">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/post-your-name-definitions/4232/29</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 25 May 2010 16:39:23 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-4232-29</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/post-your-name-definitions/4232.rss">Post Your Name Definitions</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Post Your Name Definitions</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[gugamilare]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I already posted, but found another definition interesting using French variation of my name.</p>
<p>Damn, mah name it tha shit! [sic]  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/smiley.png?v=9" title=":smiley:" class="emoji" alt=":smiley:"></p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<ol>
<li>Gustave<br>
Most infamous crocodile in Africa, due to it being the largest, and reports that it has killed and eaten 300 natives, said to be over 60 years old. Somtimes used to describe a particularly draconian dictator in Africa.<br>
<span class="bbcode-i">-Gustave has gone on yet another killing frenzy</span><br>
<span class="bbcode-i">-Gustave is one huge crocodile</span>
</li>
</ol>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Again, this is also true: <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Gustave_%28crocodile%29" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Gustave (crocodile)</a>:</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Wikipedia">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Wikipedia:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>In 2004 he was estimated to be 60 years old, 20 feet (6.1 m) in length and to weigh around 1 ton, making him the largest confirmed crocodile ever seen in Africa.[1]  He is a notorious man-eater, who is rumored to have claimed as many as 300 victims from the banks of the Ruzizi River and the northern shores of Lake Tanganyika. While this number is likely exaggerated, Gustave has attained a near-mythical status and is greatly feared by people in the region. He is said to hunt and leave his victims’ corpses uneaten.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I am dangerous, guys, don’t mess with me :3</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/post-your-name-definitions/4232/28">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/post-your-name-definitions/4232/28</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 25 May 2010 16:39:17 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-4232-28</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/post-your-name-definitions/4232.rss">Post Your Name Definitions</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Post Your Name Definitions</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Steppenwolf]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<ol>
<li>
<p>mathas:<br>
This is a name for a good guy that most people like.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Mathias:<br>
An awesome and down to earth guy who everyone loves. He makes you feel like you are the only one there and makes you feel very very special. He cares and doesn’t let other people be mean to his girlfriend. He respects you and always says how much he loves you and cares about you. Not always in the same language but still. You won’t be able to resist the loving and hottness of someone like him.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Mathias:<br>
Given to those who possess a thick penis and irregularly placed pubic hair. Also, the upper body is unusually smaller than the lower body giving the image of a ridiculously fruity christmas tree.</p>
</li>
</ol>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Number three is a bit… weird?  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/smiley.png?v=9" title=":smiley:" class="emoji" alt=":smiley:"></p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="DansonDelta40">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/d/bbce88/40.png" class="avatar"> DansonDelta40:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Now my real life first name: Ole</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Do you have danish ancestors?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/post-your-name-definitions/4232/27">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/post-your-name-definitions/4232/27</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 25 May 2010 15:32:50 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-4232-27</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/post-your-name-definitions/4232.rss">Post Your Name Definitions</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Post Your Name Definitions</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[jerry]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Jerry:</p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>Jerry was used by the British in the Great War as a nickname for the Germans. One possible origin is that Jerry was thought to be a common name among Germans, like ‘John’ with Americans. Another, and perhaps the true origin, is that bed pans/chamber pots were called Jerries, and the Germans helmets looked like them, so… Jerry was one of many nicknames used to call the Germans, the French preferred Boche, the Americans, Krauts. Another common one was ‘Hun’. The usage of Jerry, and the rest, although I can’t say I have seem much use of Boche outside of WW I related things, continued during the Second World War. The gas/water container used by the Germans in WW II was nicknamed a Jerry can. During the Great War, the Germans, when talking to the Englishmen in the opposite trenches, would use Tommy to reference them, while the British, of course, used Jerry in regard to the Germans.<br>
<span class="bbcode-i">My high school had this great set of WW II books, and I can remember this one story from a veteran that, for whatever reason, has stuck with me. He and his unit had assaulted a German airfield. “We were running around securing the hangars. I passed the door to an office and kicked it open. I tossed in a grenade and the Jerry behind the desk caught it and shouted, “Nein! Nein!” I yelled, “Ja! Ja!” and slammed the door shut.”</span></p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/post-your-name-definitions/4232/26">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/post-your-name-definitions/4232/26</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 25 May 2010 14:07:02 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-4232-26</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/post-your-name-definitions/4232.rss">Post Your Name Definitions</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Post Your Name Definitions</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Savant]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Urban Dictionary">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Urban Dictionary:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Croatian alpha-male<br>
That Tomislav, he likes to get do it Balkan style</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>:fffuuu:</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/post-your-name-definitions/4232/25">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/post-your-name-definitions/4232/25</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 25 May 2010 13:15:54 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-4232-25</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/post-your-name-definitions/4232.rss">Post Your Name Definitions</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Post Your Name Definitions</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[samzala]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I was sorta implying with my first post that everyone’d search for the really bizarre ones, and skip the usual sexual reference ones, it’s pretty much stated already that 90% of every name definition has something to do with big dicks and hawtness.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/post-your-name-definitions/4232/24">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/post-your-name-definitions/4232/24</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 25 May 2010 13:13:59 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-4232-24</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/post-your-name-definitions/4232.rss">Post Your Name Definitions</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Post Your Name Definitions</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Suggestive]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Nikki.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>buy nikki mugs, tshirts and magnets<br>
Quite possibly the cutest, sweetest, and most attractive girl you’ll ever meet. Not only is she pretty and hot, but she has great intellectual insight and is all around a perfect person. No matter what she does, you could never get mad at her. When you see her pictures, her smile, her eyes, you feel not only turned on, but content. Content because you know that she is everything you could ask for.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>^ Lies</p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>buy nikki mugs, tshirts and magnets<br>
the anatomy of amazing and awesome!! fantastic.<br>
a joy to be around… always</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>^ Lies</p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>Probably, and by probably I mean it’s highly likely that Nikki is the most badass supah fly baller you’ll ever meet. She’s also a sex fiend who loves Newports and coffee.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>^ This one worries me a great deal. I get the feeling someone I know has written this one  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/expressionless.png?v=9" title=":expressionless:" class="emoji" alt=":expressionless:"><br>
Wat do?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/post-your-name-definitions/4232/23">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/post-your-name-definitions/4232/23</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 25 May 2010 12:02:44 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-4232-23</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/post-your-name-definitions/4232.rss">Post Your Name Definitions</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Post Your Name Definitions</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Mango_Assassin]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Step aside ladies…</p>
<p>[COLOR=‘Blue’]James[/SIZE] :</p>
<p>Someone who is un usually well [COLOR=‘Red’]hung. People with the name James are generally known for their good looks (especially the eyes) and women are just simply attracted to them.<br>
“Oh Yeah, he’s definately a James”</p>
<p>In early European lore the demigod James was said to possess unrivaled charm and seductive prowess in addition to having genitalia of supernatural size. Throughout medieval times and up until the late Renaissance, Pagan and Christian farmers routinely prayed to James as a god of fertility, believing that his massive penis would inspire them to spectacular heights of fertility. Today, the term James still carries with it subtexts of truly gigantic genitals which is perhaps why James is the name most frequently given to male newborns in the United States.<br>
Currently the word James can be used to mean an enormous penis and anyone with that name can be assumed to possess a heavy and girthy penis.<br>
“Man, check out that James!”</p>
<p>“Look at the buldge in his trousers, he [COLOR=‘Lime’]MUST have a James in there girlfriend!”</p>
<p>“I don’t think I could ever fit a [COLOR=‘Blue’]James in my mouth.”</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/post-your-name-definitions/4232/22">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/post-your-name-definitions/4232/22</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 25 May 2010 11:59:15 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-4232-22</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/post-your-name-definitions/4232.rss">Post Your Name Definitions</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Post Your Name Definitions</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Ballsopt]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><span class="bbcode-b">Emiliano</span></p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>A hero - notably from Mexican history (Emiliano Zapata);<br>
a leader; someone who challenges convention</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-i">“He was so Emiliano when he rescued the cat from the sewer”</span></p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>:awesome:</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/post-your-name-definitions/4232/21">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/post-your-name-definitions/4232/21</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 25 May 2010 08:21:17 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-4232-21</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/post-your-name-definitions/4232.rss">Post Your Name Definitions</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
