<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>My Retro Platforming Adventures</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/my-retro-platforming-adventures/5843</link>
    <description>Hey guys,

After reading in the nostalgia thread someone say that Rayman and Rayman 2 were two of the best (if not THE best) games ever made, I decided to give them a play for myself. One quick Wine workaround later and I was playing it, and I have to say: It really is that good.

I missed out completely on every video game generation up to the second most-recent one. I never had a NES, a SNES, an N64, Dreamcast, PSX, PS2, Xbox or anything up to a Gamecube; my only experience came from playing some games at other peoples&#39; houses. I did once spend an entire weekend playing Spyro on a friend&#39;s PS2, but other than that my platforming experience was limited to Psychonauts and Super Mario 64 on an N64 emulator a few years ago. So I&#39;m really eager to continue playing those retro games that I missed out on all those years ago (at the moment platformers, but in the future who really knows?).

I&#39;m about half way through Rayman 2 (though I need to go back and collect the remaining lums - the rampant perfectionist within me demands I do so), but after that I was thinking:

Crash Bandicoot (one of them?)
Spyro (the first PSX one?)

But after that I&#39;m stumped. Does anyone else have any suggestions for retro games? Preferably platformers (seemingly the definitive genre that I have the least experience with), but anything else to waste my time with over the summer would also be great.

Peace.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2010 19:25:31 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Technology and Gaming</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/my-retro-platforming-adventures/5843.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>My Retro Platforming Adventures</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Maxx_Skywalker]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="FireTime">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/f/ba8739/40.png" class="avatar"> FireTime:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>BattleTanx needs a proper remake like yesterday.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Needs another sequel, not a remake. Course, 3DO has been under for quite some time.  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/frowning.png?v=9" title=":frowning:" class="emoji" alt=":frowning:"></p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="(rot)(fodder">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 (rot)(fodder:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>1st Snowboard kids (2), 2nd Paper Mario, 3rd Turok: Dinosaur Hunter…Great obscure games in my opinion.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I don’t think either of those games are considered obscure.</p>
<p>Turok was awesome. Hands down. Just sayin’</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/my-retro-platforming-adventures/5843/30">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/my-retro-platforming-adventures/5843/30</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2010 19:25:31 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-5843-30</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/my-retro-platforming-adventures/5843.rss">My Retro Platforming Adventures</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My Retro Platforming Adventures</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[loony636]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Alright, I encountered a game breaking bug in Spyro that prevents me from completing a number of levels in the dream world. While I could struggle through and try to complete what I can, I’m putting this down to a corrupted ISO and will look into re-downloading it in the future. I completed the game to 71% (allegedly), so I think I can speak for it pretty well. In the mean time, I’ve written down my thoughts on the first two games (feel free not to read them; its just my musings):</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Rayman 2</span></p>
<p><span class="bbcode-u">Liked</span>: Rayman!!!</p>
<p>Dialogue and voices (even if the PC version ones are just random garbled words), simple premise which allows for all the levels to be easily stringed together.</p>
<p>Different ways of getting through levels that make it interesting (like the snake monster and raindancing friend).</p>
<p>A reasonable variety in levels. There was no repetition so evident in other games like, say, Spyro, for instance.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-u">Didn’t Like</span>: The lava level. Dear god, they could not have designed a more annoying level if they’d tried. This was actually the deal breaker for me; I lost about an hour on this level and didn’t have the heart to go back.</p>
<p>The single weapon. As fun as the energy ball is, it gets a bit boring after a while. Other platformers mix it up with a variety of different ways to kill enemies, whereas here there’s only one.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Spyro</span></p>
<p><span class="bbcode-u">Liked</span>: He’s a tiny dragon. What’s not to like? Oh, that’s right. Most things.</p>
<p>The dragonfly. I liked him (Sparks?), mostly because he gave you lives (effectively) and helped pick up things. When he temporarily died I realised how much I’d relied on him to collect those damn crystals. He was probably the only thing that made it even slightly bearable.</p>
<p>Good clean fun. Most of the levels are quite short and can be dealt with in a matter of minutes, rather than hours. This ensures variety in the levels and a game that you can get through in a number of days, rather than weeks. That’s good for a platformer with such a limited premise and so much repetition, and makes it alright.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-u">Didn’t Like</span>: The amount of crystals. Jesus. Divide by 10 or something. Going into a level and having to collect 500 of those fuckers is ridiculous. Especially when 90-95% of them are ridiculously easy to find, and the remaining 5-10% are stupidly hard. It effectively involves you not only killing every single enemy on the entire map, but also scouring the back of every pillar, wall and cliff face to find the last three of them. Christ almighty, EASE OFF A LITTLE.</p>
<p>I liked mixing up the head butting and fire breathing, but I kept wanting something more. Almost every enemy is a one hit kill, and it ends up just being a bit repetitive. Even the enemies that you’re told to hit with special moves like the super charge can be killed just by flaming, so there’s no real challenge for most of the game. And most of the challenge comes from the frustration.</p>
<p>Level design where they deliberately wanted you to go off the edge of the game where it really looks like you shouldn’t go. In a few levels I just flew aimlessly around before realising that there wasn’t an invisible wall blocking me from going off the edge of the screen. Then, just after jumping with glee after thinking that I’d hacked the game, I saw the crystals. Fucking. Hell.</p>
<p>The lives system works well enough most of the time, forcing you to actually take care and work through levels systematically, but it ends up being a massive fucking pain when you get to the more frustrating levels. In a few of the levels you have to charge a number of enemies that stand perilously close to the edge, and which can hit you off, meaning that if you mis-time your charge even a little you’ll be back at the beginning (or your last save). Do that more than a few times and you’re gone. Successful implementation of the lives system was predicated on good level design and gameplay focus that did more than just make things frustrating, which it doesn’t do here.</p>
<p>The dash-jumping puzzles, especially in the Tree Tops level. This is mostly a lives-system complaint, but its also a frustration-inducing complain. Someone, please, destroy this level.</p>
<p>Anyway, I’m going to start with the NES games. Will post as I play them!</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/my-retro-platforming-adventures/5843/29">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/my-retro-platforming-adventures/5843/29</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2010 13:06:07 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-5843-29</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/my-retro-platforming-adventures/5843.rss">My Retro Platforming Adventures</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My Retro Platforming Adventures</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[_rot_fodder]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>SNES: 1st Hook, 2nd James Pond</p>
<p>N64: 1st Snowboard kids (2), 2nd Paper Mario, 3rd Turok: Dinosaur Hunter</p>
<p>In those orders. Great obscure games in my opinion, even if hook is brutally frusterating. I had snowboard kids one, so that is the nostalgia piece for me, but snowboard kids 2 really is the better game imo.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/my-retro-platforming-adventures/5843/28">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/my-retro-platforming-adventures/5843/28</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2010 07:10:17 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-5843-28</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/my-retro-platforming-adventures/5843.rss">My Retro Platforming Adventures</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My Retro Platforming Adventures</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[FireTime]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>BattleTanx needs a proper remake like yesterday.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/my-retro-platforming-adventures/5843/27">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/my-retro-platforming-adventures/5843/27</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2010 06:30:27 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-5843-27</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/my-retro-platforming-adventures/5843.rss">My Retro Platforming Adventures</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My Retro Platforming Adventures</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Maxx_Skywalker]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Nostalgia-Filled is an adequate description. My favorite platformers were Donkey Kong 64, Super Mario 64, Banjo-Kazooie/Tooie, Kirby 64: The Crystal Shards, Rayman 2, and Bomberman Heroes. Had some good times with these games. Haven’t played Conker yet, but it’s on my radar now that I have the Xbox remake. No one made platformers like Rare, you know?</p>
<p>I’m sad though that the 3D platformer genre pretty much died, along with vehicular combat. You know nothing beats Vigilante 8, Twisted Metal, and BattleTanx.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/my-retro-platforming-adventures/5843/26">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/my-retro-platforming-adventures/5843/26</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2010 00:09:05 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-5843-26</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/my-retro-platforming-adventures/5843.rss">My Retro Platforming Adventures</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My Retro Platforming Adventures</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[loony636]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Maxx Skywalker">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Maxx Skywalker:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>As a side note: I wasn’t impressed with either Tomba adventure, Rayman was a little dull, and Spyro didn’t hold the same charm as any of the N64 platformers. Just call me biased.  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/wink.png?v=9" title=":wink:" class="emoji" alt=":wink:"></p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I must say that Spyro has none of the charm of, say, Conker’s Bad Fur Day. But, then again, Spyro’s gameplay is very different; its full of a bunch of short and simple jewel and dragon hunts, whereas Conker’s is far more lols-driven. I suspect a day or two of Spyro and I’ll be done/bored of it; its quite repetitive and the version I have has broken music.</p>
<p>On the bright side, I found Wineskin which runs ePSXe <span class="bbcode-i">very</span> well. Much better than Winebottler.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Maxx Skywalker">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Maxx Skywalker:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Is it a bad thing when N64 and PSone titles are classified as retro?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I realise its probably not strictly accurate, but for me it feels retro, if by retro we just mean filled with nostalgia.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/my-retro-platforming-adventures/5843/25">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/my-retro-platforming-adventures/5843/25</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 15 Nov 2010 10:40:28 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-5843-25</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/my-retro-platforming-adventures/5843.rss">My Retro Platforming Adventures</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My Retro Platforming Adventures</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Maxx_Skywalker]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Is it a bad thing when N64 and PSone titles are classified as retro?</p>
<p>I prefer N64 games as classics and PSone games as obsolete (save for a few very excellent titles).</p>
<p>As a side note: I wasn’t impressed with either Tomba adventure, Rayman was a little dull, and Spyro didn’t hold the same charm as any of the N64 platformers. Just call me biased.  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/wink.png?v=9" title=":wink:" class="emoji" alt=":wink:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/my-retro-platforming-adventures/5843/24">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/my-retro-platforming-adventures/5843/24</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 15 Nov 2010 07:08:06 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-5843-24</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/my-retro-platforming-adventures/5843.rss">My Retro Platforming Adventures</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My Retro Platforming Adventures</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[loony636]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Well I got to the lava level in Rayman 2 and was defeated by how stupidly retarded it was. Then I quit and forgot that it wouldn’t save my progress. So I’ve replaced that game back into the game container for a while.</p>
<p>I got selected for the Battlestar Galactica Online Closed Beta, so that MMO is going to be taking some of my time. I spent an hour or so today getting ePSXe working on my Mac and Spyro works like a charm, so I’m going to spend a while playing that.</p>
<p>After that, however, I’ll get stuck right in to the game suggestions here, probably starting with the NES games (and progressing chronologically). I leave on a holiday in about two weeks at which point I’ll have to stop playing, but in the interim I’m hoping to take some large chunks out of the list.</p>
<p>And if I haven’t said so before, thanks for the suggestions! I’m dying a little from the nostalgia, and its proving a welcome distraction from study  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=9" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/my-retro-platforming-adventures/5843/23">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/my-retro-platforming-adventures/5843/23</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 15 Nov 2010 05:24:14 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-5843-23</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/my-retro-platforming-adventures/5843.rss">My Retro Platforming Adventures</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My Retro Platforming Adventures</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[mankyman6]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>The first resident evil for PS1</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/my-retro-platforming-adventures/5843/22">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/my-retro-platforming-adventures/5843/22</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 13 Nov 2010 17:37:53 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-5843-22</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/my-retro-platforming-adventures/5843.rss">My Retro Platforming Adventures</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My Retro Platforming Adventures</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[FireTime]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>casino zone.</p>
<p>nuff sed</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/my-retro-platforming-adventures/5843/21">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/my-retro-platforming-adventures/5843/21</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 13 Nov 2010 17:23:29 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-5843-21</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/my-retro-platforming-adventures/5843.rss">My Retro Platforming Adventures</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My Retro Platforming Adventures</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[taxi_evil]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Sonic the Hedgehog<br>
Sonic the Hedgehog 2</p>
<p>Two greatest platformers ever made, back on the Megadrive.</p>
<p>Also Ghouls N’ Ghosts, but it is harder than a diamond-tipped Jesus</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/my-retro-platforming-adventures/5843/20">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/my-retro-platforming-adventures/5843/20</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 13 Nov 2010 16:37:35 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-5843-20</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/my-retro-platforming-adventures/5843.rss">My Retro Platforming Adventures</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My Retro Platforming Adventures</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[loony636]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Narfin">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/n/46a35a/40.png" class="avatar"> Narfin:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Are you going to play some retro games on the consoles or in emulators? Because for some games, that makes a huge difference. Still owning everything back to an NES (I never once sold or discarded a console) I can’t find the same enjoyment in emulators. Unless of course I use a usb controller that feels very similar to the classic controllers, then it’s tolerable.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I, unfortunately, don’t have the time or money to get around to buying all those consoles, or even buy a controller at the moment. I fear I must put up with the keyboard for now.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="FireTime">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/f/ba8739/40.png" class="avatar"> FireTime:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Get, and play Conker’s bad fur day now! Amazing platformer that pushed the n64 to its absolute limits. Was the first game to feature in game lip syncing and a multitude of game play elements.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Conker’s was (is) fantastic. I completely forgot that I got it working on an N64 emulator years ago. I still remember throwing rolls of toilet paper into a giant poo monster…fun times.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/my-retro-platforming-adventures/5843/19">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/my-retro-platforming-adventures/5843/19</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 13 Nov 2010 14:03:26 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-5843-19</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/my-retro-platforming-adventures/5843.rss">My Retro Platforming Adventures</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My Retro Platforming Adventures</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[jerry]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>yeah, Abe was awesome  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/smiley.png?v=9" title=":smiley:" class="emoji" alt=":smiley:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/my-retro-platforming-adventures/5843/18">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/my-retro-platforming-adventures/5843/18</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 13 Nov 2010 13:50:46 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-5843-18</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/my-retro-platforming-adventures/5843.rss">My Retro Platforming Adventures</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My Retro Platforming Adventures</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[ac3d]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Katana">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/k/db5fbb/40.png" class="avatar"> Katana:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>How about Banjo Kazooie and Banjo Tooie?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I was about to rage but, good old Ctrl+F  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=9" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
<p>Also, Abe’s Oddysee</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/my-retro-platforming-adventures/5843/17">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/my-retro-platforming-adventures/5843/17</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 13 Nov 2010 11:32:39 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-5843-17</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/my-retro-platforming-adventures/5843.rss">My Retro Platforming Adventures</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My Retro Platforming Adventures</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[nunzilla]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Silent Hill on PSX.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/my-retro-platforming-adventures/5843/16">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/my-retro-platforming-adventures/5843/16</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 13 Nov 2010 01:43:06 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-5843-16</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/my-retro-platforming-adventures/5843.rss">My Retro Platforming Adventures</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My Retro Platforming Adventures</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Urug]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>My favourite one i played on Sega Mega Drive II:<br>
<span class="bbcode-b">Maui Mallard in Cold Shadow</span></p>
<p>Incredible song:<br>
<a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=wNNADbkI9eg&amp;feature=related" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=wNNADbkI9eg&amp;feature=related</a></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/my-retro-platforming-adventures/5843/15">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/my-retro-platforming-adventures/5843/15</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 13 Nov 2010 00:38:45 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-5843-15</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/my-retro-platforming-adventures/5843.rss">My Retro Platforming Adventures</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My Retro Platforming Adventures</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[blastedt]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I am seeing a distinct lack of Mario here.</p>
<p>Play Super Mario Bros. 1 and 3.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/my-retro-platforming-adventures/5843/14">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/my-retro-platforming-adventures/5843/14</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 12 Nov 2010 23:56:34 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-5843-14</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/my-retro-platforming-adventures/5843.rss">My Retro Platforming Adventures</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My Retro Platforming Adventures</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Katana]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>How about Banjo Kazooie and Banjo Tooie?</p>
<p>Also maybe Goldeneye 64 or Perfect Dark (same engine, same style, etc). It’d seem like a POS compared to many modern shooters, but there’s a lot of gunning through many enemies at once which is fun.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/my-retro-platforming-adventures/5843/13">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/my-retro-platforming-adventures/5843/13</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 12 Nov 2010 23:46:05 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-5843-13</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/my-retro-platforming-adventures/5843.rss">My Retro Platforming Adventures</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My Retro Platforming Adventures</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[FireTime]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Get, and play Conker’s bad fur day now! Amazing platformer that pushed the n64 to its absolute limits. Was the first game to feature in game lip syncing and a multitude of game play elements.</p>
<p>Also to this day i’m still not sure whether is has the absolute best or worst ending to a game ever.</p>
<p>If you want Roms I started <a href="https://firetime.dyndns.org/C:/Users/FireTime/Documents/roms/" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">my server</a> again, I’ll keep it up for a few days</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/my-retro-platforming-adventures/5843/12">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/my-retro-platforming-adventures/5843/12</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 12 Nov 2010 23:32:37 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-5843-12</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/my-retro-platforming-adventures/5843.rss">My Retro Platforming Adventures</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My Retro Platforming Adventures</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Leet]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>PSX:</p>
<p>Resident Evil 2 and 3<br>
Crash Bandicoot 1,2,3 and Crash Team Racing.<br>
Tomba and Tomba 2<br>
Ghost in (a?)the Shell<br>
Digimon World<br>
Syphon Filter 2,3 (Never played 1).</p>
<p>Enjoy!</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/my-retro-platforming-adventures/5843/11">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/my-retro-platforming-adventures/5843/11</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 12 Nov 2010 22:27:22 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-5843-11</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/my-retro-platforming-adventures/5843.rss">My Retro Platforming Adventures</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My Retro Platforming Adventures</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[russilker]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>This isn’t exactly “retro”, or a platformer, but GTA II is, was and forever will be one of my favorite games with a huge amount of replayability. And, yes, I’ve mentioned it in other threads, but its just <span class="bbcode-i">that</span> good.</p>
<p>EDIT: Plus, its free to download from the Rockstar Games website</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/my-retro-platforming-adventures/5843/10">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/my-retro-platforming-adventures/5843/10</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 12 Nov 2010 19:09:52 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-5843-10</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/my-retro-platforming-adventures/5843.rss">My Retro Platforming Adventures</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My Retro Platforming Adventures</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[bobbo]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><span class="bbcode-b"><span class="bbcode-u">Snes or Sega Genesis:</span></span> Zombies Ate My Neighbors, Earthworm Jim 2</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b"><span class="bbcode-u">N64:</span></span> Silicon Valley</p>
<p>just a few that came to mind.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/my-retro-platforming-adventures/5843/9">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/my-retro-platforming-adventures/5843/9</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 12 Nov 2010 19:05:31 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-5843-9</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/my-retro-platforming-adventures/5843.rss">My Retro Platforming Adventures</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My Retro Platforming Adventures</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Narfin]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Are you going to play some retro games on the consoles or in emulators? Because for some games, that makes a huge difference. Still owning everything back to an NES (I never once sold or discarded a console) I can’t find the same enjoyment in emulators. Unless of course I use a usb controller that feels very similar to the classic controllers, then it’s tolerable.</p>
<p>Anyway, here is my list of <span class="bbcode-i">some</span> of my favorite games ordered by console, with YouTube links:</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b"><span class="bbcode-u">NES</span></span><br>
-<a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=BMpZznee74I" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Micro Machines</a> (One of my all-time favorite games)<br>
-<a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=7tiL_R3QIVs" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Rampage</a> (kinda boring without a friend though)<br>
-<a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=_Mq1kJ25LVA" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Snake, Rattle &amp; Roll</a> (probably my favorite NES game of all time)<br>
-<a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=kWMyoNhGHbk" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Contra</a><br>
-Of course the ever-popular <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=2SfvhZgD7Bk&amp;feature=related" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Super Mario Brothers</a> (1 &amp; 3)<br>
-Many, many more, but for the sake of post length let’s leave it there</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-u"><span class="bbcode-b">SNES</span></span><br>
-Of course the legendary <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=K__xF33Zwt0" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Donkey Kong Country</a> (Both 1 &amp; 2 were great)<br>
-<a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=8uS9lIxuED8" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Kirby Superstar</a><br>
-<a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=LsUxIhCEaV8" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Starfox</a> (The N64 version looks a lot nicer, if this one hurts your eyeballs)</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b"><span class="bbcode-u">Sega Genesis</span></span><br>
-<a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=19DyaxVzctg&amp;feature=related" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Lemmings</a> (My absolute favorite game of all time, but make sure it’s the Sega version; the NES version and sequels were all pretty bad)<br>
-<a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=-MRLNrlFYs8" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Marble Madness</a> (again, the Sega version only)<br>
-<a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=IdZO_e0hHdc&amp;feature=related" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Sonic the Hedgehog 2</a> (skip the stupid 35 second video intro in the link)</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b"><span class="bbcode-u">N64</span></span><br>
-<a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Ipx7kxSbF48" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Super Smash Brothers</a><br>
-<a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=t1iZUEjoALM" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Donkey Kong 64</a> (really long game, at a rather slow pace)<br>
-<a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=aundeN2eX_E" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Mario Kart 64</a></p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b"><span class="bbcode-u">PlayStation</span></span> - I really wish I could give experienced suggestions, but I’ve never owned very many games for the PS1. Here’s all the help I can give:<br>
-<a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=UZWlRGOhTCc" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Twisted Metal</a> (<span class="hashtag">#2</span> was my favorite, <span class="hashtag">#3</span> was my least fav. of the three)<br>
-<a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=-YFWgJplzGo" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Jet Moto</a> (So many memories xD)<br>
-And you named it, <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=_9duLa-mixQ" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Crash Bandicoot</a></p>
<p>I’m going to stop there to avoid any tl;dr, the only games from Xbox I ever liked were Halo 1 and Crimson Skies, and I assume I don’t need to mention Half-Life as the greatest game of all time. Also, the list for classic PC games is too endless for me, I started playing them before I was old enough to write.</p>
<p>Cheers!</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/my-retro-platforming-adventures/5843/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/my-retro-platforming-adventures/5843/8</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 12 Nov 2010 16:39:46 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-5843-8</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/my-retro-platforming-adventures/5843.rss">My Retro Platforming Adventures</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My Retro Platforming Adventures</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[szparrow]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>But you can’t say it’s a bad game.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/my-retro-platforming-adventures/5843/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/my-retro-platforming-adventures/5843/7</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 12 Nov 2010 16:39:04 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-5843-7</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/my-retro-platforming-adventures/5843.rss">My Retro Platforming Adventures</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My Retro Platforming Adventures</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Mr.Shadow]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>^bscly</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/my-retro-platforming-adventures/5843/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/my-retro-platforming-adventures/5843/6</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 12 Nov 2010 12:15:43 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-5843-6</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/my-retro-platforming-adventures/5843.rss">My Retro Platforming Adventures</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
