<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>My Mod Needs You!</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/my-mod-needs-you/8758</link>
    <description>Hello fellow pirates, rapists, and pillagers... oh wait! Wrong speech!

 Hello fellow modders. 

I&#39;ve decided to post this up as I have thought of creating an intense single player mod with the potential to be multiplayer and already started to build some levels and have started writing the story to follow. I need a hard working reliable team that can use the Source Engine to its full potential and push the boundaries of the game engine. People that are willing to take orders like mindless drones but also throw their own ideas into the mix of things without going too far off topic or away from the script. You will also need to be open to constructive criticism and who can work and script to the thing I want for the mod to give you a real sense of the environment.
I&#39;m looking for; 
•	Experienced Mod Creators - To help copy game files and place the mod in one place and write simple installation programs.
•	Modellers - For the creation of London&#39;s objects, weapons and characters. (People, Cars, busses, police, soldiers, weapons)
•	World Builders (Experience preferred) - to create highly detailed worlds in Valve&#39;s Hammer Editor and creating puzzles to prevent you getting from a-b for the ultimate experience.
•	Animators - To add life to models, characters and weapons.
•	Scripter&#39;s\Coders - To manipulate things to make them how we want them and put the game together and create cutscenes
•	Texture Artists - Creating detailed high resolution textures and bump maps for each map, characters and weapons...
•	2D Artists - To draw comic book style images for cut scenes.
•	Sound engineers - To record some authentic sounds to throw into the game creating the best moods and experiences for the players.

The Mod: 

AXIOM (Ax-e-om) 
The word &quot;axiom&quot; comes from the Greek word axioma, a verbal noun from the verb axioein, meaning &quot;to deem worthy&quot; or in a modern concept &quot;truth&quot;.

The Plot:
The story or plot will be set in the not too distant future in the bleak depths of society in a once thriving city (London) which is now under the oppressive watch of the goverments counter-terrorism act. Surrounded by check points and police, held under the grasp and control of the Army everyone is being watched. 

You are a normal man, an artist in the wrong place at the wrong time... Framed for a crime you did not commit... A terrorist attack and the blame has been pinned on you.

•	Your adventure would take you from some of the city&#39;s famous locations. Marvel in the wonders of Piccadilly circus, Big Ben and houses of parliament, Battersea power station and some of the less popular underworld of London as you go on the run from the government in search of the truth.  
•	Use your friends, and various gang land contacts to fight your way through the streets, sewers and buildings around London acquiring realistic weapons to defend yourself. 
•	Take the challenge and navigate your way around each map with puzzles and hordes of police and soldiers.

To summarise:
If you think you might like the sound of this project visit our ModDB website at;
[url]https://www.moddb.com/mods/axiom[/url]

Or visit our page at;
[url]https://www.wix.com/daviz1987/candle-design#!home|mainPage[/url] 

Contact me through my website with a reference to your work (e.g. pictures, web portfolio etc) and I will forward you a small part of the script to opening scene of this game. 

Regards,
Dan Davies, CANDLe Design


Small videos of some work - 
[url]https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=qFtoiNUKopU[/url]
[url]https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=rCpovXMP52k[/url]
[url]https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=T5w9bzC8Hk8[/url]</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 30 May 2012 21:36:48 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Help and Support</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/my-mod-needs-you/8758.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>My Mod Needs You!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[PumaB]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>this is a good metro map <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=LFk20E2oa88" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=LFk20E2oa88</a></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/my-mod-needs-you/8758/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/my-mod-needs-you/8758/8</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 30 May 2012 21:36:48 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8758-8</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/my-mod-needs-you/8758.rss">My Mod Needs You!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My Mod Needs You!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[daviz1987]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Jack Freeman">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Jack Freeman:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Nice mapping!<br>
I could perhaps help with my prop modelling skills… Not the best, but I can do small and medium sized props.<br>
Also, I would recommend you to either buy a domain and get a webhost or use X10’s free (extremely limited) web hosting. Still better than Wix though.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Sure, if you feel you can help then contact me with any work you would like… i have tones of props need making.<br>
send us an email of skill you have, ill send you my script, tell me what you think.<br>
do you know any other modelers?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/my-mod-needs-you/8758/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/my-mod-needs-you/8758/7</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 30 May 2012 20:37:47 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8758-7</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/my-mod-needs-you/8758.rss">My Mod Needs You!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My Mod Needs You!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Jack_Freeman]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Nice mapping!<br>
I could perhaps help with my prop modelling skills… Not the best, but I can do small and medium sized props.<br>
Also, I would recommend you to either buy a domain and get a webhost or use X10’s free (extremely limited) web hosting. Still better than Wix though.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/my-mod-needs-you/8758/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/my-mod-needs-you/8758/6</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 30 May 2012 17:12:49 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8758-6</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/my-mod-needs-you/8758.rss">My Mod Needs You!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My Mod Needs You!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[daviz1987]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>i have began work on the first chapter now…</p>
<p>beta video… <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=T5w9bzC8Hk8" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=T5w9bzC8Hk8</a></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/my-mod-needs-you/8758/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/my-mod-needs-you/8758/5</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 30 May 2012 16:06:07 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8758-5</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/my-mod-needs-you/8758.rss">My Mod Needs You!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My Mod Needs You!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[OrderOfDagon]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Yobym">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/y/8c91f0/40.png" class="avatar"> Yobym:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I have realized that I have used “don’t” a lot of times; for some reason it is stuck in my head.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Don’t worry about it.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/my-mod-needs-you/8758/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/my-mod-needs-you/8758/4</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 13 May 2012 23:54:31 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8758-4</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/my-mod-needs-you/8758.rss">My Mod Needs You!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My Mod Needs You!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[lithium.bb]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I don’t imagine that he was looking for the BMS devs to help, but rather to the community.<br>
Anyways, looks interesting, I might give it a go :3 Haven’t had much incentive to do any mapping lately, so…</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/my-mod-needs-you/8758/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/my-mod-needs-you/8758/3</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 13 May 2012 17:46:25 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8758-3</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/my-mod-needs-you/8758.rss">My Mod Needs You!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My Mod Needs You!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Yobym]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Well, don,t expect the BMS dev team to help anytime soon. We have waited like around 8 years, don’t want that to get any bigger. I would help but i don’t have much skill in creating a game. Good luck and don’t give up like a lot of mods have in the past.</p>
<p>I have realized that i have used “don’t” a lot of times, for some reason it is stuck in my head.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/my-mod-needs-you/8758/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/my-mod-needs-you/8758/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 13 May 2012 17:03:09 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8758-2</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/my-mod-needs-you/8758.rss">My Mod Needs You!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My Mod Needs You!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[daviz1987]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Hello fellow pirates, rapists, and pillagers… oh wait! Wrong speech!</p>
<p>Hello fellow modders.</p>
<p>I’ve decided to post this up as I have thought of creating an intense single player mod with the potential to be multiplayer and already started to build some levels and have started writing the story to follow. I need a hard working reliable team that can use the Source Engine to its full potential and push the boundaries of the game engine. People that are willing to take orders like mindless drones but also throw their own ideas into the mix of things without going too far off topic or away from the script. You will also need to be open to constructive criticism and who can work and script to the thing I want for the mod to give you a real sense of the environment.<br>
I’m looking for;<br>
•	Experienced Mod Creators - To help copy game files and place the mod in one place and write simple installation programs.<br>
•	Modellers - For the creation of London’s objects, weapons and characters. (People, Cars, busses, police, soldiers, weapons)<br>
•	World Builders (Experience preferred) - to create highly detailed worlds in Valve’s Hammer Editor and creating puzzles to prevent you getting from a-b for the ultimate experience.<br>
•	Animators - To add life to models, characters and weapons.<br>
•	Scripter’s\Coders - To manipulate things to make them how we want them and put the game together and create cutscenes<br>
•	Texture Artists - Creating detailed high resolution textures and bump maps for each map, characters and weapons…<br>
•	2D Artists - To draw comic book style images for cut scenes.<br>
•	Sound engineers - To record some authentic sounds to throw into the game creating the best moods and experiences for the players.</p>
<p>The Mod:</p>
<p>AXIOM (Ax-e-om)<br>
The word “axiom” comes from the Greek word axioma, a verbal noun from the verb axioein, meaning “to deem worthy” or in a modern concept “truth”.</p>
<p>The Plot:<br>
The story or plot will be set in the not too distant future in the bleak depths of society in a once thriving city (London) which is now under the oppressive watch of the goverments counter-terrorism act. Surrounded by check points and police, held under the grasp and control of the Army everyone is being watched.</p>
<p>You are a normal man, an artist in the wrong place at the wrong time… Framed for a crime you did not commit… A terrorist attack and the blame has been pinned on you.</p>
<p>•	Your adventure would take you from some of the city’s famous locations. Marvel in the wonders of Piccadilly circus, Big Ben and houses of parliament, Battersea power station and some of the less popular underworld of London as you go on the run from the government in search of the truth.<br>
•	Use your friends, and various gang land contacts to fight your way through the streets, sewers and buildings around London acquiring realistic weapons to defend yourself.<br>
•	Take the challenge and navigate your way around each map with puzzles and hordes of police and soldiers.</p>
<p>To summarise:<br>
If you think you might like the sound of this project visit our ModDB website at;<br>
<a href="https://www.moddb.com/mods/axiom" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://www.moddb.com/mods/axiom</a></p>
<p>Or visit our page at;<br>
<a href="https://www.wix.com/daviz1987/candle-design#!home%7CmainPage" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://www.wix.com/daviz1987/candle-design#!home|mainPage</a></p>
<p>Contact me through my website with a reference to your work (e.g. pictures, web portfolio etc) and I will forward you a small part of the script to opening scene of this game.</p>
<p>Regards,<br>
Dan Davies, CANDLe Design</p>
<p>Small videos of some work -<br>
<a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=qFtoiNUKopU" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=qFtoiNUKopU</a><br>
<a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=rCpovXMP52k" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=rCpovXMP52k</a><br>
<a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=T5w9bzC8Hk8" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=T5w9bzC8Hk8</a></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/my-mod-needs-you/8758/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/my-mod-needs-you/8758/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 13 May 2012 14:46:03 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8758-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/my-mod-needs-you/8758.rss">My Mod Needs You!</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
