<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>A problem with soundtrack</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/a-problem-with-soundtrack/13867</link>
    <description>Hello everyone. 

I bought the game today, played a little bit and I noticed that there is no soundtrack in the game. For example, early in the game, when you in the train, I&#39;m not had heard the song Black Mesa Inbound. What is the problem?

UPD: I installed the game on another computer with the same system (Windows 8.1 64-bit) - the problem persists, the soundtrack is missing. Is the problem in the system?

P.S. Sorry for my bad english.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 May 2016 11:42:05 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>In-game Issues</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/a-problem-with-soundtrack/13867.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>A problem with soundtrack</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[djcj]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="bardsong">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/b/3ab097/40.png" class="avatar"> bardsong:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Have managed to fix this annoying issue by manually installing every Visual C++ redist from Microsoft; 2005, 2010, 2012, 2013, 2015. both x86 and x64.<br>
Also on Windows 10 and I think 8 and 8.1, make sure the “Give me updates for other Microsoft products when I update Windows.” is ticked in the advanced options area of Windows Update because that will update visual c++ redists as well.<br>
Steam cloud seems to have no effect on whether or not the music works after updating vcredist so don’t worry about that.<br>
Hope this helps people still stuck reinstalling over and over again and turning steamcloud off and on again.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Installing and updating all the Visual C++ redist packages did it for me. Thanks for that tip.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/a-problem-with-soundtrack/13867/24">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/a-problem-with-soundtrack/13867/24</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 17 May 2016 11:42:05 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13867-24</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/a-problem-with-soundtrack/13867.rss">A problem with soundtrack</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>A problem with soundtrack</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[bardsong]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Have managed to fix this annoying issue by manually installing every Visual C++ redist from Microsoft; 2005, 2010, 2012, 2013, 2015. both x86 and x64.<br>
Also on Windows 10 and I think 8 and 8.1, make sure the “Give me updates for other Microsoft products when I update Windows.” is ticked in the advanced options area of Windows Update because that will update visual c++ redists as well.<br>
Steam cloud seems to have no effect on whether or not the music works after updating vcredist so don’t worry about that.<br>
Hope this helps people still stuck reinstalling over and over again and turning steamcloud off and on again.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/a-problem-with-soundtrack/13867/23">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/a-problem-with-soundtrack/13867/23</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 23 Feb 2016 03:36:46 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13867-23</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/a-problem-with-soundtrack/13867.rss">A problem with soundtrack</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>A problem with soundtrack</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Aden_D_T]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="FurianAvenger69">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/f/ac91a4/40.png" class="avatar"> FurianAvenger69:</div>
<blockquote>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Feline">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/f/ecd19e/40.png" class="avatar"> Feline:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I solved the problem as follows:</p>
<ol>
<li>Start Steam.</li>
<li>Disable Steam Cloud.</li>
<li>Delete all files in Steam\userdata\SteamID\AppID.</li>
<li>Start the game to create fresh (and thus different) new files.</li>
<li>Exit the game and Steam.</li>
<li>Delete remotecache.vdf in Steam\userdata\SteamID\AppID.</li>
<li>Start Steam.</li>
<li>Enable Steam Cloud and “Sync conflict” should appear in your game status.<br>
Note that this method may not affect all the files (and you need to modify all of them if you want to delete all of them later).</li>
</ol>
<p>After removing the data from the Steam Cloud, appeared soundtrack. Now everything works fine.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Steam\userdata\SteamID\AppID isn’t a valid file path for me… after Steam\userdata\ my only folder option is labeled “176755873” and when clicked leads to more gibberish folders. Running Windows 10 and downloaded off steam. Please help. I have 0 sound in this game  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/frowning.png?v=9" title=":frowning:" class="emoji" alt=":frowning:"></p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>What is going on, is that you’re seeing a number that steam uses to identify a user, called your SteamID just like in the url above. If you only have one folder with numbers that had lots of numbers in it, then what you need to do is find the content id number of black mesa. If there is more than one then you probably have more than one user using steam on your computer and you’ll have to figure out which folder is who’s based on things like the number of games each of you own or other similar simple things like that. Now, what you are looking for, is called the AppID of black mesa, also just as stated in the url above in your repost. For me that number is 362890 and that may be the same for you so if you wanna try it skip to step 3.</p>
<ol>
<li>
<p>To find the black mesa content id number, so that you can find the right folder to open, you have to go into your steam library.  Once there right click on retail black mesa and select the option to “Create desktop shortcut”. Once you do that, go to your desktop and find the black mesa shortcut you just created. IF YOU ALREADY HAVE A BLACK MESA SHORTCUT ON YOUR DESKTOP(Skip to here) you obviously don’t need a new one.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>What you do now is right click on the desktop icon shortcut you created and then click properties. Either under the tab that says details, or web document there should be a url that looks like this “steam://rungameid/362890”. The number you need to identify the folder you need to open to remove cloud files from is that number at the end of the file.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Now what you do is go back into that folder that has the number that identifies the steam user’s account, (within the filepath “Steam\userdata\SteamID”) and go into where the long list of folders is named with all sorts of different numbers, and you look for the one with that black mesa content id number, the “AppID”, which was 362890 for me, (which makes my filepath look like this "Steam\userdata\SteamID\362890 with my steam id missing for security.) You open up the black mesa folder id’ed by that number and follow the rest of the steps that you reposted above to clear out your cloud data as written in that nice list and you should be golden.</p>
</li>
</ol>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/a-problem-with-soundtrack/13867/22">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/a-problem-with-soundtrack/13867/22</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 24 Jan 2016 11:24:49 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13867-22</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/a-problem-with-soundtrack/13867.rss">A problem with soundtrack</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>A problem with soundtrack</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[FurianAvenger69]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Feline">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/f/ecd19e/40.png" class="avatar"> Feline:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I solved the problem as follows:</p>
<ol>
<li>Start Steam.</li>
<li>Disable Steam Cloud.</li>
<li>Delete all files in Steam\userdata\SteamID\AppID.</li>
<li>Start the game to create fresh (and thus different) new files.</li>
<li>Exit the game and Steam.</li>
<li>Delete remotecache.vdf in Steam\userdata\SteamID\AppID.</li>
<li>Start Steam.</li>
<li>Enable Steam Cloud and “Sync conflict” should appear in your game status.<br>
Note that this method may not affect all the files (and you need to modify all of them if you want to delete all of them later).</li>
</ol>
<p>After removing the data from the Steam Cloud, appeared soundtrack. Now everything works fine.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Steam\userdata\SteamID\AppID isn’t a valid file path for me… after Steam\userdata\ my only folder option is labeled “176755873” and when clicked leads to more gibberish folders. Running Windows 10 and downloaded off steam. Please help. I have 0 sound in this game  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/frowning.png?v=9" title=":frowning:" class="emoji" alt=":frowning:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/a-problem-with-soundtrack/13867/21">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/a-problem-with-soundtrack/13867/21</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jan 2016 22:45:01 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13867-21</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/a-problem-with-soundtrack/13867.rss">A problem with soundtrack</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>A problem with soundtrack</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Aden_D_T]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Feline">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/f/ecd19e/40.png" class="avatar"> Feline:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I solved the problem as follows:</p>
<ol>
<li>Start Steam.</li>
<li>Disable Steam Cloud.</li>
<li>Delete all files in Steam\userdata\SteamID\AppID.</li>
<li>Start the game to create fresh (and thus different) new files.</li>
<li>Exit the game and Steam.</li>
<li>Delete remotecache.vdf in Steam\userdata\SteamID\AppID.</li>
<li>Start Steam.</li>
<li>Enable Steam Cloud and “Sync conflict” should appear in your game status.<br>
Note that this method may not affect all the files (and you need to modify all of them if you want to delete all of them later).</li>
</ol>
<p>After removing the data from the Steam Cloud, appeared soundtrack. Now everything works fine.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Okay so after meticulously retrying this solution after once again wiping my installation of black mesa this fix worked perfectly! So if this didn’t work for you the first time, literally keep trying it, cuz it is likely your entire problem.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/a-problem-with-soundtrack/13867/20">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/a-problem-with-soundtrack/13867/20</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 19 Jan 2016 00:08:14 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13867-20</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/a-problem-with-soundtrack/13867.rss">A problem with soundtrack</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>A problem with soundtrack</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[burke.brunson]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Feline">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/f/ecd19e/40.png" class="avatar"> Feline:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I solved the problem as follows:</p>
<ol>
<li>Start Steam.</li>
<li>Disable Steam Cloud.</li>
<li>Delete all files in Steam\userdata\SteamID\AppID.</li>
<li>Start the game to create fresh (and thus different) new files.</li>
<li>Exit the game and Steam.</li>
<li>Delete remotecache.vdf in Steam\userdata\SteamID\AppID.</li>
<li>Start Steam.</li>
<li>Enable Steam Cloud and “Sync conflict” should appear in your game status.<br>
Note that this method may not affect all the files (and you need to modify all of them if you want to delete all of them later).</li>
</ol>
<p>After removing the data from the Steam Cloud, appeared soundtrack. Now everything works fine.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I also have not been able to resolve this issue with the shown steps. I’ve tried them a few times and had no success. I also have tried reinstalling the game files and still encounter the issue. I am running a virtual-mode-Windows 10 setup with Parallels, which may be part of my problem. However, I am not so sure that it is - whenever I reach the part of the game where you climb up the ladder into a red-lighted duct and get chased by the snarks, the soundtrack song that is supposed to play there successfully loads and I hear it. Every other soundtrack song throughout the game does not load properly, though. It’s so weird…if anyone has another thought, I’d love to hear it.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/a-problem-with-soundtrack/13867/19">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/a-problem-with-soundtrack/13867/19</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 17 Jan 2016 16:50:38 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13867-19</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/a-problem-with-soundtrack/13867.rss">A problem with soundtrack</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>A problem with soundtrack</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Gord0n_FreeMan]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Hello Black Mesa Scientist, and friends of the Black Mesa Game, i have discovered something, and it led me to believe that it is directx related. I don’t really have a solution, probably if you look to update from microsoft or updater your directx files, unless you consider changing your OS to Win10 Pro as one solution. First time i played BMS steam, just after i bought it, i was on Windows 7 ultimate, directx 11; and last attempt on win7 was the last weeks of month december! And, every time i lauched the game via steam, as i supposed to, every single time the installer of dx poped up; and probably, failing; partially. Now, i got rid of that installing some dx pack from microsoft, one that did solve my problems among other games. But it seems, not on this one. But, eventually, i was going to upgrade anyway, since i love Win10 Pro. I opened it via steam, as usual, on the last week of december, using Windows 10 Professional with directx 11.1 this time, and dx12 for sound, also my current setup/OS. Guess what: only one time, One, the dx installer opened, the first time i ever launched the game under Win10 Pro OS. Aaaanndd,…SURPRISE. Once the game fully opened, i was looking at the menu, new game, overlay, etc. and…Listening to the Soundtrack! Now, what do you guys say? Since then i played 8 chapters, and every time, the soundtrack was, and is, there, even improved(sorry guys for the spoiler   <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/smiley.png?v=9" title=":smiley:" class="emoji" alt=":smiley:">  , etc. ). If you really HATE, like i did, “playing” with no soundtrack, and you are willing to change to Win10 Pro, the best out there my advise and evaluation, DO IT (or you can try to update your Windows OS directx instalation, but i don’t know to what result it leads). You can play with the mighty soundtrack, and have overall improvements too!(because os10, indeed).</p>
<p>Have a very safe, and productive day. :thumbup: [ProFist]</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/a-problem-with-soundtrack/13867/18">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/a-problem-with-soundtrack/13867/18</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Jan 2016 23:20:48 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13867-18</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/a-problem-with-soundtrack/13867.rss">A problem with soundtrack</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>A problem with soundtrack</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Aden_D_T]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Totally having the same issues! All the suggestions above similarly didn’t help me out at all. My music will not play in game,  and it says the same in the console about the files not being found. Looked in my files, and am having the same issues as everyone here. No music was ever unpacked and the ogg files just aren’t there. All other sounds work flawlessly. Hope either the devs see this and patch the issue if they can figure out why it’s happening or that somebody here figures out a fix…</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/a-problem-with-soundtrack/13867/17">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/a-problem-with-soundtrack/13867/17</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 30 Dec 2015 10:17:54 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13867-17</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/a-problem-with-soundtrack/13867.rss">A problem with soundtrack</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>A problem with soundtrack</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Bepples]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>This is the only thread I could find with the same issue. I recently installed Black Mesa to a new drive and it didn’t install (or perhaps didn’t extract) the music. There should be a “sounds” folder containing the music but this is missing. I have tried redownloading to the old drive and again to the new drive. I have also tried verifying the integrity of the game cache.</p>
<p>I’m not sure if it’s not downloading the music or it is and it just isn’t extracting it. This is what my bms file looks like before running the game for the first time:</p>
<p><a href="https://i.imgur.com/eP4BR1z.png" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://i.imgur.com/eP4BR1z.png</a></p>
<p>After I run the game, the “downloadlists” and “materials” folder appear, but no “sounds”.  I get console errors like these:</p>
<p>Failed to load sound “*<span class="hashtag">#ui</span>\gamestartup_1.ogg”, file probably missing from disk/repository<br>
Failed to load sound “#*music\bms - inbounda.ogg”, file probably missing from disk/repository</p>
<p>I also tried the steam cloud stuff above, but it didn’t help. It did reach the “Sync conflict” screen but I wasn’t sure which option to pick (local copy or cloud server).</p>
<p>I tried copying the “sounds” folder from the free mod version of the game, but this did not fix it even though it contained all the music files.</p>
<p>I don’t understand why reinstalling entirely doesn’t work, but no matter what I do it will not extract the music files. Oddly enough, all the in-game sounds work; just not the music.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/a-problem-with-soundtrack/13867/16">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/a-problem-with-soundtrack/13867/16</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 13 Nov 2015 13:39:51 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13867-16</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/a-problem-with-soundtrack/13867.rss">A problem with soundtrack</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>A problem with soundtrack</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[triceratopnotch]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Feline">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/f/ecd19e/40.png" class="avatar"> Feline:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I solved the problem as follows:</p>
<ol>
<li>Start Steam.</li>
<li>Disable Steam Cloud.</li>
<li>Delete all files in Steam\userdata\SteamID\AppID.</li>
<li>Start the game to create fresh (and thus different) new files.</li>
<li>Exit the game and Steam.</li>
<li>Delete remotecache.vdf in Steam\userdata\SteamID\AppID.</li>
<li>Start Steam.</li>
<li>Enable Steam Cloud and “Sync conflict” should appear in your game status.<br>
Note that this method may not affect all the files (and you need to modify all of them if you want to delete all of them later).</li>
</ol>
<p>After removing the data from the Steam Cloud, appeared soundtrack. Now everything works fine.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Followed those instructions but no dice.</p>
<p>So bummed out  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/frowning.png?v=9" title=":frowning:" class="emoji" alt=":frowning:">  Not going to play SP until I can fix.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/a-problem-with-soundtrack/13867/15">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/a-problem-with-soundtrack/13867/15</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 10 May 2015 03:20:51 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13867-15</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/a-problem-with-soundtrack/13867.rss">A problem with soundtrack</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>A problem with soundtrack</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Feline]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="KCKI113R">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/user_avatar/leakfree.org/kcki113r/40/4336_2.png" class="avatar"> KCKI113R:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Tried that. Tried a lot of things. Soundtrack still not working for me. Any more ideas, or should I just wait patiently?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Then reinstall the game again.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/a-problem-with-soundtrack/13867/14">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/a-problem-with-soundtrack/13867/14</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 09 May 2015 16:17:11 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13867-14</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/a-problem-with-soundtrack/13867.rss">A problem with soundtrack</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>A problem with soundtrack</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[KCKI113R]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Tried that. Tried a lot of things. Soundtrack still not working for me. Any more ideas, or should I just wait patiently?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/a-problem-with-soundtrack/13867/13">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/a-problem-with-soundtrack/13867/13</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 09 May 2015 14:23:36 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13867-13</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/a-problem-with-soundtrack/13867.rss">A problem with soundtrack</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>A problem with soundtrack</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[CatzEyes93]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>That cloud has caused me issues in the past.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/a-problem-with-soundtrack/13867/12">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/a-problem-with-soundtrack/13867/12</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 09 May 2015 12:50:32 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13867-12</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/a-problem-with-soundtrack/13867.rss">A problem with soundtrack</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>A problem with soundtrack</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Feline]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I solved the problem as follows:</p>
<ol>
<li>Start Steam.</li>
<li>Disable Steam Cloud.</li>
<li>Delete all files in Steam\userdata\SteamID\AppID.</li>
<li>Start the game to create fresh (and thus different) new files.</li>
<li>Exit the game and Steam.</li>
<li>Delete remotecache.vdf in Steam\userdata\SteamID\AppID.</li>
<li>Start Steam.</li>
<li>Enable Steam Cloud and “Sync conflict” should appear in your game status.<br>
Note that this method may not affect all the files (and you need to modify all of them if you want to delete all of them later).</li>
</ol>
<p>After removing the data from the Steam Cloud, appeared soundtrack. Now everything works fine.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/a-problem-with-soundtrack/13867/11">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/a-problem-with-soundtrack/13867/11</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 09 May 2015 09:26:16 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13867-11</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/a-problem-with-soundtrack/13867.rss">A problem with soundtrack</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>A problem with soundtrack</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[triceratopnotch]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Crypt">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/user_avatar/leakfree.org/crypt/40/4394_2.png" class="avatar"> Crypt:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>[sup]Did reinstalling fix it?[/sup]</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>No, still getting the same missing file message in the console. Is it possible that Steam just didn’t download these assets?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/a-problem-with-soundtrack/13867/10">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/a-problem-with-soundtrack/13867/10</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 09 May 2015 07:20:35 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13867-10</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/a-problem-with-soundtrack/13867.rss">A problem with soundtrack</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>A problem with soundtrack</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Stairway_To_Sto_Vo_K]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I also have the mod version installed, both are labeled “Black Mesa” in my library and the only sound issue I’ve encountered was the silent mp5 pickup which is a separate issue.<br>
Could installing the game to a non-standard directory path possibly cause something like this? All my music works fine and i installed it in the default location C:\Program Files\Steam\SteamApps</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/a-problem-with-soundtrack/13867/9">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/a-problem-with-soundtrack/13867/9</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 09 May 2015 05:17:21 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13867-9</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/a-problem-with-soundtrack/13867.rss">A problem with soundtrack</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>A problem with soundtrack</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypt]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>No, the two are completely separate. In fact, I still have the mod version installed, alongside the Steam release, albeit with a modified game name.<br>
[sup]Did reinstalling fix it?[/sup]</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/a-problem-with-soundtrack/13867/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/a-problem-with-soundtrack/13867/8</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 09 May 2015 05:09:58 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13867-8</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/a-problem-with-soundtrack/13867.rss">A problem with soundtrack</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>A problem with soundtrack</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[triceratopnotch]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Update from me: deleted local content via Steam and re-downloaded. Did have the original mod installed beforehand - could this be a factor?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/a-problem-with-soundtrack/13867/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/a-problem-with-soundtrack/13867/7</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 09 May 2015 04:42:52 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13867-7</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/a-problem-with-soundtrack/13867.rss">A problem with soundtrack</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>A problem with soundtrack</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Feline]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="DaftMink">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/d/8e7dd6/40.png" class="avatar"> DaftMink:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Is it giving a red error saying it can’t find the file or just not playing ?.<br>
In the menu under “Audio” there’s “Music volume” which if turned off could cause the problem.</p>
<p>You can also use in console</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Yes, a message appears in the console: "<span class="bbcode-i">Failed to load sound “*<span class="hashtag">#ui</span>\gamestartup_1.ogg”, file probably missing from disk/repository"</span> and  "<span class="bbcode-i">Failed to load sound “#*music\bms - inbounda.ogg”, file probably missing from disk/repository", </span>etc.</p>
<p>Music volume - High. Music is still missing.<br>
<span class="bbcode-i"></span></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/a-problem-with-soundtrack/13867/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/a-problem-with-soundtrack/13867/6</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 07 May 2015 20:49:41 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13867-6</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/a-problem-with-soundtrack/13867.rss">A problem with soundtrack</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>A problem with soundtrack</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[DaftMink]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Is it giving a red error saying it can’t find the file or just not playing ?.<br>
In the menu under “Audio” there’s “Music volume” which if turned off could cause the problem.</p>
<p>You can also use in console</p>
<pre><code class="lang-auto">snd_musicvolume "1.000000"</code></pre>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/a-problem-with-soundtrack/13867/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/a-problem-with-soundtrack/13867/5</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 07 May 2015 20:24:04 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13867-5</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/a-problem-with-soundtrack/13867.rss">A problem with soundtrack</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>A problem with soundtrack</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[KCKI113R]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I’ve experienced the same problem. No music</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/a-problem-with-soundtrack/13867/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/a-problem-with-soundtrack/13867/4</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 07 May 2015 19:43:07 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13867-4</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/a-problem-with-soundtrack/13867.rss">A problem with soundtrack</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>A problem with soundtrack</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Feline]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>UPD 2: If I start a new game must be played after downloading the song “Inbound”, but the song is not playing. In the console, the following message appears: “Failed to load sound” # * music \ bms - inbounda.ogg “, file probably missing from disk / repositor”.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/a-problem-with-soundtrack/13867/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/a-problem-with-soundtrack/13867/3</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 07 May 2015 13:32:27 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13867-3</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/a-problem-with-soundtrack/13867.rss">A problem with soundtrack</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>A problem with soundtrack</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[triceratopnotch]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Just registered to report the same issue - no music. Holding off playing because I know how amazing the soundtrack is  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/wink.png?v=9" title=":wink:" class="emoji" alt=":wink:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/a-problem-with-soundtrack/13867/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/a-problem-with-soundtrack/13867/2</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 07 May 2015 13:15:13 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13867-2</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/a-problem-with-soundtrack/13867.rss">A problem with soundtrack</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>A problem with soundtrack</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Feline]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Hello everyone.</p>
<p>I bought the game today, played a little bit and I noticed that there is no soundtrack in the game. For example, early in the game, when you in the train, I’m not had heard the song Black Mesa Inbound. What is the problem?</p>
<p>UPD: I installed the game on another computer with the same system (Windows 8.1 64-bit) - the problem persists, the soundtrack is missing. Is the problem in the system?</p>
<p>P.S. Sorry for my bad english.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/a-problem-with-soundtrack/13867/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/a-problem-with-soundtrack/13867/1</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 07 May 2015 12:31:39 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13867-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/a-problem-with-soundtrack/13867.rss">A problem with soundtrack</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
