<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Rebinding joystick axis and keystrokes</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/rebinding-joystick-axis-and-keystrokes/9347</link>
    <description>This is a little difficult to explain, so TL;DR on the bottom. i want to bind WASD-like movement to an analog joystick...

...aaaaaaaaand keep mouse-look bound to mouse. When i play FPS&#39; like Half-Life with gripping story sections or when i play scary games, i like to emote. My fiance likes to watch and she likes how i play games, so it&#39;s not uncommon for me to ham it up and &quot;act&quot; with my character. i like to walk, move slowly, gradually speed up and generally move in a more natural manner.

My roomie just got one of [url=&#39;https://www.newegg.com/Product/Product.aspx?Item=N82E16823126050&amp;Tpk=logitech%20gameboard&#39;]these[/url] and he was disappointed that he can&#39;t rebind the analog stick. While trying to find a solution, i got an idea. Something that&#39;s always driven me crazy in FPS&#39; is that with WASD, there&#39;s only two or three speeds your character can move; walk, run, sprint. With an analog stick you get a more natural flow of motion. ...but i can&#39;t aim worth shit with another stick. What i want to do is use a combination of analog stick in my left hand and mouse in the right.

i used to play older FPS&#39; back in the day with this setup so i&#39;m used to it and find it comfortable. i use a Dualshock2 via PS2/USB dongle.

Problem is now, every freakin&#39; game with kystick support uses 360 control binds for their &quot;joystick&quot; option. it&#39;s TWO sticks or no sticks; and may God help you if you want X and Y toggled or sticks flipped or UP/Down/Strafe switched to UP/Down/Turn toggled or whatever. What i want is to use the left thumbstick for the same forward/backpedal/strafe functions as WASD would be used while using the mouse for head movement only. i use a [url=&#39;https://www.newegg.com/Product/Product.aspx?Item=N82E16826104318&#39;]Logitech G500[/url] so i have plenty of buttons to use in both hands, including shoulder buttons and L3 on the PS2 controller.

in Source, &quot;joystick controls&quot; automatically assign look Up&amp;Down and strafe Left&amp;Right to the left stick and Forward&amp;Backpedal and turn Left&amp;Right to the right stick. There&#39;s no conceivable way within the game to flippy flop or reassign axis. is there a way OUTSiDE the game to rebind joystick buttons, keyboard keys and joystick axis to NEW ones using another driver? Back in the day, when i wanted to switch keys in a DOS and Win95 games that didn&#39;t have the options for it, i used to rebind keyboard keys to others via a background-running rebinding tool OUTSiDE the game programming. i&#39;m curious if i can find and use something similar (if it exists) to rebind joystick controls and key strokes to NEW ones.

ie: rebind &quot;space&quot; to &quot;joy6&quot;, &quot;L-shift&quot; to &quot;joy7&quot;, &quot;R&quot; to &quot;joy8&quot;. Reassign L-stick Y-axis to R-stick Y-axis, etc. in short, i want to rebind KEYS, no actions.

-Kawai Tei-

TL;DR : i&#39;m a sucker for pacing gameplay and emoting in games. i&#39;m also a double-jointed freak who wants to play with a combination of joystick and mouse. Problem is, no games i play bind the proper movements to joystick controls. is there a way i can re-bind X&amp;Y for individual sticks to new functions and bind keyboard keys to joystick buttons?</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Sep 2012 08:53:09 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Technology and Gaming</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/rebinding-joystick-axis-and-keystrokes/9347.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Rebinding joystick axis and keystrokes</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[OldDirtyBastard]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>you have bigger problems than making your joystick work</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/rebinding-joystick-axis-and-keystrokes/9347/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/rebinding-joystick-axis-and-keystrokes/9347/3</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 08 Sep 2012 08:53:09 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9347-3</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/rebinding-joystick-axis-and-keystrokes/9347.rss">Rebinding joystick axis and keystrokes</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Rebinding joystick axis and keystrokes</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Tirppa]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>You might give this a try:<br>
<a href="https://www.electracode.com/4/joy2key/JoyToKey%20English%20Version.htm" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://www.electracode.com/4/joy2key/JoyToKey%20English%20Version.htm</a></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/rebinding-joystick-axis-and-keystrokes/9347/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/rebinding-joystick-axis-and-keystrokes/9347/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 08 Sep 2012 06:11:23 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9347-2</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/rebinding-joystick-axis-and-keystrokes/9347.rss">Rebinding joystick axis and keystrokes</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Rebinding joystick axis and keystrokes</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Tei]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>This is a little difficult to explain, so TL;DR on the bottom. i want to bind WASD-like movement to an analog joystick…</p>
<p>…aaaaaaaaand keep mouse-look bound to mouse. When i play FPS’ like Half-Life with gripping story sections or when i play scary games, i like to emote. My fiance likes to watch and she likes how i play games, so it’s not uncommon for me to ham it up and “act” with my character. i like to walk, move slowly, gradually speed up and generally move in a more natural manner.</p>
<p>My roomie just got one of <a href="https://www.newegg.com/Product/Product.aspx?Item=N82E16823126050&amp;Tpk=logitech%20gameboard" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">these</a> and he was disappointed that he can’t rebind the analog stick. While trying to find a solution, i got an idea. Something that’s always driven me crazy in FPS’ is that with WASD, there’s only two or three speeds your character can move; walk, run, sprint. With an analog stick you get a more natural flow of motion. …but i can’t aim worth shit with another stick. What i want to do is use a combination of analog stick in my left hand and mouse in the right.</p>
<p>i used to play older FPS’ back in the day with this setup so i’m used to it and find it comfortable. i use a Dualshock2 via PS2/USB dongle.</p>
<p>Problem is now, every freakin’ game with kystick support uses 360 control binds for their “joystick” option. it’s TWO sticks or no sticks; and may God help you if you want X and Y toggled or sticks flipped or UP/Down/Strafe switched to UP/Down/Turn toggled or whatever. What i want is to use the left thumbstick for the same forward/backpedal/strafe functions as WASD would be used while using the mouse for head movement only. i use a <a href="https://www.newegg.com/Product/Product.aspx?Item=N82E16826104318" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Logitech G500</a> so i have plenty of buttons to use in both hands, including shoulder buttons and L3 on the PS2 controller.</p>
<p>in Source, “joystick controls” automatically assign look Up&amp;Down and strafe Left&amp;Right to the left stick and Forward&amp;Backpedal and turn Left&amp;Right to the right stick. There’s no conceivable way within the game to flippy flop or reassign axis. is there a way OUTSiDE the game to rebind joystick buttons, keyboard keys and joystick axis to NEW ones using another driver? Back in the day, when i wanted to switch keys in a DOS and Win95 games that didn’t have the options for it, i used to rebind keyboard keys to others via a background-running rebinding tool OUTSiDE the game programming. i’m curious if i can find and use something similar (if it exists) to rebind joystick controls and key strokes to NEW ones.</p>
<p>ie: rebind “space” to “joy6”, “L-shift” to “joy7”, “R” to “joy8”. Reassign L-stick Y-axis to R-stick Y-axis, etc. in short, i want to rebind KEYS, no actions.</p>
<p>-Kawai Tei-</p>
<p>TL;DR : i’m a sucker for pacing gameplay and emoting in games. i’m also a double-jointed freak who wants to play with a combination of joystick and mouse. Problem is, no games i play bind the proper movements to joystick controls. is there a way i can re-bind X&amp;Y for individual sticks to new functions and bind keyboard keys to joystick buttons?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/rebinding-joystick-axis-and-keystrokes/9347/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/rebinding-joystick-axis-and-keystrokes/9347/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 08 Sep 2012 02:49:34 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9347-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/rebinding-joystick-axis-and-keystrokes/9347.rss">Rebinding joystick axis and keystrokes</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
