<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>I&#39;m back with a new song</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/im-back-with-a-new-song/8137</link>
    <description>Hopefully you know by now that I make techno, electronic, dance, chiptune music. I&#39;m really excited right now so I just want to get this song I spent roughly a week making out there. The links below, so make sure to click it, leave a message, possibly subscribe if you want, maybe add me as a friend (if you&#39;re also a musician or artist, then I look at the comment to see if its good or bad, good being like &quot;holy baby Jesus this sh.. is so f...... awesome&quot; bad being &quot;this is boring...&quot;, then I&#39;ll leave a reply regardless, checking every 20 mins. to see if anybody listened to the song, eat a banana, watch a ufo show on history channel or American Guns or Sons Of Guns on Discovery channel (shout out to anybody else who loves these shows, and then get a cup of coffe and sit back and relax while watching my bro play dead island or Skyrim or possibly but very unlikely Black Mesa Source however the chances are like 1 to 10000000000 haha jk I&#39;ll shut up now... Thanks for listening  :slight_smile: 

Watch End Of The Line here- [url]https://youtu.be/ELTIwKz1FgM[/url]

Aldo make sure to check out [url=&#39;https://snowbeard64.webs.com&#39;]snowbeard64.webs.com[/url] to download all my music for FREE!
Thanks for listening, snowbeard64</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 29 Nov 2011 08:17:30 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Show Off</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/im-back-with-a-new-song/8137.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>I&#39;m back with a new song</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[E-Nelson]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>That was awesome. Of course I’m on drugs right now so idk how i’ll feel tomorrow.</p>
<p>also i hate fade endings</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/im-back-with-a-new-song/8137/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/im-back-with-a-new-song/8137/4</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 29 Nov 2011 08:17:30 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8137-4</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/im-back-with-a-new-song/8137.rss">I&#39;m back with a new song</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>I&#39;m back with a new song</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Schizophriend]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I loved it. Had a little bit of a Postal Service and Owl City vibe with chip tunes.</p>
<p>Its a bit long, but I notice in the description you stated you had lyrics that went with it as well, so I’m guessing thats why it was so long.</p>
<p>I could think of a few things that I would tweak personally, but they are things you will eventually learn and are more personal preference than anything.</p>
<p>Good work!</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/im-back-with-a-new-song/8137/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/im-back-with-a-new-song/8137/3</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 29 Nov 2011 07:42:16 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8137-3</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/im-back-with-a-new-song/8137.rss">I&#39;m back with a new song</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>I&#39;m back with a new song</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[tomdemko]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Boring</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/im-back-with-a-new-song/8137/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/im-back-with-a-new-song/8137/2</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 29 Nov 2011 07:27:02 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8137-2</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/im-back-with-a-new-song/8137.rss">I&#39;m back with a new song</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>I&#39;m back with a new song</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[GravityGun]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Hopefully you know by now that I make techno, electronic, dance, chiptune music. I’m really excited right now so I just want to get this song I spent roughly a week making out there. The links below, so make sure to click it, leave a message, possibly subscribe if you want, maybe add me as a friend (if you’re also a musician or artist, then I look at the comment to see if its good or bad, good being like “holy baby Jesus this sh… is so f… awesome” bad being “this is boring…”, then I’ll leave a reply regardless, checking every 20 mins. to see if anybody listened to the song, eat a banana, watch a ufo show on history channel or American Guns or Sons Of Guns on Discovery channel (shout out to anybody else who loves these shows, and then get a cup of coffe and sit back and relax while watching my bro play dead island or Skyrim or possibly but very unlikely Black Mesa Source however the chances are like 1 to 10000000000 haha jk I’ll shut up now… Thanks for listening  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=9" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
<p>Watch End Of The Line here- <a href="https://youtu.be/ELTIwKz1FgM" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://youtu.be/ELTIwKz1FgM</a></p>
<p>Aldo make sure to check out <a href="https://snowbeard64.webs.com" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">snowbeard64.webs.com</a> to download all my music for FREE!<br>
Thanks for listening, snowbeard64</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/im-back-with-a-new-song/8137/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/im-back-with-a-new-song/8137/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 27 Nov 2011 02:55:46 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8137-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/im-back-with-a-new-song/8137.rss">I&#39;m back with a new song</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
