<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Office Complex &quot;Emergency Broadcast&quot;</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/office-complex-emergency-broadcast/13986</link>
    <description>This was so cool, I loved how you guys implemented it for the game. It really lets to stop for a second and think about your situation, that the incident isn&#39;t just contained in the little in the hallway your in but gives the sense how big it really is. But if I could make a suggestion, could you guys maybe put it on &quot;loop&quot; so it could repeat itself. I was kind of upset that I didn&#39;t discover it in time while I was looking around and when I did find, it was just about over with. By repeating itself it not only makes if more realistic, but makes it like the &quot;Kleiner cast&quot; from episode 1. Giving the player a moment to stop and take in their surroundings and get some background information, or just continue on. It couldn&#39;t be that hard to do could it?</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 11 May 2015 02:14:07 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>The Cafeteria</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/office-complex-emergency-broadcast/13986.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Office Complex &quot;Emergency Broadcast&quot;</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Strider397]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>This was so cool, I loved how you guys implemented it for the game. It really lets to stop for a second and think about your situation, that the incident isn’t just contained in the little in the hallway your in but gives the sense how big it really is. But if I could make a suggestion, could you guys maybe put it on “loop” so it could repeat itself. I was kind of upset that I didn’t discover it in time while I was looking around and when I did find, it was just about over with. By repeating itself it not only makes if more realistic, but makes it like the “Kleiner cast” from episode 1. Giving the player a moment to stop and take in their surroundings and get some background information, or just continue on. It couldn’t be that hard to do could it?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/office-complex-emergency-broadcast/13986/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/office-complex-emergency-broadcast/13986/1</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 11 May 2015 02:14:07 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13986-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/office-complex-emergency-broadcast/13986.rss">Office Complex &quot;Emergency Broadcast&quot;</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
