<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Black Mesa wallpapers</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/black-mesa-wallpapers/10531</link>
    <description>Hello guys and ladies,

my name is Paul, I&#39;m from Poland.
I&#39;m graphic designer for 8 years, and I run small design studio here.

After hours I love to make some works in Photoshop.
When I was younger I used to play Half Life alot. When I&#39;ve completed game and all add-ons for it, I realized it was/it still is, one of the best game I&#39;ve ever played. Maybe graphics is not so fresh any more, but plot just kick ass IMHO.

Yesterday when I was checking games news, I read that couple of fans created remake of this awesome game, on source engine. I&#39;ve downloaded it of course, it was surprise for me that Black Mesa is a free game! I was even ready to pay for it if it&#39;s necessary...

Game of course [b]is freakin&#39; awesome![/b] Because, as I wrote above, I&#39;m graphic designer, I&#39;ve decided to make something for You aswell. And of course for free.

Here, I&#39;ve designed some wallpapers, for PC&#39;s (16:9), Android devices or iPhones. Fell free to use it. If somebody can send me cool screenshots from game or original font/logo, I will make more of them. You can send me them via email: [b]pmikolajek@pmtek.pl[/b]

thanks,
keep doing great job guys.  :slight_smile: 
I really appreciate this kind of initiative.


[url=https://iv.pl/images/54177873754738170530.jpg][img]https://www.iv.pl/images/04801402171032136965.jpg[/img][/url]

[url=https://iv.pl/images/73113901698626662911.jpg][img]https://www.iv.pl/images/56415825870911703733.jpg[/img][/url]

[img]https://www.iv.pl/images/26406675481625811368.jpg[/img]</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 17 Sep 2012 10:56:55 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Show Off</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/black-mesa-wallpapers/10531.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Black Mesa wallpapers</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[rejnold]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Hello guys and ladies,</p>
<p>my name is Paul, I’m from Poland.<br>
I’m graphic designer for 8 years, and I run small design studio here.</p>
<p>After hours I love to make some works in Photoshop.<br>
When I was younger I used to play Half Life alot. When I’ve completed game and all add-ons for it, I realized it was/it still is, one of the best game I’ve ever played. Maybe graphics is not so fresh any more, but plot just kick ass IMHO.</p>
<p>Yesterday when I was checking games news, I read that couple of fans created remake of this awesome game, on source engine. I’ve downloaded it of course, it was surprise for me that Black Mesa is a free game! I was even ready to pay for it if it’s necessary…</p>
<p>Game of course <span class="bbcode-b">is freakin’ awesome!</span> Because, as I wrote above, I’m graphic designer, I’ve decided to make something for You aswell. And of course for free.</p>
<p>Here, I’ve designed some wallpapers, for PC’s (16:9), Android devices or iPhones. Fell free to use it. If somebody can send me cool screenshots from game or original font/logo, I will make more of them. You can send me them via email: <span class="bbcode-b">pmikolajek@pmtek.pl</span></p>
<p>thanks,<br>
keep doing great job guys.  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=9" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"><br>
I really appreciate this kind of initiative.</p>
<p><a href="https://iv.pl/images/54177873754738170530.jpg" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener"><span alt="" class="broken-image" title="This image is broken"><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-unlink svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#unlink"></use></svg></span></a></p>
<p><a href="https://iv.pl/images/73113901698626662911.jpg" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener"><span alt="" class="broken-image" title="This image is broken"><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-unlink svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#unlink"></use></svg></span></a></p>
<p><span alt="" class="broken-image" title="This image is broken"><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-unlink svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#unlink"></use></svg></span></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/black-mesa-wallpapers/10531/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/black-mesa-wallpapers/10531/1</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 17 Sep 2012 10:56:55 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-10531-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/black-mesa-wallpapers/10531.rss">Black Mesa wallpapers</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
