<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Dream thread</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/dream-thread/1572</link>
    <description>Patonki suggested a dreaming thread, here it is!

Post your dreams and general dream discussion here!</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 20 Aug 2010 08:05:52 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Off Topic</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/dream-thread/1572.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Dream thread</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Rossman]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I had a dream the other night that the girl I have a crush on came up to me in distress. I could clearly see that she was pregnant. She said she did not know how she became pregnant; she hadn’t slept with anyone ever. But what really struck out to me was she was asking me to be the father. Not in a sense that she need someone to help her, but in the sense that she wanted me as her husband. I knew she was looking towards me as a thoughtful and loving husband and a father. why she would choose me out of everyone else that was in the dream. Everyone knew each other; some more then others, but she came up to me in the sense that I would be the best for her and the baby. I was Kinda touched after that dream thinking, “If I ever do fall in love and get married, I want that person to treat me like that dream was. I want the women to know that I could be a loving father and that she could love me like that.” I really do want it to be like that.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/dream-thread/1572/460">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/dream-thread/1572/460</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 Aug 2010 08:05:52 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-1572-460</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/dream-thread/1572.rss">Dream thread</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Dream thread</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[mrfohlin]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>@ Orpheon, ohh ahaha, the second part was kinda funny. Sounds like a mix of HL2, the smurfs and Alan Wake, this was pretty fun.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/dream-thread/1572/459">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/dream-thread/1572/459</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 Aug 2010 06:02:29 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-1572-459</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/dream-thread/1572.rss">Dream thread</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Dream thread</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Orpheon]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I had two really weird dreams last night. In the first, I was back in high school. I had been transferred to a new school and this was my first day to go there. I got a little lost because I started going to my old school first, and then I realized I had been transferred and started going to my new school. On the way there I came to a motorcycle dealership, and I thought, what the hell, and stole one. I drove it around some neighborhoods most of the day, which was pretty fun. Then, around 5 pm, I decided to go home, so I got on the highway and was close to home when I realized I was heading into a construction zone. So, being the rebel that I apparently was in this dream, I started going through it, driving through dirt and trying to avoid impaling myself on jutting rebar or getting run over by giant earth-moving trucks. At some point I came to a row of what appeared to be oil wells. One of them collapsed and began spewing a green-black liquid. I fell off the motorcycle and people started running and shouting orders. I started to protest that there was no way I could have caused that, but they just ran past me and started to work on the well. I ran away from the well and jumped over a low wall. I looked back at the wall and saw a bunch of high-power electrical equipment starting to overload, when my father (Jeff Bridges) ran up and stuck a screwdriver in them to fix it. Then we hugged and cried for some reason.</p>
<p>The second dream was even stranger. So apparently Earth was being invaded by aliens or something and I was helped to fight back. But it seems there were also zombies. Anyway, I forgot a lot of it but I ended up in my house after all this bad stuff had happened, and I was hiding there with someone else, don’t remember who. Weird stuff kept happening, like in the dark parts of the house there was this ghost-like thing that I had to fight off, and when I shone a flashlight on it, it would disappear. So I decided to stay in the lighted part of the house. I saw outside that some of the windows had fallen off. The person with me said this other person would get worried if they saw that, so the person had me move the windows out of sight. I went back inside and then I looked out a window and saw these little blue alien things walking away into the woods. So me and this girl called Chameleon chase after them. I can’t really do anything but Chameleon can turn invisible (in my dream I see her as being brown and green to show she’s cloaked). So these alien things have disguised themselves as mobsters with guns, but she beats them all up since they can’t see her. When it’s over we run to this garage with a milk truck in it. There are some people here too but I don’t remember who. Then I saw Will Ferrell hiding in a foam mattress spying on us. Just saw his eye looking out of a mattress and knew it was him. So I tried to attack him but he disappeared. Then he appeared on the floor and a giant door cut him in half. Then this other van like the A-Team van drove up, and inside that van was a smaller van. I was like “wat” and that was it.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/dream-thread/1572/458">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/dream-thread/1572/458</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 19 Aug 2010 23:20:53 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-1572-458</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/dream-thread/1572.rss">Dream thread</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Dream thread</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Soup]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="jerry">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/j/5daacb/40.png" class="avatar"> jerry:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I dreamt that i died. I actually believed that i was dying, and when i woke up i was like HOLY SHIT</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Ladies and gentlemen, the dreams of a retarded twelve year old.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/dream-thread/1572/457">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/dream-thread/1572/457</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 18 Aug 2010 10:14:10 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-1572-457</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/dream-thread/1572.rss">Dream thread</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Dream thread</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Comrade_Tiki]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Maxey">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/user_avatar/leakfree.org/maxey/40/4358_2.png" class="avatar"> Maxey:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>God damn. You people are massive nerds.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Did I ever tell you about the time I had a thrilling night’s rest in TFC Murderball?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/dream-thread/1572/456">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/dream-thread/1572/456</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 17 Aug 2010 21:21:35 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-1572-456</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/dream-thread/1572.rss">Dream thread</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Dream thread</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[mrfohlin]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>:awesome:</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/dream-thread/1572/455">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/dream-thread/1572/455</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 17 Aug 2010 19:31:22 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-1572-455</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/dream-thread/1572.rss">Dream thread</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Dream thread</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Jeannotvb]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I sometimes have problems coming up with good designs for levels in video games, yet when I’m dreaming I can see extremely large environments to the finest details.</p>
<p>I wish I could make screenshots of my dreams, would make it so much easier. :3</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/dream-thread/1572/454">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/dream-thread/1572/454</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 17 Aug 2010 19:29:50 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-1572-454</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/dream-thread/1572.rss">Dream thread</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Dream thread</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[RandomSpoon]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I dreamt a nuke went off just over the hill you can see from my front window, i distinctly remember the mushroom cloud and a wave of death coming down the hill towards my house.</p>
<p>It was fucking awesome.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/dream-thread/1572/453">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/dream-thread/1572/453</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 17 Aug 2010 19:23:30 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-1572-453</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/dream-thread/1572.rss">Dream thread</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Dream thread</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[jerry]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I dreamt that i died. I actually believed that i was dying, and when i woke up i was like HOLY SHIT</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/dream-thread/1572/452">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/dream-thread/1572/452</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 17 Aug 2010 18:15:44 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-1572-452</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/dream-thread/1572.rss">Dream thread</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Dream thread</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[mrfohlin]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Maxey">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/user_avatar/leakfree.org/maxey/40/4358_2.png" class="avatar"> Maxey:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>God damn. You people are massive nerds.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I can’t help what I dream off can’t I? =)</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/dream-thread/1572/451">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/dream-thread/1572/451</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 17 Aug 2010 17:45:58 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-1572-451</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/dream-thread/1572.rss">Dream thread</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Dream thread</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Maxey]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>God damn. You people are massive nerds.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/dream-thread/1572/450">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/dream-thread/1572/450</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 17 Aug 2010 17:44:16 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-1572-450</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/dream-thread/1572.rss">Dream thread</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Dream thread</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[mrfohlin]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Well, perhaps my most disturbing dream I had in a while started like this…</p>
<p>I was in my local gamestop show going to buy Metal Gear Solid 3: Subsistence. However they didn’t have this game avaiable so the girl gave me a Gamereactor magazine. In this magazine I found the MGS3 game, but then I realised I had no Ps2 to play it on since my Ps3 isn’t backwardcompatible so I had to go to another store to buy it.<br>
Here’s where the disturbing, while I was walking to who knows where I was followed by a brain who looked like a <a href="https://fc06.deviantart.net/fs34/f/2008/295/5/0/Gears_of_war_2_Reaver_by_jpizzle6298.jpg" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Reaver</a> from Gears of War. It was pretty ok, nice and such. But that was the nonthinking side. On the housetops another of those brainythings followed me with a really evil look. It consumed a human standing on the tops.</p>
<p>As I countined my journey to buy a Ps2 this thing consumed everything behind me. Suddenly there was a house where this friendly brain had followed me stayd. Eventually this evil brain showed up and fused with it and turned into something looking like the <a href="https://www6.incrysis.com/images/Art_CD/hunter_concept.jpg" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">final boss</a> of Crysis but very organic and tentacles everywhere.</p>
<p>Of course now the hunting scene started where I had to run from house to house to hide from this things tentacles. Eventually I outran it and ended up in a electronicstore where there was a lot of Ps2’s. I bought one and proceded to plug it in one of their tvs. I inserted MGS3 into the console, where this Brain guy popped up into the screen. I ran to one of the aisles and after a while of running I fell from exhaustion. When I turn around it stands there and attacks.</p>
<p>I woke up sweaty. No more sleep for me that night.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/dream-thread/1572/449">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/dream-thread/1572/449</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 17 Aug 2010 17:37:55 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-1572-449</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/dream-thread/1572.rss">Dream thread</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Dream thread</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[ashton93]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>guys, one time i dreamt that black mesa actually was released     :hmph:</p>
<p>Go on</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/dream-thread/1572/448">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/dream-thread/1572/448</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 17 Aug 2010 15:08:51 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-1572-448</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/dream-thread/1572.rss">Dream thread</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Dream thread</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[johnyo]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Imonfire">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/i/e47c2d/40.png" class="avatar"> Imonfire:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>You do dream. I thought I was in the same situation, until I went in a sleep clinic. It looks like I rarely go into the sleeping phase that allows me to dream (due to insomnia), but when I do, I just don’t remember them.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Yeah, well not dreaming at all or not remembering dreams at all hardly makes any differnece.  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/frowning.png?v=9" title=":frowning:" class="emoji" alt=":frowning:"><br>
Come to think of it, I’m really not the person to post in a thread like this.</p>
<p><a class="mention" href="/u/bolteh">@Bolteh</a>: I have that feeling like once a year.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/dream-thread/1572/447">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/dream-thread/1572/447</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 17 Aug 2010 15:08:39 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-1572-447</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/dream-thread/1572.rss">Dream thread</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Dream thread</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Bolteh]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Same. I hardly ever remember my dreams, though sometimes I have this  feeling I had an awesome dream, bit have no idea about what exactly</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/dream-thread/1572/446">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/dream-thread/1572/446</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 17 Aug 2010 15:04:31 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-1572-446</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/dream-thread/1572.rss">Dream thread</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Dream thread</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Imonfire]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="johnyo">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/j/a9a28c/40.png" class="avatar"> johnyo:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I never dream. Ever. Am I missing out on something?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>You do dream. I thought I was in the same situation, until I went in a sleep clinic. It looks like I rarely go into the sleeping phase that allows me to dream (due to insomnia), but when I do, I just don’t remember them.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/dream-thread/1572/445">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/dream-thread/1572/445</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 17 Aug 2010 14:57:20 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-1572-445</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/dream-thread/1572.rss">Dream thread</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Dream thread</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[mrfohlin]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Comrade Tiki">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Comrade Tiki:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>wow<br>
<span class="bbcode-i">my</span> Nintendo 64 dream was WAY more fun than yours  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=9" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"></p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>It’s only one of the weird dreams I have had about videogames. I have had a very disturbing dream. I might even post it here! :b</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/dream-thread/1572/444">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/dream-thread/1572/444</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 17 Aug 2010 12:56:33 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-1572-444</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/dream-thread/1572.rss">Dream thread</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Dream thread</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Comrade_Tiki]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>wow<br>
<span class="bbcode-i">my</span> Nintendo 64 dream was WAY more fun than yours  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=9" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/dream-thread/1572/443">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/dream-thread/1572/443</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 17 Aug 2010 12:53:28 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-1572-443</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/dream-thread/1572.rss">Dream thread</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Dream thread</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[mrfohlin]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I dreamt that I got lost in the Water Temple from OoT while being chased by <a href="https://www.mariowiki.com/images/thumb/0/07/Skeeter64.jpg/180px-Skeeter64.jpg" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Skeeters</a> from Super Mario 64.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/dream-thread/1572/442">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/dream-thread/1572/442</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 17 Aug 2010 12:50:34 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-1572-442</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/dream-thread/1572.rss">Dream thread</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Dream thread</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Maxey]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I once dreamed I was having lunch in Steven Spielberg’s house. At some point I needed to go to the bathroom take a leak and there was this big window from which Steven and his daughter kept observing me taking said leak.</p>
<p>It was pretty awkward.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/dream-thread/1572/441">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/dream-thread/1572/441</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 17 Aug 2010 12:42:33 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-1572-441</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/dream-thread/1572.rss">Dream thread</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Dream thread</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[johnyo]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I never dream. Ever. Am I missing out on something?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/dream-thread/1572/440">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/dream-thread/1572/440</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 17 Aug 2010 12:40:08 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-1572-440</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/dream-thread/1572.rss">Dream thread</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Dream thread</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Comrade_Tiki]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I was playing a BattleTanx campaign, still in third-person (looking at the tank from behind) but my perspective was in 3D. The explosions and everything were also more violent than it seems on-screen.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/dream-thread/1572/439">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/dream-thread/1572/439</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 17 Aug 2010 07:57:24 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-1572-439</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/dream-thread/1572.rss">Dream thread</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Dream thread</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Orpheon]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I had a dream where I got left without a car in a city (Austin) about an hour away from my hometown. However, the city had tracks everywhere for this little device I was riding. It looked like a pogo stick with no handlebar, just the foot supports and a wheel underneath. There were tracks on top of giant glass pyramid buildings, and in malls and stores and everywhere. I was trying to get home but I wondered how I would do that without a car.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/dream-thread/1572/438">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/dream-thread/1572/438</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 17 Aug 2010 01:30:43 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-1572-438</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/dream-thread/1572.rss">Dream thread</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Dream thread</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[k3nny1550]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>The cloaking ninja enemy from F.E.A.R. electrocuted me out of my sleep once. My chest actually <span class="bbcode-i">hurt</span> when I started from my bed. I guess it’s the whole “dying in a dream makes you wake up” Inception-ish shtick that was going on.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/dream-thread/1572/437">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/dream-thread/1572/437</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 16 Aug 2010 20:38:58 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-1572-437</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/dream-thread/1572.rss">Dream thread</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Dream thread</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Moonpooman]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="BahamutBBob">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/b/e9bcb4/40.png" class="avatar"> BahamutBBob:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I think I’ve seen that troll picture before.  One of my sisters spent a year and a half in Norway, and one of the things she brought back was a book on trolls, and I think that picture was in it.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>It’s named “Skogstroll” (“Forest Troll” in English)</p>
<p>It’s made by the painter Theodor Kittelsen.</p>
<p>Here’s another painting by him:</p>
<p><a href="https://img51.imageshack.us/i/kittelsennokken.jpg/" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener"><span alt="" class="broken-image" title="This image is broken"><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-unlink svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#unlink"></use></svg></span></a></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/dream-thread/1572/436">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/dream-thread/1572/436</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 16 Aug 2010 10:34:12 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-1572-436</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/dream-thread/1572.rss">Dream thread</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
