<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Hivehand VS HECU and few other issues</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/hivehand-vs-hecu-and-few-other-issues/13931</link>
    <description>1. I noticed hivehand makes marines do cover animation and they stay in it. And I think they do this not only for direct hits but for close ones too. This way hivehand is extremely OP against HECU

2. Assassins now has extremely good aim, no matter if you stand still at any distance or run around. Fighting them is not interesting anymore and set pieces made for those fights is not used to full potential because there is only one valid strategy now - grab a corner as fast as you can, preferably with only one way in and solid ceiling.  Their accuracy should be reduced. I can only imagine how new players feel entering assassin fights for first time: Who is it? Oh wait, I&#39;m dead.

3.  Same thing with accuracy goes with gunship. Now it basically lands each and every one MG shot in you, obliterating you in seconds. Such gameplay moments is not &quot;hard&quot; they are frustrating.

4. AI currently have multiple issues. Vorts stuck in one position without idle animations is most noticable one. I also seen stuck HECU soldiers, and HECU shotgunner running around me without ability to make a decision. Also, most of HECU marines charge you like headless chicken instead of keeping range.
And alien grunts stuck in place too, f.e. those two fellas are supposed to participate in iconic HECU vs Xen battle (the one with Osprey) but prefer to stay still until triggered buy attack or close player proximity: [url=&#39;https://images.akamai.steamusercontent.com/ugc/32993531153241706/BE571F6033D7E3D0611DE6F73CD5BBDC2EE45CF5/&#39;]One of them looks at me doing nothing[/url]</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 09 May 2015 11:43:58 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>In-game Issues</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/hivehand-vs-hecu-and-few-other-issues/13931.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Hivehand VS HECU and few other issues</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[BeezOne84]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <ol>
<li>
<p>I noticed hivehand makes marines do cover animation and they stay in it. And I think they do this not only for direct hits but for close ones too. This way hivehand is extremely OP against HECU</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Assassins now has extremely good aim, no matter if you stand still at any distance or run around. Fighting them is not interesting anymore and set pieces made for those fights is not used to full potential because there is only one valid strategy now - grab a corner as fast as you can, preferably with only one way in and solid ceiling.  Their accuracy should be reduced. I can only imagine how new players feel entering assassin fights for first time: Who is it? Oh wait, I’m dead.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Same thing with accuracy goes with gunship. Now it basically lands each and every one MG shot in you, obliterating you in seconds. Such gameplay moments is not “hard” they are frustrating.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>AI currently have multiple issues. Vorts stuck in one position without idle animations is most noticable one. I also seen stuck HECU soldiers, and HECU shotgunner running around me without ability to make a decision. Also, most of HECU marines charge you like headless chicken instead of keeping range.<br>
And alien grunts stuck in place too, f.e. those two fellas are supposed to participate in iconic HECU vs Xen battle (the one with Osprey) but prefer to stay still until triggered buy attack or close player proximity: <a href="https://images.akamai.steamusercontent.com/ugc/32993531153241706/BE571F6033D7E3D0611DE6F73CD5BBDC2EE45CF5/" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">One of them looks at me doing nothing</a></p>
</li>
</ol>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/hivehand-vs-hecu-and-few-other-issues/13931/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/hivehand-vs-hecu-and-few-other-issues/13931/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 09 May 2015 11:43:58 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13931-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/hivehand-vs-hecu-and-few-other-issues/13931.rss">Hivehand VS HECU and few other issues</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
