<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>UK taxi driver kills 12, wounds 25 in rampage</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/uk-taxi-driver-kills-12-wounds-25-in-rampage/4366</link>
    <description>from Yahoo News
[quote]
SEASCALE, England – A taxi driver drove his vehicle on a shooting spree across a tranquil stretch of northwest England on Wednesday, methodically killing 12 people and wounding 25 others before turning the gun on himself, officials said. The rampage in the county of Cumbria was Britain&#39;s deadliest mass shooting since 1996 and it jolted a country where handguns are banned and multiple shootings rare.

The body of the suspected gunman, 52-year-old Derrick Bird, was found in woods near Boot, a hamlet popular with hikers and vacationers in England&#39;s hilly, scenic Lake District. Police said two weapons were recovered from the scene.

Eight of the wounded were in the hospital, with three of them in critical condition. In a sign of the scale of the tragedy, Queen Elizabeth II issued a message saying she was &quot;deeply shocked&quot; and shared in &quot;the grief and horror of the whole country.&quot; She passed on her sympathy to the families of the victims.

The shootings had &quot;shocked the people of Cumbria and around the country to the core,&quot; Police Deputy Chief Constable Stuart Hyde said.

Police said it was too early to say what the killer&#39;s motive was, or whether the shootings had been random. Some reports said Bird had quarreled with fellow cab drivers the night before the killings.

Peter Leder, a taxi driver who knew Bird, said he had seen the gunman Tuesday and didn&#39;t notice anything that was obviously amiss. But he was struck by Bird&#39;s departing words.

&quot;When he left he said, &#39;See you Peter, but I won&#39;t see you again,&#39;&quot; Leder told Channel 4 News.

The first shootings were reported in the coastal town of Whitehaven, about 350 miles (560 kilometers) northwest of London. Witnesses said the dead there included two of Bird&#39;s fellow cabbies.

Police warned residents to stay indoors as they tracked the gunman&#39;s progress across the county. Witnesses described seeing the gunman driving around shooting from the window of his car.

Victims died in Seascale and Egremont, near Whitehaven, and in Gosforth, where a farmer&#39;s son was shot dead in a field. Workers at the nearby Sellafield nuclear processing plant were ordered to stay inside while the gunman was on the loose.

Hyde said there were 30 separate crime scenes. Many bodies remained on the ground late Wednesday, covered with sheets, awaiting the region&#39;s small and overstretched force of forensic officers.

Police would not discuss the identity of those killed, but local reports said Bird killed a 66-year-old woman near her home and a retired man who was out cycling.

A spokesman for the local health authority denied reports that Bird had tried to seek medical assistance Tuesday and said he was not known to their mental health services.

Barrie Walker, a doctor in Seascale who certified one of the deaths, told the BBC that victims had been shot in the face, apparently with a shotgun.

Lyn Edwards, 59, a youth worker in Seascale, said she saw a man who had been shot in his car.

&quot;I could see a man screaming and I could see blood and there were two ladies helping him at the time,&quot; she said.

Deadly shootings are rare in Britain, where gun ownership is tightly restricted. In recent years, there have been fewer than 100 gun murders annually across the country.

Rules on gun ownership were tightened after two massacres in the 1980s and 1990s. In 1987, gun enthusiast Michael Ryan killed 16 people in the English town of Hungerford. In 1996, Thomas Hamilton killed 16 children and a teacher at a primary school in Dunblane, Scotland.

About 600,000 people in Britain legally own a shotgun, most of them farmers and hunters in rural areas. Witnesses described Bird as using a shotgun or a rifle.

Prime Minister David Cameron said the government would do everything it could to help the affected region.

&quot;When lives and communities are suddenly shattered in this way, our thoughts should be with all those caught up in these tragic events, especially the families and friends of those killed or injured,&quot; he told lawmakers in the House of Commons.

Local lawmaker Jamie Reed said people in the quiet area were in shock.

&quot;This kind of thing doesn&#39;t happen in our part of the world,&quot; he told the BBC. &quot;We have got one of the lowest, if not the lowest, crime rates in the country.&quot;

Glenda Pears, who runs L&amp;G Taxis in Whitehaven, said one of the victims was another taxi driver who was a friend of Bird&#39;s.

&quot;They used to stand together having a (laugh) on the rank,&quot; she said. &quot;He was friends with everybody and used to stand and joke on Duke Street.&quot;

Sue Matthews, who works at A2B Taxis in Whitehaven, said Bird was self-employed, quiet and lived alone. Some reports said he was divorced and the father of two sons.

&quot;I would say he was fairly popular. I would see him once a week out and about. He was known as &#39;Birdy,&#39;&quot; she said. &quot;I can&#39;t believe he would do that — he was a quiet little fellow.&quot;

Emergency services were still working late Wednesday to identify all the dead and inform their families.

Rod Davies, landlord of Gosforth Hall Inn near one of the crime scenes, said residents were &quot;used to &#39;neighbor&#39;s cat missing&#39; stories making the news — not this sort of thing.

&quot;There&#39;s a lot of fear. A lot of people are expecting to hear names of people they know.&quot; 
[/quote]
that&#39;s horrible , I wonder what his motives were ?</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 06 Jun 2010 11:01:27 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Off Topic</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/uk-taxi-driver-kills-12-wounds-25-in-rampage/4366.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>UK taxi driver kills 12, wounds 25 in rampage</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Comrade_Tiki]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="SassyRobot">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 SassyRobot:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>So the odd nutcase getting his hands on one seems a little less severe than every psycho having easy access to them.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>yeah<br>
But what if Germany finally decides to get off their asses and finish what they started, making their way over? What kind of militia would that leave you with? A bunch of incompetent nancies with a shotgun shortage to rival Ancient Greece? Any form of non-military resistance would be doomed.</p>
<p>History’s most capable combatants have come from long backgrounds with firearms, dozen-plus-kill snipers especially, with little need for military training when joining a campaign. <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Lyudmila_Pavlichenko#Early_life" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Here’s a pretty good example</a> to get the gist across. While some crazies have an easier time finding weapons, to cause a few pointless deaths, the populace has the ability to better inflict a <span class="bbcode-i">great</span> many more objective-specific casualties. It can be argued that one random dead man in peacetime is acceptable collateral for several incapacitated invaders.</p>
<p>You could hope war is at an utter end, and <a href="https://www.smbc-comics.com/index.php?db=comics&amp;id=1899#comic" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">select option D from the Prisoner’s Dilemma</a>, but if your democracy is trustworthy and other governments are not, you’re better off taking the blasted deal. Face it, if the United Kingdom were not allied to every nation in its proximity, it’d be invaded in a heartbeat for being both valuable and internally vulnerable.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/uk-taxi-driver-kills-12-wounds-25-in-rampage/4366/42">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/uk-taxi-driver-kills-12-wounds-25-in-rampage/4366/42</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 06 Jun 2010 11:01:27 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-4366-42</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/uk-taxi-driver-kills-12-wounds-25-in-rampage/4366.rss">UK taxi driver kills 12, wounds 25 in rampage</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>UK taxi driver kills 12, wounds 25 in rampage</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Mr.Shadow]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Ballsopt">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/b/85e7bf/40.png" class="avatar"> Ballsopt:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>seriously, your crazy paranoid gun-nut logic makes my brain hurt. and what are these phantom “unlawful citizens” you constantly speak of, how do you define someone like that in your book</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>What she said was that taking guns away from law abiding citizens won’t stop the psychos from acquiring weapons, so it’ll only hurt the ones that do follow the law.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/uk-taxi-driver-kills-12-wounds-25-in-rampage/4366/41">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/uk-taxi-driver-kills-12-wounds-25-in-rampage/4366/41</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 06 Jun 2010 09:22:54 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-4366-41</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/uk-taxi-driver-kills-12-wounds-25-in-rampage/4366.rss">UK taxi driver kills 12, wounds 25 in rampage</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>UK taxi driver kills 12, wounds 25 in rampage</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[DeleteThis]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="eateroftheflame">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/e/df788c/40.png" class="avatar"> eateroftheflame:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>You do realise that calling 911 wouldn’t do anything in the UK?<br>
Also there was a statement saying that there was no opportunity to stop the gunman earlier, by the time the armed police arrived at wherever he was sighted he had already moved on</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>He was driving around in a Taxi, shooting people and there are more cameras then people in England<br>
Not that hard to find</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/uk-taxi-driver-kills-12-wounds-25-in-rampage/4366/40">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/uk-taxi-driver-kills-12-wounds-25-in-rampage/4366/40</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 06 Jun 2010 01:09:54 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-4366-40</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/uk-taxi-driver-kills-12-wounds-25-in-rampage/4366.rss">UK taxi driver kills 12, wounds 25 in rampage</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>UK taxi driver kills 12, wounds 25 in rampage</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Bolteh]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>The really sad part is that it’ll now be a wee bit harder to get a taxi in the UK  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/frowning.png?v=9" title=":frowning:" class="emoji" alt=":frowning:"></p>
<p>Though on the other hand, there’s now less people to occupy a taxi in the UK, so I guess it balances out.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/uk-taxi-driver-kills-12-wounds-25-in-rampage/4366/39">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/uk-taxi-driver-kills-12-wounds-25-in-rampage/4366/39</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 06 Jun 2010 00:13:25 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-4366-39</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/uk-taxi-driver-kills-12-wounds-25-in-rampage/4366.rss">UK taxi driver kills 12, wounds 25 in rampage</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>UK taxi driver kills 12, wounds 25 in rampage</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Ballsopt]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="CatzEyes93">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/user_avatar/leakfree.org/catzeyes93/40/4402_2.png" class="avatar"> CatzEyes93:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>'Tis one of the main reasons we came across the pond.  The moment you take the weapon away from the law abiding citizen is the day the unlawful run rampant with their illegally acquired weapon.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>seriously, your crazy paranoid gun-nut logic makes my brain hurt. and what are these phantom “unlawful citizens” you constantly speak of, how do you define someone like that in your book</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/uk-taxi-driver-kills-12-wounds-25-in-rampage/4366/38">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/uk-taxi-driver-kills-12-wounds-25-in-rampage/4366/38</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 06 Jun 2010 00:10:38 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-4366-38</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/uk-taxi-driver-kills-12-wounds-25-in-rampage/4366.rss">UK taxi driver kills 12, wounds 25 in rampage</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>UK taxi driver kills 12, wounds 25 in rampage</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[eateroftheflame]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Bluemen230">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Bluemen230:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>YES! LET’S BLAME VIDEO GAMES FOR EVERY NUTCASE THAT GOES OUT AND SHOOTS PEOPLE!<br>
YEAH! LET’S NOT BLAME THE POLICE OFFICERS WHO SHOULD’VE BEEN ON SCENE TO STOP THAT MANIAC!<br>
OR THE PEOPLE WHO NEGLECTED TO CALL 911!<br>
OR THE ONE WHO CAUSED THE GUY TO SNAP IN THE FIRST PLACE!</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>You do realise that calling 911 wouldn’t do anything in the UK?<br>
Also there was a statement saying that there was no opportunity to stop the gunman earlier, by the time the armed police arrived at wherever he was sighted he had already moved on</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/uk-taxi-driver-kills-12-wounds-25-in-rampage/4366/37">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/uk-taxi-driver-kills-12-wounds-25-in-rampage/4366/37</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 05 Jun 2010 23:48:51 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-4366-37</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/uk-taxi-driver-kills-12-wounds-25-in-rampage/4366.rss">UK taxi driver kills 12, wounds 25 in rampage</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>UK taxi driver kills 12, wounds 25 in rampage</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[DeleteThis]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>YES! LET’S BLAME VIDEO GAMES FOR EVERY NUTCASE THAT GOES OUT AND SHOOTS PEOPLE!<br>
YEAH! LET’S NOT BLAME THE POLICE OFFICERS WHO SHOULD’VE BEEN ON SCENE TO STOP THAT MANIAC!<br>
OR THE PEOPLE WHO NEGLECTED TO CALL 911!<br>
OR THE ONE WHO CAUSED THE GUY TO SNAP IN THE FIRST PLACE!</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/uk-taxi-driver-kills-12-wounds-25-in-rampage/4366/36">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/uk-taxi-driver-kills-12-wounds-25-in-rampage/4366/36</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 05 Jun 2010 05:52:23 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-4366-36</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/uk-taxi-driver-kills-12-wounds-25-in-rampage/4366.rss">UK taxi driver kills 12, wounds 25 in rampage</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>UK taxi driver kills 12, wounds 25 in rampage</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[sersoft]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>it’s obvious this guy plays too much GTA</p>
<p>BAN ALL VIDEOGAMES THEY ARE THE DEVIL SPAWN</p>
<p>IM A GOD WARRIOR IN JESUS NAME ILL PRAY</p>
<p><em>goes on killing spree in gods name</em></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/uk-taxi-driver-kills-12-wounds-25-in-rampage/4366/35">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/uk-taxi-driver-kills-12-wounds-25-in-rampage/4366/35</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 03 Jun 2010 22:16:18 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-4366-35</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/uk-taxi-driver-kills-12-wounds-25-in-rampage/4366.rss">UK taxi driver kills 12, wounds 25 in rampage</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>UK taxi driver kills 12, wounds 25 in rampage</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Comrade_Tiki]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I say: Mandatory firearms for those with an IQ above 120.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/uk-taxi-driver-kills-12-wounds-25-in-rampage/4366/34">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/uk-taxi-driver-kills-12-wounds-25-in-rampage/4366/34</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 03 Jun 2010 21:57:39 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-4366-34</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/uk-taxi-driver-kills-12-wounds-25-in-rampage/4366.rss">UK taxi driver kills 12, wounds 25 in rampage</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>UK taxi driver kills 12, wounds 25 in rampage</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[eateroftheflame]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Scrawny">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/s/b5ac83/40.png" class="avatar"> Scrawny:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>It may have happened, but it might have not been as bad.  He is saying when you make guns illegal the law abiding citizens wont have em, but outlawing something does not make it disappear.  It only puts it in the hands of the criminals.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I don’t think there should be a complete ban I just don’t think giving everyone a gun will help, like you said individual shootings wouldn’t be as bad but they would be more frequent.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/uk-taxi-driver-kills-12-wounds-25-in-rampage/4366/33">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/uk-taxi-driver-kills-12-wounds-25-in-rampage/4366/33</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 03 Jun 2010 21:08:07 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-4366-33</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/uk-taxi-driver-kills-12-wounds-25-in-rampage/4366.rss">UK taxi driver kills 12, wounds 25 in rampage</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>UK taxi driver kills 12, wounds 25 in rampage</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Scrawny]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Mr.Shadow">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/m/43a26b/40.png" class="avatar"> Mr.Shadow:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Yeah, like a complete gun ban would’ve prevented this. People need their brains to think again before they are spouting out random stuff about guns being bad and should be banned. Also: Best solution to guns ever: Make the bullets really expensive. Like, 2000 bucks each. That would make people think twice about shooting. They shoot somebody and imediatly run up to them to pull the bullet out of the chest.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>your post confuses me are you saying they should be banned or not?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/uk-taxi-driver-kills-12-wounds-25-in-rampage/4366/32">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/uk-taxi-driver-kills-12-wounds-25-in-rampage/4366/32</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 03 Jun 2010 20:44:09 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-4366-32</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/uk-taxi-driver-kills-12-wounds-25-in-rampage/4366.rss">UK taxi driver kills 12, wounds 25 in rampage</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>UK taxi driver kills 12, wounds 25 in rampage</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Medevilae]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Bolteh">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/b/ecae2f/40.png" class="avatar"> Bolteh:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Are you talking about the guy that was so excited to get a glimpse of the Queen and forgot to brake?<br>
[COLOR=‘Black’]Also, I was being sarcastic.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>And he forgot to let go of the trigger too, right? :S</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/uk-taxi-driver-kills-12-wounds-25-in-rampage/4366/31">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/uk-taxi-driver-kills-12-wounds-25-in-rampage/4366/31</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 03 Jun 2010 20:41:02 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-4366-31</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/uk-taxi-driver-kills-12-wounds-25-in-rampage/4366.rss">UK taxi driver kills 12, wounds 25 in rampage</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>UK taxi driver kills 12, wounds 25 in rampage</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[CatzEyes93]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>so does my daddy.  =-) He makes his own bullets.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/uk-taxi-driver-kills-12-wounds-25-in-rampage/4366/30">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/uk-taxi-driver-kills-12-wounds-25-in-rampage/4366/30</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 03 Jun 2010 20:40:37 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-4366-30</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/uk-taxi-driver-kills-12-wounds-25-in-rampage/4366.rss">UK taxi driver kills 12, wounds 25 in rampage</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>UK taxi driver kills 12, wounds 25 in rampage</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Rossman]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Yep that’s why I have a reloader.  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=9" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/uk-taxi-driver-kills-12-wounds-25-in-rampage/4366/29">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/uk-taxi-driver-kills-12-wounds-25-in-rampage/4366/29</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 03 Jun 2010 20:37:18 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-4366-29</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/uk-taxi-driver-kills-12-wounds-25-in-rampage/4366.rss">UK taxi driver kills 12, wounds 25 in rampage</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>UK taxi driver kills 12, wounds 25 in rampage</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Bolteh]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>You watched Chris Rock too much (or at least I believe it was him who made that bullet-joke).</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/uk-taxi-driver-kills-12-wounds-25-in-rampage/4366/28">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/uk-taxi-driver-kills-12-wounds-25-in-rampage/4366/28</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 03 Jun 2010 20:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-4366-28</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/uk-taxi-driver-kills-12-wounds-25-in-rampage/4366.rss">UK taxi driver kills 12, wounds 25 in rampage</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>UK taxi driver kills 12, wounds 25 in rampage</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Mr.Shadow]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Yeah, like a complete gun ban would’ve prevented this. People need their brains to think again before they are spouting out random stuff about guns being bad and should be banned. Also: Best solution to guns ever: Make the bullets really expensive. Like, 2000 bucks each. That would make people think twice about shooting. They shoot somebody and imediatly run up to them to pull the bullet out of the chest.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/uk-taxi-driver-kills-12-wounds-25-in-rampage/4366/27">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/uk-taxi-driver-kills-12-wounds-25-in-rampage/4366/27</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 03 Jun 2010 20:34:37 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-4366-27</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/uk-taxi-driver-kills-12-wounds-25-in-rampage/4366.rss">UK taxi driver kills 12, wounds 25 in rampage</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>UK taxi driver kills 12, wounds 25 in rampage</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[hercule_poirots_nuts]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>meanwhile, in the real world <a href="https://www.nationmaster.com/graph/cri_mur_wit_fir_percap-crime-murders-firearms-per-capita" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://www.nationmaster.com/graph/cri_mur_wit_fir_percap-crime-murders-firearms-per-capita</a></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/uk-taxi-driver-kills-12-wounds-25-in-rampage/4366/26">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/uk-taxi-driver-kills-12-wounds-25-in-rampage/4366/26</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 03 Jun 2010 20:32:42 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-4366-26</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/uk-taxi-driver-kills-12-wounds-25-in-rampage/4366.rss">UK taxi driver kills 12, wounds 25 in rampage</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>UK taxi driver kills 12, wounds 25 in rampage</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Scrawny]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="eateroftheflame">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/e/df788c/40.png" class="avatar"> eateroftheflame:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>It’s such a shame. We have some of the strictest gun laws in Europe and this was still able to happen.</p>
<p>Edit: Catz are you seriously suggesting that this wouldn’t have happend if the victims had guns?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>It may have happened, but it might have not been as bad.  He is saying when you make guns illegal the law abiding citizens wont have em, but outlawing something does not make it disappear.  It only puts it in the hands of the criminals.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/uk-taxi-driver-kills-12-wounds-25-in-rampage/4366/25">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/uk-taxi-driver-kills-12-wounds-25-in-rampage/4366/25</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 03 Jun 2010 20:30:07 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-4366-25</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/uk-taxi-driver-kills-12-wounds-25-in-rampage/4366.rss">UK taxi driver kills 12, wounds 25 in rampage</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>UK taxi driver kills 12, wounds 25 in rampage</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[eateroftheflame]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>It’s such a shame. We have some of the strictest gun laws in Europe and this was still able to happen.</p>
<p>Edit: Catz are you seriously suggesting that this wouldn’t have happend if the victims had guns?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/uk-taxi-driver-kills-12-wounds-25-in-rampage/4366/24">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/uk-taxi-driver-kills-12-wounds-25-in-rampage/4366/24</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 03 Jun 2010 20:03:50 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-4366-24</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/uk-taxi-driver-kills-12-wounds-25-in-rampage/4366.rss">UK taxi driver kills 12, wounds 25 in rampage</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>UK taxi driver kills 12, wounds 25 in rampage</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Imonfire]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>tbh I’m not really surprised. Taxi drivers in the UK are crazy as fuckin’ hell. I saw two people being hit by a cab in a week when I went to London a couple of months ago.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/uk-taxi-driver-kills-12-wounds-25-in-rampage/4366/23">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/uk-taxi-driver-kills-12-wounds-25-in-rampage/4366/23</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 03 Jun 2010 19:55:16 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-4366-23</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/uk-taxi-driver-kills-12-wounds-25-in-rampage/4366.rss">UK taxi driver kills 12, wounds 25 in rampage</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>UK taxi driver kills 12, wounds 25 in rampage</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[DellBoy321]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Apparently the guy was upset about being left out of the will.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/uk-taxi-driver-kills-12-wounds-25-in-rampage/4366/22">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/uk-taxi-driver-kills-12-wounds-25-in-rampage/4366/22</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 03 Jun 2010 19:31:58 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-4366-22</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/uk-taxi-driver-kills-12-wounds-25-in-rampage/4366.rss">UK taxi driver kills 12, wounds 25 in rampage</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>UK taxi driver kills 12, wounds 25 in rampage</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Rossman]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>What’s that about cars not being used as weapons?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/uk-taxi-driver-kills-12-wounds-25-in-rampage/4366/21">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/uk-taxi-driver-kills-12-wounds-25-in-rampage/4366/21</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 03 Jun 2010 19:09:55 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-4366-21</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/uk-taxi-driver-kills-12-wounds-25-in-rampage/4366.rss">UK taxi driver kills 12, wounds 25 in rampage</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>UK taxi driver kills 12, wounds 25 in rampage</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[hercule_poirots_nuts]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>The first stone has been cast; godspeed revolutionary brother xx</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/uk-taxi-driver-kills-12-wounds-25-in-rampage/4366/20">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/uk-taxi-driver-kills-12-wounds-25-in-rampage/4366/20</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 03 Jun 2010 17:02:59 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-4366-20</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/uk-taxi-driver-kills-12-wounds-25-in-rampage/4366.rss">UK taxi driver kills 12, wounds 25 in rampage</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>UK taxi driver kills 12, wounds 25 in rampage</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[CatzEyes93]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>'Tis one of the main reasons we came across the pond.  The moment you take the weapon away from the law abiding citizen is the day the unlawful run rampant with their illegally acquired weapon.</p>
<p>Sad tragedy to be sure.  I too wonder what his motives were.   <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/frowning.png?v=9" title=":frowning:" class="emoji" alt=":frowning:">   I wonder what he and the other cabbies were bickering about the night before.  So sad.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/uk-taxi-driver-kills-12-wounds-25-in-rampage/4366/19">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/uk-taxi-driver-kills-12-wounds-25-in-rampage/4366/19</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 03 Jun 2010 16:54:15 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-4366-19</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/uk-taxi-driver-kills-12-wounds-25-in-rampage/4366.rss">UK taxi driver kills 12, wounds 25 in rampage</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>UK taxi driver kills 12, wounds 25 in rampage</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Scrawny]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>banning guns… pfft, please… that won’t ever work</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/uk-taxi-driver-kills-12-wounds-25-in-rampage/4366/18">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/uk-taxi-driver-kills-12-wounds-25-in-rampage/4366/18</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 03 Jun 2010 14:43:40 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-4366-18</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/uk-taxi-driver-kills-12-wounds-25-in-rampage/4366.rss">UK taxi driver kills 12, wounds 25 in rampage</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
