<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Invisible Vortigaunts?</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/invisible-vortigaunts/12380</link>
    <description>First time poster here, so I&#39;m going to take a quick second to say &#39;hi&#39;.
...Hi.  :slight_smile: 


So I&#39;ve already played through Black Mesa once, back when it first released, and for the most part it played great. A few FPS stutters here and there, but my laptop isn&#39;t the best for gaming, so this was expected.

However, I&#39;m playing it through a second time and, for some reason, the Vortigaunts are completely invisible. I can see the green animation that comes from their hands as they go to shoot their &#39;bolt&#39; attack, but other than that, I literally have no idea where they&#39;re at. So far I&#39;ve just been waiting for them to shoot and react accordingly, but it&#39;s getting harder to manage. I&#39;m not too far into this playthrough, close to the cafeteria, and it&#39;s starting to become a pain since they&#39;re showing up more and more. 

I tried looking this up to see if anyone else has had similar issues, whether it was with Vortigaunts, Headcrabs, Soldiers, or what have you.. couldn&#39;t manage to find anything. I was hoping maybe someone else has had a similar issue, and could give me some advice? I&#39;d most certainly appreciate it.


EDIT: I just realized I forgot my system specs, apologies.

Processor: Inter(R) Core(TM) i3 CPU    M 330 @2.13GHz
RAM: 4 GB
OS: Windows 8, 64-bit x64-based processor
Graphics: NVidia GeForce 310 M</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 14 Jul 2013 21:05:42 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>In-game Issues (Mod)</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/invisible-vortigaunts/12380.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Invisible Vortigaunts?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[sersoft]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>that’s probably because valve is updating HL2/EP2 and the source engine/dev tools and broke pretty much all mods for the time being</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/invisible-vortigaunts/12380/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/invisible-vortigaunts/12380/3</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 14 Jul 2013 21:05:42 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12380-3</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/invisible-vortigaunts/12380.rss">Invisible Vortigaunts?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Invisible Vortigaunts?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[CarnageV1]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Just to add, I tried catching up on my Windows Update and at first it made the Vortigaunts come back, but my weapons all had pink and black missing textures on them, and the Vortigaunts ‘bolt’ spells had crazy lines coming out of them, same for a lot of enemies. I found out it was because, somehow, my game had gotten switched to DirectX 0.8. <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/expressionless.png?v=9" title=":expressionless:" class="emoji" alt=":expressionless:"></p>
<p>I got that switched back to DX9.0, and now I’m back to square one. No missing textures, no crazy lines/lights, just invisible Vortigaunts. I don’t understand why it simply stopped working, it played fine from beginning to end initially. I may try to uninstall/reinstall, I was just trying to avoid it since my internet is crap and it’s a 3GB download.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/invisible-vortigaunts/12380/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/invisible-vortigaunts/12380/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2013 15:10:28 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12380-2</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/invisible-vortigaunts/12380.rss">Invisible Vortigaunts?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Invisible Vortigaunts?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[CarnageV1]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>First time poster here, so I’m going to take a quick second to say ‘hi’.<br>
…Hi.  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=9" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
<p>So I’ve already played through Black Mesa once, back when it first released, and for the most part it played great. A few FPS stutters here and there, but my laptop isn’t the best for gaming, so this was expected.</p>
<p>However, I’m playing it through a second time and, for some reason, the Vortigaunts are completely invisible. I can see the green animation that comes from their hands as they go to shoot their ‘bolt’ attack, but other than that, I literally have no idea where they’re at. So far I’ve just been waiting for them to shoot and react accordingly, but it’s getting harder to manage. I’m not too far into this playthrough, close to the cafeteria, and it’s starting to become a pain since they’re showing up more and more.</p>
<p>I tried looking this up to see if anyone else has had similar issues, whether it was with Vortigaunts, Headcrabs, Soldiers, or what have you… couldn’t manage to find anything. I was hoping maybe someone else has had a similar issue, and could give me some advice? I’d most certainly appreciate it.</p>
<p>EDIT: I just realized I forgot my system specs, apologies.</p>
<p>Processor: Inter® Core™ i3 CPU    M 330 <span class="mention">@2.13GHz</span><br>
RAM: 4 GB<br>
OS: Windows 8, 64-bit x64-based processor<br>
Graphics: NVidia GeForce 310 M</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/invisible-vortigaunts/12380/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/invisible-vortigaunts/12380/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2013 01:45:40 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12380-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/invisible-vortigaunts/12380.rss">Invisible Vortigaunts?</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
