<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>The Forum | Complaints &amp; Concerns Go Here</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/the-forum-complaints-concerns-go-here/3158</link>
    <description>I want to try something for the next week or so by taking a quick temperature check of the forums.  [COLOR=&#39;LemonChiffon&#39;][b]So for you lurkers, this is your opportunity to post why it is that you are NOT posting.[/b]

Without naming names and without directly attacking others on these forums, I would like to hear how you folks feel about the forums and what some of your concerns are.  Beef about moderators? Beef about behaviors? Beef about topics?  Beef about  _________ ?

[b][COLOR=&#39;LemonChiffon&#39;]Please use constructive words and keep your raging to an extreme minimum.  [/SIZE][/b]Just as your local grocery store is going to card anyone that &#39;looks&#39; under 30, I am going to delete any posts that &#39;look&#39; like an attack on someone specifically.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 24 Mar 2010 14:18:34 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Website Issues</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/the-forum-complaints-concerns-go-here/3158.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>The Forum | Complaints &amp; Concerns Go Here</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[CatzEyes93]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>And now I finally saw the FAQ that was in the header up top that brought you to a search page.  wow… that wasnt really helpful eh?  Our kind developers removed it for us, so now we can have folks rely on the wiki or thread.</p>
<p>Thanks for bringing this to light.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/the-forum-complaints-concerns-go-here/3158/324">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/the-forum-complaints-concerns-go-here/3158/324</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 24 Mar 2010 14:18:34 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3158-324</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/the-forum-complaints-concerns-go-here/3158.rss">The Forum | Complaints &amp; Concerns Go Here</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The Forum | Complaints &amp; Concerns Go Here</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[CatzEyes93]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I think it might help if the wiki faq areas (i see three…is this correct) had one last entry pointing folks to “Other FAQ’s as seen on the forums”.  Perhaps do the same in the forum FAQ and point back to the wiki faq areas.</p>
<p>Would this help? What do you guys think?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/the-forum-complaints-concerns-go-here/3158/323">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/the-forum-complaints-concerns-go-here/3158/323</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 23 Mar 2010 21:27:49 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3158-323</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/the-forum-complaints-concerns-go-here/3158.rss">The Forum | Complaints &amp; Concerns Go Here</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The Forum | Complaints &amp; Concerns Go Here</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[sebastianface]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I did not have any problem personally locating the FAQ so very long ago (I lurked for about 2 years before joining), but I see now where confusion may be encountered. There are at least 3 FAQs. The one I mentioned is a FAQ for how to utilize the forums: posting, replying, attachments, etc. The second is the sticky FAQ for forum etiquette. The third includes the FAQs in the wiki pertaining to the mod itself: singleplayer FAQ, General FAQ, and Deathmatch FAQ. It is fairly often someone states that he/she has read the FAQ but did not find the information they should have. Perhaps the person read the incorrect FAQ. They are all valid FAQs on differing topics, so the only way I can see to “fix” this is to redirect the member to the appropriate FAQ. Another factor, which I believe has been resolved, was that after the wiki was made, many people would say “the FAQ is outdated, check the wiki.” This led to some confusion at the time, but I believe it has been resolved.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/the-forum-complaints-concerns-go-here/3158/322">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/the-forum-complaints-concerns-go-here/3158/322</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 23 Mar 2010 19:26:46 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3158-322</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/the-forum-complaints-concerns-go-here/3158.rss">The Forum | Complaints &amp; Concerns Go Here</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The Forum | Complaints &amp; Concerns Go Here</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[_amp_955_dam]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Is it just me, or am I expecting a dramatic reading of Sebastian’s post?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/the-forum-complaints-concerns-go-here/3158/321">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/the-forum-complaints-concerns-go-here/3158/321</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 23 Mar 2010 18:30:40 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3158-321</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/the-forum-complaints-concerns-go-here/3158.rss">The Forum | Complaints &amp; Concerns Go Here</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The Forum | Complaints &amp; Concerns Go Here</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Doop]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Because of this thread, I started posting more  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/smiley.png?v=9" title=":smiley:" class="emoji" alt=":smiley:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/the-forum-complaints-concerns-go-here/3158/320">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/the-forum-complaints-concerns-go-here/3158/320</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 23 Mar 2010 17:02:23 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3158-320</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/the-forum-complaints-concerns-go-here/3158.rss">The Forum | Complaints &amp; Concerns Go Here</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The Forum | Complaints &amp; Concerns Go Here</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[CatzEyes93]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="sebastianface">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/s/65b543/40.png" class="avatar"> sebastianface:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>…If you are a newcomer, then you are almost always here for information. As such the wiki is the primary source. However, at first glance of the forum page one is directed to read the FAQ and provided with a link. The problem is this links to a search page rather than the FAQs contained within the wiki. I have been lurking for a couple years so I do not remember how it was set up then, but looking at it now I can see this is a source of possible error.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>The real FAQ is found as a sticky thread in the topic area 	Black Mesa: Community Forums &gt; Black Mesa &gt;  The Cafeteria &gt; Sticky: <a href="https://forums.blackmesasource.com/showthread.php?t=24" data-bbcode="true">FAQ - Please Read</a></p>
<p>Please let me know where the link to the faq is broken and I will do what I can to get it fixed.  Or is it that some schmuck was being schmucky in a thread and instead of linking you to the actual faq you were linked to the search instead?</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="sebastianface">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/s/65b543/40.png" class="avatar"> sebastianface:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>…<br>
The one problem that these two groups have in common is the responses of some who are intentionally derogatory. I mean this in the literal sense of the word: detracting from the character or status of something. I say intentionally because, as the typed word has no inflection or body language, posts are sometimes honestly misconstrued. This will always happen and is usually quickly settled. Posts that are intentionally harsh should be reported. To effectively moderate these forums requires the participation of its members. Members should be reminded that if they witness an occurrence of this the first response should be to report, not to reply. After the report has been made it becomes the responsibility of the moderator to act in a manner appropriate to the situation. As such, the community weeds out those not suited for its environs.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I agree wholeheartedly.  In order for these forums to be productive, we all need to work together to not mess the place up.  Everyone loves a great college frat party, yet no one loves to clean up the mess the next morning.  We all need to work together to make this a place we not only want to party in, but also live in.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="sebastianface">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/s/65b543/40.png" class="avatar"> sebastianface:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>…As for the attitudes of the moderators and developers in this forum, I revel in it. I find the humor quite entertaining. This is why I frequent these forums. However, it is not for all. No place is. I will continue to lurk without posting, but I think we should keep in mind the newcomers are here for information. They will ask the wrong questions and for information that has been discussed. Some should be shrugged off if they have obviously not made any effort, but ultimately these people are excited and want to learn as much as possible. If they fit in they may even stay for the community and unrelated “discussion”. We must not coddle, nor should we burn without discretion.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I think this is why I actually put this thread together.  I wanted the regulars to see how they were affecting the newcomers. We all love a good crispy treat, but I think all of us as a group need to remember that patience IS a virtue.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="sebastianface">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/s/65b543/40.png" class="avatar"> sebastianface:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>… I don’t believe serious statements and profanity mix well as it is less likely to be receptive to a constructive response. Serious Business, you guys.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Who was it that said profanity proves a lack of education. That if you can’t get your point across without cussing, then you only show your ignorance.  Oh wait, my mom always said that! Yep, she had a lot of things right.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="sebastianface">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/s/65b543/40.png" class="avatar"> sebastianface:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>…P.P.S. People should stop saying “about seven” and then debating as to whether or not it should be a lesser number since time has passed since its first incarnation. Humor is part creation not mere repetition and it has become tiresome to read after about seven times.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>This is an old joke made annoying by its continued use.  I am bolding what bears repeating…  <span class="bbcode-b">Humor is part creation not mere repetition.</span></p>
<p>Thank you for posting sebastianface.  =0)</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/the-forum-complaints-concerns-go-here/3158/319">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/the-forum-complaints-concerns-go-here/3158/319</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 23 Mar 2010 15:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3158-319</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/the-forum-complaints-concerns-go-here/3158.rss">The Forum | Complaints &amp; Concerns Go Here</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The Forum | Complaints &amp; Concerns Go Here</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[sebastianface]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>This is likely to be my only post in this forum. By definition, I am a lurker, not a poster. That being said, I feel that I might be able to share some of my views on this forum, its operation, and its members.</p>
<p>I visit this forum everyday. The first thing I check is if the mod has been released. Afterwards, I read some threads for new posts and to pass the time. I find that the atmosphere among the members and moderators/developers is a relaxed and jocular one, one that keeps me entertained. It is, in fact, the reason I frequent this forum.</p>
<p>On the other hand, I shall state this. When I first came to the forums I was looking for information, as most new members do. I went and read the FAQ and many threads. I have found that nowadays, there is little relevant discussion concerning the mod itself. The reason for this is that there is not much left to discuss that has not been discussed already. The only new material I see on the mod itself is when a very specific question is asked in the “Got a Question? - Enquiries about the mod” thread.</p>
<p>Others before me have stated that the lack of new material to be discussed is a problem. This may or may not be a valid point depending on how long you have been here and what you expect from these forums.</p>
<p>If you are a newcomer, then you are almost always here for information. As such the wiki is the primary source. However, at first glance of the forum page one is directed to read the FAQ and provided with a link. The problem is this links to a search page rather than the FAQs contained within the wiki. I have been lurking for a couple years so I do not remember how it was set up then, but looking at it now I can see this is a source of possible error.</p>
<p>If you are a long time member or frequent these forums, then most likely you are here for the community and the entertainment it provides. As such the lack of new information is less likely to be a factor in your enjoyment of these forums. One comes for information and stays for the people.</p>
<p>The one problem that these two groups have in common is the responses of some who are intentionally derogatory. I mean this in the literal sense of the word: detracting from the character or status of something. I say intentionally because, as the typed word has no inflection or body language, posts are sometimes honestly misconstrued. This will always happen and is usually quickly settled. Posts that are intentionally harsh should be reported. To effectively moderate these forums requires the participation of its members. Members should be reminded that if they witness an occurrence of this the first response should be to report, not to reply. After the report has been made it becomes the responsibility of the moderator to act in a manner appropriate to the situation. As such, the community weeds out those not suited for its environs.</p>
<p>As for the attitudes of the moderators and developers in this forum, I revel in it. I find the humor quite entertaining. This is why I frequent these forums. However, it is not for all. No place is. I will continue to lurk without posting, but I think we should keep in mind the newcomers are here for information. They will ask the wrong questions and for information that has been discussed. Some should be shrugged off if they have obviously not made any effort, but ultimately these people are excited and want to learn as much as possible. If they fit in they may even stay for the community and unrelated “discussion”. We must not coddle, nor should we burn without discretion.</p>
<p>P.S. Profanity does not bother me, but many a well composed and meaningful post has been lessened by it in this thread. This thread was tailored for serious discussion. Making a great post and ending it with such a statement seems to detract from it in my eyes, but that is a personal feeling. I don’t believe serious statements and profanity mix well as it is less likely to be receptive to a constructive response. Serious Business, you guys.</p>
<p>P.P.S. People should stop saying “about seven” and then debating as to whether or not it should be a lesser number since time has passed since its first incarnation. Humor is part creation not mere repetition and it has become tiresome to read after about seven times.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/the-forum-complaints-concerns-go-here/3158/318">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/the-forum-complaints-concerns-go-here/3158/318</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 23 Mar 2010 04:13:01 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3158-318</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/the-forum-complaints-concerns-go-here/3158.rss">The Forum | Complaints &amp; Concerns Go Here</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The Forum | Complaints &amp; Concerns Go Here</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[_rot_fodder]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Acristoff">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/a/ea666f/40.png" class="avatar"> Acristoff:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>There is a lack of chairs here.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>aww hell, THIS.</p>
<p>I hate walking into the chat thread and having to sit on the floor/lean on the wall because just because Hubi cheaps out on the furniture/Nutsack breaks it.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/the-forum-complaints-concerns-go-here/3158/317">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/the-forum-complaints-concerns-go-here/3158/317</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 12 Mar 2010 03:55:03 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3158-317</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/the-forum-complaints-concerns-go-here/3158.rss">The Forum | Complaints &amp; Concerns Go Here</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The Forum | Complaints &amp; Concerns Go Here</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[sersoft]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="mattemuse">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/m/dc4da7/40.png" class="avatar"> mattemuse:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Temporarily hilarious? No, It’s ETERNALLY hilarious. Every time I think I can’t take any more forced memes, pointless asininity and trolling, Winged One’s custom title restores my faith in humanity.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I was gonna say it’s not temporary at all, that user title is here till the next database collapse.  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=9" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/the-forum-complaints-concerns-go-here/3158/316">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/the-forum-complaints-concerns-go-here/3158/316</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 12 Mar 2010 01:18:18 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3158-316</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/the-forum-complaints-concerns-go-here/3158.rss">The Forum | Complaints &amp; Concerns Go Here</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The Forum | Complaints &amp; Concerns Go Here</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Acristoff]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>There is a lack of chairs here.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/the-forum-complaints-concerns-go-here/3158/315">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/the-forum-complaints-concerns-go-here/3158/315</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 12 Mar 2010 01:12:43 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3158-315</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/the-forum-complaints-concerns-go-here/3158.rss">The Forum | Complaints &amp; Concerns Go Here</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The Forum | Complaints &amp; Concerns Go Here</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[CatzEyes93]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>so any other concerns or complaints for the mod team?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/the-forum-complaints-concerns-go-here/3158/314">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/the-forum-complaints-concerns-go-here/3158/314</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 12 Mar 2010 01:09:06 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3158-314</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/the-forum-complaints-concerns-go-here/3158.rss">The Forum | Complaints &amp; Concerns Go Here</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The Forum | Complaints &amp; Concerns Go Here</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Winged_One]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Haha, I lol’d at Ram’s reason for banning him.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/the-forum-complaints-concerns-go-here/3158/313">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/the-forum-complaints-concerns-go-here/3158/313</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 11 Mar 2010 23:59:30 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3158-313</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/the-forum-complaints-concerns-go-here/3158.rss">The Forum | Complaints &amp; Concerns Go Here</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The Forum | Complaints &amp; Concerns Go Here</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Dillxn]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Winged One">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Winged One:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Remember that one guy who kept on whining because we weren’t censored?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Oh yeah, my homie Daventry! Lmao.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/the-forum-complaints-concerns-go-here/3158/312">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/the-forum-complaints-concerns-go-here/3158/312</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 11 Mar 2010 20:15:05 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3158-312</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/the-forum-complaints-concerns-go-here/3158.rss">The Forum | Complaints &amp; Concerns Go Here</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The Forum | Complaints &amp; Concerns Go Here</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[mattemuse]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="MysticJ">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/m/839c29/40.png" class="avatar"> MysticJ:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>oh, btw, it’s really stupid, although temporarily hilarious, to give someone the custom “level” “I tried to suck Raminator’s dick…”</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Temporarily hilarious? No, It’s ETERNALLY hilarious. Every time I think I can’t take any more forced memes, pointless asininity and trolling, Winged One’s custom title restores my faith in humanity.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/the-forum-complaints-concerns-go-here/3158/311">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/the-forum-complaints-concerns-go-here/3158/311</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 11 Mar 2010 16:23:06 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3158-311</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/the-forum-complaints-concerns-go-here/3158.rss">The Forum | Complaints &amp; Concerns Go Here</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The Forum | Complaints &amp; Concerns Go Here</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[raw_bean]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Fuck 'im.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/the-forum-complaints-concerns-go-here/3158/310">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/the-forum-complaints-concerns-go-here/3158/310</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 11 Mar 2010 16:21:52 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3158-310</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/the-forum-complaints-concerns-go-here/3158.rss">The Forum | Complaints &amp; Concerns Go Here</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The Forum | Complaints &amp; Concerns Go Here</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Winged_One]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Remember that one guy who kept on whining because we weren’t censored?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/the-forum-complaints-concerns-go-here/3158/309">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/the-forum-complaints-concerns-go-here/3158/309</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 11 Mar 2010 16:03:42 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3158-309</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/the-forum-complaints-concerns-go-here/3158.rss">The Forum | Complaints &amp; Concerns Go Here</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The Forum | Complaints &amp; Concerns Go Here</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[bur]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="MysticJ">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/m/839c29/40.png" class="avatar"> MysticJ:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>oh, btw, it’s really stupid, although temporarily hilarious, to give someone the custom “level” “I tried to suck Raminator’s dick…”</p>
<p>Please refrain from that kind of joking. Lead by examples, pretty please with sugar on the top.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>you’re really stupid  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/frowning.png?v=9" title=":frowning:" class="emoji" alt=":frowning:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/the-forum-complaints-concerns-go-here/3158/308">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/the-forum-complaints-concerns-go-here/3158/308</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 11 Mar 2010 13:33:39 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3158-308</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/the-forum-complaints-concerns-go-here/3158.rss">The Forum | Complaints &amp; Concerns Go Here</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The Forum | Complaints &amp; Concerns Go Here</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Dr_Strangelove]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Somebody’s jealous.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/the-forum-complaints-concerns-go-here/3158/307">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/the-forum-complaints-concerns-go-here/3158/307</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 11 Mar 2010 13:25:51 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3158-307</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/the-forum-complaints-concerns-go-here/3158.rss">The Forum | Complaints &amp; Concerns Go Here</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The Forum | Complaints &amp; Concerns Go Here</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[MysticJ]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>oh, btw, it’s really stupid, although temporarily hilarious, to give someone the custom “level” “I tried to suck Raminator’s dick…”</p>
<p>Please refrain from that kind of joking. Lead by examples, pretty please with sugar on the top.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/the-forum-complaints-concerns-go-here/3158/306">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/the-forum-complaints-concerns-go-here/3158/306</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 11 Mar 2010 12:55:55 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3158-306</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/the-forum-complaints-concerns-go-here/3158.rss">The Forum | Complaints &amp; Concerns Go Here</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The Forum | Complaints &amp; Concerns Go Here</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Spycrabz]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Banhammers at dawn.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/the-forum-complaints-concerns-go-here/3158/305">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/the-forum-complaints-concerns-go-here/3158/305</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 11 Mar 2010 07:48:21 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3158-305</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/the-forum-complaints-concerns-go-here/3158.rss">The Forum | Complaints &amp; Concerns Go Here</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The Forum | Complaints &amp; Concerns Go Here</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[mattemuse]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>If anyone could ban anyone, ah reckon there’d be a lot less trollin’ in these here parts o’ tha woods.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/the-forum-complaints-concerns-go-here/3158/304">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/the-forum-complaints-concerns-go-here/3158/304</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 11 Mar 2010 02:52:42 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3158-304</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/the-forum-complaints-concerns-go-here/3158.rss">The Forum | Complaints &amp; Concerns Go Here</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The Forum | Complaints &amp; Concerns Go Here</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Dr_Strangelove]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Although one or two new moderators might be useful for those heavy traffic days.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/the-forum-complaints-concerns-go-here/3158/303">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/the-forum-complaints-concerns-go-here/3158/303</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 11 Mar 2010 02:48:18 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3158-303</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/the-forum-complaints-concerns-go-here/3158.rss">The Forum | Complaints &amp; Concerns Go Here</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The Forum | Complaints &amp; Concerns Go Here</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Winged_One]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Isn’t that reason enough?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/the-forum-complaints-concerns-go-here/3158/302">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/the-forum-complaints-concerns-go-here/3158/302</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 11 Mar 2010 02:39:12 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3158-302</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/the-forum-complaints-concerns-go-here/3158.rss">The Forum | Complaints &amp; Concerns Go Here</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The Forum | Complaints &amp; Concerns Go Here</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[sersoft]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I think this idea is not original and not worth implementing.</p>
<p>Do you really feel like seeing every post in every thread replaced with the word PENIS copy pasted 200 times? Because if anyone can be a mod, someone will do it.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/the-forum-complaints-concerns-go-here/3158/301">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/the-forum-complaints-concerns-go-here/3158/301</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 11 Mar 2010 02:31:25 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3158-301</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/the-forum-complaints-concerns-go-here/3158.rss">The Forum | Complaints &amp; Concerns Go Here</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The Forum | Complaints &amp; Concerns Go Here</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Winged_One]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>YES</p>
<p>At least for a day.  I think Ram was gonna do it once, but then he realized what we were capable of with the Manchild experiment.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/the-forum-complaints-concerns-go-here/3158/300">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/the-forum-complaints-concerns-go-here/3158/300</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 11 Mar 2010 02:29:14 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-3158-300</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/the-forum-complaints-concerns-go-here/3158.rss">The Forum | Complaints &amp; Concerns Go Here</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
