<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Seeing Purple</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/seeing-purple/13082</link>
    <description>I ran this game on my laptop and had absolutely no problems but only my PC i keep seeing purple on objects that aren&#39;t supposed to be purple. At first I thought it was just that exit sign in the beginning but it&#39;s everywhere. I have everything on max settings, I tried running it in direct x 9 and 9.8 and I even uninstalled it, redownloaded it and reinstalled it. Can someone help me out?

AMD FX(tm)-8320 Eight-Core Processor
Radeon 260x
8 gigs of Ram

PS: I tried to take a screenshot of it using F12 but it looks fine in the screen shot. So I tried to print screen it but it just pasted a dark screen into Paint. So then I tried to get smart and turn it into a window and print screen it but apparently it&#39;s not a problem in windowed mode, just full screen.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 15 Mar 2014 14:44:47 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Help!</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/seeing-purple/13082.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Seeing Purple</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[blackredx]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I ran this game on my laptop and had absolutely no problems but only my PC i keep seeing purple on objects that aren’t supposed to be purple. At first I thought it was just that exit sign in the beginning but it’s everywhere. I have everything on max settings, I tried running it in direct x 9 and 9.8 and I even uninstalled it, redownloaded it and reinstalled it. Can someone help me out?</p>
<p>AMD FX™-8320 Eight-Core Processor<br>
Radeon 260x<br>
8 gigs of Ram</p>
<p>PS: I tried to take a screenshot of it using F12 but it looks fine in the screen shot. So I tried to print screen it but it just pasted a dark screen into Paint. So then I tried to get smart and turn it into a window and print screen it but apparently it’s not a problem in windowed mode, just full screen.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/seeing-purple/13082/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/seeing-purple/13082/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 15 Mar 2014 14:44:47 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-13082-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/seeing-purple/13082.rss">Seeing Purple</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
