<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>How did you discover Black Mesa/The Half-life Series?</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/how-did-you-discover-black-mesa-the-half-life-series/14125</link>
    <description>In this thread you can share your stories about how you discovered Half-Life or Black Mesa. Did you follow the Series since HL1 or did you first play HL2? Did you experience the launch of these games or did you recently catch up?
I also apologize in advance if there already exists a thread like this, I couldnt find one.

I didnt really knew anything about Half-life when a german Youtuber called Gronkh started a Lets Play of Black Mesa Source. I have played Portal 2 before (a friend of mine recommended it to me) and knew it was somehow related to Half-Life, but nothing more. I enjoyed the LP a lot and decided to download the game and play it on my own. It was also the first Singleplayer-Shooter I&#39;ve played until then. After finishing playing Black Mesa on my own I enjoyed it very much and wanted more. I immediatly ordered the Orange Box (ordered it from Canada because the german version is horribly censored) and used the time waiting for it to watch a LP of the Xen Chapters as I wanted to know how HL1 ended before playing the sequel. I then played (and Steam-perfected) Portal1, HL2 and its Episodes and am now patiently waiting for Half-Life 3 like anybody else.

(Also: Can anybody tell me if its worth playing HL1(Source?) and its Expansions from a modern standpoint? (I dont have any nostalgia attached to them, obviously) I know the games I just didnt play them)

Edit: I also realised that this is probably the wrong forum for this as this topic would better fit into &#39;technology and gaming&#39;</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 08 Jun 2015 23:09:53 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Off Topic</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/how-did-you-discover-black-mesa-the-half-life-series/14125.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>How did you discover Black Mesa/The Half-life Series?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Sybill]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>This game was met by a youtube channel. Then directly by steam.<br>
I love half life 1,  I have the original cd of the game. My Father was playing a lot, and i saw him play.<br>
Personally I love the idea of escaping Black Mesa. Half Life 2 did not taste much like the first.<br>
It is for this reason that Black Mesa Source liked it so much</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/how-did-you-discover-black-mesa-the-half-life-series/14125/31">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/how-did-you-discover-black-mesa-the-half-life-series/14125/31</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jun 2015 23:09:53 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14125-31</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/how-did-you-discover-black-mesa-the-half-life-series/14125.rss">How did you discover Black Mesa/The Half-life Series?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How did you discover Black Mesa/The Half-life Series?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NoriMori]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>(Warning, long post ahead)</p>
<p>I actually don’t really remember how I discovered the <span class="bbcode-i">Half-Life</span> series. I got into the series via <span class="bbcode-i">Portal</span>, and I don’t recall where I first heard of that.</p>
<p>I grew up with almost no exposure to video games (save for things like <span class="bbcode-i">Bugdom</span>, <span class="bbcode-i">Nanosaur</span>, and <span class="bbcode-i">Marble Blast Gold</span>), since my parents wouldn’t get me any and my early experiences with computer games at school convinced me that I just wasn’t meant for them (because I was terrible at them), so I didn’t play them with friends either. Then the trailer for <span class="bbcode-i">BioShock</span> aired and it filled me with awe; I decided right then and there that when I had my own money and a good enough computer, I was going to buy that and play it, and try out other games too. And then, I don’t remember how I found out about <span class="bbcode-i">Portal</span>, but that ended up being the first “real” video game I played. My computer at the time didn’t meet the system requirements for the licensed game, so I torrented it. It didn’t run incredibly well, but I didn’t know the difference and I really enjoyed it. From there I found out about <span class="bbcode-i">Half-Life 2</span> and the episodes, and played them as well.</p>
<p>(In case you’re wondering, I bought them on Steam, and I bought <span class="bbcode-i">Portal</span> on Steam too once I had a computer that could run it.)</p>
<p>By then I was roped in. I waited for <span class="bbcode-i">Portal 2</span> with bated breath, and played it for the first time at a party I threw to celebrate/mock the <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/2011_end_times_prediction" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Rapture</a> (lol). Then I found out about <span class="bbcode-i">Freeman’s Mind</span> (again, don’t remember how) and started watching that, and then reading the Combine OverWiki, and learning in a rather oblique way about the plot of <span class="bbcode-i">Half-Life</span>.</p>
<p>To be honest, because of how old it is, my lack of exposure to games when I was young, and my lack of exposure to old games in general, <span class="bbcode-i">Half-Life</span> itself never seemed like a game I’d really have a great time with, and it still doesn’t. And I loved <span class="bbcode-i">Half-Life 2</span> and its story, but I couldn’t get myself to really care about <span class="bbcode-i">Half-Life</span>’s story. It just wasn’t compelling for me. When I watched <span class="bbcode-i">Freeman’s Mind</span> and imagined what the game is like to actually play, the characters didn’t feel seem real, and because you don’t connect with anyone emotionally, the protagonist didn’t feel real, either.</p>
<p>But then I found out about <span class="bbcode-i">Black Mesa</span>, (oddly enough I don’t remember how that happened either), and that got me really excited. I tend to derive more enjoyment from games that have better or more realistic graphics, so I knew that, whether I cared about the story or not, I’d enjoy playing a <span class="bbcode-i">Half-Life</span> that looked and behaved more like <span class="bbcode-i">Half-Life 2</span>, than one that looked like <span class="bbcode-i">Half-Life</span> actually does. So I got stoked for <span class="bbcode-i">Black Mesa</span>, and waited.</p>
<p>And when I played that… Oh my God, that changed everything. I was shocked to find myself caring about Gordon’s journey on a level that rivalled <span class="bbcode-i">Half-Life 2</span>. I found myself caring about everyone else in the facility. After I launched the rocket, as I gazed at the moon above the silo (holy shit that night sky is beautiful, good job guys), I imagined how I would be feeling right now, if I were Gordon. The guilt and fear and anger that would be rolling around in my head, now that I actually had a moment of peace to think. And I felt overwhelmed emotionally by this immersion into his situation, because I realized how how truly awful and incredibly <span class="bbcode-i">lonely</span> it was. That sense of “In The End You Are On Your Own” stayed with me through the rest of the game — and beyond, because it coloured my experience with <span class="bbcode-i">Blue Shift</span> and <span class="bbcode-i">Opposing Force</span> when I finally played them. (I still haven’t played <span class="bbcode-i">Half-Life</span>; I’ve only gotten partway through “Unforeseen Consequences”.)</p>
<p>As I gazed at that moon, I also realized how <span class="bbcode-i">brave</span> Gordon was. Now that he’s had time to really think about how fucked up this situation is, surely his resolve might be wavering, just a little. And <a href="https://tvtropes.org/pmwiki/pmwiki.php/Main/WhatYouAreInTheDark" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">he could just decide he’s had enough</a>, that he can’t do this anymore, and try to wait out the rest of the disaster out here. But he’s not going to. He’s going to keep moving forward, because there are lives at stake and he has to fix this. “Courage Is Not the Absence of Fear”.</p>
<p>To my amazement, as “End Credits 2” rolled, I thought of all Gordon had endured, all he had sacrificed, all he had witnessed, and how many people died…and I was <span class="bbcode-i">sad</span>. As Gordon, didn’t know what would happen to the people I had left behind; I didn’t know if I could fix all this; I didn’t know if what I was about to do would be worth everything I had already suffered. I didn’t know if I would even <span class="bbcode-i">survive</span>. And I was still, ultimately, totally alone. All I had as I prepared to face whatever horrors lay beyond, were memories of people getting killed and people suffering. My heart felt so heavy. And yet I was awestruck, too. Because I had connected on an emotional level with a story that I had thought held no emotional value. That’s what <span class="bbcode-i">Black Mesa</span> did for me.</p>
<p>So, even though this started as a post about how I discovered the <span class="bbcode-i">Half-Life</span> series and <span class="bbcode-i">Black Mesa</span>, it ends as a thank you to the Crowbar Collective, for taking the story of <span class="bbcode-i">Half-Life</span> and giving it the power to move me.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/how-did-you-discover-black-mesa-the-half-life-series/14125/30">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/how-did-you-discover-black-mesa-the-half-life-series/14125/30</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jun 2015 22:55:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14125-30</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/how-did-you-discover-black-mesa-the-half-life-series/14125.rss">How did you discover Black Mesa/The Half-life Series?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How did you discover Black Mesa/The Half-life Series?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[raw_bean]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Ha, no shit!  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/smiley.png?v=9" title=":smiley:" class="emoji" alt=":smiley:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/how-did-you-discover-black-mesa-the-half-life-series/14125/29">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/how-did-you-discover-black-mesa-the-half-life-series/14125/29</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jun 2015 08:58:57 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14125-29</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/how-did-you-discover-black-mesa-the-half-life-series/14125.rss">How did you discover Black Mesa/The Half-life Series?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How did you discover Black Mesa/The Half-life Series?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[jambo]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="raw_bean">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/r/439d5e/40.png" class="avatar"> raw_bean:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Like danielsangeo I’ve been playing FPS games since the grandfather of them all - Wolfenstein 3D. I was heavily into Doom and Duke Nuk’em 3D as a kid, was never a big fan of Quake or Quake 2 though.  I saw a friend playing Half-Life at the back end of 1998, and remember the intriguing magazine ads (a sepia toned picture of a vulnerable looking child with lambdas for pupils, nothing at all to do with the game but very eye-catching and original) and the rave reviews and buzz. Got it myself and played it through probably in early 1999, and was just blown away.  Even just the cinematic style opening credits were a revelation at the time, let alone the whole first section being without a gun, or enemies, but just setting the tone and introducing the world and story.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I was pretty much the same, but I found out about HL via PCPowerPlay and PC Gamer when it was previewed in 1997 or so.</p>
<p>I probably played way more CS than HL, but I did play an awful lot of SP mods for HL.</p>
<p>As for Black Mesa, I joined the Leak-Free forums back in the days of HL2’s release as I was fairly disappointed with HL Source and had heard about a Source remake on a few different forums.</p>
<p>I’ve had a few posts on the various BM forums over the years &gt;_&gt;</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/how-did-you-discover-black-mesa-the-half-life-series/14125/28">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/how-did-you-discover-black-mesa-the-half-life-series/14125/28</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jun 2015 02:07:20 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14125-28</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/how-did-you-discover-black-mesa-the-half-life-series/14125.rss">How did you discover Black Mesa/The Half-life Series?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How did you discover Black Mesa/The Half-life Series?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Chickenprotector]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>^Funnily enough, I’m a similar case. My father introduced me to HL1 when I was around 8-9 yrs old. It was the first FPS I ever played (and the second game Diablo II was my first) ever. It still holds a special place in my life.</p>
<p>As for BM I stumbled across it when it was a CS:S Mod. But I wasn’t interested in it until around 2009/2010.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/how-did-you-discover-black-mesa-the-half-life-series/14125/27">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/how-did-you-discover-black-mesa-the-half-life-series/14125/27</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 02 Jun 2015 11:24:02 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14125-27</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/how-did-you-discover-black-mesa-the-half-life-series/14125.rss">How did you discover Black Mesa/The Half-life Series?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How did you discover Black Mesa/The Half-life Series?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Johnwalter]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>My uncle was the one who introduced me to gaming, ad the first FPS i played was actually HL2.<br>
So, since i was like 9 years old, for me it was like a brand new world.<br>
Also this sound got stuck in my head forever.<br>
<a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=txvWy2PNkUY" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=txvWy2PNkUY</a></p>
<p>And i found BM by searching the internet.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/how-did-you-discover-black-mesa-the-half-life-series/14125/26">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/how-did-you-discover-black-mesa-the-half-life-series/14125/26</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jun 2015 05:24:35 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14125-26</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/how-did-you-discover-black-mesa-the-half-life-series/14125.rss">How did you discover Black Mesa/The Half-life Series?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How did you discover Black Mesa/The Half-life Series?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[BendyBread]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I had heard of Half Life before but never really looked it up or found interest in it.</p>
<p>Used to watch “Let’s Play”-ers on youtube. One in particular started playing the newly-released BM in 2012. Thought “hey thats cool” and downloaded it. She got to the first ichthyosaur encounter before I stopped watching incase of more spoilers. Decided to look up the ichthyosaur, which led to looking at all the aliens/enemies and weapons and just expanding into the half life universe. It all hooked me in.<br>
Stopped my BM playthrough (wasn’t even up to WGH yet), played through HL1, liked it. Well mostly anyway, cause I hadn’t ever played it before and it’s a fairly old game it didn’t really interest me as much as black mesa did just cause of it’s age. Finished my BM runthrough, absolutely loved it and then went back to play HL 2 and Eps 1 and 2.</p>
<p>Here I am nearly 3 years later and still loving it. So compared to most people who have posted I’m still quite “young” to the series.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/how-did-you-discover-black-mesa-the-half-life-series/14125/25">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/how-did-you-discover-black-mesa-the-half-life-series/14125/25</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jun 2015 04:25:55 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14125-25</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/how-did-you-discover-black-mesa-the-half-life-series/14125.rss">How did you discover Black Mesa/The Half-life Series?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How did you discover Black Mesa/The Half-life Series?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[CPU]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Purchased Half Life shortly after it came out and fell in love with it. I pursued anything and everything that had something to do with the Half Live universe. I became a beta tester for one of the mods where I heard about a new mod that was starting called Black Mesa so, I’ve been following the mod since its beginning.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/how-did-you-discover-black-mesa-the-half-life-series/14125/24">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/how-did-you-discover-black-mesa-the-half-life-series/14125/24</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 30 May 2015 18:44:32 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14125-24</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/how-did-you-discover-black-mesa-the-half-life-series/14125.rss">How did you discover Black Mesa/The Half-life Series?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How did you discover Black Mesa/The Half-life Series?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[BaTz281]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>FragUPlenty, kinda the same for me.</p>
<p>My uncle (who introduced me to building computers and gaming in general in ~1995 when I was 7) told me about this “cool new game where you start underground, fight a bunch of aliens and get to the surface”.  That was probably a year after HL came out, around 1999.  Then I found out about USS Darkstar from a friend, which lead me to hunting for HL mods (They Hunger, Poke646, Challenger Deep, etc).  Then, of course, came Opposing Force and Blue Shift, and Half Life 2 was pre-loaded before release.</p>
<p>I think I found out about Black Mesa when I still subscribed to PC Gamer, then MaximumPC did a quick blurb on it, and I’ve been following since.</p>
<p>I’m waiting until Xen to buy the retail version, personally.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/how-did-you-discover-black-mesa-the-half-life-series/14125/23">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/how-did-you-discover-black-mesa-the-half-life-series/14125/23</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 30 May 2015 18:32:44 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14125-23</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/how-did-you-discover-black-mesa-the-half-life-series/14125.rss">How did you discover Black Mesa/The Half-life Series?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How did you discover Black Mesa/The Half-life Series?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[JohnWorfin]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I played around half of half life in '99 but my computer died, took the HD install with it and  my physical disk was damaged after a move. I started playing HL2 in 2005 after a friend showed it to me. I was hooked. I found BMS in dec 2006  while trying to dig up info on EP2. I have followed the mod, played it and bought the game.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/how-did-you-discover-black-mesa-the-half-life-series/14125/22">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/how-did-you-discover-black-mesa-the-half-life-series/14125/22</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 30 May 2015 18:09:06 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14125-22</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/how-did-you-discover-black-mesa-the-half-life-series/14125.rss">How did you discover Black Mesa/The Half-life Series?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How did you discover Black Mesa/The Half-life Series?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[FragUPlenty]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I started playing Half-life in the year 2000. I loved the games and the mods especially They hunger and Uss Darkstar. I didnt have the internet at the time and I would rely on PCGamer cds to get patches and mods. I discovered Black Mesa while on MODDB and downloaded the mod version when it was released and then when the retail version was released I purchased that.</p>
<p>I am hoping that there is going to one day be a remake of USS Darkstar or They Hunger allthough I dont think it is going to be made by Neil Manke.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/how-did-you-discover-black-mesa-the-half-life-series/14125/21">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/how-did-you-discover-black-mesa-the-half-life-series/14125/21</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 30 May 2015 17:33:41 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14125-21</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/how-did-you-discover-black-mesa-the-half-life-series/14125.rss">How did you discover Black Mesa/The Half-life Series?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How did you discover Black Mesa/The Half-life Series?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[DaWilyWoodster]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Well, I found the Black Mesa trailer back in 2011, or so on Youtube while browsing around, if I recall correctly.</p>
<p>Meanwhile, I found Half-Life because of that one guy… You know, Ross Scott, the Freeman’s Mind guy.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/how-did-you-discover-black-mesa-the-half-life-series/14125/20">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/how-did-you-discover-black-mesa-the-half-life-series/14125/20</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 30 May 2015 13:17:06 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14125-20</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/how-did-you-discover-black-mesa-the-half-life-series/14125.rss">How did you discover Black Mesa/The Half-life Series?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How did you discover Black Mesa/The Half-life Series?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[fresh_heels]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I first read about Black Mesa in russian gaming magazine “Igromania” (I still have that issue somewhere).<br>
Maybe I’ll try to translate that tiny article.<br>
Here’s the screenshot from that issue (april 2006) (I highlighted Black Mesa stuff):</p>
<div class="spoiler">
<p><div class="lightbox-wrapper"><a class="lightbox" href="https://i.imgur.com/f3XwZwe.jpg" title="" rel="nofollow noopener"><img src="https://i.imgur.com/f3XwZwe.jpg" alt="" width="353" height="500"><div class="meta"><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-far-image svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#far-image"></use></svg><span class="filename"></span><span class="informations">1025×1450</span><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-discourse-expand svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#discourse-expand"></use></svg></div></a></div></p>
</div>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/how-did-you-discover-black-mesa-the-half-life-series/14125/19">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/how-did-you-discover-black-mesa-the-half-life-series/14125/19</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 30 May 2015 09:45:36 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14125-19</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/how-did-you-discover-black-mesa-the-half-life-series/14125.rss">How did you discover Black Mesa/The Half-life Series?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How did you discover Black Mesa/The Half-life Series?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[ac3d]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Saw my brother playing Uplink, he tried to teach me how to play,  I couldn’t understand how to play properly so I ran off through the house crying, I came back a couple hours later to try again and he said “you’re not gonna run off crying again are you?” I eventually got it. Though back then it was hard as shit, peeking through the storage container to take out the turret nest, good times.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/how-did-you-discover-black-mesa-the-half-life-series/14125/18">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/how-did-you-discover-black-mesa-the-half-life-series/14125/18</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 30 May 2015 08:13:02 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14125-18</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/how-did-you-discover-black-mesa-the-half-life-series/14125.rss">How did you discover Black Mesa/The Half-life Series?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How did you discover Black Mesa/The Half-life Series?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Bladebitch]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Kairouseki">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/k/57b2e6/40.png" class="avatar"> Kairouseki:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Computers were not new in 1998.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I did not imply that they never existed before then but it was still very much new to me at that age.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/how-did-you-discover-black-mesa-the-half-life-series/14125/17">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/how-did-you-discover-black-mesa-the-half-life-series/14125/17</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 30 May 2015 05:07:05 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14125-17</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/how-did-you-discover-black-mesa-the-half-life-series/14125.rss">How did you discover Black Mesa/The Half-life Series?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How did you discover Black Mesa/The Half-life Series?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Massey]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>When I was little (like 9 years old?), my grandma used to play video games with me all the time. Well around that time, she bought Half Life (came out a year before she bought it) and Unreal (I think it came out at the same-ish time) and I got hooked on HL and Unreal at like age 9/10. I particularly liked (and beat several times) HL and continued to play it for years (till I was… 15? When HL2 came out? It was 2004 right?) where I heard about HL2. About a year later she had bought it and all the rest of Valves games on Steam, which got me into CS, DoD, TF, and the expansions for HL as well as HLDM. I also played and beat HL2 at this point.</p>
<p>Then I bought and played the episodes and such as they came out.</p>
<p>I discovered BMS like… 5 years ago? I think I just ran into it accidentally on some social media site (tumblr maybe) and was like “cool. I’ll keep an eye on it.” Annndddd then I joined and just recently had to make a new profile cause I lost my old info.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/how-did-you-discover-black-mesa-the-half-life-series/14125/16">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/how-did-you-discover-black-mesa-the-half-life-series/14125/16</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 30 May 2015 00:39:16 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14125-16</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/how-did-you-discover-black-mesa-the-half-life-series/14125.rss">How did you discover Black Mesa/The Half-life Series?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How did you discover Black Mesa/The Half-life Series?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Kairouseki]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Computers were not new in 1998.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/how-did-you-discover-black-mesa-the-half-life-series/14125/15">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/how-did-you-discover-black-mesa-the-half-life-series/14125/15</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 May 2015 23:11:42 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14125-15</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/how-did-you-discover-black-mesa-the-half-life-series/14125.rss">How did you discover Black Mesa/The Half-life Series?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How did you discover Black Mesa/The Half-life Series?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Bladebitch]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I became acquainted with Half-Life 1 around the same time it was released however at that time I did not play any games myself. At first I simply watched when my brothers played games, Half-Life being one of them. This was back in the day when computers was still new so we only had one we had to share between us. I was always fascinated with the game so when I started to play on my own and get my own computer Half-Life was the game of choice for me.  I also played through the expansions with the same glee.</p>
<p>Then the hype for the sequel started and I can remember very clearly how my brothers and I watched a promo video that the displayed how the new graphics looked. We where not disappointed when it got released and the episodes of course added to the fun.</p>
<p>I came in contact with Black Mesa around a year after it had started via my brother who is a dev on the mod. He linked me to the site after happily announced that he had been added to the team. I’ve been following it closely ever since. It’s a very nice distraction while we wait for Half-Life 3.^^</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/how-did-you-discover-black-mesa-the-half-life-series/14125/14">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/how-did-you-discover-black-mesa-the-half-life-series/14125/14</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 May 2015 19:27:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14125-14</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/how-did-you-discover-black-mesa-the-half-life-series/14125.rss">How did you discover Black Mesa/The Half-life Series?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How did you discover Black Mesa/The Half-life Series?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Tiki]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I miss ZDTV, before it became TechTV… before it became G4.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/how-did-you-discover-black-mesa-the-half-life-series/14125/13">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/how-did-you-discover-black-mesa-the-half-life-series/14125/13</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 27 May 2015 06:42:17 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14125-13</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/how-did-you-discover-black-mesa-the-half-life-series/14125.rss">How did you discover Black Mesa/The Half-life Series?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How did you discover Black Mesa/The Half-life Series?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Kairouseki]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I’m pretty sure I had heard about it before, probably on X Play in the early 2000s. Though it wasn’t something I was that familiar with but I saw the PS2 version of HL1 at EB games and picked it up. Don’t think I ever beat it but that was the first time I played HL1. Then I got the Orange Box on the 360 and beat HL2 and both episodes I think. At some point I bought all the games on Steam when I started moving more towards playing games on PC. I remember X Play’s coverage of HL2 before it was released and when they reviewed it. Man, I miss X Play.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/how-did-you-discover-black-mesa-the-half-life-series/14125/12">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/how-did-you-discover-black-mesa-the-half-life-series/14125/12</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 27 May 2015 05:59:54 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14125-12</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/how-did-you-discover-black-mesa-the-half-life-series/14125.rss">How did you discover Black Mesa/The Half-life Series?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How did you discover Black Mesa/The Half-life Series?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[raw_bean]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Like danielsangeo I’ve been playing FPS games since the grandfather of them all - Wolfenstein 3D. I was heavily into Doom and Duke Nuk’em 3D as a kid, was never a big fan of Quake or Quake 2 though.  I saw a friend playing Half-Life at the back end of 1998, and remember the intriguing magazine ads (a sepia toned picture of a vulnerable looking child with lambdas for pupils, nothing at all to do with the game but very eye-catching and original) and the rave reviews and buzz. Got it myself and played it through probably in early 1999, and was just blown away.  Even just the cinematic style opening credits were a revelation at the time, let alone the whole first section being without a gun, or enemies, but just setting the tone and introducing the world and story.</p>
<p>I think PCZone magazine running a feature on BM introduced me to it, back when Denzil was still running the colossal BM Steam Forum thread, and the BM:S website and forums had just broken away from the original Leak Free. I apparently just missed the ‘purism war’ on the forums, although there was still bickering about how pure a recreation of every tiny facet of HL BM should be, rather than re-imagining/improving/expanding where appropriate. As I write this all the Pro-gamer/Adrenaline Gamer fan bitching about bhop, circle-strafe, etc. suddenly seems very much like history repeating itself.</p>
<p>I also remember when the ‘Steam News’ pop-up window used to be actual news snippets written by Valve staff rather than just a series of adverts for new releases and special offers, and Valve mentioned BM for the first time. At the time lots of people were wondering if Valve would shut BM down with a Cease and Desist notification for using their intellectual property, so it was really massive news when Valve highlighted the mod in their own news item and said they were looking forward to playing it. At one and the same time that makes it seem incredible, and yet also almost inevitable, how we ended up with Valve coming to an agreement with CC to sell BM on Steam all these years later!  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=9" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/how-did-you-discover-black-mesa-the-half-life-series/14125/11">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/how-did-you-discover-black-mesa-the-half-life-series/14125/11</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 26 May 2015 20:50:47 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14125-11</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/how-did-you-discover-black-mesa-the-half-life-series/14125.rss">How did you discover Black Mesa/The Half-life Series?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How did you discover Black Mesa/The Half-life Series?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Agent6]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>It can be said that my journey towards the HL universe was somewhat stupid, but interesting at the same time.</p>
<p>Growing up in a city where, by the time I’ve learned about HL, CS was extremely popular and almost every kid was playing, I first discovered that CS started out as a HL1 mod. Then I though ,What is a mod and why would CS be based on it,. I’ve found very fast what was a so-called mod and that CS was based on its content, rather than a (for ex.) remake/continuation of it.</p>
<p>After this I began to be interested in the game and watched some gameplay videos on YT! (I was around 11yrs old when this happened (<span class="mention">@2007</span>). It felt very unique, something I’ve never played (and rightfully so. Before CS I’ve played only NFS and GTA), and the way it was played amazed me. I’ve downloaded it soon after I’ve read about it and the universe, although I hadn’t watched any walkthroughs, so I had no idea what was going on more exactly and what the hell I need to do. I think I’ve played it until I reached Unforeseen Consequences, then I basically got lost in the facility, very, very confused, and ceased to play the game and went back to CS. I didn’t play a lot of FPS’ after this however. Basically, I’d lost my interest in the genre somehow.</p>
<p>I came back to it, however, in 2011 or so. Since at that time I though that the graphics are the most important in a game and not the actual gameplay (I know, very stupid way of thinking), I didn’t want to play HL1 and chose HL2 instead. This time I was able to play the game from start to finish. Since I wasn’t at that time a gamer and played very few games, the graphics, atmosphere, gameplay, and story of HL2 just amazed me and it easily became the best game I’ve ever played. I enjoyed the subsequent episodes just as much as the original game. However, I knew that not playing a game that is widely regarded as a masterpiece (and rightfully so) just for being ,old, was just dumb, and began playing HL1 again. And this time I finished it  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=9" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:">  , although the longest part in the game was, for me, On a Rail, for the simple reason of being just… like a huge maze. I think I’d wasted a week after which I started shooting everything because I couldn’t find a way to progress in the game, and noticed that I was able to rotate the signs, which opened the way. The Xen part was probably the best part of the game for me. It was simply unique, I loved it. And of course, I’ve played Opposing Force and Blue Shift (I consider the latter to be the weakest in the HL1 series, but still a good game nonetheless).</p>
<p>Then I found HL:S, played it a little but never actually finished it (again). It just felt very, very cheap, and I considered it as a waste of time. Although I’d found some HD/UD packs and jumped back in, and it was a lot more enjoyable this way, I still wasn’t satisfied. The ,game, was basically a simple damn port and nothing more, incredibly lazy.</p>
<p>Then I took an interest in modding and played a total amount of over 100 mods (mostly for HL2, and very few for HL1). The best HL1 mods I’ve played are by far Point of View, Zombie Edition, Sven Co-Op, They Hunger, and Life’s End. I’ve played many smaller mods than these but none were as enjoyable. And for HL2, Human Error (both Episode and and Co-Op, although despite and early beta, Co-Op was a lot of fun), The Citizen, and Mission Improbable. I’d also say Combine Destiny, but it was nothing more than playing from a Combine Soldier’s perspective, and a, honestly, lame one, compared to Human Error, although I appreciate their effort.</p>
<p>And finally, around the end of 2011 I discovered Black Mesa  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=9" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:">  (very late, since the development started in 2004-2005 I believe) (Once I found BM I also found OBM and GD). It just amazed me by how ambitious it was, and I’ve anxiously waited it to come out, and followed it ever since. I’ve learned that it was initially scheduled for release in 2009, which drove me away from it unfortunately. As a consequence, each time I’ve heard about it I was like ,Oh, it’s that HL1 remake, hope they’ll release it someday, yeah…,. And, to my astonishment, it did in fact come out in 2012. It was beyond my expectations, I never though that such an ambitious project will come into being one day, but it did. It was well worth the wait, although I was a bit disappointed by Surface Tension as they cut some areas (On a Rail, honestly, didn’t really bother me so much). Either way, it was great, and the 2015 version is even better. Also, Multiplayer is available  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=9" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"> .</p>
<p>It never bothered me that Xen was not included because I understood the team’s goal, so I’ve always been patiently waiting for (and still am, and I know it’ll be worth the wait. That’s undeniable).</p>
<p>And this is how I found the HL universe (and Black Mesa), and I’m glad that I did  <img src="https://leakfree.org/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=9" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:">  .</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/how-did-you-discover-black-mesa-the-half-life-series/14125/10">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/how-did-you-discover-black-mesa-the-half-life-series/14125/10</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 25 May 2015 17:50:25 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14125-10</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/how-did-you-discover-black-mesa-the-half-life-series/14125.rss">How did you discover Black Mesa/The Half-life Series?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How did you discover Black Mesa/The Half-life Series?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[danielsangeo]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>As for how I came across Black Mesa:</p>
<p>I was playing Action Quake 2 with friends for a while and was enjoying the custom maps so I wondered if the “Action” mod team did anything for Half-Life.  I found “Action Half-Life” and, while my friends weren’t playing it, it turned me on to the idea of Half-Life mods, so I searched around.  I came across Blue Shift and Opposing Force which I played a lot of.  But that wasn’t enough for me.  I’ve played everything from Azure Sheep to Point of View, but I wanted even more.</p>
<p>Half-Life 2 came out and I started searching around for mods for that.  I saw a port of Half-Life called “Half-Life: Source” and played some of that, but it was just Half-Life with some additional stuff so I wanted more.  Then I found this mod calling itself “Black Mesa: Source” and it was purported to have updated graphics for Half-Life, so I began watching the mod.</p>
<p>Then I began posting on the forum for it.  The madness took hold.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/how-did-you-discover-black-mesa-the-half-life-series/14125/9">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/how-did-you-discover-black-mesa-the-half-life-series/14125/9</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 25 May 2015 17:16:51 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14125-9</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/how-did-you-discover-black-mesa-the-half-life-series/14125.rss">How did you discover Black Mesa/The Half-life Series?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How did you discover Black Mesa/The Half-life Series?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Diabolical]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I discover Half-Life in early 2000s from a PS2 gaming magazine that I can’t remember what it’s called. Then few months later I get to chance to play the demo of it on my PS2 from another PS2 mag that comes with a demo disc. And one I was disappoint is not the gameplay or anything else about the game, It’s just demo has to make the game short because I just want to play it even more. So I have the rent the game from a video store to play the full game of it. So I played it, love it and I’ve been following HL series ever since.</p>
<p>As for Black Mesa, I discover it 5 years ago from a gaming magazine PC PowerPlay while I was working at the newsagency. And I was pretty excited when I first read it and I just can’t wait to get my hands on it, that is until 2012 when it first launched. So yeah, that’s pretty much all I got to say.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/how-did-you-discover-black-mesa-the-half-life-series/14125/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/how-did-you-discover-black-mesa-the-half-life-series/14125/8</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 25 May 2015 16:37:22 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14125-8</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/how-did-you-discover-black-mesa-the-half-life-series/14125.rss">How did you discover Black Mesa/The Half-life Series?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How did you discover Black Mesa/The Half-life Series?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[JeffMOD]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I walked into my brother’s room one day to watch him play games, and he was part-way through Half-Life. I think this was around 2004, so it was only a few months before he got HL2 on launch.</p>
<p>For BM, I believe I was reading Concerned: <span class="bbcode-i">The Half-Life and Death of Gordon Frohman</span> and one of the post-comic notes Chris Livingston had written mentioned it in passing. Either that or I found it on the VDC like DKY did.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/how-did-you-discover-black-mesa-the-half-life-series/14125/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/how-did-you-discover-black-mesa-the-half-life-series/14125/7</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 25 May 2015 15:53:36 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14125-7</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/how-did-you-discover-black-mesa-the-half-life-series/14125.rss">How did you discover Black Mesa/The Half-life Series?</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
