<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Finished BMS on Linux (a.k.a. thanking everyone involved)</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/finished-bms-on-linux-a-k-a-thanking-everyone-involved/10336</link>
    <description>First of all, I need to thank

* the [b]BMS crew[/b], obviously. It was and is an incredibly nostalgic experience. The level of finesse matches that of commercial titles, the level of polish and fine-tuning is far better than others (i.e. very few bugs and other signs of rushing things),
* the [b]Wine developers[/b] for their outstanding work - everything, literally everything Source related runs out of the box, directly from Steam, just like it should,
* the [b]Bumblebee project[/b] for making it possible to utilize nvidia&#39;s Optimus technology
* and everybody else who contributed to the entire free software stack that&#39;s between me and the iron. Great work.
* Edit: and [b]Valve[/b] obviously!


Some technical details for those interested: I&#39;m running on an Asus laptop (i5, 8 gigs of RAM) with Intel and nvidia GT 540M graphics. The Intel GPU is the primary, wired directly to the output, while the secondary (nvidia) gets powered only when heavy lifting is required. Its output is copied into the primary GPU&#39;s framebuffer and that&#39;s how it gets to the display. This is implemented with the Bumblebee daemon (an implementation of nvidia&#39;s Optimus technology). The game runs on a separate X server and its output frames are copied using a VirtualGL transport back into the main X server. As a nice side effect of that is that Source allows me to set &quot;High&quot; shadow details, something which it never seems to permit in a Windows environment (on Windows it&#39;s either Low or Medium). Overall, performance is pretty much identical to native environment, mostly at constant vsynced 60 Hz at 1366x768 with every option maxed out.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 16 Sep 2012 22:25:54 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>The Cafeteria</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/finished-bms-on-linux-a-k-a-thanking-everyone-involved/10336.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Finished BMS on Linux (a.k.a. thanking everyone involved)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[smoke.tetsu]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>That’s interesting because I’ve gotten many DirectX games to run in WINE almost perfectly. Not just Black Mesa. I’m also on a secondary OS for WINE… Mac to be specific. WINE sure saved the day when it comes to Black Mesa. I do not want to waste space, time, etc. on dual booting to Windows.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/finished-bms-on-linux-a-k-a-thanking-everyone-involved/10336/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/finished-bms-on-linux-a-k-a-thanking-everyone-involved/10336/5</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 16 Sep 2012 22:25:54 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-10336-5</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/finished-bms-on-linux-a-k-a-thanking-everyone-involved/10336.rss">Finished BMS on Linux (a.k.a. thanking everyone involved)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Finished BMS on Linux (a.k.a. thanking everyone involved)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[PlausibleSarge]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>yeah I could never get DirectX applications running properly under WINE so I gave up and dual-booted</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/finished-bms-on-linux-a-k-a-thanking-everyone-involved/10336/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/finished-bms-on-linux-a-k-a-thanking-everyone-involved/10336/4</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 16 Sep 2012 19:04:04 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-10336-4</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/finished-bms-on-linux-a-k-a-thanking-everyone-involved/10336.rss">Finished BMS on Linux (a.k.a. thanking everyone involved)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Finished BMS on Linux (a.k.a. thanking everyone involved)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[theridane]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I knew I forgot something!</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/finished-bms-on-linux-a-k-a-thanking-everyone-involved/10336/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/finished-bms-on-linux-a-k-a-thanking-everyone-involved/10336/3</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 16 Sep 2012 18:54:39 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-10336-3</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/finished-bms-on-linux-a-k-a-thanking-everyone-involved/10336.rss">Finished BMS on Linux (a.k.a. thanking everyone involved)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Finished BMS on Linux (a.k.a. thanking everyone involved)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[PlausibleSarge]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>doesnt Valve also deserve credit for writing an efficient, reliable, steadfast engine that doesn’t break the moment something goes wrong, meaning WINE has a much easier time running with it</p>
<p>I am looking at you, Bethesda</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/finished-bms-on-linux-a-k-a-thanking-everyone-involved/10336/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/finished-bms-on-linux-a-k-a-thanking-everyone-involved/10336/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 16 Sep 2012 18:30:06 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-10336-2</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/finished-bms-on-linux-a-k-a-thanking-everyone-involved/10336.rss">Finished BMS on Linux (a.k.a. thanking everyone involved)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Finished BMS on Linux (a.k.a. thanking everyone involved)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[theridane]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>First of all, I need to thank</p>
<ul>
<li>the <span class="bbcode-b">BMS crew</span>, obviously. It was and is an incredibly nostalgic experience. The level of finesse matches that of commercial titles, the level of polish and fine-tuning is far better than others (i.e. very few bugs and other signs of rushing things),</li>
<li>the <span class="bbcode-b">Wine developers</span> for their outstanding work - everything, literally everything Source related runs out of the box, directly from Steam, just like it should,</li>
<li>the <span class="bbcode-b">Bumblebee project</span> for making it possible to utilize nvidia’s Optimus technology</li>
<li>and everybody else who contributed to the entire free software stack that’s between me and the iron. Great work.</li>
<li>Edit: and <span class="bbcode-b">Valve</span> obviously!</li>
</ul>
<p>Some technical details for those interested: I’m running on an Asus laptop (i5, 8 gigs of RAM) with Intel and nvidia GT 540M graphics. The Intel GPU is the primary, wired directly to the output, while the secondary (nvidia) gets powered only when heavy lifting is required. Its output is copied into the primary GPU’s framebuffer and that’s how it gets to the display. This is implemented with the Bumblebee daemon (an implementation of nvidia’s Optimus technology). The game runs on a separate X server and its output frames are copied using a VirtualGL transport back into the main X server. As a nice side effect of that is that Source allows me to set “High” shadow details, something which it never seems to permit in a Windows environment (on Windows it’s either Low or Medium). Overall, performance is pretty much identical to native environment, mostly at constant vsynced 60 Hz at 1366x768 with every option maxed out.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/finished-bms-on-linux-a-k-a-thanking-everyone-involved/10336/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/finished-bms-on-linux-a-k-a-thanking-everyone-involved/10336/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 16 Sep 2012 18:22:24 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-10336-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/finished-bms-on-linux-a-k-a-thanking-everyone-involved/10336.rss">Finished BMS on Linux (a.k.a. thanking everyone involved)</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
