<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Multiple games crashing with similar reason</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/multiple-games-crashing-with-similar-reason/12765</link>
    <description>I&#39;ve been recently having lots of games crashing on me, but some of them still work. Half Life 2 and RO2 multiplayer are two of them. When I look in the event viewer it says for both of these and the others that the faulting module is nvd3dum.dll, which is related to Nvidia. I tried reinstalling the drivers and it didn&#39;t fix the issue. I&#39;m wondering if there&#39;s issues with these drivers in general and will probably roll back and see if the issue continues. Anything else that could cause this issue that I could try to fix?

Edit: Metro LL, BF4, and Batman AO work, at least last time I checked. It seems it&#39;s only DX9 games that are having the issue, if that helps. I just tried installing DX9 from one of the games with the installer in it and that didn&#39;t fix anything.

Edit 2: Okay, yeah it&#39;s definitely something with DX9. I started up CivV in both DX11 and DX9 mode, and it ran fine in DX11 mode but crashed on startup in DX9 mode.

Edit 3: Turning off MSI Afterburner allows the games to work fine. It was working before though but now it suddenly isn&#39;t.

Okay so I don&#39;t have to entirely turn off MSI Afterburner to get things to work, I only have to shut off the overlay. What I find strange is that it worked perfectly fine before. I played through Stalker SoC (which is DX9) while using the overlay and had no issue for example.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2013 06:17:41 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Help and Support</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/multiple-games-crashing-with-similar-reason/12765.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Multiple games crashing with similar reason</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[papernick]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="sersoft">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/user_avatar/leakfree.org/sersoft/40/5837_2.png" class="avatar"> sersoft:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>msi afterburner is mainly for overclocking ATI cards, for nvidia you should try EVGA precision X</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>???</p>
<p>I have a 560ti and use afterburner with no issues whatsoever</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/multiple-games-crashing-with-similar-reason/12765/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/multiple-games-crashing-with-similar-reason/12765/7</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2013 06:17:41 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12765-7</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/multiple-games-crashing-with-similar-reason/12765.rss">Multiple games crashing with similar reason</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Multiple games crashing with similar reason</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Kairouseki]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Update for this. I reinstalled EVGA Precision X, which contains pretty much the exact same thing that Afterburner uses to do its on screen display and it has no issues whatsoever with crashing DX9 games with it enabled. So I guess I’m using it from now one. Would like to know what was causing the issue though.</p>
<p>Shame too because I like Afterburner’s UI better than Precision X’s.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/multiple-games-crashing-with-similar-reason/12765/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/multiple-games-crashing-with-similar-reason/12765/6</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2013 22:57:59 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12765-6</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/multiple-games-crashing-with-similar-reason/12765.rss">Multiple games crashing with similar reason</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Multiple games crashing with similar reason</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Kairouseki]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>It would be nice if I could get either Afterburner or PrecisionX to work but I don’t think that’s going to happen. Fraps is nice but it doesn’t allow jpg images and only displays framerate, no temps or other info. Is there an Nvidia equivalent of your ATI tray tools that you know of?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/multiple-games-crashing-with-similar-reason/12765/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/multiple-games-crashing-with-similar-reason/12765/5</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 17 Nov 2013 09:09:32 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12765-5</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/multiple-games-crashing-with-similar-reason/12765.rss">Multiple games crashing with similar reason</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Multiple games crashing with similar reason</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[sersoft]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>it doesn’t matter if the app is 64 bit or not, if the GPU is overclocked, it just is.</p>
<p>if you’re talking about the OSD, I dunno I never use that, I use ati tray tools to display an FPS counter and that works with 64-bit games no problem</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/multiple-games-crashing-with-similar-reason/12765/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/multiple-games-crashing-with-similar-reason/12765/4</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 17 Nov 2013 07:49:31 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12765-4</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/multiple-games-crashing-with-similar-reason/12765.rss">Multiple games crashing with similar reason</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Multiple games crashing with similar reason</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Kairouseki]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I had Precision X and for some reason switched to Afterburner. I think they’re pretty much identical though so I may switch back at some point. I know that Afterburner doesn’t work with 64 bit applications, do you know if Precision X does?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/multiple-games-crashing-with-similar-reason/12765/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/multiple-games-crashing-with-similar-reason/12765/3</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 17 Nov 2013 01:33:46 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12765-3</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/multiple-games-crashing-with-similar-reason/12765.rss">Multiple games crashing with similar reason</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Multiple games crashing with similar reason</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[sersoft]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>msi afterburner is mainly for overclocking ATI cards, for nvidia you should try EVGA precision X</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/multiple-games-crashing-with-similar-reason/12765/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/multiple-games-crashing-with-similar-reason/12765/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 17 Nov 2013 01:31:39 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12765-2</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/multiple-games-crashing-with-similar-reason/12765.rss">Multiple games crashing with similar reason</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Multiple games crashing with similar reason</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Kairouseki]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I’ve been recently having lots of games crashing on me, but some of them still work. Half Life 2 and RO2 multiplayer are two of them. When I look in the event viewer it says for both of these and the others that the faulting module is nvd3dum.dll, which is related to Nvidia. I tried reinstalling the drivers and it didn’t fix the issue. I’m wondering if there’s issues with these drivers in general and will probably roll back and see if the issue continues. Anything else that could cause this issue that I could try to fix?</p>
<p>Edit: Metro LL, BF4, and Batman AO work, at least last time I checked. It seems it’s only DX9 games that are having the issue, if that helps. I just tried installing DX9 from one of the games with the installer in it and that didn’t fix anything.</p>
<p>Edit 2: Okay, yeah it’s definitely something with DX9. I started up CivV in both DX11 and DX9 mode, and it ran fine in DX11 mode but crashed on startup in DX9 mode.</p>
<p>Edit 3: Turning off MSI Afterburner allows the games to work fine. It was working before though but now it suddenly isn’t.</p>
<p>Okay so I don’t have to entirely turn off MSI Afterburner to get things to work, I only have to shut off the overlay. What I find strange is that it worked perfectly fine before. I played through Stalker SoC (which is DX9) while using the overlay and had no issue for example.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/multiple-games-crashing-with-similar-reason/12765/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/multiple-games-crashing-with-similar-reason/12765/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 16 Nov 2013 22:14:55 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12765-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/multiple-games-crashing-with-similar-reason/12765.rss">Multiple games crashing with similar reason</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
