<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>XBOX 360 Wired Controller Problem / OS X Wineskin Install</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/xbox-360-wired-controller-problem-os-x-wineskin-install/14440</link>
    <description>Hello Forum:

After searching through the many threads on how to use a wired XBOX controller with BMS on the OS X, I have still not found a solution that speaks to my problem.
HL2 is my all-time favorite game, and I have been waiting for two years to have enough time set aside to tackle Black Mesa Source.

I am running OS X 10.8.5 on a 27&quot; iMac with 2.66 ghz Intel Core i5 with 12GB ram.

Yesterday I followed Forum user moomoohk&#39;s instructions step by step (as seen here) and, performed every Winetrick listed (except for PSM=enabled and VSM=hardware, as those options weren&#39;t available)
and was able to get the game up and running smoothly. I&#39;ve never been a mouse and keyboard player, ever (sorry), and have used a wired XBOX 360 controller for years, using the tattiebogle driver. It works perfectly
on many games, including Steam games (most recently, The Long Dark). But while the mouse works super well on BMS, and the 360 controller&#39;s been enabled (I&#39;ve done it as a checked option, as well as a code input on
console mode). BUT IT DOES NOT WORK. AT ALL.

Now, using wine as a wrapper around the game made me think that perhaps my configuration or preferences were being warped, by having both a native Steam account for my mac and the version 7 that runs from within Wine.
But no, when I run the wine-steam skin to launch the game, there&#39;s even a little xbox controller in the upper right hand window of the Steam launch page. So everything seems to be in order, as far as my ignorant self can see. The controller&#39;s
lit up, the option in controls is ticked, I just used the controller on a different game yesterday. What gives.

If there is anybody out there who&#39;s come across this problem before, please respond below. It took several trips to these forums to get the game going yesterday, and I suspect there are some of you out there who might have a tip or two.
I&#39;m desperate here….many thanks…


TL; DR I still can&#39;t get a wired XBOX controller to work with the MAC OS X Wine version of BMS</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 17 Oct 2015 22:58:46 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Help!</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/xbox-360-wired-controller-problem-os-x-wineskin-install/14440.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>XBOX 360 Wired Controller Problem / OS X Wineskin Install</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[bdown68]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Hello Forum:</p>
<p>After searching through the many threads on how to use a wired XBOX controller with BMS on the OS X, I have still not found a solution that speaks to my problem.<br>
HL2 is my all-time favorite game, and I have been waiting for two years to have enough time set aside to tackle Black Mesa Source.</p>
<p>I am running OS X 10.8.5 on a 27" iMac with 2.66 ghz Intel Core i5 with 12GB ram.</p>
<p>Yesterday I followed Forum user moomoohk’s instructions step by step (as seen here) and, performed every Winetrick listed (except for PSM=enabled and VSM=hardware, as those options weren’t available)<br>
and was able to get the game up and running smoothly. I’ve never been a mouse and keyboard player, ever (sorry), and have used a wired XBOX 360 controller for years, using the tattiebogle driver. It works perfectly<br>
on many games, including Steam games (most recently, The Long Dark). But while the mouse works super well on BMS, and the 360 controller’s been enabled (I’ve done it as a checked option, as well as a code input on<br>
console mode). BUT IT DOES NOT WORK. AT ALL.</p>
<p>Now, using wine as a wrapper around the game made me think that perhaps my configuration or preferences were being warped, by having both a native Steam account for my mac and the version 7 that runs from within Wine.<br>
But no, when I run the wine-steam skin to launch the game, there’s even a little xbox controller in the upper right hand window of the Steam launch page. So everything seems to be in order, as far as my ignorant self can see. The controller’s<br>
lit up, the option in controls is ticked, I just used the controller on a different game yesterday. What gives.</p>
<p>If there is anybody out there who’s come across this problem before, please respond below. It took several trips to these forums to get the game going yesterday, and I suspect there are some of you out there who might have a tip or two.<br>
I’m desperate here….many thanks…</p>
<p>TL; DR I still can’t get a wired XBOX controller to work with the MAC OS X Wine version of BMS</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/xbox-360-wired-controller-problem-os-x-wineskin-install/14440/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/xbox-360-wired-controller-problem-os-x-wineskin-install/14440/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 17 Oct 2015 22:58:46 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14440-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/xbox-360-wired-controller-problem-os-x-wineskin-install/14440.rss">XBOX 360 Wired Controller Problem / OS X Wineskin Install</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
