<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>[concept/mod idea] horror mode.</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/concept-mod-idea-horror-mode/15170</link>
    <description>this is going to be the dumbest thing I have ever posted cause I know it will never happen and it is not worth it. but here it goes.



IDEA: survival horror mode (least likely of anything here to happen so it goes first)
info: play through black mesa with more enemies bigger threats and worst of all NO HEV suit. in this unique take on half life freeman suit is damaged in the cascade leaving him with no way to carry excess ammo and weapons.


changes from base campaign in this mode.
*headcrab latch mechanic that was partially in the mod added.
*3 new weapons two of which are used by hecu grunts
*enemies are more common
*ammo is less common (except 9mm)
*can&#39;t use HEV chargers or health chargers (but can use medkits)


weapon added with mode in concept.


desert eagle
info: while not standard issue a few guards have been allowed to bring their own .357 caliber desert eagles. differences from revolver is it holds one more round and has a L.A.M instead of a sighted aim. its only real downside is it is much less accurate then the magnum.
found: one in office complex in a side passage room. one being used by the guard from questionable ethics.


m16
info: while not the best CQB weapon a few hecu grunts on the ground are equipped with the m16 for its range. this weapon is unique to this mode and can take out a unarmored player in 6-7 hits.
function: 3 round burst
ammo: 30/60
damage: 18 per round
secondary: swaps between burst and single fire (more accurate in single fire)



m249 saw
info: heavy bulky and used by gunners while the .50 cals are set up. the m249 saw rarely saw combat in black mesa but it was used.  ( like to think in half life you just don&#39;t run into any units armed with this). if only found once near the end of the game used by 2 of the hecu grunts gaurding the last tank.
function: automatic
ammo:150/60
secondary: NA
damage: 18 per round





GAME PLAY CHANGES: not much it is still half life game play but with the limitations of 2 guns and no armor. combat would largely be the same but with the player having less ammo and weapon options at their finger tips they will have to think on their feet and use everything they can to survive. (game will likely get really easy once the hive hand is found)

other notes: mode only lasts to the lambda core, where you can get a new suit and revert back to normal game play for xen or use your damaged one and take on xen with an extra challenge.










As stated this is likely the dumbest idea I have posted in a long time, and I once posted a hardcore mode idea that made zero sense for a half life stile game.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 13 May 2017 15:01:15 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>The Cafeteria</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/concept-mod-idea-horror-mode/15170.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>[concept/mod idea] horror mode.</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[darkone]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>this is going to be the dumbest thing I have ever posted cause I know it will never happen and it is not worth it. but here it goes.</p>
<p>IDEA: survival horror mode (least likely of anything here to happen so it goes first)<br>
info: play through black mesa with more enemies bigger threats and worst of all NO HEV suit. in this unique take on half life freeman suit is damaged in the cascade leaving him with no way to carry excess ammo and weapons.</p>
<p>changes from base campaign in this mode.<br>
*headcrab latch mechanic that was partially in the mod added.<br>
*3 new weapons two of which are used by hecu grunts<br>
*enemies are more common<br>
*ammo is less common (except 9mm)<br>
*can’t use HEV chargers or health chargers (but can use medkits)</p>
<p>weapon added with mode in concept.</p>
<p>desert eagle<br>
info: while not standard issue a few guards have been allowed to bring their own .357 caliber desert eagles. differences from revolver is it holds one more round and has a L.A.M instead of a sighted aim. its only real downside is it is much less accurate then the magnum.<br>
found: one in office complex in a side passage room. one being used by the guard from questionable ethics.</p>
<p>m16<br>
info: while not the best CQB weapon a few hecu grunts on the ground are equipped with the m16 for its range. this weapon is unique to this mode and can take out a unarmored player in 6-7 hits.<br>
function: 3 round burst<br>
ammo: 30/60<br>
damage: 18 per round<br>
secondary: swaps between burst and single fire (more accurate in single fire)</p>
<p>m249 saw<br>
info: heavy bulky and used by gunners while the .50 cals are set up. the m249 saw rarely saw combat in black mesa but it was used.  ( like to think in half life you just don’t run into any units armed with this). if only found once near the end of the game used by 2 of the hecu grunts gaurding the last tank.<br>
function: automatic<br>
ammo:150/60<br>
secondary: NA<br>
damage: 18 per round</p>
<p>GAME PLAY CHANGES: not much it is still half life game play but with the limitations of 2 guns and no armor. combat would largely be the same but with the player having less ammo and weapon options at their finger tips they will have to think on their feet and use everything they can to survive. (game will likely get really easy once the hive hand is found)</p>
<p>other notes: mode only lasts to the lambda core, where you can get a new suit and revert back to normal game play for xen or use your damaged one and take on xen with an extra challenge.</p>
<p>As stated this is likely the dumbest idea I have posted in a long time, and I once posted a hardcore mode idea that made zero sense for a half life stile game.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/concept-mod-idea-horror-mode/15170/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/concept-mod-idea-horror-mode/15170/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 13 May 2017 15:01:15 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-15170-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/concept-mod-idea-horror-mode/15170.rss">[concept/mod idea] horror mode.</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
