<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Source Filmmaker=Source 2?</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/source-filmmaker-source-2/9202</link>
    <description>Ok. Everyone knows how some people found references to Source 2 and Source Hybrid within Source Film Maker&#39;s files a while back right? Valve has since removed the files, but I have a theory as to why they were there. SFM has more advanced graphical settings available than regular Source, including SSAO, per object motion blur, and depth of field. I think, that the reason it references Source 2, is because it is (or was) a form of Source 2. Either that, or Source 2 evolved out of SFM as Valve understood they would need a new engine for HL3.

[url=&#39;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=1GVDo-JSfi8&#39;]See this video.[/url] Pretty slick right? However, for the most part, everything that&#39;s in that video, is possible as an in game cinematic within more recent engines. My thought is that, possibly by releasing the SFM free to the public, they are gathering performance data from the community, to see how well the fanbase&#39;s computers can run it.

This isn&#39;t quite as related, but I might as well point out some theories I have towards the &quot;Source Hybrid&quot; thing. A few lines of code also referenced &quot;l4d2 port&quot; in SFM. This is of course referring to the Linux port of Left 4 Dead 2 coming sometime soon. I believe &quot;Hybrid&quot; is the engine this port will run on. No Linux game can (legally) be based on DirectX technology, and Valve hasn&#39;t updated their DirectX license since Source first came out. Some more competent people than I, have pointed out that Source 2 may be heavily OpenGL based, correct? I&#39;d say its probably entirely OpenGL based, think about it. No ties to Microsoft, whom Valve has shown no love for recently, and no platform restrictions, theoretically allowing this new engine to be playable on mobile devices even (though I&#39;ll get to that later).

Source &quot;Hybrid&quot; will most likely be the final form of Source 1. An engine that includes both the DirectX and OpenGL versions of Source 1, perhaps even finally allowing porting of old Source content like mods to non Windows platforms. Source Hybrid could possibly even be used as a low end form of Source 2 for those whose computers can&#39;t handle it.

Sorry if this post was a little too long and rambling, just wanted to throw this idea out there, so this forum can discuss this topic.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 21 Aug 2012 13:17:23 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Technology and Gaming</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/source-filmmaker-source-2/9202.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Source Filmmaker=Source 2?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Rekenaar]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>They’ll probably just leave support for directx in and beef up opengl support in Source 2. They could just write a wrapper class to talk to either directx or opengl based on the platform.<br>
Also, I’m thinking that SFM is the SourceHybrid that is mentioned because it uses non-realtime effects and has much more advanced animation and post processing. (Perhaps from Source 2?)</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/source-filmmaker-source-2/9202/13">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/source-filmmaker-source-2/9202/13</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 21 Aug 2012 13:17:23 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9202-13</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/source-filmmaker-source-2/9202.rss">Source Filmmaker=Source 2?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Source Filmmaker=Source 2?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[TheDragonMask]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Pun?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/source-filmmaker-source-2/9202/12">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/source-filmmaker-source-2/9202/12</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 21 Aug 2012 09:00:13 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9202-12</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/source-filmmaker-source-2/9202.rss">Source Filmmaker=Source 2?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Source Filmmaker=Source 2?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[lunertexcosmo]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I find it hard to believe that Source 2 just came out SFM.  More than likely, they were both being worked on around the same time.  Valve needed a good tool to make videos out of their games (no pun intended) since the demo recorder/smoother is just plain obsolete and hard to use.  They probably just added features from Source 2 to SFM to add more polish to SFM videos.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/source-filmmaker-source-2/9202/11">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/source-filmmaker-source-2/9202/11</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 21 Aug 2012 07:53:13 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9202-11</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/source-filmmaker-source-2/9202.rss">Source Filmmaker=Source 2?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Source Filmmaker=Source 2?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[TheDragonMask]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Intriguing, I never really thought about them having to update the DirectX version for Xbox considering the 360 only uses DX9 with some under developed DX10 elements. Like I said, “Source Hybrid could possibly even be used as a low end form of Source 2 for those whose computers can’t handle it.” but perhaps that could apply to consoles as well. I don’t think Valve will be <span class="bbcode-i">really pushing the envelope</span> in terms of graphics for next gen consoles, but Hybrid could work to bring Source engine 2 content to Xbox and probably more importantly the WiiU. Xbox because of DirectX, WiiU because of processing power. Sort of like I assume “Unreal Engine 3.5” might do for the WiiU when playing UE4 games.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Rekenaar">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/r/8e8cbc/40.png" class="avatar"> Rekenaar:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>The main reasons are that valve have been using it internally for quite a while and some of the effects, such as the Ambient Occlusion, (Pretty sure its not SSAO) are ray-traced and thus not fast enough for realtime use.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>That’s why I believe it is also a possiblity that Source 2 evolved from SFM.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/source-filmmaker-source-2/9202/10">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/source-filmmaker-source-2/9202/10</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 21 Aug 2012 05:40:57 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9202-10</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/source-filmmaker-source-2/9202.rss">Source Filmmaker=Source 2?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Source Filmmaker=Source 2?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[lunertexcosmo]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I’m a PC gamer and all for the switch to Open GL.  But what about the Xbox since it only supports Direct X?  Surely Valve wouldn’t ditch the Xbox right?  That’s a lot of money they would be losing out on.</p>
<p>Okay, this just came to me: What if Hybrid is a part of Source 2 that changes the way the engine runs in order to fit certain criteria.  For instance, running an Open GL system on Xbox?  Or as I said earlier, running Source 1 content in Source 2?  Or as also said, running newer content on older machines.  So I guess what I’m trying to say is, a “compatibility engine” of sorts.  Sounds far fetched but Valve really seems to be pushing the “open-ness” of their games.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/source-filmmaker-source-2/9202/9">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/source-filmmaker-source-2/9202/9</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 21 Aug 2012 05:32:04 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9202-9</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/source-filmmaker-source-2/9202.rss">Source Filmmaker=Source 2?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Source Filmmaker=Source 2?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[mankyman6]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>valve could have simply been using Film Maker while working on HL3, and could have simply forgotten to delete the files before releasing it to the public.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/source-filmmaker-source-2/9202/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/source-filmmaker-source-2/9202/8</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 20 Aug 2012 20:39:07 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9202-8</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/source-filmmaker-source-2/9202.rss">Source Filmmaker=Source 2?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Source Filmmaker=Source 2?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Rekenaar]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I don’t think that SFM is too closely related to source 2. The main reasons are that valve have been using it internally for quite a while and some of the effects, such as the Ambient Occlusion, (Pretty sure its not SSAO) are ray-traced and thus not fast enough for realtime use.</p>
<p>I’m also thinking that they’ll move completely over to OpenGL, as the upcoming linux and current mac ports use it.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/source-filmmaker-source-2/9202/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/source-filmmaker-source-2/9202/7</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 20 Aug 2012 20:26:43 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9202-7</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/source-filmmaker-source-2/9202.rss">Source Filmmaker=Source 2?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Source Filmmaker=Source 2?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Jack_Freeman]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Also, that trailer was fuckin’ badass.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/source-filmmaker-source-2/9202/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/source-filmmaker-source-2/9202/6</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 20 Aug 2012 15:09:31 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9202-6</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/source-filmmaker-source-2/9202.rss">Source Filmmaker=Source 2?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Source Filmmaker=Source 2?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[lunertexcosmo]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I like your idea about Source Hybrid.  If I may add, I think it may potentially be a way to get Source games to run on Source 2 as well as other OS’s.  And about Open GL, Gabe has expressed that everything should be more “free to play” and “open”.  Which is something Open GL would be good at.  So that could be a real possibility.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/source-filmmaker-source-2/9202/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/source-filmmaker-source-2/9202/5</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 20 Aug 2012 10:17:53 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9202-5</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/source-filmmaker-source-2/9202.rss">Source Filmmaker=Source 2?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Source Filmmaker=Source 2?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[xalener]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>It sounds very plausible. Especially the Open GL stuff.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/source-filmmaker-source-2/9202/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/source-filmmaker-source-2/9202/4</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 20 Aug 2012 09:28:18 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9202-4</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/source-filmmaker-source-2/9202.rss">Source Filmmaker=Source 2?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Source Filmmaker=Source 2?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[SoloTimeParadox]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Good theory. It sounds pretty interesting if it’s true.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/source-filmmaker-source-2/9202/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/source-filmmaker-source-2/9202/3</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 20 Aug 2012 04:20:10 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9202-3</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/source-filmmaker-source-2/9202.rss">Source Filmmaker=Source 2?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Source Filmmaker=Source 2?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Jack_Freeman]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Perhaps. But I would rather wait for an official announcement than trusting on speculation.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/source-filmmaker-source-2/9202/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/source-filmmaker-source-2/9202/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 19 Aug 2012 19:52:29 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9202-2</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/source-filmmaker-source-2/9202.rss">Source Filmmaker=Source 2?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Source Filmmaker=Source 2?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[TheDragonMask]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Ok. Everyone knows how some people found references to Source 2 and Source Hybrid within Source Film Maker’s files a while back right? Valve has since removed the files, but I have a theory as to why they were there. SFM has more advanced graphical settings available than regular Source, including SSAO, per object motion blur, and depth of field. I think, that the reason it references Source 2, is because it is (or was) a form of Source 2. Either that, or Source 2 evolved out of SFM as Valve understood they would need a new engine for HL3.</p>
<p><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=1GVDo-JSfi8" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">See this video.</a> Pretty slick right? However, for the most part, everything that’s in that video, is possible as an in game cinematic within more recent engines. My thought is that, possibly by releasing the SFM free to the public, they are gathering performance data from the community, to see how well the fanbase’s computers can run it.</p>
<p>This isn’t quite as related, but I might as well point out some theories I have towards the “Source Hybrid” thing. A few lines of code also referenced “l4d2 port” in SFM. This is of course referring to the Linux port of Left 4 Dead 2 coming sometime soon. I believe “Hybrid” is the engine this port will run on. No Linux game can (legally) be based on DirectX technology, and Valve hasn’t updated their DirectX license since Source first came out. Some more competent people than I, have pointed out that Source 2 may be heavily OpenGL based, correct? I’d say its probably entirely OpenGL based, think about it. No ties to Microsoft, whom Valve has shown no love for recently, and no platform restrictions, theoretically allowing this new engine to be playable on mobile devices even (though I’ll get to that later).</p>
<p>Source “Hybrid” will most likely be the final form of Source 1. An engine that includes both the DirectX and OpenGL versions of Source 1, perhaps even finally allowing porting of old Source content like mods to non Windows platforms. Source Hybrid could possibly even be used as a low end form of Source 2 for those whose computers can’t handle it.</p>
<p>Sorry if this post was a little too long and rambling, just wanted to throw this idea out there, so this forum can discuss this topic.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/source-filmmaker-source-2/9202/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/source-filmmaker-source-2/9202/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 19 Aug 2012 18:42:12 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-9202-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/source-filmmaker-source-2/9202.rss">Source Filmmaker=Source 2?</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
