<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>About the Gluon on Xen</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/about-the-gluon-on-xen/62755</link>
    <description>I had no Idea where to post this, hopefully it fits around here.


I really liked how the Gluon Gun was used in the later sections of Xen but i couldn&#39;t help but notice a missed opportunity for when the Gluon gets supercharged.

As you know the Gluon Gun has a display monitoring its status. So, wouldn&#39;t it be cool if the screen&#39;s readings changed as the gun becomes engulfed by green crystal energy?

It&#39;s a relatively small detail, but I believe it would greatly increase immersion while making it easier to understand what is happening to the gun.


What are your thoughts on this?</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 28 Dec 2019 20:38:13 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>The Cafeteria</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/about-the-gluon-on-xen/62755.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>About the Gluon on Xen</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Ale]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I had no Idea where to post this, hopefully it fits around here.</p>
<p>I really liked how the Gluon Gun was used in the later sections of Xen but i couldn’t help but notice a missed opportunity for when the Gluon gets supercharged.</p>
<p>As you know the Gluon Gun has a display monitoring its status. So, wouldn’t it be cool if the screen’s readings changed as the gun becomes engulfed by green crystal energy?</p>
<p>It’s a relatively small detail, but I believe it would greatly increase immersion while making it easier to understand what is happening to the gun.</p>
<p>What are your thoughts on this?</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/about-the-gluon-on-xen/62755/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/about-the-gluon-on-xen/62755/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Dec 2019 11:13:33 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-62755-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/about-the-gluon-on-xen/62755.rss">About the Gluon on Xen</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
