<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>&quot;Micro&quot; stutters</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/micro-stutters/14747</link>
    <description>Hey all, been a few years since I&#39;ve done a play through of the mod, I downloaded and installed the original version of the mod (too poor to buy the early access thing on steam at the moment) and I&#39;ve been plagued by a series of what I can only think of to call as micro stutters.

Every few seconds and at completely random intervals the audio, and frame rate itself will stutter for a split second. I did all the things in the [u]day one performance sticky[/u] and none of it worked, and most of what I was able to find via searching either suggests I do the same thing in the sticky or that it may be related to some old version of some audio driver or some such thing that the source 2k7 SKD uses?

Anyhow, I don&#39;t believe it&#39;s a hardware thing but I&#39;ll attach my dxdiag info anyways. Thanks in advance for any help.
&lt;a class=&#39;attachment&#39; href=&#39;/uploads/default/original/2X/b/b7973a0dc85d8a97f6a99f7eaac1b23decc9289c.txt&#39;&gt;DxDiag.txt&lt;/a&gt; (27.5 KB)</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 08 May 2016 14:35:13 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>In-game Issues</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/micro-stutters/14747.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>&quot;Micro&quot; stutters</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[RedEye]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Sounds like Windows is ruled out because you did a fresh install.<br>
I prefer not to run CCleaner or Glary Utilities on a fresh install, especially the registry cleaner portion. I doubt removing a couple hundred empty registry entries on something that has thousands of entries, (especially when the registry is running on a lightning fast SSD, AND Microsoft recommends that you don’t,) will measurably affect performance. Same for temp file cleanup on an SSD fresh install.<span class="bbcode-i"> But that’s just me.</span></p>
<p>Here are just a few ideas, from easy to technical.</p>
<p>Temporarily disable your anti-virus protection and test again.</p>
<p>Verify all fans are working and heatsinks are clean.</p>
<p>If your overclocking anything, disable the overclock and re-test.</p>
<p>Verify trim is enabled on the SSD.</p>
<p>Almost every piece of electronics has built-in software that controls it.  From the motherboards bios to the firmware on your Corsair SSD.<br>
Verify that your GPU, motherboard, ssd / hdd’s and even the lowly cdrom drives have the latest version BIOs or firmware.</p>
<p>Verify you have the latest soundcard drivers.</p>
<p>Reset the motherboard, remove the battery and wait 30 seconds and short the reset pins. Restore factory defaults. You might need to re-setup the Ram timings if they don’t auto-detect.</p>
<p>If the video card drivers offer a clean install, pick that choice. Otherwise use the Display Driver Uninstaller app <a href="https://www.guru3d.com/files-details/display-driver-uninstaller-download.html" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://www.guru3d.com/files-details/display-driver-uninstaller-download.html</a></p>
<p>Look at the guides on <a href="http://tweakguides.com" rel="nofollow noopener">tweakguides.com</a>, especially the <span class="bbcode-b">TweakGuides Tweaking Companion</span> (TGTC).</p>
<p>EDIT**<br>
Is anything unnecessary running in the Startup folder that could be shutdown.<br>
Especially any program like CCleaner in the system tray which lurks around waiting to free up memory (not needed, you have 16 gigs) and prevent the dreaded cookie or temp file from lingering around longer than a nanosecond.</p>
<p>And Test on  a fresh restart, before opening any other programs.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/micro-stutters/14747/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/micro-stutters/14747/4</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 08 May 2016 14:35:13 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14747-4</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/micro-stutters/14747.rss">&quot;Micro&quot; stutters</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>&quot;Micro&quot; stutters</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[InfiniteWeird]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="CPU">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/user_avatar/leakfree.org/cpu/40/4349_2.png" class="avatar"> CPU:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>First, update Windows. You’re behind on updates.<br>
Second, update your video card drivers.<br>
Lastly, Install and run CCleaner.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Not sure how you came to that conclusion. This is a fresh install of windows and zero updates are currently available (Edit: as in it was run untill everything was completely up to date when I reloaded two days ago). Video drivers are the most recent from nvidia as of the 1st when I installed them and CCleaner is is installed and had been ran as needed post install.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/micro-stutters/14747/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/micro-stutters/14747/3</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 04 May 2016 01:42:51 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14747-3</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/micro-stutters/14747.rss">&quot;Micro&quot; stutters</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>&quot;Micro&quot; stutters</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[CPU]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>First, update Windows. You’re behind on updates.<br>
Second, update your video card drivers.<br>
Lastly, Install and run CCleaner.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/micro-stutters/14747/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/micro-stutters/14747/2</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 04 May 2016 00:52:59 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14747-2</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/micro-stutters/14747.rss">&quot;Micro&quot; stutters</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>&quot;Micro&quot; stutters</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[InfiniteWeird]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Hey all, been a few years since I’ve done a play through of the mod, I downloaded and installed the original version of the mod (too poor to buy the early access thing on steam at the moment) and I’ve been plagued by a series of what I can only think of to call as micro stutters.</p>
<p>Every few seconds and at completely random intervals the audio, and frame rate itself will stutter for a split second. I did all the things in the <span class="bbcode-u">day one performance sticky</span> and none of it worked, and most of what I was able to find via searching either suggests I do the same thing in the sticky or that it may be related to some old version of some audio driver or some such thing that the source 2k7 SKD uses?</p>
<p>Anyhow, I don’t believe it’s a hardware thing but I’ll attach my dxdiag info anyways. Thanks in advance for any help.<br>
<a class="attachment" href="https://leakfree.org/uploads/default/original/2X/b/b7973a0dc85d8a97f6a99f7eaac1b23decc9289c.txt">DxDiag.txt</a> (27.5 KB)</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/micro-stutters/14747/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/micro-stutters/14747/1</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 03 May 2016 18:23:49 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-14747-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/micro-stutters/14747.rss">&quot;Micro&quot; stutters</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
