<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Control problem in Darksiders on PC</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/control-problem-in-darksiders-on-pc/5643</link>
    <description>I decided I&#39;d post on here because the official support forums receive no official support, and hopefully some of you might also have the game and so tell me where I&#39;m going wrong. I&#39;ve tried re-doing it from earlier saves and even re-starting, and this hasn&#39;t worked either.

I won&#39;t post my full specs yet as I&#39;ve had no trouble running the game and I use an official 360 wired pad for the PC, as the system requirements ask for/suggest, but it&#39;s the Hellbook edition (mainly as it&#39;s not available on Steam in the UK) but it&#39;s patched to version 1.1 (which happened automatically after I installed it). This problem happens when Steam is online and offline. I&#39;ve had no other control or camera issues.

So, I was playing Darksiders and I got to the part after you first meet Samael and he gives you the glide wings. I go towards the Twilight Cathedral and into the subway car, then through the tunnels until I get to the first set of two Shadow Currents (if that&#39;s what they&#39;re called?). I double-jump to activate the wings, then glide down to the first current, which propels me really high until I hit the ceiling, and War descends so steeply that I end up only getting 2/3 of the way to the second current, so I can&#39;t get past this and so I&#39;m stuck.

I&#39;ve looked on a few walkthroughs on You Tube, and the only ones that show this section have no trouble with it. They also seem to glide further than I can in the rest of the game, so I don&#39;t know if it&#39;s because I&#39;m holding forwards, but trying it without seems to make no difference. I did once manage to make it to the second current somehow, but after the second one I then didn&#39;t get far enough to reach the ledge to continue.

I have seen two other mentions of this same problem online, but they were both comments on a ripped copy available for torrenting, so I don&#39;t know if there&#39;s some in-built anti-cheating device along the lines of Arkham Asylum that shouldn&#39;t be happening to me.

Any suggestions would be welcomed! I haven&#39;t tried re-installing it yet or downloading via Steam as it&#39;s around 10GB, but if there&#39;s no other solutions then I will do it.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 06 Oct 2010 20:53:25 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Help and Support</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/control-problem-in-darksiders-on-pc/5643.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Control problem in Darksiders on PC</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[blue]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>arent the first currents next to samael ? And if you mean the ones in the cave, man i died a fucking a lot of times there, the game is a bit bugged when it comes to controls, use keyboard and mouse yo get past that part ;f<br>
Also great game, graphics are so mindblowing that after i saw the new leaked bm media i thought it looked like pretty bad, best looking game i ever played, makes other games look bad  ;f</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/control-problem-in-darksiders-on-pc/5643/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/control-problem-in-darksiders-on-pc/5643/2</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 06 Oct 2010 20:53:25 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-5643-2</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/control-problem-in-darksiders-on-pc/5643.rss">Control problem in Darksiders on PC</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Control problem in Darksiders on PC</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[SkyBlue]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I decided I’d post on here because the official support forums receive no official support, and hopefully some of you might also have the game and so tell me where I’m going wrong. I’ve tried re-doing it from earlier saves and even re-starting, and this hasn’t worked either.</p>
<p>I won’t post my full specs yet as I’ve had no trouble running the game and I use an official 360 wired pad for the PC, as the system requirements ask for/suggest, but it’s the Hellbook edition (mainly as it’s not available on Steam in the UK) but it’s patched to version 1.1 (which happened automatically after I installed it). This problem happens when Steam is online and offline. I’ve had no other control or camera issues.</p>
<p>So, I was playing Darksiders and I got to the part after you first meet Samael and he gives you the glide wings. I go towards the Twilight Cathedral and into the subway car, then through the tunnels until I get to the first set of two Shadow Currents (if that’s what they’re called?). I double-jump to activate the wings, then glide down to the first current, which propels me really high until I hit the ceiling, and War descends so steeply that I end up only getting 2/3 of the way to the second current, so I can’t get past this and so I’m stuck.</p>
<p>I’ve looked on a few walkthroughs on You Tube, and the only ones that show this section have no trouble with it. They also seem to glide further than I can in the rest of the game, so I don’t know if it’s because I’m holding forwards, but trying it without seems to make no difference. I did once manage to make it to the second current somehow, but after the second one I then didn’t get far enough to reach the ledge to continue.</p>
<p>I have seen two other mentions of this same problem online, but they were both comments on a ripped copy available for torrenting, so I don’t know if there’s some in-built anti-cheating device along the lines of Arkham Asylum that shouldn’t be happening to me.</p>
<p>Any suggestions would be welcomed! I haven’t tried re-installing it yet or downloading via Steam as it’s around 10GB, but if there’s no other solutions then I will do it.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/control-problem-in-darksiders-on-pc/5643/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/control-problem-in-darksiders-on-pc/5643/1</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 06 Oct 2010 19:46:38 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-5643-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/control-problem-in-darksiders-on-pc/5643.rss">Control problem in Darksiders on PC</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
