<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Texture glitch</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/texture-glitch/12208</link>
    <description>I am running Black Mesa on a Mac through a Wineskin wrapper. It&#39;s not perfect, but it works. However, I am experiencing a texture pack glitch where certain items will turn eye-numbingly bright colors. I know the textures are there, because I can see them sometimes, but they often appear as these colors, and it&#39;s quite distracting. It started happening when I changed wrappers, because the one I was using had a Steam installation issue. Can anyone help me?

Link to the wrapper I am currently using: [url]https://portingteam.com/files/file/7630-dota-2/[/url]

Link to a screenshot of my issue: 
[url]https://docs.google.com/file/d/0Bws9Hwks_FkgS0xhZVR2TlVlMGc/edit?usp=sharing[/url]</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2013 01:29:20 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Help!</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/texture-glitch/12208.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Texture glitch</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Ramirezoid]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>That bright magenta means the textures are missing. This can be caused by many things, usually because said textures are corrupted, have missing/erroneous VMT values, or simply haven’t been included in your installation.</p>
<p>If a clean install downloaded from a different mirror doesn’t fix this, it’s probably a porting thing. Try your luck with bootcamp.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/texture-glitch/12208/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/texture-glitch/12208/2</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2013 01:29:20 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12208-2</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/texture-glitch/12208.rss">Texture glitch</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Texture glitch</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Fear_Will_Find_You]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I am running Black Mesa on a Mac through a Wineskin wrapper. It’s not perfect, but it works. However, I am experiencing a texture pack glitch where certain items will turn eye-numbingly bright colors. I know the textures are there, because I can see them sometimes, but they often appear as these colors, and it’s quite distracting. It started happening when I changed wrappers, because the one I was using had a Steam installation issue. Can anyone help me?</p>
<p>Link to the wrapper I am currently using: <a href="https://portingteam.com/files/file/7630-dota-2/" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://portingteam.com/files/file/7630-dota-2/</a></p>
<p>Link to a screenshot of my issue:<br>
<a href="https://docs.google.com/file/d/0Bws9Hwks_FkgS0xhZVR2TlVlMGc/edit?usp=sharing" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">https://docs.google.com/file/d/0Bws9Hwks_FkgS0xhZVR2TlVlMGc/edit?usp=sharing</a></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/texture-glitch/12208/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/texture-glitch/12208/1</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2013 19:21:50 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12208-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/texture-glitch/12208.rss">Texture glitch</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
