<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Fluctuating framerate around 60 fps potentially causing stuttering?</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/fluctuating-framerate-around-60-fps-potentially-causing-stuttering/12795</link>
    <description>I&#39;m not sure if anyone can help me with thing, it seems like kind of a stranger issue and it&#39;s really only become pretty obvious while playing DMC4. When using Fraps to measure my framerate, I notice that it&#39;s going from 59 to 60 to 61 back and forth quite a lot and I swear that this is causing a bit of microstutter, not anything that makes the game unplayable but it&#39;s annoying regardless. I&#39;m pretty sure I&#39;ve noticed it with other games too. And this is with vsync on. Without vsync on my framerate is upwards of 250 fps so I think it&#39;s strange that the framerate wouldn&#39;t be a solid 60 fps with it on. I also noticed that I have two settings for refresh rate in selecting it for my monitor, 59 Hz and 60 Hz. Selecting 60 Hz and then going back in just has it go back to 59 Hz, but then when I go into the Nvidia control panel the refresh rate there is at 60 Hz. I&#39;m not sure if this means anything though. With things that are more precise than Fraps is when it comes to measuring framerate it rarely ever hits 60, it&#39;s always like 59 point something.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2013 01:21:32 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Help!</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/fluctuating-framerate-around-60-fps-potentially-causing-stuttering/12795.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Fluctuating framerate around 60 fps potentially causing stuttering?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Kairouseki]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I’m not sure if anyone can help me with thing, it seems like kind of a stranger issue and it’s really only become pretty obvious while playing DMC4. When using Fraps to measure my framerate, I notice that it’s going from 59 to 60 to 61 back and forth quite a lot and I swear that this is causing a bit of microstutter, not anything that makes the game unplayable but it’s annoying regardless. I’m pretty sure I’ve noticed it with other games too. And this is with vsync on. Without vsync on my framerate is upwards of 250 fps so I think it’s strange that the framerate wouldn’t be a solid 60 fps with it on. I also noticed that I have two settings for refresh rate in selecting it for my monitor, 59 Hz and 60 Hz. Selecting 60 Hz and then going back in just has it go back to 59 Hz, but then when I go into the Nvidia control panel the refresh rate there is at 60 Hz. I’m not sure if this means anything though. With things that are more precise than Fraps is when it comes to measuring framerate it rarely ever hits 60, it’s always like 59 point something.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/fluctuating-framerate-around-60-fps-potentially-causing-stuttering/12795/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/fluctuating-framerate-around-60-fps-potentially-causing-stuttering/12795/1</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2013 01:21:32 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-12795-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/fluctuating-framerate-around-60-fps-potentially-causing-stuttering/12795.rss">Fluctuating framerate around 60 fps potentially causing stuttering?</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
