<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>The Paisley Plane - Chapter One</title>
    <link>https://leakfree.org/t/the-paisley-plane-chapter-one/8393</link>
    <description>I&#39;ve been working on a novel, titled [i]The Paisley Plane,[/i] for over two years now.  It started out as a simple wacky idea for a short story about a thief who steals a magic book, and then rapidly starting evolving in my mind into a full-fledged fantasy epic.  I fought it for a long time, because it was always my intention for the story to be humorous, satirical, and, in places, blatantly parodic.

I finally gave up fighting it and let the story do its own thing.  At first I was trying to adhere to as strict a stereotypical Tolkien-esque fantasy world as I could.  After all, that gave me reams of fantasy conventions to make fun of.  Then I decided that that was boring, and allowed the setting to adopt some punk elements.  I also managed to keep the humor intact.  I&#39;m happy with the result.

After my initial burst of inspiration - where I generated thirty-something handwritten pages in one Friday evening - I sat down and generated as much of a storyboard as I could stomach, because I could sense that I&#39;d got a hold of a good idea and that I was going to need to do some intense planning if I ever wanted to see it through.  I outlined fourteen chapters before I grew impatient and dove into writing them.

Then I hit the end of the storyboard and, predictably, a brick wall.  The story sat stagnant for almost half a year while I spent my time occupied with real life - until last night, when I had a burst of inspiration in, of course, the shower.  With renewed enthusiasm, I started on a new chapter, but also revisited and revised what I&#39;d written already.  I&#39;d like to present the first chapter of [i]The Paisley Plane.[/i]  I released a much earlier draft of it as a Facebook note over a year ago, and I think the only person who ever read it was a woman I dated for a few weeks last spring.

So, this is the most recent draft, but is certainly still not final.  I&#39;m open to any and all criticism, though if you&#39;d do your best to keep it constructive, I&#39;d be much obliged.

[url=https://docs.google.com/document/d/12wHKUHlhVlwfclpA8pvXa8sJToZCx5TCKvHprhnUTJ4/edit]Copy-pasting it was dumb.  So here it is in a nice google doc.[/url]</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 24 Jan 2012 09:52:46 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Show Off</category>
    <atom:link href="https://leakfree.org/t/the-paisley-plane-chapter-one/8393.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>The Paisley Plane - Chapter One</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Corruptz0rz]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I don’t know why but when i clicked on this thread i could have sworn it said “The Pastry Plane”… then i went back and read it and went:[. I would totally go first class on that plane… just thought i would let you guys know… It’s 4 am and i have only had 5 hours of sleep in the past 48 hours im sorry</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/the-paisley-plane-chapter-one/8393/9">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/the-paisley-plane-chapter-one/8393/9</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jan 2012 09:52:46 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8393-9</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/the-paisley-plane-chapter-one/8393.rss">The Paisley Plane - Chapter One</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The Paisley Plane - Chapter One</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[geekofalltrades]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>^ @ this comment: I don’t disagree, but that’s not the case here.  It seemed that way for a long time, but what I found was that I was putting the actual plot on the backburner to develop the setting further.  This world has a ridiculously detailed lore now, and in a way, it’s nice, because it gives me a lot to draw on as I write.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="OrderOfDagon">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/user_avatar/leakfree.org/orderofdagon/40/4963_2.png" class="avatar"> OrderOfDagon:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>It’s an interesting little story; I’d read on if it were a little longer – you should keep writing it.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="BahamutBBob">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://leakfree.org/letter_avatar_proxy/v4/letter/b/e9bcb4/40.png" class="avatar"> BahamutBBob:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>It was interesting.  I’d read more.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Ah… well, there is, in fact, more.  Chapters 1, 2, 3, 4, 6, 7, 8, and 9 exist in complete drafts, and I started chapter 11 last night.  Maybe I’ll post up another if I judge it done enough.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/the-paisley-plane-chapter-one/8393/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/the-paisley-plane-chapter-one/8393/8</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jan 2012 08:19:51 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8393-8</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/the-paisley-plane-chapter-one/8393.rss">The Paisley Plane - Chapter One</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The Paisley Plane - Chapter One</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[OrderOfDagon]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Don’t wait too long to finish it, either. I find that we become apathetic to our own stories if we keep them built up in our minds too long.</p>
<p>I can’t tell you how many stories that I scrapped simply because a year had passed and I didn’t feel the desire to write anymore…</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/the-paisley-plane-chapter-one/8393/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/the-paisley-plane-chapter-one/8393/7</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jan 2012 05:04:45 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8393-7</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/the-paisley-plane-chapter-one/8393.rss">The Paisley Plane - Chapter One</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The Paisley Plane - Chapter One</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[BahamutBBob]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>It was interesting.  I’d read more.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/the-paisley-plane-chapter-one/8393/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/the-paisley-plane-chapter-one/8393/6</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jan 2012 04:34:23 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8393-6</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/the-paisley-plane-chapter-one/8393.rss">The Paisley Plane - Chapter One</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The Paisley Plane - Chapter One</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[OrderOfDagon]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>It’s an interesting little story; I’d read on if it were a little longer – you should keep writing it.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/the-paisley-plane-chapter-one/8393/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/the-paisley-plane-chapter-one/8393/5</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jan 2012 04:23:13 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8393-5</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/the-paisley-plane-chapter-one/8393.rss">The Paisley Plane - Chapter One</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The Paisley Plane - Chapter One</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Kaweebo]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Did you find out all your good ideas are in the shower - in the shower? Though I must say, it’s actually not that bad. I don’t really have constructive criticsm as I usually think of flaws after thinking about it a bit more after reading it. So I’ll get back to you on the whole constructive criticsm thing. As of now though, it was pretty good.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/the-paisley-plane-chapter-one/8393/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/the-paisley-plane-chapter-one/8393/4</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jan 2012 02:50:48 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8393-4</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/the-paisley-plane-chapter-one/8393.rss">The Paisley Plane - Chapter One</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The Paisley Plane - Chapter One</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[geekofalltrades]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Yeah, fixing it now.  I’m going to put in a google doc.  Guess where I had that idea?  The shower.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/the-paisley-plane-chapter-one/8393/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/the-paisley-plane-chapter-one/8393/3</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jan 2012 02:21:32 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8393-3</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/the-paisley-plane-chapter-one/8393.rss">The Paisley Plane - Chapter One</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The Paisley Plane - Chapter One</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Bloodshot]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>If this site didn’t have a black background and that had more spacing I would read it.</p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/the-paisley-plane-chapter-one/8393/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/the-paisley-plane-chapter-one/8393/2</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jan 2012 02:19:37 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8393-2</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/the-paisley-plane-chapter-one/8393.rss">The Paisley Plane - Chapter One</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The Paisley Plane - Chapter One</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[geekofalltrades]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I’ve been working on a novel, titled <span class="bbcode-i">The Paisley Plane,</span> for over two years now.  It started out as a simple wacky idea for a short story about a thief who steals a magic book, and then rapidly starting evolving in my mind into a full-fledged fantasy epic.  I fought it for a long time, because it was always my intention for the story to be humorous, satirical, and, in places, blatantly parodic.</p>
<p>I finally gave up fighting it and let the story do its own thing.  At first I was trying to adhere to as strict a stereotypical Tolkien-esque fantasy world as I could.  After all, that gave me reams of fantasy conventions to make fun of.  Then I decided that that was boring, and allowed the setting to adopt some punk elements.  I also managed to keep the humor intact.  I’m happy with the result.</p>
<p>After my initial burst of inspiration - where I generated thirty-something handwritten pages in one Friday evening - I sat down and generated as much of a storyboard as I could stomach, because I could sense that I’d got a hold of a good idea and that I was going to need to do some intense planning if I ever wanted to see it through.  I outlined fourteen chapters before I grew impatient and dove into writing them.</p>
<p>Then I hit the end of the storyboard and, predictably, a brick wall.  The story sat stagnant for almost half a year while I spent my time occupied with real life - until last night, when I had a burst of inspiration in, of course, the shower.  With renewed enthusiasm, I started on a new chapter, but also revisited and revised what I’d written already.  I’d like to present the first chapter of <span class="bbcode-i">The Paisley Plane.</span>  I released a much earlier draft of it as a Facebook note over a year ago, and I think the only person who ever read it was a woman I dated for a few weeks last spring.</p>
<p>So, this is the most recent draft, but is certainly still not final.  I’m open to any and all criticism, though if you’d do your best to keep it constructive, I’d be much obliged.</p>
<p><a href="https://docs.google.com/document/d/12wHKUHlhVlwfclpA8pvXa8sJToZCx5TCKvHprhnUTJ4/edit" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Copy-pasting it was dumb.  So here it is in a nice google doc.</a></p>
          <p><a href="https://leakfree.org/t/the-paisley-plane-chapter-one/8393/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://leakfree.org/t/the-paisley-plane-chapter-one/8393/1</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jan 2012 01:46:25 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">leakfree.org-post-8393-1</guid>
        <source url="https://leakfree.org/t/the-paisley-plane-chapter-one/8393.rss">The Paisley Plane - Chapter One</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
